<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[The murky world of Madagascar’s roaring vanilla trade]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/news/2019/07/05/the-murky-world-of-madagascars-roaring-vanilla-trade]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_EFP001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-05T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This piece is from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.1843magazine.com/&quot;&gt;1843&lt;/a&gt;, our sister magazine of ideas, lifestyle and culture. It was published in the June/July 2019 issue.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I follow Felicité Raminisoa and her father, Romain Randiambololona, up a narrow track along the forested slopes of her family’s farm in southern Madagascar. It is lychee season and, as we walk, we break off branches of fruit and peel off the pink, spiky shells. Large yellow jackfruit grow like Chinese lanterns among loquat and clove trees, pepper vines and coffee plants. Sapphire dragonflies flash by as they chase each other over ponds of tilapia dammed into the valley. The air is muggy under the banana leaves but grows fresher as we climb. In all directions we can see vanilla vines winding around tree trunks. Each zigzag stem has been trained so that it grows no higher than Raminisoa can reach. Every so often she stops at a pale-yellow bloom and parts its waxy petals. With a spike snapped from an orange tree, she delicately scrapes away the membrane separating the anther from the stigma in order to pollinate the flower. This is a task that requires perfect timing. Each flower must be pollinated by hand on the morning it blooms or the beans won’t sprout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The family began to plant vanilla vines about 20 years ago mostly as “decoration”, says Randiambololona, his big grin punctuated by a missing tooth. At first the family sold fresh green vanilla pods to tourists, surprised that they would pay anything for them. But in 2014 the price of vanilla began to rise. Over the next three years it went from less than $40 per kilogram to more than $600 per kilogram. It felt like money was growing on their trees. In 2016 Raminisoa travelled to the northern region of Sava, where vanilla has been grown for generations, to learn how to cure the green pods into the commodity that was in such demand: pungent and wizened black beans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It can be difficult to grow vanilla in plantations, where it becomes susceptible to disease. But the humid heights of Madagascar offer the right climate for the plant to thrive. And the large pool of poor smallholders on the island provides abundant workers to grow this labour-intensive plant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Curing vanilla pods requires precise judgment and intuition, like winemaking. The beans, which grow in long green-fingered bunches, are harvested individually. Green vanilla must be blanched in hot water at a temperature of between 62°C and 64°C within a week of being picked. Over the next three months, the vanilla is wrapped in blankets, then massaged and spread in the sun to dry. Green vanilla is flavourless. The enzymes that transform the glucovanillin in the plant into vanillin – the molecule that gives vanilla its distinctive aroma – emerge only through curing. One expert described the smell of high-quality cured vanilla to me as a combination of prunes, leather and Play-Doh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Raminisoa returned from the north she built a curing hut on the slope behind her parents’ house. “You have to have everything prepared,” she says. “Charcoal to heat the water, large pots, blankets and drying racks. In the north they have a special song they sing, about paying attention, about having patience.” Working with vanilla, she explains, “needs discipline and passion”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The family income rose with the price of vanilla. But this has put their crops – and even their lives – at risk. In 2015 the whole family congregated for a funeral. When they returned home they found that all the trees in the lower part of their property had been stripped of their pods. Everyone knew who the culprits were, says Raminisoa, but the police did nothing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Few Malagasys have much confidence in the state. A coup in 2009 scared away foreign investors and tourists. The soaring price of vanilla has been accompanied by an opportunistic crime wave: raiders rip out whole vines to transplant them elsewhere and armed robbers hold up warehouses. Estimates vary but upwards of 15% of the crop is stolen each year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_EFP002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190706_EFP002.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190706_EFP002.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190706_EFP002.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190706_EFP002.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190706_EFP002.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190706_EFP002.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190706_EFP002.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190706_EFP002.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190706_EFP002.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like vanilla farmers all over Madagascar, Raminisoa’s father and brothers now patrol their fields at night. They band together with neighbours and hired guards, and brandish machetes. Bush justice can be brutal. There are stories of beatings, even decapitations. The United Nations Commission on Human Rights says that over 150 Malagasy died between 2016 and 2018 because of vigilantism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past two years, despite thefts, a drought in 2016 and rain during the drying period last season, Raminisoa’s family has earned more than $20,000 in a country where the average income is less than a dollar a day. Previously the family scratched a bare living from growing bananas, coffee and rice. The vanilla boom has enabled them to buy a cow, a new electricity dynamo and a rice-planting machine that they hope to rent out. Raminisoa bought a house in the nearby town so her four children can live closer to their school. She finished her education at 13; her kids, she hopes, will go to university.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though Madagascar now produces 80% of the world’s vanilla, the vine is native to Mexico. The Maya were the first to cultivate it in the jungles of the Yucatan peninsular. They flavoured their chocolate drink with the spice. When the Spanish conquistadores arrived early in the 16th century, they took both cacao and vanilla back to Europe. By the end of the 18th century, Mexico was exporting a million vanilla beans a year to Europe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vanilla was considered a luxury. Its delicate flavour is best expressed in the presence of fat, which is why the creams and custards of the elite’s pastry chefs became its natural milieu. One of its earliest appearances was in a recipe for “vanilla ice” in a cookery book published in Naples in the 1690s. Thomas Jefferson fell in love with French food when he served as the American ambassador to France in the 1780s. He transcribed many recipes including one for “ice cream”, using egg-yolk custard simmered with “a stick of vanilla”. When he became president in 1801, Jefferson served these dishes in the White House – his import eventually became a classic American desert.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But for well over a century real vanilla remained out of the reach of most Americans. Spain controlled the Mexican trade and though a number of people tried to grow vanilla elsewhere, the blooms failed to produce beans because they lacked natural pollinators. It took a young slave boy called Edmond Albius, working on a plantation in the French colony of Réunion, to discover a method for hand-pollinating vanilla flowers in the 1840s. His technique quickly spread to nearby Madagascar, where French administrators encouraged its cultivation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Artificial vanilla was developed around the same time. Nearly 200 molecules give vanilla its subtle flavour. Artificial vanilla synthesises just one of these – vanillin. This used to be obtained from cheaper products such as cloves and wood (today the vast majority of artificial vanilla is derived from petrochemical by-products). The development of artificial vanilla went hand in hand with the industrialisation of food production in the mid-to-late 19th century. New manufacturers such as Fry’s, Cadbury’s and Nestlé all used it at that time to make their chocolate silkier and more buttery. Vanilla essence (as distinct from vanilla extract, which is the concentration of natural vanilla pods in alcohol) found its way into cakes and biscuits. Vanilla is now used in thousands of the food products we find in our supermarkets. Over the years, it has come to describe anything that is bland, unchallenging and ordinary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Häagen-Dazs shook things up. In the 1990s the company started selling its ice cream as a premium, indulgent treat. Their advertising campaign was sexy and risqué – beautiful people tempering their lust with a ball of the frozen stuff. It was a triumph of branding. The name Häagen-Dazs was confected to suggest European sophistication (the firm is American). The picture of a vanilla bloom on the carton drew attention to the vanilla extract that gave the ice cream its rich flavour. The Häagen-Dazs moment was one cause of the vanilla rush.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another one was broader and more recent. Over the past 15 years, food companies have faced increasing pressure from consumers to use natural, ethically sourced ingredients. Flavour companies began to trace beans back to their original villages and farms in order to earn certifications of fair trade and sustainability that commanded top prices. In 2015 Nestlé announced that it would eliminate artificial flavouring from its chocolates sold in America, citing consumer interest in more natural ingredients. Other multi­nationals followed. It didn’t hurt that the price of natural vanilla was low. Among artisanal and mass-market producers alike, flecks of vanilla became a proxy for quality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Madagascar is one of the poorest countries in the world, according to the World Bank. Near-impossible logistics reinforce its poverty. The island is close to the size of France, and in the rainy season the bush roads turn into impassable rivers of mud. It can take four days to drive from Sava to Antananarivo, the capital, a distance of 550km. The towns boast banks, public transportation, clinics and high schools. The bush has almost no amenities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even within rural regions in this small nation there are clear variations in wealth. In the Central Highlands, where the hills are terraced into rice paddies, hand-pulled rickshaws are the main form of transport in the towns. When I flew north, to the heart of vanilla county, I could see new fleets of yellow motorised tuk-tuks. On the drive, I noticed fancy new “vanilla mansions”. Several storeys high, painted red or bright blue and mounted with balconies, these are fenced off by concrete balustrades and garishly lit up at night in a country where most people have no access to the electricity grid. Sava is in the grip of a heady vanilla boom. By some estimates, over $800m poured into the region in the 2017 season alone as foreign buyers bought vanilla.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For many years Madagascar&amp;#x27;s government set the price of vanilla at around $80 a kilogram. Harvests were variable and sometimes ravaged by cyclones. A portion of the crop was stockpiled as insurance against years when yields were low. This forestalled shortages and prevented price fluctuations. Between 80,000 and 100,000 smallholders sold their green pods to middlemen known as “collectors”. These, in turn, sold them to preparers, who owned curing warehouses, or exporters (often Chinese-Malagasy families who had been in the business for generations). The beans were then bought by international traders or large foreign flavour companies such as Symrise and Firmenich in Europe, and Virginia Dare in America. These rendered the vanilla into high-quality extract to supply the big multinationals: Nestlé, Unilever, Mars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a stable if swampy system, but not all buyers felt they had fair access to Madagascar’s vanilla. In the early 1990s, as part of a wider privatisation policy, the World Bank insisted that vanilla prices be allowed to float. Yet no market institutions or regulations were put in place. In the ensuing free-for-all, the price of vanilla plummeted to below $40 a kilogram and farmers neglected the crop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The path from pod to pot of ice cream is a long one and could not be hurried in the face of rising demand. Many vanilla vines grow on forested slopes and often lie several days walk from paved road. A newly planted vine takes three years to bear pods. Even once it does, says Henry Todd of Virginia Dare, it can take another two years for the fruit to reach a tub of ice cream. Todd, a boyish American in his early 50s, is the son of a vanilla trader who sent him to France for his education so that he could learn the language of the flavour fluently. He has spent his working life in Madagascar immersed in vanilla production. “The supply chain is long and complex and a little bit opaque because of the lack of infrastructure,” he says. For many years, collectors acted as the hinge in the market, linking farmers with exporters, the bush with the road. They brokered deals and financed loans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/oguPMXcrOVY&quot; width=&quot;640&quot; height=&quot;360&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the market was liberalised – but before the current boom – exporters generally set the price of vanilla. They weighed the expected global demand against the size and quality of a harvest. But as demand rose, many collectors – the middle men in the system – tried to pay low prices to growers while selling to exporters for much more. By 2017, some exporters were paying exorbitant sums for poor quality beans. As the price mounted, speculation and stock-piling became rife. Several hundred collectors multiplied into thousands of middlemen frantically buying and selling, often to each other. Farmers played the market too, half curing their vanilla and then preserving it in vacuum packs until the price rose again. This created more fluctuations in the market and damaged the all-important vanillin content of the beans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Every week, a different price,” shrugs one man, hanging out with a group of small-time collectors on a side street in Antalaha, the vanilla capital of Madagascar. “Last year was good, we had many millions,” says his friend, who wears a medallion around his neck and has tattoos on both shoulders. “A lot of people bought four-by-fours, big motors. We bought everything, even leather sofas.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I spent almost two weeks in Sava observing the vanilla market. Every time I thought I had worked out the relationship between supply and demand, quality and processing, the hierarchy of middlemen and the relative price of green and black vanilla, I found that a new factor – currency fluctuations, corruption, cyclones – confounded me anew. “That’s about right,” Todd sympathises. “That’s one of the things vanilla people love about the business: it’s never the same season twice.” But why did the price rise so high? Though demand had risen, it hadn’t grown tenfold in three years. And although the Enawo cyclone blew through Sava in March 2017, it didn&amp;#x27;t destroy 90% of the vanilla vines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2018, the price fell back a little to around $400, from a peak of over $600. Foreign buyers like Todd believe that the industry is still in “crisis” and publically rue the deterioration of quality caused by speculation. But privately, Todd and almost everyone else I speak to agree that money from the illegal rosewood trade fuelled the vanilla boom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rosewood is a beautiful hardwood that grows abundantly in the forests of Madagascar’s national parks in the Sava region. It is prized for its deep-red hue, particularly by furniture-makers in China. Logging from national parks is illegal but has always been carried out on a small scale. But after storms toppled many trees in 2007, Madagascar’s president granted export licences to several traders to buy wood felled by “acts of god”. Some interpreted this as permission to start cutting down trees again. The brokers of illegal rosewood sales often operated in vanilla regions and had connections to vanilla collectors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2010 the international community, concerned about deforestation, pushed the Madagascan government to close the loophole allowing rosewood exports. The vast sums that had been made needed an outlet. Much of the rise in vanilla prices seems to have been fuelled by money laundering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Todd and executives at other large flavour companies have been grappling with the varying quality and price fluctuations of Madagascan vanilla for years (along with logistical challenges, such as transporting tens of thousands of dollars in rucksacks across the bush to pay for pods). Virginia Dare’s main client is General Mills, which owns Häagen-Dazs, one of the world’s largest customers of natural vanilla. No matter the price, Häagen-Dazs’s brand identity requires its use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2017 the quality of beans plummeted: so much green vanilla was being stolen from the vine that many farmers were picking their pods early and unripe. Even so, prices were higher than they had ever been. Todd and other buyers realised, with increased urgency, that the only way forward was to strengthen direct relationships with farmers and cut out the middlemen who were manipulating the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_EFP003.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190706_EFP003.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190706_EFP003.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190706_EFP003.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190706_EFP003.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190706_EFP003.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190706_EFP003.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190706_EFP003.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190706_EFP003.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190706_EFP003.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past four seasons, Virginia Dare has worked directly with a farmers’ co-operative in the village of Belambo, north of Sambava, to ensure that they have a reliable supply of vanilla. They pay farmers a fair price and train a new generation to cure the stuff. Belambo is 18km from the paved road, and takes an hour to reach on the back of a dirt bike. Chickens peck at scraps; zebu, a species of humped cattle, loll under jackfruit trees. At a handful of “hotelys” – small eateries – you can buy a dish of delicious zebu stew with local red rice. Yet the young men wear new American sports gear and rev shiny dirt bikes. Some sit in the shade chewing qat or playing music from handheld speakers. “Three or four years ago, the bush was silent,” Todd tells me, “now it’s full of music.” It’s also better lit than it used to be. Almost every house has a cheap Chinese solar panel on the roof to provide electricity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Madagascar’s Central Bank, between $340m and $450m is stashed under the new mattresses in Sava. Many farmers don’t trust the banks, which anyway are far away and hard to reach. Most people pay their day-to-day expenses using mobile-phone accounts. But there is no infrastructure to handle the large number of bank notes needed for transactions during vanilla season. Prices in Sava are often double those in Antananarivo, the capital. At $10, a chicken costs more in Belambo than it does in Paris.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2015, the first year that the vanilla price jumped, everyone splashed out. One man apparently filled an inflatable pool with beer; another took to sleeping on four mattresses. People treated themselves to mobile phones, solar panels, TVs and dirt bikes. In the second year people went for four-wheel-drive pick-ups, rebuilt their houses with new wood, corrugated iron or even cement, which is incredibly expensive to transport into the bush. In the third year, they bought houses in towns so that their children could attend better schools. Now people are beginning to think about longer-term investments: buying land and starting small businesses, making furniture to satisfy new demand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rabezaka, who is probably in his 60s and is one of the older Belambo co-operative farmers, rolls his eyes at the excesses of some of the villagers. He has seen it before: in 2003 the vanilla price briefly shot up to $500 a kilogram after a cyclone hit, but soon crashed. That year he earned enough to build and furnish a wooden house. This time he has rebuilt his home with concrete and painted it pink, his wife’s favourite colour. And, he says, “it was the cheapest.” His wife, Juliette, wears an old T-shirt on which is written “Burberry”, a gold chain with a medallion and gold earrings. His granddaughter, Suamarie, who looks about 11, tells me she likes mathematics and wants to become a doctor. “And a vanilla farmer!” calls out her grandfather.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I ask the women how their lives have changed since the vanilla boom, they laugh as if to say “not much”. Juliette shows me her kitchen, a low hut adjacent to the house, and squats down to add more wood to the fire under a big stew pot, coughing and squinting to show me how uncomfortable and smoky the unventilated space was. But, she says, they eat much better food now. For the first time they can buy yogurt in the village. “The thing we don’t know is how to prepare the vanilla to cook with,” admits Rabezaka. I say that the best thing is to infuse it into milk or custard. Rabezaka and his wife and daughter are unimpressed; vanilla does not feature in Malagasy cuisine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rabezaka, like the rest of his generation in Belambo, rues the social changes that prosperity has brought, even as he enjoys the new comforts. People had once been willing to lend a hand when required, he says. Now they expect to be paid. Girls flock around the rich young collectors. Boys don’t want to continue their education. All anyone wants is a piece of the vanilla pie. And it has become less safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I visited the Virginia Dare warehouse, where members of the Malagasy army were guarding $5m-worth of vanilla. Workers – mostly women – are frisked by hand every time they leave. An alliance of local vanilla networks, exporters and the military have tamped down the violence. But the benefits of the boom have been unevenly distributed. A small tax is supposed to be levied on each vanilla transaction, but most sellers sidestep this. Export taxes are imposed according to volume rather than value. The Malagasy government has made little effort to cash in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_EFP004.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190706_EFP004.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190706_EFP004.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190706_EFP004.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190706_EFP004.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190706_EFP004.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190706_EFP004.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190706_EFP004.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190706_EFP004.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190706_EFP004.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The contrast between private wealth and impoverished public services is striking. In Belambo people complain that there is no drinking water, that the school building is dilapidated, the teachers barely literate and that there is no clinic or doctor nearby. The lack of services is so axiomatic in Madagascar that it rarely provokes much outrage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In recent years, some multinationals have begun to fill the void. Symrise, a big flavour company, has set up a health-insurance scheme for several dozen villages. Alban Bonnet, their sustainability manager, explains that these efforts are part charity, part capacity-building and part self-interest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many observers believe that a crash will occur soon – and fear that villagers are ill prepared for it. Todd’s great hope, shared with farmers in Belambo, is that the village co-operative will eventually cure its own vanilla and become an exporter in its own right. It would be much easier, says Todd, to take delivery of cured black vanilla without the investment and complications of operating in Sava. It’s a model that would change the relationship between Western consumers and developing-world producers, eradicating tiers of middlemen. But the volatility of the vanilla market means that multinationals could ultimately be forced to look elsewhere for supplies. Historically market corrections have been catastrophic; most buyers would prefer a stable and fair price – around $100 to $150 per kilogram – to a dirt-cheap but potentially volatile one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;High prices have driven down demand by 30% from its peak, as food companies have started to incorporate artificial vanilla again. Some artisanal ice-cream makers no longer offer the most basic flavour. Gilles Marchal, a Parisian pâtissière, says that many of his colleagues have stopped using vanilla altogether. “When the price got to €500 ($560) a kilo they just said, ‘that’s enough’.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In December 2018, the talk in Sava was of the lateness and paucity of the vanilla blooms. A poor harvest could send the price soaring again, prolonging the uncertainty. But it could also be the last gasp for the pod boom. Indonesia, Uganda and Papua New Guinea are all planting vanilla. American agriculture researchers are exploring ways to genetically engineer a more labour-efficient plant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The villagers of Belambo are enjoying the glory days while they last. I watch as one of the new bicycle vendors arrives with an insulated box from which he produces milk-flavoured choc-ices at 20 cents a pop. It’s the kind of consumption – an everyday luxury – that flourishing economies are built on. I ask 12-year-old Willis Law if he likes ice cream. “Of course,” he says, “it’s good to have something cold when it’s hot, and it’s rich and cold and sweet.” The kids lick and slurp, then cheerfully drop the wrappers onto the road.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wendell Steavenson is a writer based in Paris&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 17:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Are extraterrestrials extra patriotic?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/07/04/are-extraterrestrials-extra-patriotic]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_WOC365.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN THE FINAL scene of “Independence Day”, a blockbuster film from 1996, Captain Steve Hiller (Will Smith), having saved the world from alien annihilation, watches as exploding debris from a UFO mothership lights up the sky, just in time for the American holiday. Turning to his stepson, he says with a smile, “Didn’t I promise you fireworks?” For Americans, such pyrotechnic displays are an important Fourth of July tradition. Can the same be said for UFOs?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps. According to the National UFO Reporting Centre (NUFORC), an American non-profit organisation that has collected reports of unidentified flying objects since 1974, UFO sightings tend to spike on July 4th. Between 1995 and 2018, around 2% of all sightings recorded by NUFORC fell on this date; seven times more than would be expected by chance. What explains this strange phenomenon?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hollywood may be partly to blame. In the two years before the release of the Will Smith flick, NUFORC recorded an average of seven UFO sightings on July 4th (eight in 1995 and six in 1996). In 1997, a year after aliens burst onto the big screen, there were 74—more than ten times as many. Traditions of the July 4th holiday may also help explain the spike. Independence Day is typically spent outdoors. Heavy alcohol use is not uncommon. Intoxication may cause some to confuse celebratory fireworks with alien aircraft.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_WOC367.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190706_WOC367.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190706_WOC367.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190706_WOC367.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190706_WOC367.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190706_WOC367.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190706_WOC367.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190706_WOC367.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190706_WOC367.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190706_WOC367.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;UFO sightings cannot be blamed entirely on drunkenness. They often have earthly explanations. Some of the biggest spikes in reported UFO sightings in recent years have later been explained by meteors, missiles or debris from satellites re-entering the atmosphere. Or so the government would have you believe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 03:40:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ari Aster returns with “Midsommar”]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/07/04/ari-aster-returns-with-midsommar]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BKP508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-04T17:19:40Z&quot;&gt;Jul 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE NEW wave of high-class horror rolls on with “Midsommar”, a sinister, slow-burning film by Ari Aster, which is being hailed by many critics as one of the best of the year. Following the director’s acclaimed debut, “Hereditary”, Jordan Peele’s “Get Out” and “Us”, John Krasinski’s “A Quiet Place” and Luca Guadagnino’s “Suspiria”, “Midsommar” is a horror movie with crossover potential. It has the resonant themes, painstaking cinematography and Oscar-worthy acting to pull in viewers in the mood for a prestigious drama; but it will also appeal to those who just fancy seeing close-ups of good-looking youngsters being mutilated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The film’s star, Florence Pugh, is especially impressive. A British actress best known for indie dramas (“The Falling”, “Lady Macbeth”), Ms Pugh is as expressive when she is glaring silently as when she is collapsing in a fit of racking sobs. The reason for these sobs is that the sister and parents of her character, Dani, are killed in the film’s opening minutes: like “Hereditary”, “Midsommar” explores grief. Dani’s passive-aggressive dolt of a boyfriend Christian (Jack Reynor) isn’t much help, and he blames her for his neglectful behaviour as well as for her own woes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before the deaths, Christian had been planning to break up with Dani but, more out of cowardice than compassion, he decides in the circumstances to let her tag along on his boys’ holiday to northern Sweden. His American graduate-student buddies (Will Poulter and William Jackson Harper) are not too pleased, but his Swedish friend Pelle (Vilhelm Blomgren) reassures Dani that she is more than welcome. He has invited them all to a nine-day solstice festival in the woodland commune where he grew up, and he seems suspiciously sure that Dani will fit right in. On arrival, she agrees. The ancient rites and the perpetual sunshine in Pelle’s remote enclave may be disorientating, but the white-robed tribespeople are warm and beatific, and the psychotropic mushrooms they hand out turn the meadows into rippling oceans of wild flowers. It is quite a while before Dani learns how much trouble she is in. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Too long, perhaps. As anyone who has seen Robin Hardy’s British cult classic “The Wickerman” (1973) will know, things never end well for outsiders who poke their noses into an isolated community’s pagan festivities—sex and ritual sacrifice are usually involved—and “Midsommar” comes to much the same conclusion as that film, or indeed any other folk-horror mystery. The difference is that it takes 140 minutes to get there. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not that Mr Aster wastes the time. A lot funnier than “Hereditary”, “Midsommar” is in part a cheerful comedy about bickering Americans who are befuddled by the customs and cuisine of a foreign country. The screenplay floats some provocative ideas about the sense of belonging offered by religions, however anachronistic and illogical they may appear. There are so many odd little details scattered throughout the gorgeously designed film that it never stops being intriguing. The runic inscriptions and the pictographs on the barn walls are all very well, but why is there a live bear locked in a wooden cage?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet as well-crafted as “Midsommar” is, viewers still have to wait an hour before anything unpleasant happens in the commune. When it does happen, it is so unpleasant that it is hard to believe that Dani and the others would not run for the hills, instead of shrugging and going along with the programme of solemn al fresco meals and exhausting maypole dances devised by their hosts. Many viewers will go along with it, too, though others will feel that Mr Aster is cheating. Given that two of his characters are anthropology students who ask the commune’s elders about their myths and traditions, they seem oddly incurious about the more brutal practices. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nor do they seem to care that their friends keep disappearing without trace, or that there is a locked-up bear in the vicinity. The careless plotting means that “Midsommar” is ultimately more frustrating than frightening. It gives viewers plenty of time to appreciate its myriad artistic touches, but also to notice how ridiculously implausible it is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Midsommar” is screening in Britain and America now&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 01:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Conservatism&#x27;s crisis, hard truths from Shell&#x27;s boss and insects become fish food]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/07/04/conservatisms-crisis-hard-truths-from-shells-boss-and-insects-become-fish-food]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-04T16:40:28Z&quot;&gt;Jul 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A SELECTION of three essential articles read aloud from the latest issue of The Economist. This week, the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/07/04/the-global-crisis-in-conservatism&quot; data-tegid=&quot;08hrcro5f43n94sfe0n8qp9g599565ol&quot;&gt;global crisis in conservatism.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Royal Dutch Shell’s boss delivers some hard truths on &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/07/06/shells-boss-delivers-some-hard-truths-on-oil-and-climate-change&quot;&gt;oil and climate change&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (10:18). And, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/07/06/beetles-and-flies-are-becoming-part-of-the-agricultural-food-chain&quot;&gt;insects become fish food&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (18:00). Runtime: 27 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-july4th2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id313848583&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/3a5n4DoT1xrV5rgBWBPxnR&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWVjb25vbWlzdGVkaXRvcnNwaWNrcw&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=18376&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/Politics/The-Economist-Editors-Picks-p987585/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 01:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[If everyone had voted, Hillary Clinton would probably be president]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/07/06/if-everyone-had-voted-hillary-clinton-would-probably-be-president]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-06T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-cfg=&quot;main-content:width:full&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-cfg=&quot;latest-updates:position:-1&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-cfg=&quot;article:right-rail:display:none&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190706_GDC414voting1/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;C&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;LOSE OBSERVERS&lt;/small&gt; of America know that the rules of its democracy often favour Republicans. But the party’s biggest advantage may be one that is rarely discussed: turnout is just 60%, low for a rich country. Polls show that non-voters—both people uninterested in voting and those blocked by legal or economic hurdles—mainly belong to groups that tend to back Democrats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What would change if America became the 22nd country to make voting mandatory? To estimate non-voters’ views, &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; used the Co-operative Congressional Election Study (&lt;small&gt;CCES&lt;/small&gt;), a 64,600-person poll led by Harvard University. The survey includes demographic data such as race and age, as well as participants’ recollections of whom they voted for and verified records of whether they voted. In general, voters and non-voters from similar backgrounds had similar opinions. Using a method called “multilevel regression and post-stratification”, the relationships between demography and vote choices can be used to project state-level election results—and to estimate what might have happened in the past under different rules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190706_GDC414_bars/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Non-voters are relatively uneducated, young and non-white.The first of these traits predicts conservatism, but the others point to liberalism. If everyone voted, 30% of voters in the 21 most competitive states would not be white, up from the actual figure of 25%. As a result, in a typical cycle Democrats would add 50 electoral-college votes—enough to reverse the result in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If voting were universal, parties would not benefit from whipping their bases into a frenzy. Instead, they would need to court swing voters, pushing policies towards the centre. That centre, however, would sit to the left of its current position, putting the brunt of the adjustment on Republicans. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Sources: Co-operative Congressional Election Study; Census Bureau; YouGov; &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Graphic detail&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;The silent near-majority&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 21:40:01 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Russia is back on the stage of great nations”—Putin’s PR push]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/07/04/russia-is-back-on-the-stage-of-great-nations-putins-pr-push]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_blm509.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-04T11:40:09Z&quot;&gt;Jul 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/13/what-ivan-golunovs-ordeal-reveals-about-russia&quot; data-tegid=&quot;01eibs9tdu2eksffnkd6gbrfna8p5v6o&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RUSSIA&amp;#x27;S PRESIDENT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is glad-handing in Italy, where his anti-liberal roadshow resonates. But Mr Putin’s is a twisted vision of liberalism, and at home many of his compatriots see through the ruse. We examine the “Swedish model” of&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/15/the-idea-of-criminalising-prostitutes-clients-is-spreading&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt; prostitution laws&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and how the approach endangers &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/19/the-push-to-decriminalise-sex-work-in-new-york&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;sex workers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. And, the push to make &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/06/20/cleaning-up-nuclear-waste-is-an-obvious-task-for-robots&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;robots&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that can handle environments like the melted-down Fukushima Daiichi power plant. Runtime: 23 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/e81f0263-c97b-4051-bb73-f6f516aee11c&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 20:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How a victim of the Cultural Revolution mastered economics]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/07/04/how-a-victim-of-the-cultural-revolution-mastered-economics]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_FND000_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE STUDENTS&lt;/small&gt; embarking on an economics doctorate at the University of California, Berkeley, this autumn face a daunting obstacle: Econ &lt;small&gt;201A&lt;/small&gt;, a course in microeconomic theory inflicted on all new recruits. Over 16 weeks they must acquaint themselves with some of the most formalised parts of economics, including Houthakker’s Axiom, the Slutsky matrix and Afriat’s Theorem. According to one instructor, between five and seven class members (out of 20 to 25) usually receive a grade of &lt;small&gt;B&lt;/small&gt;- or worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But anyone losing heart should take inspiration from a past student, Weijian Shan. He tried the course in 1982 after becoming one of America’s first &lt;small&gt;P&lt;/small&gt;h&lt;small&gt;D&lt;/small&gt; students from communist China. As he recounts in “Out of the Gobi”, his memoir published earlier this year, he had not taken a mathematics class beyond the age of 12. His faculty adviser, Janet Yellen, who would later chair the Federal Reserve, and George Akerlof, who would later win a Nobel prize, worried that the difficulties of Econ &lt;small&gt;201A&lt;/small&gt; would be “insurmountable”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shan, however, had already surmounted more than most. After his schooling was cut short in 1966 by the Cultural Revolution, he was “sent down” to the countryside, like millions of other city kids. He joined a Construction Army corps in the Gobi desert, trying to create farms out of salty clay in a “place that birds don’t care to shit”. They dug ditches, made bricks and harvested wheat, three of the four most tiring things in the world, according to one squad member. (The fourth was sex, which they were spared.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His march to Berkeley was long. He arrived in the Gobi knowing only a few sayings and slogans in English (“Long live Chairman Mao”). But in 1975 he was chosen by his peers and bosses to study the language in Beijing. He won nomination only after first ingratiating himself with his company by memorising the official rules and referee signals of volleyball, which made him a respected referee of platoon matches. The English he learnt in Beijing helped him win an Asia Foundation scholarship to study in America after it restored formal diplomatic ties with China in 1979. Having earned an &lt;small&gt;MBA &lt;/small&gt;in a year at the University of San Francisco, he embarked on his &lt;small&gt;P&lt;/small&gt;h&lt;small&gt;D&lt;/small&gt; at Berkeley’s business school.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his study of economics Mr Shan had one or two things going for him. Economics is the science of scarcity, a subject with which he had intimate acquaintance. Deep in the Gobi, a day’s walk from their settlement, half a box of matches could cost 50kg of potatoes. When Americans dismiss something as “bullshit”, Mr Shan recalls the patties of cow dung they used to treasure as fuel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The construction corps taught him other economic concepts, such as “value-added” and its opposite: their company turned 750,000kg of seeds into just 70,000kg of grain. He experienced the power of the division of labour. Even with the utmost industry his team could make only 200 bricks per person in a day if they each mixed, moulded and moved the materials. But by dividing those tasks between them they could make two-thirds more. He also learnt the value of capital. His platoon could have made 20,000 bricks per day with a simple mixing machine, but no one would provide the 3,000 yuan (about $1,300 at the official exchange rate) to buy it. Mr Shan wonders if he was the first hard labourer with “such a burning desire to be exploited by capital”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The pigshed academy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shan’s educational resurgence was nonetheless remarkable. Even by 1990 just 0.4% of Chinese born in 1951-55 held a university degree (see chart). The Cultural Revolution was like a mad natural experiment, depriving some people of a university education for reasons unrelated to their ability. Their loss has thus helped economists calculate the worth of a college education, which is otherwise difficult to estimate because college-goers are often more able than other people, even before they get there. According to a study in 2015 by John Giles of the World Bank, Albert Park of the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, and Meiyan Wang of the Chinese Academy of Social Sciences, about three-quarters of the returns to college in China reflect the skills and credentials that universities confer. But a quarter reflects the intrinsic abilities of the people they admit. Mr Shan’s education yielded a rich harvest. But he was also an unusually good seed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_FNC332_1.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190706_FNC332_1.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190706_FNC332_1.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190706_FNC332_1.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190706_FNC332_1.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190706_FNC332_1.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190706_FNC332_1.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190706_FNC332_1.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190706_FNC332_1.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190706_FNC332_1.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;One benefit of university is guidance. Mr Shan’s efforts to educate himself in the desert lacked system or direction. He retreated to a pigs’ kitchen, where vegetable roots, skins and leaves were boiled, to read whatever he could find: an aviation magazine, Mao’s speeches, a pesticide manual. For this reason, he feels his “little house of knowledge is built on sand”. (The vastly more privileged students of today can also struggle to study systematically, because of the surfeit of claims on their attention. Their houses can be dangerously top-heavy.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shan enjoyed Econ &lt;small&gt;201A&lt;/small&gt;, eventually. But he had to abandon his first attempt, returning only after taking the mathematics class that Ms Yellen and Mr Akerlof had recommended. The maths textbook was over 400 pages long. He read it seven times. “I would have enjoyed studying in a more leisurely manner,” he writes, but “I had so much ground to make up.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He followed his &lt;small&gt;P&lt;/small&gt;h&lt;small&gt;D&lt;/small&gt; with a brief stint at the World Bank and a longer one as a professor at Wharton Business School. He founded the &lt;em&gt;China Economic Review&lt;/em&gt; (which in 1990 published an article by a 32-year-old Yi Gang, now head of China’s central bank), then entered finance, becoming a big shot in private equity at Newbridge Capital. During long negotiations in hotel conference rooms he would marvel at the luxury of round-the-clock room service. His colleagues would tell him to shut up and gain some weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the Cultural Revolution ended in 1976 and reforms began, Mr Shan, like his country, had a lot of potential—and a lot of ground to make up. Since then they have both been compelling examples of convergence. When capital, of the human or physical variety, is scarce, the returns to investment can be high. And after the rigours of the past both were accustomed to the deferred gratification that heavy investment requires. The man who eventually mastered Econ &lt;small&gt;201A&lt;/small&gt; is an economics lesson in himself.&lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Finance and economics&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Yellen’s unlikeliest student&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 20:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A warlord’s offensive against Tripoli is flagging]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/07/04/a-warlords-offensive-against-tripoli-is-flagging]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_MAP008.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;N TRIPOLI&lt;/small&gt;, the capital of Libya, children play on the beach, cafés buzz late into the night and the manager of a beauty parlour reports that laser treatments, hair-removals and nose-jobs are on the rise. “War hasn’t put off custom,” says Kherea Dughman. About 15km (9 miles) away a rebel army is fighting to take the capital. But after eight years of civil war, Libyans have become inured to the rumble of artillery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There have been several attempts to stabilise Libya since the overthrow in 2011 of Muammar Qaddafi, its former dictator. In 2016 the &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt; installed a “government of national accord” (&lt;small&gt;GNA&lt;/small&gt;) in Tripoli. But it is beholden to the militias in the west that back it. Khalifa Haftar, the head of the self-styled Libyan National Army (&lt;small&gt;LNA&lt;/small&gt;), controls the east and much of the south, including Libya’s largest oilfields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Talks arranged by the &lt;small&gt;UN &lt;/small&gt;to broker a peace between them in April were upended by Mr Haftar, who launched a surprise attack on the capital just after the &lt;small&gt;UN &lt;/small&gt;secretary-general had arrived. Mr Haftar has little interest in negotiating a settlement. The 75-year-old former general thinks Libya is not yet ready for democracy and that it needs a strongman—himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Haftar returned from exile in America after Qaddafi’s fall and raised a force of perhaps 20,000 fighters. They would, his supporters repeatedly promised, clear the capital of the chaos of “terrorist militia” rule. His sneak-attack was intended to snatch Tripoli swiftly. But three months on his forces are being pushed back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Militias that had previously fought each other have rallied against Mr Haftar. On June 26th they captured Gharyan, cutting his supply line to the south (see map). That leaves his troops over 1,000km from their main base at al-Rajmah. Whereas the defenders of Tripoli can go home and shower at the end of a day of fighting, Mr Haftar’s troops are in the desert. The tribes backing him are reluctant to send more men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Haftar, though, has powerful friends. Saudi Arabia, Egypt and the United Arab Emirates (&lt;small&gt;UAE&lt;/small&gt;) provide arms, fighter jets and money to pay recruits. They see Mr Haftar as an ally in their counter-revolution against the popular, and often Islamist, uprisings the Arab spring unleashed in 2011. And they view Libya’s oil, territory and ports as strategic assets that they want to keep out of the hands of their regional foes, Turkey and Qatar. With their support, Mr Haftar hopes to battle on just as he did in Benghazi, Libya’s second city. He took it in 2017 after three years of fighting, but only by destroying and depopulating it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkey and Qatar, meanwhile, have sent weapons and armoured trucks to reinforce Tripoli. Both say they are buttressing the forces of democratic and popular change. They have also supported armed groups who share their Islamist ideology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Foreign intervention risks turning a civil war into a regional one. In June Mr Haftar’s men threatened to strike all Turkish vessels in Libyan waters. It detained six Turkish sailors and released them only after Turkey threatened military action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt; Security Council is too divided to restrain the parties. Libya’s former colonial rulers, France and Italy, have backed opposing sides, fuelled by their oil interests. (Total, a French company, has most of its fields in the east; Italy’s oil giant, Eni, is concentrated in the west.) Russia, which favours autocrats across the region, has thrown its support behind Mr Haftar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America, which could be an umpire, acts like a bystander. Since Barack Obama’s presidency, it has opted to “lead from behind”. Donald Trump phoned to congratulate Mr Haftar—a naturalised American citizen—when it seemed his offensive would be successful. America, which had supported calls for a ceasefire in the &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt;, abruptly threatened to veto them. Since Mr Haftar’s offensive has failed Mr Trump’s interest seems to have waned in another of what he once called the Middle East’s “stupid wars”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the conflict, the dinar has stabilised. Oil production is near its post-2011 peak of 1.1m barrels a day and at current prices could earn Libya $27bn this year. In the current fighting both camps are avoiding anything that might damage the oilfields because revenue from them pays the salaries of armed groups on each side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Mr Haftar tries to regain the initiative, however, that could change. Although he controls most of the fields, a &lt;small&gt;UN &lt;/small&gt;embargo on non-government sales prevents him from boosting his own coffers while shrinking those of the government. Previous efforts to sell oil independently were thwarted by America, but Mr Haftar is thought to be mulling trying again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He may also become more destructive. Since losing Gharyan he has stepped up his bombardment of Tripoli. Fighting has already destroyed one airport and threatens a second. On July 3rd an attack killed 44 African migrants in a detention centre on the edge of Tripoli. Power lines and the pipes bringing water are also vulnerable to attack. Electricity is down to nine hours a day. Schoolchildren complain it is too hot to prepare for exams. More than 100,000 people have left the capital’s outlying suburbs for the city centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most people in Tripoli want a government able to collect the rubbish and put an end to the militias’ extortion and turf wars. (“It’s like taming wildcats in a circus,” is how a government official describes governing Tripoli.) Some may have once welcomed the order that Mr Haftar promised to restore. But his bombardment has punctured such hopes. His flamboyant uniforms, his nepotistic promotion of his sons and backing from the former regime’s henchmen stir fears of a second Qaddafi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, the horror goes on. Field hospitals and ambulances ferrying the wounded have come under attack. A nurse camped in a school with her children, after the shelling destroyed her home, begs for relief. “Why don’t they both just go away,” she sobs. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Middle East and Africa&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Siege on the Mediterranean&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 20:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Boris Johnson may reverse Britain’s embrace of sin taxes]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/07/04/boris-johnson-may-reverse-britains-embrace-of-sin-taxes]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BRP003.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;C&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;ONSIDERING THEY&lt;/small&gt; call themselves Conservatives, Britain’s recent leaders have been unusually willing to meddle with individual choices. Plastic straws are to be banned, over concerns about pollution of the oceans. A tax on plastic bags, introduced in 2015, may double under plans currently out for consultation. The Tories have also expanded so-called sin taxes on unhealthy behaviour. Worried about bulging obesity levels, last year the government introduced a tax on sugary drinks, which led manufacturers to change their recipes or raise their prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some would like the nanny state to be stricter still. Jamie Oliver, a celebrity chef, wants to tax milkshakes. Professor Dame Sally Davies, England’s chief medical officer, is due to deliver in September a report that is likely to recommend more taxes on unhealthy foods. The Institute for Public Policy Research, a leftish think-tank, recently called for more food taxes and for sweets, crisps and soft drinks to be sold in plain packets, as cigarettes already are. Some environmentalists support a meat tax.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On July 3rd Boris Johnson, the probable next prime minister, announced as part of his campaign for the Tory leadership that he would take a different approach. He promised no new sin taxes until his government had studied whether existing ones—including long-standing taxes on alcohol and tobacco—work, and whether they disproportionately hurt the poor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Awkwardly, the answer to both questions is probably that they do. Although the Johnson campaign cites a dissenting study, on the whole there is good evidence that sin taxes change people’s behaviour. In the case of alcohol and tobacco, for example, economists tend to find that a 1% increase in prices is associated with a 0.5% decline in sales. But because poor people tend to spend a higher proportion of their income than others on things deemed sinful, such taxes hit them hardest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Johnson’s plans are likely to go down well with the Conservative Party members whose votes he is courting. Health campaigners may be less impressed. On the same day as his announcement, a report by Cancer Research &lt;small&gt;UK&lt;/small&gt; found that obesity caused more cases of cancer than tobacco in Britain. As for targeting the poor, advocates for sin taxes sometimes argue this is in fact an advantage of the policies, because the poor will disproportionately reap the promised health benefits of having their behaviour changed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This ignores their associated loss of personal choice, however. It also misses a point that Mr Johnson understands very well: the thing about sinful behaviour is that it is often pleasurable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Britain&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Boris eyes the nanny&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 20:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OPEC’s predictable deal cannot conceal its long-term difficulties]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/07/04/opecs-predictable-deal-cannot-conceal-its-long-term-difficulties]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_FNP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE MEETING&lt;/small&gt; of the Organisation of Petroleum Exporting Countries (&lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt;) in Vienna on July 1st and 2nd was, in some respects, a snooze. The deal announced by &lt;small&gt;OPEC &lt;/small&gt;and its allies was the continuation of one struck late last year. For at least another nine months, daily production will remain 1.2m barrels below last October’s level. But behind the predictability giant problems loom, for the oil market and for &lt;small&gt;OPEC &lt;/small&gt;itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America and Iran, an &lt;small&gt;OPEC &lt;/small&gt;member, are flirting with war. The decline in Venezuela’s production has steepened since January, when America announced sanctions against &lt;small&gt;PDVSA&lt;/small&gt;, its national oil company. Escalating conflict in Libya could cause production there to plummet as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, oil producers are more concerned about weakening demand than tight supply. The price of Brent crude climbed to $74 a barrel in late April, after President Donald Trump said he would not extend waivers to sanctions on Iranian exports. It then plunged in May as inventories built up, investors fretted about the trade war and government-bond yields tumbled in America and Europe. The announcement on June 29th that America and China would resume trade talks has helped, but a deal is far from certain. Faced with shaky economic indicators, &lt;small&gt;OPEC &lt;/small&gt;is keen to avoid a market awash with oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_FNC350_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But &lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt;’s decision to trim output points to further uncertainties within the alliance. The first is how long it will be willing to continue losing market share to America. In 2014, as American oil flowed freely, &lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt; declined to curb output, hoping that slumping prices would teach gung-ho American oilmen a lesson. The ensuing crash pained petrostates and wildcatters alike. But shale production has roared back—last year America produced more crude than any other country—and &lt;small&gt;OPEC &lt;/small&gt;has become reluctant to let prices dive again. The result is that &lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt;’s share of global production has dipped, from 42.2% in 2016 to 39.2% in March, and America’s has risen, from 10.9% to 14.5% (see chart).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second question is whether Saudi Arabia and Russia will start to feel the pain of production cuts more acutely. Sinking output in Venezuela and Iran has helped &lt;small&gt;OPEC &lt;/small&gt;to keep a lid on supply even as American output has risen. Wood Mackenzie, an energy-research group, estimates that America (excluding Alaska and Hawaii) will pump 1.2m more barrels of crude a day this year than it did in 2018. Iran will pump 1m fewer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That helps explain why, despite cutting production somewhat, Saudi Arabia accounts for almost as much of the global market as it did in 2016. Russia has been even more protected. That year it agreed to work with &lt;small&gt;OPEC &lt;/small&gt;to stabilise the oil price. Its influence in the Middle East has grown and it has helped shape &lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt;’s decisions, big and small. On June 29th Vladimir Putin, Russia’s president, said that he had agreed with Saudi Arabia to extend &lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt;’s production cuts, making the imminent meeting in Vienna seem all but redundant. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russia has given up relatively little in return. In most months its output has exceeded the level it had agreed with &lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt;. (May was a rare—and possibly unintended—exception: an important crude pipeline suffered contamination.) In March its share of the global market was higher than in 2016. “By doing only a little, they got quite a lot,” says Martijn Rats of Morgan Stanley, a bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;OPEC &lt;/small&gt;and Russia look set to continue co-operating. The meeting in Vienna included a charter to formalise &lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt;’s partnerships with non-members. But there is a limit to how much further output in Venezuela and Iran can fall. If oil prices remain low, Saudi Arabia and Russia may face an uncomfortable choice: let prices dip or cut production more steeply, thereby losing market share and propping up American shale. This month’s meeting was straightforward. Future ones may be less so. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Finance and economics&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Making the cut&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 20:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>