<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[High mid-terms turnout was driven by young and Hispanic Americans]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/04/25/high-mid-terms-turnout-was-driven-by-young-and-hispanic-americans]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_USP510.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T15:50:39Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATES performed so well in last year’s mid-term elections that pundits dubbed the cycle a “big blue wave”. By another measure, it was more akin to a 100-year flood. The final count of ballots reveals that, at 50.3%, a higher share of America’s eligible voters turned out to vote than for any mid-term election since 1914. New data from the US Census Bureau shows that this was driven especially by young people, Hispanics, and those with a college degree. These are groups that have been particularly outraged by President Donald Trump. If their political engagement continues, it could affect the outcome of the presidential election next year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mid-term elections have tended to be affairs for the politically-engaged. It requires unusual attention to politics to go out and vote for a political representative you may not have seen much of. Presidential elections, on the other hand, suck up media attention and advertising dollars from up to two years before Election Day. Over the past century, the average turnout for mid-terms has been 43%—16 percentage points lower than average turnout in presidential contests. The voters who typically cast ballots in mid-term elections have tended to be older, whiter, and better-educated than those that vote for president. This demographic portrait held true in 2018, but with some notable changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analysis by Michael McDonald, a political scientist, of the 2018 Current Population Survey (CPS), a nationwide poll conducted by the US Census Bureau in the November following each even-year election, shows that the increase in voter turnout was large for every major demographic group. But a few groups stood out. Turnout among Americans between the ages of 18 and 29, Hispanics and those who began or completed a college degree increased 13, 16 and 13 percentage points since the last mid-terms in 2014. Whites and Americans without a college degree—groups that tend to be more loyal than not to Mr Trump—increased their turnout by 11 and 7 percentage points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Young women turned out in particularly high numbers. This is unsurprising given that the past two years have been marked by a series of women’s campaigns including the Women’s March and #MeToo movement. Among young voters, 33% of women reported voting last year, compared to 27% of men. That constitutes an increase of 16 and 13 percentage points compared to 2014 levels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mid-term elections are often referred to as referendums on the party in power. But 2018’s referendum was most unusual. Not only was turnout exceptionally high; voters also swung left in percentages not seen since 1974. According to Catalist, a data company, compared to the 2014 election, the 18-29 age group was 24 points more Democratic; college-educated voters swung 27 points to the left while Hispanics moved 16 points. In other words, the voters that were more likely to turn out in higher numbers were also among the most likely to switch from Republican to Democratic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is bad news for Mr Trump’s 2020 campaign. If these voters stay engaged until next November the president will face a big hurdle to his re-election. Meanwhile, longer term demographic changes give Democrats more cause for cheer: America is growing younger, darker-skinned and better educated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 04:08:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How genetic engineering will reshape humanity]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/04/25/how-genetic-engineering-will-reshape-humanity]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_OPP508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T17:17:33Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW GENETIC technologies are exhilarating and terrifying. Society might overcome diseases by tweaking individual genomes or selecting specific embryos to avoid health problems. But it may also give rise to &amp;quot;superhumans&amp;quot; who are optimised for certain characteristics (like intelligence or looks) and exacerbate inequalities in society. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is certain is that people will be able to make decisions about their lives in ways that were impossible in the past, when we relied more on random evolution than deliberation. In the words of Jamie Metzl, we are &amp;quot;Hacking Darwin,&amp;quot; the title of his latest book. It is a thoughtful romp through new genetic technologies, with insights on what it means for individuals, society and even great-power politics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The theme draws together discrete strands of Mr Metz&amp;#x27;s diverse background. He&amp;#x27;s worked for the United Nations on humanitarian issues in Cambodia and served on America&amp;#x27;s National Security Council under President Bill Clinton. He&amp;#x27;s been an executive at a biotechnology company, a partner at large investment fund in New York and a candidate for Congress from Missouri. But perhaps even more relevantly, he is the author of two sci-fi novels on genetics, &amp;quot;Genesis Code&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Eternal Sonata.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of &lt;em&gt;The Economist’s&lt;/em&gt; Open Future project, we asked Mr Metzl about genetic engineering, inequality and the new “liberal agenda”. Below the interview is an excerpt from his book, on the history of eugenics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*      *      *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Economist: What are the ways in which people are able to &amp;quot;hack Darwin&amp;quot; today and over the next 15 years or so?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jamie Metzl:&lt;/strong&gt; We have always fought against the inherent cruelty of natural selection, one of the two essential pillars of Darwinian evolution. We are now beginning to hack away at the second pillar, random mutation. Our growing understanding of how genes and biology function is opening the door to incredible medical applications like using genome sequencing and gene therapies to fight cancer and other diseases. But the healthcare applications of genetic technologies are only a station along the way to where these technologies are taking us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our ability to select embryos during in vitro fertilisation (IVF)—based on informed genetic predictions of both health-related traits and intimate characteristics like height, IQ and personality style—will grow over the coming years. We’ll use stem cell technologies to expand the number of eggs that prospective mothers can use in IVF and therefore the range of reproductive options for parents. We’ll deploy gene editing tools far more precise than today’s CRISPR systems to make heritable genetic changes to our future offspring. Over the coming decades, Darwin’s original concept of random mutation and natural selection will gradually give way to a process that is far more self-guided than anything Darwin could have imagined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Economist: Changing the nature of what it means to be human has huge consequences. What are the main ones?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Metzl:&lt;/strong&gt; We have internalised the idea that information technology is variable, which is why we expect each generation of our phones and computers to be better than the last. It’s harder for us to come to grips with the idea that our biology could be as variable as our IT, even though we understand intellectually that somehow we evolved from single cell organisms to complex humans over the past 3.8 billion years. Starting to see all of life, including our own, as increasingly manipulable will force us to think more deeply about what values will guide us as we begin altering biology more aggressively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_OPP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190427_OPP503.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190427_OPP503.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190427_OPP503.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190427_OPP503.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190427_OPP503.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190427_OPP503.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190427_OPP503.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190427_OPP503.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190427_OPP503.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;If we want to avoid dividing our species into genetic have and have-nots—a dangerous reduction in our diversity—or a genetic determinism that undermines our humanity, we’ll need to start living our values. But though we need to be mindful of the dangers, we must also keep in mind that these technologies have the potential to do tremendous good. Someday they might well help us avoid extinction level events like dangerous synthetic pathogens, a warmer climate, the fallout from a nuclear war or the eventual expiration of our sun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: Do we have the ethical framework to handle this? If not, what might it look like if things go wrong?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Metzl:&lt;/strong&gt; We create beautiful art, philosophy and universal concepts like human rights but wipe out millions of each other in wars and genocides and still today invest massive amounts of our collective wealth in tools of mass murder. The “better angels of our nature” remain primary drivers in our development of genetic technologies, but the dark side of human nature could also be empowered through these same tools. We need a very strong ethical and cultural framework to increase the odds that we’ll use these technologies wisely, not least because access to them will be decentralised and democratised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the positive possibilities far outweigh the negatives, it would be crazy to ignore the many ways things could go wrong. Like Icarus, we could fly too close to the sun and get burned if we hubristically assume we know more than we actually do. Our gene drives could crash ecosystems. We could use these tools to undermine our common identity as a species and social cohesion. The good news is that while the technologies are new, the values we’ll need to use them wisely are often old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: What sort of regulations need to be in place to &amp;quot;enable&amp;quot; these technologies—and what rules should &amp;quot;constrain&amp;quot; them?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Metzl:&lt;/strong&gt; Genetic technologies touch the source code of what it means to be human and must be regulated. This job is all the more difficult because the technology is racing forward faster than the governance structures around them can keep up. On both the national and international levels, we’ll need enough governance and regulation to prevent abuses and promote public safety while not so much to impede beneficial research and applications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To avoid dangerous medical tourism, every country should have a national regulatory system in place that aligns with international best practices and the country’s own values and traditions. We also have to start developing global norms that can ultimately underpin flexible international standards and regulations. These systems must be guided by core values rather than inflexible rules because what may now seem unthinkable, like actively selecting and even editing our future offspring, will increasingly become normalised over time. We urgently need to start preparing for what is coming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: This takes the issue of human liberty to a new level (people should be free to change themselves or offspring), as well as the potential for unbridgeable inequalities (not just of wealth or life outcomes, but of capabilities encoded in oneself and family). How must the idea of liberalism adapt to address this? What does the &amp;quot;liberal agenda&amp;quot; look like for the 21st century vis-à-vis “hacking Darwin”?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Metzl:&lt;/strong&gt; If and when it becomes possible for some parents to give their children enhanced IQs, lifespans and resistance to disease, we will have to ask what this means for everyone else. Some will see these parents as first-adopters paving the way for everyone else, like the first privileged people buying smartphones. Others will call them usurpers laying the foundation for dangerously divided societies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever the case, differences within and between societies, fuelled by competition, will drive adoption of these technologies and present societies with stark choices. Too few regulations could lead to a dangerous genetic engineering free-for-all and arms race. But trying to ban genetic manipulations would increasingly require the trappings of the most oppressive police states. Some liberal societies may choose to provide a basic level of access to assisted reproduction and genetic-engineering services to everyone, not least to save the expense of lifetime care for people who would otherwise be born with preventable genetic diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Societies already struggling to define the balance between the parental and state interests in the context of abortion will have an even tougher time drawing this line for parent-driven assisted reproduction. But if we thought the debates over abortion and genetically modified crops were contentious, wait until the coming debate over genetically modified people arrives. If we don’t want this to tear us asunder, we must all come together in a public process to figure out the best ways forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*      *      *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The disgraceful history of eugenics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Excerpted from “Hacking Darwin: Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity” by Jamie Metzl (Sourcebooks, 2019)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The term eugenics combines the Greek roots for good and birth. Although coined in the nineteenth century, the concept of selective breeding and human population culling has a more ancient history. Infanticide was written into Roman law and practiced widely in the Roman Empire. “A father shall immediately put to death,” Table IV of the Twelve Tables of Roman Law stated, “a son who is a monster, or has a form different from that of the human race.” In ancient Sparta, city elders inspected newborns to ensure that any who seemed particularly sickly would not survive. The German tribes, pre-Islamic Arabs, and ancient Japanese, Chinese, and Indians all practiced infanticide in one form or another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 1859 publication of Darwin’s The Origins of Species didn’t just get scientists thinking about how finches evolved in the Galapagos but about how human societies evolved more generally. Applying Darwin’s principles of natural selection to human societies, Darwin’s cousin and scientific polymath Sir Francis Galton theorized that human evolution would regress if societies prevented their weakest members from being selected out. In his influential books Hereditary Talent and Character (1885) and then Hereditary Genius (1889), he outlined how eugenics could be applied positively by encouraging the most capable people to reproduce with each other and negatively by discouraging people with what he considered disadvantageous traits from passing on their genes. These theories were embraced by mainstream scientific communities and championed by luminaries like Alexander Graham Bell, John Maynard Keynes, Woodrow Wilson, and Winston Churchill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_OPP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190427_OPP502.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190427_OPP502.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190427_OPP502.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190427_OPP502.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190427_OPP502.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190427_OPP502.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190427_OPP502.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190427_OPP502.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190427_OPP502.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although his work was partly in the spirit of the Victorian England times, Galton was then and even more now what we would call a racist. “The science of improving stock,” he wrote, “takes cognizance of all the influences that tend in however remote degree to give the more suitable races or strains of blood a better chance of prevailing speedily over the less suitable than they otherwise would have had.” In 1909, Galton and his colleagues established the journal Eugenics Review, which argued in its first edition that nations should compete with each other in “race-betterment” and that the number of people in with “pre-natal conditions” in hospitals and asylums should be “reduced to a minimum” through sterilization and selective breeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Galton’s theories gained increasing prominence internationally, particularly in the New World. Although eugenics would later accrue sinister connotations, many of the early adopters of eugenic theories were American progressives who believed science could be used to guide social policies and create a better society for all. “We can intelligently mold and guide the evolution in which we take part,” progressive theologian Walter Rauschenbusch wrote. “God,” Johns Hopkins economic professor Richard Ely asserted, “works through the state.” Many American progressives embraced eugenics as a way of making society better by preventing those considered “unfit” and “defective” from being born. “We know enough about eugenics so that if that knowledge were applied, the defective classes would disappear within a decade,” University of Wisconsin president Charles Van Hise opined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the United States, the “science” of eugenics became intertwined with disturbing ideas about race. Speaking to the 1923 Second International Congress of Eugenics, President Henry Osborn of New York’s American Museum of Natural History argued that scientists should:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“ascertain through observation and experiment what each race is best fitted to accomplish…  If the Negro fails in government, he may become a fine agriculturist or a fine mechanic…  The right of the state to safeguard the character and integrity of the race or races on which its future depends is, to my mind, as incontestable as the right of the state to safeguard the health and morals of its peoples. As science has enlightened government in the prevention and spread of disease, it must also enlighten government in the prevention of the spread and multiplication of worthless members of society, the spread of feeblemindedness, of idiocy, and of all moral and intellectual as well as physical diseases”.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Major research institutes like Cold Spring Harbor, funded by the likes of the Rockefeller Foundation, the Carnegie Institution of Washington, and the Kellogg Race Betterment Foundation, provided a scientific underpinning for a progressive eugenics movement growing in popularity as a genetic determinism swept the country. The American Association for the Advancement of Science put its full weight behind the eugenics movement through its trend-setting publication, Science. If Mendel showed there were genes for specific traits, the thinking went, it was only a matter of time before the gene dictating every significant human trait would be found. Ideas like these moved quickly into state policies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indiana in 1907 became the first U.S. state to pass a eugenics law making sterilization mandatory for certain types of people in state custody. Thirty different states and Puerto Rico soon followed with laws of their own. In the first half of the twentieth century, approximately sixty thousand Americans, mostly patients in mental institutions and criminals, were sterilized without their acquiescence. Roughly a third of all Puerto Rican women were sterilized after providing only the flimsiest consent. These laws were not entirely uncontroversial, and many were challenged in courts. But the U.S. Supreme Court ruled in its now infamous 1927 Buck v. Bell decision, that eugenics laws were constitutional. “Three generations of imbeciles,” progressive Supreme Court justice Oliver Wendell Holmes disgracefully wrote in the decision, “are enough.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the eugenics movement played out in the United States, another group of Europeans was watching closely. Nazism was, in many ways, a perverted heir of Darwinism. German scientists and doctors embraced Galton’s eugenic theories from the beginning. In 1905, the Society for Racial Hygiene was established in Berlin with the express goal of promoting Nordic racial “purity” through sterilization and selective breeding. An Institute for Hereditary Biology and Racial Hygiene was soon opened in Frankfurt by a leading German eugenicist, Otmar Freiherr von Verschuer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eugenic theories and U.S. efforts to implement them through state action were also very much on Adolf Hitler’s mind as he wrote his ominous 1925 manifesto, Mein Kampf, in Landsberg prison. “The stronger must dominate and not mate with the weaker,” he wrote:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Only the born weakling can look upon this principle as cruel, and if he does so it is merely because he is of a feebler nature and narrower mind; for if such a law did not direct the process of evolution then the higher development of organic life would not be conceivable at all… Since the inferior always outnumber the superior, the former would always increase more rapidly if they possessed the same capacities for survival and for the procreation of their kind; and the final consequence would be that the best in quality would be forced to recede into the background. Therefore a corrective measure in favor of the better quality must intervene…for here a new and rigorous selection takes place, according to strength and health”.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the first laws passed by the Nazis after taking power in 1933 was the Law for the Prevention of Hereditary Defective Offspring, with language based partly on the eugenic sterilization law of California. Genetic health courts were established across Nazi Germany in which two doctors and a lawyer helped determine each case of who should be sterilized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the next four years, the Nazis forcibly sterilized an estimated four hundred thousand Germans. But simply sterilizing those with disabilities was not enough for the Nazis to realize their eugenic dreams. In 1939, they launched a secret operation to kill disabled newborns and children under the age of three. This program was then quickly expanded to include older children and then adults with disabilities considered to have lebensunwertes leben, or lives unworthy of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Making clear the conceptual origins of these actions lay in scientifically and medically legitimated eugenics, medical professionals oversaw the murder of an ever-widening group of undesirables in “gassing installations” around the country. This model then expanded from euthanizing the disabled and people with psychiatric conditions to criminals and to those considered to be racial inferiors, including Jews and Roma, as well as homosexuals. It was not by accident that Joseph Mengele, the doctor who decided who would be sent to the gas chambers at Auschwitz, was a former star student of von Verschuer at the Frankfurt Institute for Hereditary Biology and Racial Hygiene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By the mid-1930s, the American scientific community was pulling away from eugenics. In 1935, the Carnegie Institution concluded the science of eugenics was not valid and withdrew its funding for the Eugenics Records Office at Cold Spring Harbor. Reports of Nazi atrocities amplified by the 1945–46 Nuremberg trials put the nail in the coffin of the eugenics movement in the West. Although eugenics laws were finally scrapped from the books only in the 1960s in the United States and the 1970s in Canada and Sweden, very few people were forcibly sterilized after the war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But as new technologies more recently began to revolutionize the human reproduction process and create new tools for assessing, selecting, or genetically engineering preimplanted embryos, many critics raised the specter of eugenics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[…]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The parallels between the ugly eugenics of the late nineteenth century and the first half of the twentieth and what’s beginning to happen today are not insignificant. In both cases, a science at an early stage of development and with sometimes uncertain accuracy was or is being used to make big decisions—forced sterilization of the “feeble-minded” in the old days, not selecting a given embryo for implantation or terminating a pregnancy based on genetic indications today. In both cases, scientists and government officials seek to balance individual reproductive liberty with broader societal goals. In both cases, future potential children lose the opportunity to be born. In both cases, societies and individuals make culturally biased but irrevocable decisions about which lives are worth living and which are not. These parallels offer us a powerful warning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if we collectively paint all human genetic engineering with the brush of Nazi eugenics, we could kill the incredible potential of genetics technologies to help us live healthier lives. […] That there probably is an element of eugenics in decisions being made today on the future of human genetic engineering should push us to be careful and driven by positive values, but the specter of past abuses should not be a death sentence for this potentially life-affirming technology or the people it could help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[…]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s not that hard to imagine future scenarios when humans would need to genetically alter ourselves in order to survive a rapid change in our environment resulting from global warming or intense cooling following a nuclear war or asteroid strike, a runaway deadly virus, or some kind of other future challenge we can’t today predict. Genetic engineering, in other words, could easily shift from being a health or lifestyle choice to becoming an imperative for survival. Preparing responsibly for these potential future dangers may well require we begin developing the underlying technologies today, while we still have time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thinking about genetic choice in the context of imagined future scenarios is, in many ways, abstract. But potentially helping a child live a healthier, longer life is anything but. Every time a person dies, a lifetime of knowledge and relationships dissolves. We live on in the hearts of our loved ones, the books we write, and the plastic bags we’ve thrown away, but what would it mean if people lived a few extra healthy years because they were genetically selected or engineered to make that possible? How many more inventions could be invented, poems written, ideas shared, and life lessons passed on? What would we as individuals and as a society be willing to pay, what values might we be willing to compromise, to make that possible? What risks would we individually and collectively be willing to take on? Our answers to these questions will both propel us forward and present us with some monumental ethical challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Excerpted from “Hacking Darwin: Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity.” Copyright © 2019 by Jamie Metzl. Used with permission of Sourcebooks. All rights reserved.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 02:07:05 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[South Africa’s best bet, the right call on Huawei and a hot mess ahead for geoengineering]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/25/south-africas-best-bet-the-right-call-on-huawei-and-a-hot-mess-ahead-for-geoengineering]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T17:46:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THIS WEEK, how to stop the rot in South Africa. The liberal opposition cannot win the elections on May 8th, so the president must clean up his own party. Why Britain’s artful compromise on Huawei and 5G is a model for other countries (10:17). And geoengineering could alleviate climate change, but with politically explosive consequences (14:54).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-april25th2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id313848583&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/3a5n4DoT1xrV5rgBWBPxnR&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWVjb25vbWlzdGVkaXRvcnNwaWNrcw&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=18376&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/Politics/The-Economist-Editors-Picks-p987585/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 01:07:48 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EU workers in Britain are the most depressed about Brexit]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/bartleby/2019/04/25/eu-workers-in-britain-are-the-most-depressed-about-brexit]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_BLP508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T15:17:37Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IF YOU live in Britain, and ever turn on the TV or read a paper, it has been hard to escape from Brexit in the last three years. It has been bad enough if you are British-born. But EU citizens who are working in the UK have faced added uncertainty about their future status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gartner, a research company, has conducted weekly polls of around 300 UK-based employees to see how they have been affected. The key week was towards the end of March when the official deadline for Brexit was scheduled (it has since been postponed twice). In that week, more than half of EU workers in British experienced disgust, anger and sadness. Those feelings have subsided a little since, but are still running at about 40% of EU workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unsurprisingly, that has led EU workers to think about moving jobs. In the week starting March 7th, only 11% of them were doing so; by the week of April 8th that proportion had jumped to 24%. The proportion of footloose British-born workers saw a more modest rise from 15% to 21%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The polling also suggests that all this Brexit uncertainty is bad for productivity as well. In the week of March 25th, the average employee spent almost an hour of their working day thinking about Brexit, with EU citizens hitting nearly 70 minutes. Since then that proportion has dropped a bit, although EU citizens still spent 47 minutes worrying about the issue. Never has national navel-gazing proved so fruitless. As the Eagles once sang&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know what&amp;#x27;s been on your mind&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#x27;re afraid it&amp;#x27;s all been wasted time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 01:07:47 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Competition authorities throw out the merger of Sainsbury’s and Asda]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/04/25/competition-authorities-throw-out-the-merger-of-sainsburys-and-asda]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_BRP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT WAS BILLED as the retail deal of the decade, at a stroke creating Britain’s biggest supermarket chain—and one of Europe’s largest, too. No longer. On April 25th Britain’s Competition and Markets Authority (CMA) blocked the proposed £12bn ($15.5bn) merger between the country’s second-largest supermarket, Asda, which is owned by America’s Walmart, and the third largest, Sainsbury’s. By combining the pair’s market shares of 15.4% and 15.3% respectively, the new Sasda, or somesuch, would have leapfrogged the current market leader, Tesco, which has 27%. The merged entity would have had a turnover of about £51bn a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asda and Sainsbury’s argued that in Britain’s ruthlessly competitive retail market, the deal would have given them room to cut costs and thus offer lower prices to customers. Mike Coupe, the boss of Sainsbury’s, had claimed that prices would fall by as much as 10%. It would also have enabled the new firm to compete more effectively with Aldi and Lidl, two German discount stores that have been gobbling up market share over the past decade. Sainsbury’s and Asda must have been encouraged by a wave of consolidation in the retail world; in 2017 Tesco bought Booker, a wholesaler, for £3.7bn, and the previous year Sainsbury’s had bought Argos, a home retailer, for £1.4bn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not so fast, says the CMA. Despite promises from Sainsbury’s and Asda to sell between 125 and 150 of their stores to allow the merger to proceed, the CMA was unconvinced that the creation of such a giant was in the best interests of shoppers, or indeed of anyone other than the companies’ bosses. “Following our in-depth investigation,” explained Stuart McIntosh of the CMA, “we have found this deal would lead to increased prices, reduced quality and choice of products, or a poorer shopping experience for all of their UK shoppers.” In particular, the CMA found that the proposed price reductions were “unlikely to be realised” either online, in store or at the petrol pumps, with drivers likely to pay more at over 125 locations where Sainsbury’s and Asda currently have petrol stations close together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two supermarkets bemoaned the CMA’s decision. Many others, however, are relieved. Trade unions are happy that job cuts have been avoided. Farmers and other suppliers had expressed concern at the merger; they would probably have borne the brunt of the cost cuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The collapse of the deal leaves Sainsbury’s, in particular, in a pickle. Its share price, already significantly down over the past few years, dipped sharply on the news. Many analysts and investors had argued that Sainsbury’s management was investing too much faith and time in a merger that always looked vulnerable to the CMA’s intervention, while ignoring the company’s underlying weaknesses. In contrast, Tesco and Morrisons, the final member of Britain’s big four supermarkets, have been urgently addressing their own shortcomings. Tesco, in particular, has staged a spectacular comeback. In 2015 the company posted the biggest loss (£6.4bn) in British retail history; on April 10th it announced a 29% yearly jump in pre-tax profits, to £1.7bn. Sainsbury’s investors can only look on enviously. They will be looking carefully at the company’s annual results, due on May 1st. They may yet have Mr Coupe on toast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CMA’s decision may also have wider implications for British business and the economy. In the past decade Britain has witnessed about $2trn-worth of mergers and acquisitions of domestic firms. Relative to the size of the economy, that is over a fifth more than in America over the same period. American economists and politicians are increasingly concerned that their economy has become too concentrated, limiting competition and eroding consumer welfare. These same concerns have been expressed in Britain, but this is the first time the CMA has blocked such a deal since its creation in 2014. The merger’s quashing could yet prove to be an important moment in the reform of Britain’s over-concentrated economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 01:07:46 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EU workers think about the Brexit exit]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/bartleby/2019/04/25/eu-workers-think-about-the-brexit-exit]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_BLP508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T15:17:37Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IF YOU live in Britain, and ever turn on the TV or read a paper, it has been hard to escape from Brexit in the last three years. It has been bad enough if you are British-born. But EU citizens who are working in the UK have faced added uncertainty about their future status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gartner, a research company, has conducted weekly polls of around 300 UK-based employees to see how they have been affected. The key week was towards the end of March when the official deadline for Brexit was scheduled (it has since been postponed twice). In that week, more than half of EU workers in British experienced disgust, anger and sadness. Those feelings have subsided a little since, but are still running at about 40% of EU workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unsurprisingly, that has led EU workers to think about moving jobs. in the week starting March 7th, only 11% of them were doing so; by the week of April 8th that proportion had jumped to 24%. The proportion of footloose British-born workers saw a more modest rise from 15% to 21%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The polling also suggests that all this Brexit uncertainty is bad for productivity as well. In the week of March 25th, the average employee spent almost an hour of their working day thinking about Brexit, with EU citizens hitting nearly 70 minutes. Since then that proportion has dropped a bit, although EU citizens still spent 47 minutes worrying about the issue. Never has national navel-gazing proved so fruitless. As the Eagles once sang&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know what&amp;#x27;s been on your mind&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#x27;re afraid it&amp;#x27;s all been wasted time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:07:21 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A brief cultural history of the scream]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/04/25/a-brief-cultural-history-of-the-scream]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_BKP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T15:01:48Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I WAS walking along the road with two friends – the sun was setting,” Edvard Munch wrote in his diary in 1892. “Suddenly the sky turned blood red...there was blood and tongues of fire above the blue-black fjord and the city...I sensed an infinite scream passing through nature.” The scene inspired Munch’s best-known work, currently on display at the British Museum. “The Scream” exists in four different versions, each with thick, stark lines reverberating with a sound that can never be heard. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Robert Rosenblum, an art historian, has suggested that the image was inspired by a Peruvian mummy, buried with its hands clutching its face, which was exhibited at the Exposition Universelle in Paris in 1889. “Human Misery” (1888), a painting by Paul Gauguin, also drew on this particular mummy, as did his “D&amp;#x27;ou Venons Nous / Que Sommes Nous / Où Allons Nous” (1897). The frightened face recurs in Munch’s work, too. In the painting “Dead Mother and Child” (1901) a small boy stands by his mother’s corpse, his hands covering his ears; “Inheritance” (1916) bears similar traces of “The Scream”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Munch’s “face distorted by despair” has permeated popular culture. The image inspired the GhostFace mask in “Scream”, a horror film franchise, which exaggerates the ghoulish and sinister qualities of the painting. In the poster for “Home Alone” (1990), a young Macaulay Culkin assumes a similar facial expression. In the internet age, the artwork has influenced the design of the scream emoji.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why does the act of screaming fascinate viewers and audiences? Screams are disturbing, an explosion of feeling that is not verbal yet not quite nonsense. They are primal, involuntary reflexes that represent a loss of control. There are many, often contradictory, reasons to scream: fear, shock, pain and pleasure. All can be traced through art, literature and music.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arthur Janov, a psychologist, thought that screams could uncover repressed childhood trauma. The cover of his book (“The Primal Scream”, 1970) promised that “what I heard may change the nature of psychotherapy as it is now known – an eerie scream welling up from the depths of a young man”. His approach inspired John Lennon, whose screaming can be heard on the tracks “Mother” and “Well, Well, Well” on his first solo album; Yoko Ono’s music, too, features plenty of guttural sounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_BKP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190427_BKP507.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190427_BKP507.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190427_BKP507.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190427_BKP507.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190427_BKP507.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190427_BKP507.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190427_BKP507.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190427_BKP507.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190427_BKP507.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;A scream, at the beginning of a novel, jolts the reader awake. “Gravity’s Rainbow” (1973) opens as “a screaming comes across the sky”—that of a V2 rocket about to fall on London—whereby Thomas Pynchon instantly evokes the terrors of his wartime setting. When novels end with a scream, the effect is unsettling. Francis Spufford closes “Golden Hill” with the narrator remembering “how good it was,” at a pivotal moment, “to scream”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere, shrieks are imbued with philosophical depths. In the final scene of “King Lear”, Lear repeats “howl, howl, howl, howl”; his garbled scream of agony at the death of Cordelia has been reinterpreted in myriad ways by actors over the centuries. In Tennessee Williams’s short story “Miss Coynte of Greene”, the grandmother screams “like a peacock in heat” to attract the attention of her family. Abigail and her fellows in “The Crucible” (pictured, above) screech in unison as a form of manipulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cinema is also famous for its screams. The most important scene of “Psycho” (1960, pictured, top), for Alfred Hitchcock, was that of Janet Leigh in the shower; her scream of terror harmonises with Bernard Herrmann’s jagged score. Steven Spielberg made actors scream as part of the audition process for “Jurassic Park” (1993). When he watched the tapes back at home at night, Ariana Richards’s cry jolted Mr Spielberg’s wife awake, and she ran to check her children were safe. He cast Ms Richards immediately. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some screams become motifs. The “Wilhelm Scream”, a stock sound effect created in 1951 for the film “Distant Drums”, has been used in over 389 films and TV series since. It features in “Star Wars: A New Hope” (1977) when a Stormtrooper falls to his death after being shot by Luke Skywalker, and several times in the Indiana Jones films. The tagline of “Alien” (1979), “In Space, No One Can Hear You Scream”, established both the film’s appreciation of science—sound waves do not travel well through space—as well as the vastness and isolation of the setting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A blood-curdling scream represents an extreme of emotion; it both excites and terrifies. When Rosa Klebb, the villain of “From Russia With Love” (1957), interrogated her victims, she “would watch the eyes in the face a few inches away from hers and breathe in the screams as if they were perfume”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 23:06:46 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Deutsche Bank and Commerzbank call off merger talks]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/04/25/deutsche-bank-and-commerzbank-call-off-merger-talks]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_FNP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;A&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;FTER SIX&lt;/small&gt; weeks of rumour, a progress report was due. Deutsche Bank, Germany’s biggest bank, had promised investors an update on merger discussions with its Frankfurt neighbour, Commerzbank, on April 26th, alongside its first-quarter earnings. The update came, unplanned, a day early. On April 25th the two banks said they had called off the talks, the announcement prompted by a Reuters report that negotiations were about to fail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pair said that a deal would not justify the “additional execution risks, restructuring costs and capital requirements associated with such a large-scale integration”. Outside the two banks and the German government, Commerzbank’s biggest shareholder with a 15% stake, plenty had reached that conclusion even before the banks said in mid-March that talks were under way and embarked on weeks of negotiation. Two troubled lenders looked unlikely to make one strong one. Deutsche eked out only a tiny profit in 2018, its first for four years, while Commerzbank has made paltry returns. Deutsche’s shares have been trading at about 25% of book value, Commerzbank’s at little more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though Commerzbank has done a lot of reconstructive work since taking over Dresdner Bank during the global financial crisis, Deutsche still resembles a building site. It is still attempting to integrate Postbank, a retail business it bought in 2008-10, tried to sell and then decided to keep. It has retreated in investment banking, especially trading, to focus on corporate clients, who it still believes need a strong European alternative to Wall Street firms. Even a combined entity, after deep cuts in costs, would have found it difficult to build profitability in an overcrowded domestic market in which the co-operative and public sectors are also strong competitors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what was the logic of a merger? There was some, if never enough. It would have created Germany’s biggest retail bank by some distance, with about a fifth of deposits in a highly fragmented market. It might have forced a faster digitisation of German retail banking, including branch closures—loudly opposed by trade unions at both banks while the talks were under way. Commerzbank’s deposit base would have brought Deutsche cheaper and more stable funding. It would have tilted Deutsche faster towards serving companies—notably by bringing more business from Germany’s &lt;em &gt;Mittelstand&lt;/em&gt;, the backbone of both Commerzbank’s revenues and the national economy. Given Europe’s lack of banks with the clout of America’s giants, domestic consolidation has long been seen as a stepping stone to creating continent-wide players, with economies of scale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the government, one attraction of a merger was that Commerzbank would then be sure not to fall into the hands of one of the foreign suitors with which it has been repeatedly linked. Even in the past few weeks, reports have surfaced of interest from Italy’s UniCredit, which already owns &lt;small&gt;HVB&lt;/small&gt;, a large Munich-based lender, and from &lt;small&gt;ING&lt;/small&gt;, of the Netherlands, which already has a successful branchless retail bank in Germany.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Deutsche ruled out, such rumours are unlikely to go away. Ironically, the failed talks may, through a bid for Commerzbank, hasten a cross-border deal. Deutsche’s situation is as dismal as ever. In a preview of its first-quarter earnings with the announcement that talks had failed, it said it had made only a puny €200m ($227m) or so in net profit, with corporate and investment-banking revenues down on a year earlier. Put away the drawing board, and get back to the building site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Finance and economics&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;It’s off&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 22:06:26 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why you should never start a trade war with an autocracy]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/27/why-you-should-never-start-a-trade-war-with-an-autocracy]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_GDC411_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-27T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 27th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;

&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190427_GD411_tradewar/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;E&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;CONOMISTS OFTEN&lt;/small&gt; argue that trade wars cannot be won. Yet they will be among the few beneficiaries from America’s barrage of tariffs. For decades, rich countries’ sound trade policies denied academics cases of tit-for-tat protectionism to study. But new American taxes on many goods from China and metals from everywhere have produced the data set of their dreams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;America’s government seems unfazed by the damage its tariffs do to the economy. One study by scholars at the Federal Reserve and Princeton and Columbia Universities found that the new levies have raised costs for consumers by $1.4bn per month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Donald Trump is devoted to his voters. And his trading rivals have retaliated where it hurts. A paper by Joseph Parilla and Max Bouchet of the Brookings Institution, a think-tank, estimated that 61% of jobs affected by retaliatory tariffs are in counties that voted for Mr Trump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is this a coincidence? If a country’s imports from America already come from mostly Republican areas, those regions will bear the brunt of a trade war. However, a new paper by Thiemo Fetzer and Carlo Schwarz of the University of Warwick finds that America’s rivals probably did consider politics when crafting their policies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To test if recent tariffs were politically motivated, the authors needed to compare them with alternatives that were not. They devised this benchmark by creating at random 1,000 hypothetical bundles of targeted goods for each trading partner, all worth the same as the actual trade facing tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The authors then compared real-world policies with these alternatives. First, they assessed the political impact of each plan, by measuring how closely its targeted areas matched Republican gains when Mr Trump was elected. Next, they estimated how much each policy would harm a retaliating bloc’s own economy, by counting the share of its imports of the chosen goods that come from America. The more a country relies on one supplier, the more switching to a less efficient source is likely to hurt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The study found that the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; prioritised minimising such damage. Its tariffs deftly protected domestic consumers, causing less disruption than 99% of alternatives. The bloc targeted Trump voters as well—its tariffs matched the election of 2016 more closely than in 87% of simulations—but not at the cost of upsetting its own citizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In contrast, China focused on punishing Trump voters. Its tariffs tracked the election better than 99% of alternatives. They also disrupted China’s own economy more than in 99% of simulations. Even among plans including soyabeans—one of China’s main imports, grown mostly in Republican areas—China’s policy was just slightly more politically targeted than similar options, but far worse for its economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;China’s choice of tariffs seems designed to deter escalation at any cost. Only regimes with no voters to satisfy can run that risk. The lesson is clear: if you start a trade war, fight a democracy, not an autocracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/20190427_GD411_tradewar/fixes.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190427_GD411_tradewar/fixes.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Graphic detail&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;You get what you give&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 20:07:07 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why presidential libraries are controversial]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/04/25/why-presidential-libraries-are-controversial]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_BLP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T11:04:29Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE BUILDING of Barack Obama’s presidential library in Chicago ought to be uncontroversial. Unlike many other such libraries, it will not be maintained by American taxpayers. The Obama Foundation, a non-profit organisation founded by the 44th president, will foot the bill for maintaining the building, overseeing its exhibits and running its events. But not all Chicagoans are thrilled by what the foundation has called a new “economic engine for the city”. A local pressure group, Protect Our Parks, has taken city authorities to court for its decision to grant 20 acres of land in Jackson Park, on Chicago’s south side, on a 99-year lease costing just $10. Indignant at this relinquishing of public space, the group calls the act an “illegal land grab”. If legal matters can be sorted out, the complex will open in 2021. It will not be a presidential library in the traditional sense of housing Mr Obama’s records. Instead, the foundation has formed a partnership with the National Archives and Records Association (NARA), a government agency, which will digitise them. The building will be part museum, part community centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The libraries use exhibitions and events to chart the lives of their respective presidents. Some contain recreations of the Oval Office. They also hold archives of documents from the presidents and their staffers and, in the cases of Lyndon B. Johnson and Nixon, recordings of conversations they had in office. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Presidential records (such as books, correspondence, memos and papers) were once considered the property of the office holder. As a result, many documents were poorly looked after, lost or destroyed. In 1941 Franklin D. Roosevelt opened the first presidential library and donated his records to the state. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Presidential libraries can take two forms. In some cases, presidents and their supporters run the libraries themselves (as was the case with Richard Nixon’s until 2007). This applies mainly to the records of presidents who served before Herbert Hoover, because the NARA refuses to fund them. For more recent presidents, maintenance is usually overseen by NARA, which also looks after on-site archives. The Presidential Libraries Act of 1955 stipulated that presidents could build a library using funds they raised themselves, with ownership (and maintenance costs) subsequently transferred to the state. In 1978 the Presidential Records Act transferred ownership of all records to the public, bolstering libraries’ archival offerings by imposing a legal duty on presidents and their staff to ensure records are not thrown away. Later, Congress required presidents to provide an endowment in proportion to the size of the library, to contribute to maintenance costs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The libraries have been a source of controversy before. Benjamin Hufbauer of the University of Louisville says they are tantamount to presidential publicity centres. Johnson paid close attention to his library’s attendance figures, reportedly suggesting that opening times be extended and doughnuts served to boost numbers. Some libraries have provoked ire with their selectivity. An exhibit at the Nixon library, when still privately owned by the Richard Nixon Foundation, implied that the uproar over the burgling of the offices of the Democratic National Committee in 1972 in an effort to steal campaign secrets—an event that Nixon tried to cover up and for which he was forced to resign—was actually an effort by Democrats to overturn his victory in the 1972 election. This version of the Watergate scandal was only redressed when the library came under public ownership. However, even under NARA stewardship libraries can be problematic. The Iran-Contra scandal was one of the biggest controversies of Ronald Reagan’s presidency, resulting in a congressional investigation and the indictment of a number of senior administration officials. Yet it went unmentioned by exhibitions in his library until 2011.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The libraries do, however, have some more practical benefits. Many consider them a boon for the local economy. Indeed, that may well be the reason why, despite NARA’s refusal to fund libraries for presidents preceding Hoover, local groups and states fund the libraries themselves. In 2018, 100 years after the death of Theodore Roosevelt, North Dakota’s governor unveiled an as-yet-unconfirmed plan to commit $50m of state funds, matched by $100m in private donations, to a library dedicated to the former president. What should be expected from President Donald Trump’s library? Mr Hufbauer would comment only on Mr Trump’s taste:  “He does seem to have a fondness for gold.” As for the legacy of the 45th president, the records will have to speak for themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 20:07:05 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>