<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[The political nausea when feelings replace facts]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/21/the-political-nausea-when-feelings-replace-facts]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_OPP504_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T14:46:47Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SINCE THE 17th century Western societies have elevated reason above feeling as the basis for political action. Emphasising reason in this way presumed that it could be neatly separated from feelings altogether, that they were discrete categories. Politicians who acted on reason alone were virtuous, whereas those who exploited emotions and feelings were deemed to be unscrupulous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this dimension of the Enlightenment has “run aground”, argues William Davies, a political economist at Goldsmiths, University of London. His latest book, “Nervous States”, documents the struggle between “reason” and “feelings” in politics. It is very much a book for our times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Davies argues that in pursuit of reason, European countries founded an intellectual architecture that largely survives to this day; the numerous Royal Societies, academies of science, universities, learned journals and newspapers (such as &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;, launched in 1843) that codified knowledge and developed what came to be known as logico-deductive modes of reasoning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The high priests of these institutions were “experts”, and, as Mr Davies, writes, “their ability to keep feelings separate from their observations was one of their distinguishing traits.” In public life still, he writes, “an accusation of being emotional traditionally carries the implication that someone has lost objectivity and given way to irrational forces.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But for a variety of reasons, some medical/scientific, some sociological and others political, neat distinctions between reason and feelings have broken down. As Mr Davies argues in his book, “Experts and facts no longer seem capable of settling arguments to the extent that they once did.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, expertise itself is under assault in the age of Trump and Brexit. A lot of polling demonstrates how trust in the intellectual architecture of reason has steadily dwindled, including trust in most professions, and most particularly trust in government, politicians and the media. Instead, people are now allowed to trust and express their own feelings as “alternative facts”. President Donald Trump, for instance, makes much of how he will trust his gut more than any adviser.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Davies argues, convincingly, that one reason for this is that, for all its impressive data collection and sophisticated modelling and analysis, “the facts produced by experts and technocrats simply do not capture lived reality for many people”. He attributes this largely to rising inequality in the West.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For instance, it does not matter how much an expert bangs on about rising aggregate employment levels and levels of inward investment if the individual does not feel better about themselves. “If there is one thing more important than prosperity to people’s well-being then it is self-esteem. Those suffering a collapse of self-esteem, for whatever reason, are often the most receptive to nationalist rhetoric,” he writes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For this reason, Mr Davies writes, “we have to take people’s feelings seriously as political issues, and not simply dismiss them as irrational.” This, surely, was Hillary Clinton’s mistake in fighting Donald Trump in 2016, hence her unfortunate reference to the “deplorables”, those most likely to vote for Mr Trump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Likewise, in Britain the campaign to remain in the EU in the lead-up to the referendum in 2016 relied entirely on tendentious economic forecasting at the expense of any emotional appeal to a shared European future. The Brexit campaign was the exact opposite, relying almost exclusively on appeals to “feelings” of nostalgia and patriotism. It was also, of course, a vivid rebellion against the tyranny of experts and the “mainstream media”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Democracies are being transformed, Mr Davies writes, “by the power of feelings in ways that cannot be ignored or reversed. This is our reality now.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So how should “bravado rationalists”, as Mr Davies calls them, respond to this new era? One response would be to double down on scientific objectivity and institutions in even bolder terms. “In the face of nationalist reaction, this strategy offers faith in facts as the only means of resistance,” he writes. “It assumes that the unrivalled capacity of rationalist argument among qualified experts will save us from demagogues and nationalists.” But as Mr Davies makes clear, this project has been undermined progressively, particularly now by the populist right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what would an alternative construct look like, a new philosophy of knowledge to inform our politics for these troubled times? We sat down with Mr Davies to pick his brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, argues Mr Davies, it behoves liberals and rationalists to acknowledge where things went wrong. Often they have placed too much faith in statistics and forecasts that proved erroneous. This undermined faith in the whole project of evidence-based analysis more generally: “Macro-economic indicators have been justifiably pulled apart in recent years,” argues Mr Davies. He characterises the era of the Great Moderation, roughly the period from the mid-1990s to 2007, as “an era of expecting numbers to do politics for us”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Governments, such as Britain’s New Labour, grew increasingly technocratic, staffed by policy wonks. Consequently they suffered from a deep ignorance of their own country, a situation that might have been rectified by recourse to other disciplines such as anthropology and ethnography. He particularly references the famous study of Tea Party America, “Strangers in Their Own Land”, by anthropologist Arlie Russell Hochshild.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Secondly, Mr Davies argues that there is now a lot of evidence to show that “story-telling” has the power to sway peoples’ opinions as much as statistics. Story-telling can be used just as well to accompany evidence-based politics and arguments as it can be abused by populists. Story-telling is what made the great wordsmiths, such as Winston Churchill, so successful; what these politicians are asking their listeners is not so much “do my words match up to reality?”, as “do my words mobilise you?”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equally, argues Mr Davies, rationalists are lagging behind the fact that we have moved from a “verbal public sphere” to an “image-based” sphere, where photos, videos and the attendant social-media channels predominate. People have not become more emotional over time, they do not have more feelings than they used to; rather they now have an infinite variety of ways to express those feelings in real time, on smart-phones for instance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Feeling has entered politics mainly for technological reasons,” argues Mr Davies, and populism is all about quick, unfiltered responses to events. As a riposte, rationalists can use infographics and data-visualisation as a way of presenting statistics and evidence, but, Mr Davies warns, these also risk “triggering” people into knee-jerk responses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, advises Mr Davies, we should cherish those institutions, imperfect though they may be, that aspire to objectivity and truth-telling. Free marketeers, for instance, might deride the BBC for its funding formula, relying as it does on a taxpayer levy, but these concerns should now be outweighed by its contribution to maintaining a reasonable consensus on what constitutes real facts and news—a consensus that has already largely broken down in America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a quid pro quo, institutions have to be more obviously free of political influence than ever before. For a public broadcaster like the BBC, this means no longer appointing former politicians, such as Labour’s James Purnell, to top positions. It seems a reasonable trade-off to survive the post-truth world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If feelings have come to dominate politics to the detriment of good governance and evidence-led policy-making, then the rationalists need to reassert themselves; to show some emotion and take governance back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 23:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Toy Story 4” is another enjoyable, nostalgic adventure]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/21/toy-story-4-is-another-enjoyable-nostalgic-adventure]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_BKP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T12:51:58Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ONE OF the magical things about Pixar’s “Toy Story” films is the way they balance the comfort of the old and the shock of the new. The series’ first instalment, released in 1995, was also the first ever feature film to be rendered solely using three-dimensional computer-generated imagery (CGI), so it was as cutting-edge as cinema could be. But “Toy Story” was also an ode to sunlit childhoods, with such vintage toys as Mr Potatohead and Slinky Dog. Its lead character was Woody (voiced by Tom Hanks), a cowboy rag doll manufactured in the 1950s, and there weren’t many children playing with those in 1995. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the series’ fourth episode, “Toy Story 4”, the animation is more photorealistic than ever. Images of fairground lights and muddy rainwater rushing down gutters, for instance, are indistinguishable from footage shot with a camera. But, on this occasion, the film’s technical innovation is outweighed by its love of the past. Set largely in a quaint town of parks and carnivals, “Toy Story 4” never acknowledges that children now play with phones and tablets as much as they play with dolls, or that the toys they enjoy are often tied into “The Avengers”, “Star Wars”, “Harry Potter” and “Pokémon”. The setting also seems to be devoid of security cameras and webcams. How else could so many sentient toys scurry so cavalierly around playgrounds and along highways, day and night, without anyone noticing?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The plot has a retro ring to it, too: in many respects, it is the same old “Toy Story”. The film begins with Woody realising again that his owner likes another toy more than she likes him. In the 1995 version, the owner was Andy and the usurper was Buzz Lightyear (Tim Allen). In the 2019 version, the owner is Bonnie, and the favoured toy is, well, all of them except Woody: when Bonnie constructs imaginary towns, she leaves him in the cupboard. If that weren’t humiliating enough, she fashions a new toy (Tony Hale) out of a white plastic spork and names him Forky. He believes that he is a piece of cutlery, not a toy, just as Buzz believed he was an astronaut. And when Forky absconds from the family’s campervan during a driving holiday, Woody goes after him, just as he went after Buzz. Soon, his search-and-rescue mission leads him to an antique shop where he hopes to find Bo Peep (Annie Potts), his love interest in the first two films. Instead, he finds Gabby Gabby (Christina Hendricks), a doll who is planning to revitalise herself via the toy equivalent of organ harvesting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Considering how much of the film unfolds in an antique shop, it’s conceivable that one of the screenplay’s many drafts—there are ten credited screenwriters—may have admitted that toys just aren’t as central to childhood as they once were. The shop-owner even lets her granddaughter take Woody away when she finds him on the floor because, she says, “nobody ever buys the toys.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the film-makers don’t have the courage to confront their characters’ obsolescence—or, for that matter, their films’ obsolescence. A few years after “Toy Story 3” came out, a rival cartoon, “The Lego Movie”, sketched a much sharper and more accurate picture of how modern children play. What “Toy Story 4” opts for instead are the usual breakneck chases, death-defying leaps, snappy catchphrases, emotional reunions and nostalgic, warm images of America at its most wholesome. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That doesn’t mean it isn’t enjoyable. Even if it is weaker than the previous “Toy Story” episodes, the film is still a hugely endearing and consistently funny family adventure—and that can’t be said of many films which are the fourth in a series, animated or otherwise. What “Toy Story 4” offers, though, is the sentimental pleasure of getting a favourite old plaything from the attic, rather than the thrill of unwrapping something new.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Toy Story 4” is released worldwide on June 21st&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 20:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Imagine if Donald Trump could speak Latin”—Boris Johnson’s bid for power]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/21/imagine-if-donald-trump-could-speak-latin-boris-johnsons-bid-for-power]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T11:30:10Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;CHARMING BUFFOON or cunning chameleon? Welcoming liberal or snarling Brexiteer? We ask why, despite having no guiding philosophy, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/20/which-boris-would-britain-get&quot;&gt;Boris Johnson&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is so likely to become Britain’s prime minister. Our obituaries editor remembers the socialite &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/obituary/2019/06/15/obituary-claus-von-bulow-died-on-may-25th&quot;&gt;Claus von Bülow&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, his sensational attempted-murder trials in America and the enduring question of whether he did it. And, despite appearances, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/china/2019/05/02/avengers-endgame-has-been-an-unusual-hit-in-china&quot;&gt;China’s and America’s film markets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; are growing farther apart. Runtime: TK min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/072c75c9-b4ed-4699-90ba-ce8af932d1c3&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 20:39:55 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kim Jong Un entertains Xi Jinping at home]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/21/kim-jong-un-entertains-xi-jinping-at-home]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_asp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS DEFIANT circus performances go, it wasn’t too bad. “Invincible socialism” was the title of the show which North Korea had put on especially for the benefit of Xi Jinping, China’s president. Following a banquet with Kim Jong Un, the North’s dictator, on June 20th, Mr Xi was treated to fireworks, mass aerobics and a large flip-card image of his face produced by thousands of performers, all set to rousing music against a backdrop of Chinese and North Korean flags. A write-up in the &lt;em&gt;Rodong Sinmun&lt;/em&gt;, a North Korean propaganda mouthpiece, on the following day said the crowd had enjoyed the reminder of the blood the two neighbouring countries had spilled to secure their redoubtable workers’ paradises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The display topped off the first day of Mr Xi’s two-day state visit to North Korea, which Chinese state media had announced earlier in the week. The day had not been short on pomp. Earlier, Mr Kim had given his visitor a red-carpet welcome at the airport, complete with gun salutes, goose-stepping soldiers and crowds waving flowers and balloons, before whisking him off in an open-topped car for a tour through the streets of Pyongyang, the capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was Mr Xi’s first visit to North Korea since he and Mr Kim took the helm of their respective countries. China’s leader took his time over it: Mr Kim has been to visit him four times over the past year and a bit, starting with a first secretive trip to Beijing in March 2018. The fixed smiles and expansive talk of socialist brotherhood are par for the course. Despite their frequently uneasy relationship, in public the two neighbours regularly affirm their ideological kinship and eternal partnership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest shindig came a few days before the anniversary of the North’s invasion of South Korea in 1950, which started the Korean war, and ahead of Mr Xi’s planned encounter with Mr Trump at the G20 in Japan next week. (China says America requested the meeting with Mr Xi as soon as news broke of the Chinese leader’s visit to Pyongyang.) The timing suggests that Mr Xi may be looking for leverage over America in the two countries’ deepening trade war. Mr Kim, for his part, may have been seeking to send his own signal to America, that Mr Xi continues to stand by him even as nuclear negotiations between North Korea and America remain stuck in a rut.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is not known what precisely the two dictators discussed once they retired to a guest house for talks. According to Chinese and North Korean state media, they exchanged opinions on a range of “serious international issues”, including the political situation on the Korean peninsula. One of those “issues” appears to be needling America into further concessions in order to break the deadlock in nuclear talks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Chinese state media, Mr Kim complained to Mr Xi about American intransigence, saying his country had not received “positive responses” from an unnamed party despite taking “many active measures to control tensions”, though he promised to remain “patient” with this mysterious foot-dragger for the time being. Mr Xi reportedly said that China was willing to assist “within its capacity” with the North’s concerns about security and economic development, which some analysts speculate may indicate a loosening of sanctions enforcement against North Korea by China. He also said that America and North Korea should “accommodate each other’s reasonable concerns”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though there was no sign of the “grand plan” for resolving the situation on the peninsula that Mr Xi had promised ahead of his trip, the relatively moderate tone of the reported comments suggests that, for now, neither man is particularly keen to anger Mr Trump. For North Korea, a return to the frequent tests of long-range missiles and nuclear bombs that preceded last year’s diplomatic efforts is not on the cards. Mr Trump, for his part, seems relaxed about the situation: “We’re either going to have a good deal and a fair deal or we’re not going to have a deal at all, and that’s ok too,” he said at a rally in Florida on Tuesday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That suits Mr Xi, whose greatest worry with respect to his small neighbour is unpredictability. For Mr Kim a greater degree of sanctions-busting is a huge boon. But the basic problem—that America wants Mr Kim to give up its nuclear weapons, but that he shows little inclination to do so—is not going away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 20:39:54 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EU leaders fail to agree on who should lead the union]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/charlemagnes-notebook/2019/06/21/eu-leaders-fail-to-agree-on-who-should-lead-the-union]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_blp907_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T15:00:33Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;IS THE Spitzenkandidat process dead? And if so, who killed it? In 2014 the EU grudgingly accepted a convention by which the “lead candidate” of the largest parliamentary group becomes president of the European Commission, the EU’s executive. At the European Parliament elections last month most of the major party &amp;quot;families&amp;quot; duly presented their nominees. In theory, this would make allocating the EU’s various big jobs after the election easier. With the commission’s head selected, as it were, by the voters, leaders could fill the other posts, like the presidencies of the European Council (the body containing the union’s heads of government) and the European Central Bank (ECB), in a way that created a politically and ideologically balanced package. That, indeed, was the main task of last night’s discussion at the European Council summit in Brussels.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It did not work out that way. The summit ended in deadlock as the Spitzenkandidat system came under attack from various directions. The convention has always looked rather shaky. Angela Merkel, the German chancellor, was not a fan in 2014 and was bounced into supporting it that time. But the story of the current mess really begins in Helsinki last November, when the European People’s Party (EPP), the main centre-right grouping and, then as now the parliament’s largest force, picked Manfred Weber as its lead candidate. The Bavarian lacks televisual charisma, has no executive experience and has alienated centrists and centre-leftists with his long association with Viktor Orban, Hungary’s authoritarian prime minister. He made little impact during the European election campaign. A survey published on Tuesday by the European Council on Foreign Relations, a think-tank, found that only 4% of voters in France or Germany were motivated to vote by the Spitzenkandidat system.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of which provides the pretext for opponents of the system, and of Mr Weber, to rip it up. That they proceeded to do yesterday. Ahead of the summit the leaders of the parliament’s second- and third- largest groups, the centre-left Socialists and Democrats (S&amp;amp;D) and the centrist Renew Europe (RE, formerly the Alliance of Liberals and Democrats, or ALDE), announced that they would not back him. That greatly dimmed his prospects, as an incoming commission president needs the backing of a majority of the European Parliament.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the dinner on June 20th eleven of the 27 national leaders making the choice (Britain’s Theresa May is not involved) blocked his nomination. An irritated Mrs Merkel, who is backing Mr Weber, responded that in that case the other groups’ lead candidates or de-facto lead candidates—namely Frans Timmermans of S&amp;amp;D and Margrethe Vestager of RE—should also be ruled out. This aggravated Mark Rutte, the liberal Dutch prime minister, who characterised the stance as unreasonable. But it was probably a statement of reality: there is no clear majority in the parliament without EPP votes, and the EPP will be reluctant to back an alternative lead candidate if their own is rebuffed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With no majority for Mr Weber, Mr Timmermans or Ms Vestager—President Emmanuel Macron of France declared all three “ruled out” on leaving the summit—there is no consensus around a commission president candidate in either the parliament or the council. And without that first building block it is tricky to allocate the remaining big jobs. So the meeting broke up in the early hours of June 21st having settled on no nominations. Leaders will meet again on June 30th, shortly before the new parliament convenes on July 2nd and ahead of an expected vote on the nominated commission candidate two weeks later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Adding to the sense of frustration at the summit was leaders’ inability to reach agreement on a common commitment to a zero-carbon EU by 2050, with objections from Poland, the Czech Republic, Hungary and Estonia getting in the way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What next for the big jobs jigsaw? Mr Weber is not yet entirely out of the running but his prospects look poor. Even Mrs Merkel seems to be resigning herself to this, acknowledging that leaders needed to find a commission candidate capable of commanding the broad majority necessary: “We do not under any circumstances want a crisis with the parliament,” she insisted last night. The German chancellor is expected to entertain alternative figures at the next discussion. One possible compromise candidate is Michel Barnier, a French EPP politician and the EU’s chief Brexit negotiator. But it may be that other names bubble up, perhaps at the G20 summit in Japan next week, where several major EU leaders will have the chance to cut deals before the next gathering in Brussels. One option has the leaders parking the discussion about the commission job and settling instead on candidates for the council and the ECB, then working back from there. An outlandish theory doing the rounds even has Donald Tusk, the European Council president, eventually putting himself forward to lead the commission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The deadlock, like the inability to form consensus on the climate goals, is a sign of the times. Europe is a more fractured place than in the past, with bigger divides between member states and a more fragmented political landscape both in the national capitals and in the incoming European Parliament (the successful commission president will probably need the backing of three or even four groups to secure a majority, where two used to suffice). Some member states are more used to this than others. The Netherlands, which has experienced political fragmentation for longer, and to a greater extent, than most, took seven months to form its last government—as Mr Rutte reminded waiting journalists last night, urging patience. Leo Varadkar, Ireland’s taoiseach (prime minister) was less emollient, despairing: “It’s quicker to elect the pope.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 18:40:16 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump orders air strikes on Iran—then cancels them]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/21/donald-trump-orders-air-strikes-on-iran-then-cancels-them]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_map503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AFTER YEARS of fighting through sanctions and proxies, America and Iran have come to the brink of a direct confrontation. On the morning of June 20th Iran shot down an American spy drone over the Strait of Hormuz. Iran claims the aircraft was flying over its territorial waters, while America insists it was above international waters. Although Donald Trump growled that Iran had made a “big mistake,” he soon tried to downplay the incident. “I find it hard to believe it was intentional,” he said before a meeting with the Canadian prime minister, Justin Trudeau. The president suggested that a “stupid” Iranian officer could have approved anti-aircraft fire without the approval of his superiors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But by evening, American media reported, Mr Trump had approved his own response: air strikes on radar and missile batteries in Iran. Congressional leaders were summoned for a White House briefing. The New York Times reported that American warplanes were already in the air. Then Mr Trump abruptly cancelled the strikes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There has been no official confirmation of any of this, yet the details leaked almost in real time. Perhaps this is simply a head-fake from a president who built a business career on bluster. Indeed, Iranian officials claim that Mr Trump warned them of the strikes in advance. In a message passed via Oman, which has acted as a mediator in the past, he reportedly insisted that he did not want war and called for negotiations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Or perhaps his apparent volte-face reflects the turmoil in Mr Trump’s national-security apparatus. He campaigned on ending American military adventures in the Middle East. But his national security adviser, John Bolton, is a longtime Iran hawk who has advocated military action in the past. America has not had a permanent defense secretary since James Mattis stepped down in December. On June 19th Mr Trump announced that his acting defence chief, Patrick Shanahan, was also leaving amid allegations of domestic violence involving his wife and son.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Confrontation in the Gulf has been building for more than a year, since Mr Trump withdrew from the nuclear deal that Iran signed with America and other powers in 2015. The accord had lifted some economic sanctions on Iran in exchange for limits on its nuclear programme. As the Trump administration sought to choke off Iran’s oil exports through renewed sanctions, Iran kept up its end of the bargain until May, then announced that it would begin stockpiling low-enriched uranium in excess of the prescribed limits. It expects to breach that threshold later this month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It has also seemingly pursued an aggressive, albeit shadowy, response in the region. In May saboteurs blew holes in four oil tankers anchored off the port of Fujairah in the United Arab Emirates. Two more tankers were attacked as they sailed in the Gulf of Oman on June 13th. America blames Iran for both incidents (investigators have not made any formal conclusions). It released photographs that show sailors from Iran’s navy removing what appears to be an unexploded limpet mine from one of the ships damaged earlier this month. The Houthis, a Yemeni Shia militia that receives assistance from Iran, have launched several attacks on Saudi infrastructure with missiles and drones, striking an oil pipeline and an international airport, and missing a desalination plant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The attacks on shipping threaten freedom of navigation in a waterway through which one-fifth of the world’s oil passes. Firing anti-aircraft missiles over the Gulf poses another risk: the region is a busy air corridor full of jumbo jets, particularly from large Gulf carriers like Qatar Airways. In 1988 an American warship mistook a passenger jet operated by Iran Air for a military aircraft and shot it down, killing all 290 people on board. After the drone incident, the Federal Aviation Administration warned American aircraft to avoid Iran’s airspace over the Persian Gulf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America and its Gulf allies will feel the need to restore deterrence. An American aircraft-carrier group, B-52 bombers and extra American troops have already been sent to the Middle East region. But air strikes against Iran could just as easily do the opposite. Shooting down the drone sends a message about Iran’s capabilities. The aircraft, an RQ-4, is built to fly at up to 18,300 metres (60,000 feet), almost twice as high as a commercial airliner. That Iran was able to shoot it down suggests its air defences may be better than America thought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still unclear in all of this is exactly what Mr Trump wants. He has suggested that he simply wants a tougher nuclear deal. His secretary of state, Mike Pompeo, has outlined a set of demands that ask Iran not just to limit its nuclear work but realign its entire foreign policy. Mr Bolton, as a private citizen, called for regime change. Critics of the deal argued that the president’s “maximum pressure” campaign would force Iran to renegotiate. But it was always more likely to end like this—in steady escalation, with no end in sight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 18:40:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EU leaders fail to agree on who should lead the union for the next five years]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/charlemagnes-notebook/2019/06/21/eu-leaders-fail-to-agree-on-who-should-lead-the-union-for-the-next-five-years]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_blp907_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T07:00:33Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;IS THE Spitzenkandidat process dead? And if so, who killed it? In 2014 the EU introduced this convention by which the “lead candidate” of the largest parliamentary group becomes president of the European Commission, the EU’s executive. At the European Parliament elections last month most of the major party families duly presented their nominees. In theory, this would make allocating the EU’s various big jobs after the election easier. With the commission’s head selected, as it were, by the voters, leaders could fill the other posts, like the presidencies of the European Council (the body containing the union’s heads of government) and the European Central Bank (ECB), in a way that created a politically and ideologically balanced package. That, indeed, was the main task of last night’s discussion at the European Council summit in Brussels.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It did not work out that way. The summit ended in deadlock as the Spitzenkandidat system came under attack from various directions. The convention has always looked rather shaky. Angela Merkel was not a fan in 2014 and had to be bounced into supporting it that time. But the story of the current mess really begins in Helsinki last November, when the European People’s Party (EPP), the main centre-right grouping and then as now the parliament’s largest force, picked Manfred Weber as its lead candidate. The Bavarian lacks televisual charisma, has no executive experience and has alienated centrists and centre-leftists with his long association with Viktor Orban, Hungary’s authoritarian prime minister. He made little impact during the European election campaign. A survey published on Tuesday by the European Council on Foreign Relations, a think-tank, found that only 4% of voters in France or Germany were motivated to vote by the Spitzenkandidat system.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;All of which provides the pretext for opponents of the system, and of Mr Weber, to rip it up. That they proceeded to do yesterday. Ahead of the summit the leaders of the parliament’s second- and third- largest groups, the centre-left Socialists and Democrats (S&amp;amp;D) and the centrist Renew Europe (RE), announced that they would not back him. That greatly dimmed his prospects, as an incoming commission president needs the backing of a majority of the European Parliament. At the dinner eleven of the 27 national leaders making the choice (Britain’s Theresa May is not involved) blocked his nomination. An irritated Mrs Merkel, who is backing Mr Weber, responded that in that case the other groups’ lead candidates or de-facto lead candidates—namely Frans Timmermans of S&amp;amp;D and Margrethe Vestager of RE—should also be ruled out. This aggravated Mark Rutte, the liberal Dutch prime minister, who characterised the stance as unreasonable. But it was probably a statement of reality: there is no clear majority in the parliament without EPP votes, and the EPP will be reluctant to back an alternative lead candidate if their own is rebuffed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;With no majority for Mr Weber, Mr Timmermans or Ms Vestager—Emmanuel Macron declared all three “ruled out” on leaving the summit—there is no consensus around a commission president candidate in either the parliament or the council. And without that first building block its is tricky to allocate the remaining big jobs. So the meeting broke up in the early hours of this morning having settled on no nominations. Leaders will now meet again on June 30th, shortly before the new parliament convenes on July 2nd and ahead of an expected vote on the nominated commission candidate two weeks later. Adding to the sense of frustration at the summit was leaders’ inability to reach agreement on a common commitment to a zero-carbon EU by 2050, with objections from Poland, the Czech Republic, Hungary and Estonia getting in the way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;What next for the big jobs jigsaw? Mr Weber is not yet entirely out of the running but is prospects look poor. Even Mrs Merkel seems to be resigning herself to this, acknowledging that leaders needed to find a commission candidate capable of commanding the broad majority necessary: “we do not under any circumstances want a crisis with the parliament”, she insisted last night. The German chancellor is expected to entertain alternative figures at the next discussion. One possible compromise candidate is Michel Barnier, a French EPP politician and the EU’s chief Brexit negotiator. But it may be that other names bubble up, perhaps at the G20 summit in Japan next week, where several major EU leaders will have the chance to cut deals before the next gathering in Brussels. One option has the leaders parking the discussion about the commission job and settling instead on candidates for the council and the ECB, then working back from there. An outlandish theory doing the rounds even has Donald Tusk, the council president, eventually putting himself forward to lead the commission.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The deadlock, like the inability to form consensus on the climate goals, is a sign of the times. Europe is a more fractured place than in the past, with bigger divides between member states and a more fragmented political landscape both in the national capitals and in the incoming European Parliament (the successful commission president will probably need the backing of three or even four groups to secure a majority, where two used to suffice). Some member states are more used to this than others. The Netherlands, which has experienced political fragmentation for longer, and to a greater extent, than most, took seven months to form its last government—as Mr Rutte reminded waiting journalists last night, urging patience. Leo Varadkar, Ireland’s taoiseach (prime minister) was less emollient, despairing: “It’s quicker to elect the pope.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 15:40:48 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Supreme Court blesses a cross-shaped war memorial in Maryland]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/20/the-supreme-court-blesses-a-cross-shaped-war-memorial-in-maryland]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_USP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-20T22:48:03Z&quot;&gt;Jun 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE FIRST line of the First Amendment—“Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion”—has inspired sharply divergent interpretations. To glance at the vote in&lt;em&gt; American Legion v American Humanist Association,&lt;/em&gt; a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/18pdf/17-1717_4f14.pdf&quot;&gt;7-2 ruling&lt;/a&gt; handed down on June 20th, one might get the impression those differences have been largely ironed out over the 72 years since the court first addressed the meaning of the Establishment Clause in a school-bussing case from New Jersey. That impression is misleading.&lt;em&gt; American Legion&lt;/em&gt; is no picture of judicial consensus: in additional to the plurality opinion six justices wrote separately to dissent or clarify their views. In all, seven justices agreed that a 40-foot cross-shaped memorial to soldiers who died in the first world war will continue to loom over a pair of roads in Bladensburg, Maryland. But very different opinions lay behind that decision and two justices expressed a much stricter view about the place of religious symbols on public ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justice Samuel Alito, author of the plurality opinion, struck a more generous and less testy note than he often does. In their separate concurring opinions, Justices Stephen Breyer (on the left) and Brett Kavanaugh (on the right) both praised Justice Alito’s opinion as “eloquent”. Justice Elena Kagan—with whom Justice Alito &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2014/05/06/niggling-distinctions&quot;&gt;sparred&lt;/a&gt; five years ago in another religion case—commended his ruling for showing “sensitivity to and respect for this nation’s pluralism, and the values of neutrality and inclusion that the First Amendment demands”. These four justices, along with Chief Justice John Roberts, formed partially overlapping Venn diagrams that save the Bladensburg cross with a narrow and historically nuanced justification.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The analysis in the main opinion is straightforward. Yes, Justice Alito wrote, “the cross has long been a preeminent Christian symbol”, but its use on public ground in Maryland “has a special significance” that is more secular than sectarian. The image of “row after row of plain white crosses marking the overseas graves” of fallen soldiers was “emblazoned on the minds of Americans” during the war, he wrote, and the American Legion’s decision to use the cross as its memorial “must be viewed in that historical context”. As a “prominent community landmark”, the memorial expresses “the community’s grief at the loss of the young men who perished” in battle. To require the demolition or “radical alteration” of the monument nearly a century later—in response to a challenge from atheists and non-Christians who view it as alienating—would not be a “neutral act”. It would be hostile to Christianity and to “the ideals of respect and tolerance embodied in the First Amendment”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justice Alito widened the lens beyond the busy intersection outside Washington, DC to reflect on other examples of symbols and institutions in public life. Crosses are found in “many registered trademarks”, he noted, from Blue Cross Blue Shield to Bayer, but non-Christians don’t bat an eye when flashing their health insurance cards or popping an aspirin. Residents of Corpus Christi, Texas or Providence, Rhode Island, don’t petition to change the deeply religious names of their cities. And communities often find meaning in certain faith-centred sites “without necessarily embracing their religious roots”. Notre Dame in Paris is a “striking example”, Justice Alito wrote. Tears and concern for the cathedral after the recent fire show Notre Dame is “a symbol of national importance to the religious and nonreligious alike”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justices Breyer and Kagan dissented from the Supreme Court’s legislative prayer case in 2014, but they were largely on board with Justice Alito’s approach this time around. Justice Kagan opted not to join in a disparagement of the so-called &lt;em&gt;Lemon&lt;/em&gt; test—a fraught method of identifying Establishment Clause violations by looking for a secular purpose and effect and gauging the level of church-state entanglement. She also left her name off of a section drawing lessons from history “out of perhaps an excess of caution”. Better to analyse the matters “case-by-case”, she wrote, than to draw overly broad conclusions. Echoing a concern he &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/03/02/americas-porous-wall-between-church-and-state&quot;&gt;expressed&lt;/a&gt; in the February oral argument, Justice Breyer clarified that “if the cross had been erected only recently, rather than in the aftermath of World War I”, it may not pass constitutional muster. Justice Alito included just enough references to “longstanding” monuments in his opinion—your correspondent counts four—to persuade Justice Breyer that his vote wouldn’t commit the court to upholding newly built crosses or those that seem to target members of religious minorities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To the right and left of these centrist camps stood two pairs of justices with different ideas about what the Establishment Clause means. For Justice Neil Gorsuch, the plaintiffs who objected to the cross should not just lose their case; they never should have been able to sue in the first place. The “‘offended observer’ theory of standing has no basis in law”, he wrote, taking a flame-thrower to the “endorsement test” first developed by Justice Sandra Day O’Connor in 1984. That test, which the courts have never applied consistently, says a government policy or monument might violate the Establishment Clause if a reasonable observer regards it as an official endorsement of religion. “Really, most every governmental action probably offends &lt;em&gt;somebody&lt;/em&gt;”, Justice Gorsuch wrote. The remedy is not to sue but to avert one’s eyes when something seems offensive. Justice Thomas signed this concurrence and penned one of his own repeating his idiosyncratic view that only the federal government—not states or cities—should be subject to the constraints of the Establishment Clause. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the other end of the bench sat the lone dissenters in&lt;em&gt; American Legion&lt;/em&gt;, Justices Ruth Bader Ginsburg (who took the unusual move of reading a portion of her dissent from the bench) and Sonia Sotomayor. For these stricter separationists, letting the “immense” cross remain on public land, supported with public funds, is a clear breach of the church-state wall. “Just as a Star of David is not suitable to honor Christians who died serving their country“, Justice Ginsburg wrote, “so a cross is not suitable to honor those of other faiths who died defending their nation”. The state’s endorsement of the cross “elevates Christianity over other faiths, and religion over nonreligion”. And there is no reason to fear a win for the humanists heralding the bulldozing of dozens of crosses around the country. Each cross must be analysed separately, Justice Ginsburg wrote, and those deemed unacceptable could be moved to private land. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his concurrence, Justice Kavanaugh sounded a note of sympathy with Jewish veterans and others whose “sense of distress and alienation” led them to object to the cross. There are “genuine and important interests” on both sides of the dispute, he wrote, and although the constitution does not require it, perhaps the Maryland legislature would see fit to remove the cross or transfer the land on which it stands to private hands. He added a line few would contest. “[P]inning down the meaning” of the Establishment Clause “has proved to be a vexing problem”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 05:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[And then there were two]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/bagehots-notebook/2019/06/20/and-then-there-were-two]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_BRP550.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-20T19:17:42Z&quot;&gt;Jun 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AFTER TWO days of voting Tory MPs have chosen two of their colleagues to go through to the next stage of the leadership election: a run-off when the party’s 160,000 members will choose the winner. They are Boris Johnson and Jeremy Hunt, the foreign secretary. Mr Johnson got more than half the votes with 160. Mr Hunt just pipped Michael Gove, the environment secretary, with 77 votes to 75.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boris Johnson’s ascent to the prime ministership now looks even more likely than it was a week ago. Mr Johnson’s biggest problem was always winning over his fellow Conservative MPs. He’s never been much of a team player: he has devoted more time to lining his own pockets (in one year he earned £540,000 from journalism and public speaking) than to campaigning for his colleagues. He’s also been a lacklustre and lazy performer at the dispatch box in parliament. But he is adored by the party members in the country who cherish his Bertie Wooster-with-a-thesaurus speeches and flamboyant style. They also agree with him on Brexit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Hunt is unlikely to be able to slow down his momentum. The foreign secretary is in many ways an impressive figure. He inherited a marginal seat and turned it into a safe one. He was health secretary for six years—longer than anyone since the creation of the NHS. He has been a much better foreign secretary than Mr Johnson, his predecessor: foreign office insiders say that he inherited a demoralised and disoriented department and quickly reinvigorated it. But Mr Hunt is a sensible man who is trying to win the support of a party that has gone slightly bonkers: fixated on Brexit, furious about the way Britain has been treated by Brussels, and given to chasing unicorns. The majority of party members say that they support a no-deal Brexit despite overwhelming evidence about the damage that that would do to the economy. Mr Hunt also bears the Conservative Party’s equivalent of the mark of Cain: he voted Remain in 2016. Thus, although he claims that he’s now determined to deliver Brexit, he provokes comparisons with Theresa May who, according to hard-core Brexiteers, failed to deliver Brexit not because of an intractable problem and a hung parliament, but because she didn’t “believe”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Johnson would have faced a much tougher fight against Michael Gove. Mr Gove is one of the party’s most accomplished debaters—quick on his feet, frequently funny and, unlike Mr Johnson, steeped in policy details. He also has an appetite to go for the jugular. Mr Gove might have done real damage to Mr Johnson. By contrast Mr Hunt is too emollient a figure—his critics would call him “bland”—to burst the Boris balloon. Once more, luck is with the front- runner. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tory MPs are also acting out of self-preservation in their choice of Messrs Hunt and Johnson to finish off the contest. MPs knew that a contest between Mr Johnson and Mr Gove could easily have degenerated into the modern equivalent of the contest between Polynices and Eteocles who murdered each other in their determination to rule over Thebes (Mr Johnson, who read classics at Oxford, is fond of classical references). The two men were close friends at Oxford and beyond, with Mr Johnson playing the senior role and Mr Gove being something of a courtier. Mr Johnson chose Mr Gove to run his campaign for the premiership in 2016. But then Mr Gove turned against his friend and former mentor and announced that he didn’t think that he was fit to be prime minister. By choosing Mr Hunt MPs have avoided a blood-letting, and distanced the their party from one of the great psycho-dramas of recent years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The party may have limited the potential damage of the race but it certainly hasn’t escaped Scott free. The two surviving candidates are both products of private schools and Oxford University, Mr Johnson Eton and Balliol, Mr Hunt Charterhouse and Magdalen. Conservatives eliminated the son of a Pakistani bus driver who arrived in the country with £1 in his pocket (Sajid Javid), the adopted son of an Aberdeen fishmonger (Michael Gove) and a foreign office high flyer turned author turned academic who is brimming with original ideas (Rory Stewart). Mr Johnson refused to turn up to the first televised debate and the parliamentary lobby hustings. His team also reportedly used tactics worthy of the Oxford Union (of which he was once president) rather than parliament: “lending” votes to various runners up (by encouraging loyal supporters to vote for them) in order to eliminate candidates, such as Mr Stewart and Mr Gove, who might cause him the most trouble. “There have been lies and lies and lies and loads of pomposity” was one Tory MP’s summary of the race so far. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever the truth of these rumours (and it’s impossible to know given the secrecy of the ballot box) it is important for the future of the Conservative Party that some of the personal damage that has been done during this leadership campaign and its predecessor is repaired. Messrs Johnson and Stewart need to make peace (and Mr Stewart needs to swallow his pride and rescind his promise that he won’t serve in a Johnson administration). Mr Stewart has demonstrated that a Conservative can still excite middle-of-the-road voters. He would also make a superb foreign secretary. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is even more important, from the Conservative Party’s point of view, that Messrs Johnson and Gove bury the hatchet. Mr Gove is that rare thing—a Brexiteer who understands the dangers of a no-deal Brexit. He is also gifted with the very strengths that Mr Johnson lacks: an ability to re-energise government departments with conservative ideas, a broad interest in public policy and an impressive command of detail. In an ideal world Mr Gove would make an excellent CEO to Mr Johnson’s chairman of the board. But then in an ideal world Polynices and Eteocles would not have slaughtered each other. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 05:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Britain&#x27;s leadership race, “Texafornia” dreaming and pets gain the upper paw]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/20/britains-leadership-race-texafornia-dreaming-and-pets-gain-the-upper-paw]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-20T17:30:10Z&quot;&gt;Jun 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A SELECTION of three essential articles read aloud from the latest issue of The Economist. This week, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/20/which-boris-would-britain-get&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Boris Johnson&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is the favourite to become Britain&amp;#x27;s next Prime Minister. America’s future will be written in the two mega-states—&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/20/texafornia-dreaming&quot;&gt;California and Texas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;(8:23). And, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/22/pets-have-gained-the-upper-paw-over-their-so-called-owners&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;pets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; have gained the upper paw over their so-called owners (16:50). Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/f3af74a0-3c5a-4081-8b10-f7ad9da4b2e0&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 01:40:28 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>