<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Success in academia is as much about grit as talent]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/10/success-in-academia-is-as-much-about-grit-as-talent]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_woc857.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-10T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 1968 ROBERT MERTON, a sociologist at Columbia University, identified a feature of academic life that he called the Matthew effect. The most talented scientists, he observed, tend to have access to the most resources and the best opportunities, and receive a disproportionate amount of credit for their work, thus amplifying their already enhanced reputations and careers. Less brilliant ones, meanwhile, are often left scrambling for money and recognition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New research suggests this may not tell the whole story. A working paper by Yang Wang, Benjamin Jones and Dashun Wang of Northwestern University finds that success in the sciences does not always breed more success, and that scientists who fail early in their careers may benefit from the experience. The authors discovered this by collecting data on grant applications submitted between 1990 and 2005 to America’s National Institutes of Health (NIH) by junior-level scientists. In particular, they focused on two groups of applicants: those who received relatively high scores on their submissions but just missed getting a grant, and those who scored similarly well but just succeeded in being awarded one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The three researchers found that, rather than automatically holding the failures back, as the Matthew effect might be thought to predict, an early-career setback of this sort was sometimes associated with greater academic success in the long run. While those who missed out on funding were more likely to drop out from the NIH system, the scientists who persevered and continued to apply for grants after their initial failure outperformed their counterparts who had succeeded first time, as measured by the number of citations of their research that they received over the subsequent ten years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While some of this can be explained by the weakest scientists in the no-grant group giving up, the three researchers showed that other, unobservable, characteristics such as “effort” or “grit” are also at work. Overall, the authors conclude, the findings are consistent with the concept that “what doesn’t kill me makes me stronger”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 07:05:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Does gender equality start in the home?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/10/does-gender-equality-start-in-the-home]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_blp512.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-10T14:20:02Z&quot;&gt;May 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anne McElvoy asks Melinda Gates whether gender equality starts in the kitchen. The American philanthropist explains why the tech world risks entrenching bias into the future, but defends the Gates Foundation’s decision to halve its paid family leave. And Anne and Melinda swap top tips for getting teenagers to do the washing up. Runtime: 20 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-melindagates&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 00:06:16 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Researcher (full-time, one-year contract)]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/news/2019/05/10/researcher-full-time-one-year-contract]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20180224_wop001_10_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-10T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; is the leading source of analysis on international business and world affairs. We are an international company, employing staff throughout the world. We deliver information, opinion and analysis in print and through a range of digital formats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team provides some of the data that appears in &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; and helps to maintain the newspaper’s high standards. You will provide assistance to the journalists and deal with ad hoc requests and reader inquiries. Working closely with our data team, you will assist with gathering statistics and information for charts and tables and be responsible for final sign-off. Working to meet publication deadlines, you will need to check the facts in all articles in print and online. And work on the Indicators pages of the weekly newspaper. You will also be fact-checking scripts for our film unit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ideally educated to degree level with some economic/maths content, you will have some experience of working with information sources and statistics. You will have a general interest in current affairs, business and finance, politics and information. An adept user of IT, you will have a high level of numeracy and literacy coupled with excellent time-management skills. A high standard of accuracy and attention to detail is essential.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will be able to demonstrate:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent team-membership skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A practical and flexible approach to duties&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good interpersonal relations with other staff members&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A keen interest in international and world affairs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Economist Group values diversity. We are committed to equal opportunities and creating an inclusive environment for all our employees. We welcome applicants regardless of ethnic origin, national origin, gender, race, colour, religious beliefs, disability, sexual orientation or age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please send your CV with a covering letter to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.commailto:researchjob@economist.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;researchjob@economist.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Closing date for applications is June 7th 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 22:06:23 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“The Biggest Little Farm” is a quiet call to arms]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/10/the-biggest-little-farm-is-a-quiet-call-to-arms]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_BKP511.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-10T12:21:08Z&quot;&gt;May 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NATURE DOCUMENTARIES are enjoying a moment in the sun. While politicians around the world have failed to pass much meaningful legislation on climate change, film-makers have captured melting ice caps, coral bleaching and devastating floods. On May 9th Netflix announced that “Our Planet”, a mini-series examining humanity’s impact on different species and habitats, was the most-watched title on the streaming site in Britain in April. These productions combine sumptuous cinematography, engaging animal narratives and policy recommendations, demonstrating how an individual’s behaviour can have wide-ranging repercussions. After “Blue Planet II” showed birds feeding their chicks debris from the ocean, an estimated 88% of viewers changed their consumption of single-use plastic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The Biggest Little Farm”, a new documentary, looks at the challenge of sustainability from a much more intimate perspective. There are no playful orangutans or majestic sea turtles; instead it chronicles the journey of two urban-dwellers as they try to reintroduce biodiversity to an abandoned farm. By keeping its focus on practical issues and the realities of running a smallholding, the film offers a feel-good story of environmental recovery that, while sometimes overly simplistic, encourages viewers to reflect on the small changes they might make in their own lives. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;John and Molly Chester start out as an average pair of health-conscious Angelenos. John is a wildlife cinematographer, while Molly is a chef with grand ideas about proper farming techniques but little experience of agricultural work. After being evicted from their home on short notice, they decide to put their passions to work and buy a farm. There they encounter soil that has been ruined by years of monoculture, so they hire a guide—Alan York, a “renowned expert in traditional farming practices”—to teach them how to cultivate more than 200 crops and feed a range of animals that will “self-regulate”. The idea is to create a system that will feed the soil and the people equally, and the Chesters approach this challenge with idealism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet they soon encounter problems, and persistent ones. Pests, ranging from snails to coyotes, move in immediately; natural forces such as droughts, floods and wildfires—all of which have been exacerbated by climate change—mount a considerable threat to their project. “The Biggest Little Farm” depicts a relationship with the natural world that is by turns both life-affirming and horribly grim. The coyotes prove a constant menace, and John’s efforts to stymie them become the central narrative of the film. Images of ravaged chickens recur. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there are also moments of exquisite cinematography, filmed by Mr Chester himself, who also directs. He focuses his lens on the most miniscule of creatures, from ladybugs to dung beetles. When an animal that lives in manure gets a moment in the spotlight, it reflects the idea that, on a truly biodiverse farm, every player matters. Mr Chester resists the temptation to anthropomorphise these creatures, instead demonstrating the key role each plays. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These shifts in tone represent the endless cycles of life and death, of frustration and success, that come with a working farm. It is not the most dramatic narrative: at points the cycles become predictable, even while the film heads towards its happy ending. And though “The Biggest Little Farm” pointedly leaves out some of the most brutal elements of farming—the film asks the viewer to mourn for those animals killed by predators, but make little reference to what awaits the animals raised for meat—it is likely to succeed in encouraging its audience to act.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Few will be able to copy the Chesters’ actions directly, but watching two ordinary people take initiative, face setbacks and overcome challenges in the name of a better world is inspiring enough. After witnessing the couple radically re-organise their priorities and risk their own livelihood, small sacrifices such as growing vegetables, eating less meat, avoiding plastic or taking public transportation more often may seem less daunting. It is a thoughtfully narrow approach, and a valuable addition to a thriving genre. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“The Biggest Little Farm” is released in America on May 10th&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 20:06:24 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Patrick Shanahan is likely to be America’s next defence secretary]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/09/patrick-shanahan-is-likely-to-be-americas-next-defence-secretary]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_blp904.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-09T23:48:37Z&quot;&gt;May 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PATRICK SHANAHAN has made little on mark on the Pentagon during his two years as deputy defence secretary and then acting secretary following James Mattis’s resignation in December. He has instituted no major reform. He has made no memorable statement on global affairs. People who have worked alongside the former Boeing executive sound ambivalent about him. A newcomer to foreign affairs and security policy, he is not known to have strong views, ideological or otherwise. He is said to be a competent manager, which might be considered a minimal requirement for leading America’s armed forces and the vast Pentagon bureaucracy. On May 9th the White House announced that Donald Trump intended to nominate Mr Shanahan to his job on a permanent basis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This represents a big change in what Mr Trump requires from his defence secretary. He picked Mr Mattis, a highly-respected former marine general, at a time when he was new to foreign affairs, unsure of the demands of the presidency and bedazzled by a man in uniform. He referred approvingly to him by his service nickname, “Mad Dog Mattis,” though the moniker was rarely used and Mr Mattis hated it. Mr Trump’s enthusiasm for Mr Mattis dwindled once it became clear that he was neither the bull-headed killer Mr Trump had taken him for, nor prepared to be the president’s own loyal general.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While on board with some of Mr Trump’s instincts—for example, in his stepped-up bombing campaigns against the Taliban and Islamic State—Mr Mattis quietly repudiated the president’s values. He spent much of his time flying around the world trying to reassure the traditional allies Mr Trump lambasted. He stymied Mr Trump’s efforts to ban transsexuals from the armed forces. He survived in the administration for as long as he did through a combination of discretion, chaos elsewhere in the cabinet, and the defence department’s enormous heft. By replacing Mr Mattis with a much less commanding figure, Mr Trump has signalled his preference for loyalty over stature in the most independent power-base within the government.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shanahan showed his loyalty earlier this year by endorsing Mr Trump’s scheme to siphon billions of dollars from the defence budget to put towards a border-wall. He has also argued for the proposed new Space Force—in effect a sixth service branch—that Mr Trump has demanded. This is said to have won him over to Mr Trump, who had previously resisted pressure to make Mr Shanahan’s acting tenure permanent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The announcement of Mr Shanahan’s impending nomination follows the conclusion of a month-long Pentagon investigation into whether he improperly promoted Boeing and disparaged its competitors within the department. Though exonerated by the Pentagon’s acting inspector general, Mr Shanahan was described in his report as speaking peculiarly often—in almost every meeting—about his experience overseeing Boeing’s 787 Dreamliner programme. That points, if not to corruption, to his unusual callowness in government, which Republican national-security hawks such as Lindsey Graham are said to be troubled by. It will also make him a target for Democratic senators in his confirmation hearings. An investigation by the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; found that the production facility in North Carolina that makes the Dreamliner has been subject to many allegations of poor safety standards, as managers rushed to meet production targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Assuming Mr Shanahan is confirmed, his low profile and business background could both turn out to be beneficial for the defence department. It is locked in a perpetual struggle with the sorts of glitches, including inefficient basing, overstaffing and costly acquisitions programmes, he prides himself on solving at Boeing. More traditional defence secretaries—including Mr Mattis—routinely vow to get grips with such problems, before getting distracted by global security. That is less likely to happen to Mr Shanahan, who announced when taking over from Mr Mattis that he intended to travel much less than his predecessor had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flip-side of his leadership would probably be a diminution of the Pentagon’s role in shaping foreign and security policy. This is good news for Mike Pompeo and John Bolton, the belligerent secretary of state and national secretary adviser. They are already profiting from Mr Mattis’s absence. Having the ear of Mr Trump, who likes their style if not necessarily their bellicosity, they have taken the lead on security issues such as Iran—to which Mr Pompeo promised on May 9th a “swift and decisive” US response to any provocation. As well as being far better versed in foreign affairs, both are more adept inter-departmental players than Mr Shanahan, who has the least government experience of almost any defence secretary of recent times. While presiding over by far the biggest government department, he might struggle to check his cabinet colleagues. He will not check Mr Trump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 20:06:23 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“The glue between these two countries has really come unstuck”—on America and China]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/10/the-glue-between-these-two-countries-has-really-come-unstuck-on-america-and-china]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/intell.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-10T11:30:24Z&quot;&gt;May 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUST AS negotiations to end the trade war between &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/11/the-us-china-trading-relationship-will-be-fraught-for-years-to-come&quot;&gt;America and China&lt;/a&gt; seemed imminent, the Trump administration increased tariffs on Chinese goods. Whatever the outcome of the deal, the countries’ relationship will be fraught for years to come. Many weight-loss diets rely on counting &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/news/2019/03/16/death-of-the-calorie&quot;&gt;calories&lt;/a&gt;, but the scientific-sounding measure is actually very misleading. And as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/04/27/can-uber-ever-make-money&quot;&gt;Uber&lt;/a&gt; goes public, we look at previous disruptions of the taxi industry. Runtime: 22min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/unbalanceoftrade-china-americatalks&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 19:06:24 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America raises tariffs on China, and the stakes in a trade war]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/10/america-raises-tariffs-on-china-and-the-stakes-in-a-trade-war]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_blp507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-10T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;MEETING IN WASHINGTON, Chinese and American trade negotiators made it through dinner without hurling the plates at each other. But there was no truce on the menu. One minute after midnight in Washington on May 10th, America carried through on its threat to ratchet up tariffs on Chinese goods. Two minutes later, China vowed to hit back. And so the world’s two biggest economies staggered a couple of steps closer to all-out trade war. Such an outcome is still far from certain: talks are continuing and, until recently, had been making progress. But the risks are rising of economic damage in both countries, and of a rupture in their already strained relationship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The increased tariffs apply to a $200bn tranche of imports from China, including a wide range of industrial inputs such as car parts and circuit boards. Last September, in an early salvo, America hit this tranche with 10% tariffs (a further $50bn-worth had already been struck by tariffs of 25%). Now that 10% has been raised to 25% too, meaning the rate applies to almost half of Chinese exports of goods to America. China has yet to detail its retaliation plans, though it is likely to apply proportionate tariffs: aiming at fewer goods (since it imports less from America than America does from it) but also raising duties to 25%. Liquefied natural gas, meat and fruit are expected to be on its list.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With this escalation the cost from their trade brawl will soon become more visible. The new tariffs will shave as much as half a percentage point off China’s growth rate this year, according to most estimates. When tariffs were 10%, companies could generally digest the higher prices for Chinese imports, which were offset in part by a weaker yuan. At 25% they will struggle to do that, forcing them to pass more pain on to consumers. Inflation in America could increase by about half a percentage point as a result, according to economists at Société Générale, a French bank. And there could be worse to come. President Donald Trump said that America was starting the paperwork to impose 25% tariffs on the remaining $300bn or so of imports from China not yet affected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just a week ago the mood regarding the talks was upbeat. Chinese and American officials had met multiple times since the start of the year. The outlines of a deal were becoming visible China would go at least partway to addressing American demands that it enhance protection of intellectual property, stop coerced technology transfers and open its market more widely to foreign investors. It would also throw in pledges to buy large volumes of American goods, notably farm products, in order to narrow its bilateral trade surplus, a long-standing gripe of Mr Trump’s. America, in turn, would agree to remove at least some tariffs on Chinese products. On April 28th Steven Mnuchin, America’s treasury secretary, said talks were in their “final laps”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, on May 5th, Mr Trump fired off a pair of tweets that shattered the optimism. China, he said, had been attempting to renegotiate the deal. The nature of the dispute is itself a matter of dispute. According to Reuters, citing American government sources, Chinese officials had asked for sweeping edits to a 150-page draft agreement. Robert Lighthizer, the United States Trade Representative, wanted China’s commitments to be enshrined in legislation; Chinese negotiators countered that regulatory changes would be sufficient. But according to Chinese government advisers, the disagreements may run even deeper. They say that American negotiators have, in effect, asked China to undermine its own economic model in demanding that it eliminate subsidies to favoured industries and state-owned firms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given the prospect of a breakdown in negotiations, it was heartening that Liu He, China’s lead trade envoy, still went to Washington for talks that began on May 9th. Some had speculated that China might call off the meetings entirely. But the scope for progress seems limited for now. Chinese officials have long said that they will not make deals in the face of threats. Comments by Mr Liu on his arrival at the talks suggested that he was there more to reinforce that message than to make any big concessions. “I have come with sincerity,” he told Chinese state media, speaking in measured tones. The two delegations met and had dinner on May 9th and were due to resume their talks on May 10th, albeit with higher tariffs in place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The big worry is the potential political fallout from failed talks. Allegations that China reneged on its commitments are catnip for American critics of engagement with it. Trade is, after all, just one aspect of a spiralling mistrust that encompasses politics, technology and armed forces. In China, hawks have always suspected that America’s ultimate goal is to stop it from rising—a belief that has been reinforced by the trade dispute. Left-wing scholars argue that it would amount to treachery for China to give in to America’s demands. Their commercial relationship used to help bind China and America together; now it is driving a wedge between them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most economists still think that the two countries will eventually reach a deal. As the downsides from tariffs become clearer, the reasons to strike an agreement, however tenuous, will prevail. But that is another way of saying that things may have to get worse before they get better. Exactly how much worse is the question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 19:06:23 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Patrick Shanahan is likely to be America’s next defence secretary]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/10/patrick-shanahan-is-likely-to-be-americas-next-defence-secretary]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_blp904.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-10T03:48:37Z&quot;&gt;May 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PATRICK SHANAHAN has made little on mark on the Pentagon during his two years as deputy defence secretary and then acting secretary following James Mattis’s resignation in December. He has instituted no major reform. He has made no memorable statement on global affairs. People who have worked alongside the former Boeing executive sound ambivalent about him. A newcomer to foreign affairs and security policy, he is not known to have strong views, ideological or otherwise. He is said to be a competent manager, which might be considered a minimal requirement for leading America’s armed forces and the vast Pentagon bureaucracy. On May 9th the White House announced that Donald Trump intended to nominate Mr Shanahan to his job on a permanent basis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This represents a big change in what Mr Trump requires from his defence secretary. He picked Mr Mattis, a highly-respected former marine general, at a time when he was new to foreign affairs, unsure of the demands of the presidency and bedazzled by a man in uniform. He referred approvingly to him by his service nickname, “Mad Dog Mattis,” though the moniker was rarely used and Mr Mattis hated it. Mr Trump’s enthusiasm for Mr Mattis dwindled once it became clear that he was neither the bull-headed killer Mr Trump had taken him for, nor prepared to be the president’s own loyal general.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While on board with some of Mr Trump’s instincts—for example, in his stepped-up bombing campaigns against the Taliban and Islamic State—Mr Mattis quietly repudiated the president’s values. He spent much of his time flying around the world trying to reassure the traditional allies Mr Trump lambasted. He stymied Mr Trump’s efforts to ban transsexuals from the armed forces. He survived in the administration for as long as he did through a combination of discretion, chaos elsewhere in the cabinet, and the defence department’s enormous heft. By replacing Mr Mattis with a much less commanding figure, Mr Trump has signalled his preference for loyalty over stature in the most independent power-base within the government.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shanahan showed his loyalty earlier this year by endorsing Mr Trump’s scheme to siphon billions of dollars from the defence budget to put towards a border-wall. He has also argued for the proposed new Space Force—in effect a sixth service branch—that Mr Trump has demanded. This is said to have won him over to Mr Trump, who had previously resisted pressure to make Mr Shanahan’s acting tenure permanent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The announcement of Mr Shanahan’s impending nomination follows the conclusion of a month-long Pentagon investigation into whether he improperly promoted Boeing and disparaged its competitors within the department. Though exonerated by the Pentagon’s acting inspector general, Mr Shanahan was described in his report as speaking peculiarly often—in almost every meeting—about his experience overseeing Boeing’s 787 Dreamliner programme. That points, if not to corruption, to his unusual callowness in government, which Republican national-security hawks such as Lindsey Graham are said to be troubled by. It will also make him a target for Democratic senators in his confirmation hearings. An investigation by the New York Times found that the production facility in North Carolina that makes the Dreamliner has been subject to many allegations of poor safety standards, as managers rushed to meet production targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Assuming Mr Shanahan is confirmed, his low profile and business background could both turn out to be beneficial for the defence department. It is locked in a perpetual struggle with the sorts of glitches, including inefficient basing, overstaffing and costly acquisitions programmes, he prides himself on solving at Boeing. More traditional defence secretaries—including Mr Mattis—routinely vow to get grips with such problems, before getting distracted by global security. That is less likely to happen to Mr Shanahan, who announced when taking over from Mr Mattis that he intended to travel much less than his predecessor had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flip-side of his leadership would probably be a diminution of the Pentagon’s role in shaping foreign and security policy. This is good news for Mike Pompeo and John Bolton, the belligerent secretary of state and national secretary adviser. They are already profiting from Mr Mattis’s absence. Having the ear of Mr Trump, who likes their style if not necessarily their bellicosity, they have taken the lead on security issues such as Iran—to which Mr Pompeo promised on May 9th a “swift and decisive” US response to any provocation. As well as being far better versed in foreign affairs, both are more adept inter-departmental players than Mr Shanahan, who has the least government experience of almost any defence secretary of recent times. While presiding over by far the biggest government department, he might struggle to check his cabinet colleagues. He will not check Mr Trump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 13:06:38 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The role of the state in creating economic value]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/05/09/the-role-of-the-state-in-creating-economic-value]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_OPP503_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-09T16:19:50Z&quot;&gt;May 9th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE ECONOMIC reforms of Ronald Reagan in America and Margret Thatcher in Britain in the 1980s unleashed the power of the private sector for economic growth. The deregulation and privatisations that followed not only perked up their own economies, but became a template for reform in many other countries around the world, from Mexico to Russia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet did the pro-private sector, anti-state ethos go too far? In her book “The Value of Everything: Making and Taking in the Global Economy,” Mariana Mazzucato, an economist at University College London, argues that policymakers and the public have lost sight of government’s ability to create economic value. She believes that our understanding of the origins of value are misguided and that governments should be able to “explore, experiment and take risks” on behalf of the public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That view is not shared by all, since government intervention brings the risk of politicising decisions that are better made by market forces. As part of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s Open Future project, we posed several questions to Ms Mazzucato about her ideas. It is followed by a short excerpt from the book, about how classical economists viewed the role of the state, from Smith to Marx—and what a “humble citizen” today might think.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*       *       *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;An interview with Mariana Mazzucato&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: What constitutes economic value, and what do we know about how and when governments add it?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mariana Mazzucato&lt;/strong&gt;: Value is “co-created” by different actors in the economy when they come together in productive ways to create new types of goods and services—each actor adding time and effort. While this process is well understood in business—that is what they teach in business schools—it is much less understood in the public sector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is because policy is seen at best as fixing market failures, while in reality, policy has been most effective when it has actively co-created and co-shaped markets, not only fixed them: whether this was when the state provided the “investment of first resort” in the IT revolution, or the current role that public investments are playing in the green revolution, such as through the role of organisations like ARPA-E in America, but also of public banks like the KfW in Germany.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In each of these cases, government had to have a vision for the future, and make the necessary investments that later crowded-in more risk-averse private firms. But the key question is “what is being created”? Is it war machines, or tools for an economy that is more sustainable and inclusive? Even fracking initially came from government investments. Once we admit the state can be transformational, the key question is how and what.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: Governments can be too interventionist and make spending decisions that are driven by politics: can that realistically be curtailed?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Mazzucato&lt;/strong&gt;: In order to co-create and co-shape markets the state must have the right organisational structure and capabilities. Yet there is a self-fulfilling prophecy that because there is a narrow framework to understand the role of government, there is also a poor understanding of what capabilities the state requires in order to be effective. This means there is under-investment. Indeed, the irony is that when the state does not understand its role in creating public value through public purpose, then it ends up being ineffective and crowding out, and being more easily captured.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: You have written about sectors that extract value from the economy; rentiers like financial services and parts of big tech. Aren’t governments capable of being just as extractive?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Mazzucato&lt;/strong&gt;: Yes, of course. Both public and private actors can be extractive. The problem is how to transform private and public organisations so that they are more purpose-driven—but also that their interactions are more symbiotic and less parasitic. Adam Smith said that free markets were about making markets free from rent—and that means looking at how to transform both public and private organisations so that they are adding not extracting. It also fundamentally changes how we understand public-private partnerships.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: If society attributes too much value to sectors you regard as unproductive, such as financial services, is that not merely an expression of our collective priorities?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Mazzucato&lt;/strong&gt;: There are strong narratives about value creation that have also enabled more extraction to happen. While there was plenty of value extraction by landlords in the 17th century, they did not pretend to be productive, creative or innovative. They just said: give me your money. Because there is a feedback between how we value things and how things work out in the real economy—what sociologists call “performativity”—we cannot pretend that the status quo is our collective interest. There is a lot of conning going on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I also argue that the mainstream theory of value being taught in economics departments worldwide is too subjective. It’s based on preferences such as “firms maximise profits”, “consumer utility” and “workers choosing between leisure and work”. So it becomes much harder to objectively differentiate profits from rents, which was a key distinction made by the classical economists like Smith, Ricardo and Marx.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: Around the world, public trust in politicians is dismally low. Would public support give governments a more direct role in economic growth?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Mazzucato&lt;/strong&gt;: The problem is not about giving governments more or less of a role. The problem is what kind of role. There is more corruption and capture when government sees its role as just subsidising, or providing different forms of guarantees and tax cuts—as opposed to investing ambitiously to create new opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have been a strong advocate for a mission-oriented approach to address the key challenges of our time—from climate change to healthy living. But key here is that the missions themselves should be co-created. No so much of a Kennedy-style moon-shot but more of different types of actors defining what a green transition might look like and then government using all it has at its disposal—from procurement to prize schemes—to crowd-in multiple solutions to “get there”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is the lesson from the moon-shot: a clear goal; many different sectors, actors and disciplines coming together to solve the problem; all fuelled by hundreds of projects. Some may fail, so governments need to be willing to explore, experiment and take risks. But risks for the public good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; *       *       *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Government value in the history of economic thought&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Excerpted from “The Value of Everything: Making and Taking in the Global Economy” by Mariana Mazzucato (Penguin, 2018):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Economics emerged as a discipline in large part to assert the productive primacy of the private sector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starting with the French physiocrats, economists found that government was required for the orderly functioning of society and thus for setting conditions for the production of value. But in itself, government was not inherently productive; rather, it was a stabilizing background force. The physiocrats pleaded with King Louis XV to &lt;em&gt;laissez-faire&lt;/em&gt;—not to micro-manage the economy by siphoning off as much gold as possible, and thereby upset the intricate mechanism by which value was really created—through productivity of the land, not by accumulating precious metal. According to Quesnay’s &lt;em&gt;Tableau Économique&lt;/em&gt;, value produced in agriculture flowed through the economy. But government was absent, ‘unproductive’. As part of the ruling class, members of the government got a share of the value apportioned simply because they were in power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, Quesnay knew, the &lt;em&gt;Tableau&lt;/em&gt; did not work by itself. There was something to be ‘governed’. Quesnay argued that the wealth of the nation could only be upheld through ‘“roper management by the general administration”—what we would call government regulation. He thought that free competition would best benefit the economy—but to achieve this, far from excluding government, he favoured an activist state that would break monopolies and establish the institutional conditions necessary for competition and free trade to flourish and value creation to thrive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adam Smith, meanwhile, devoted the fifth book of his &lt;em&gt;The Wealth of Nations&lt;/em&gt; to the role of government in the economy. His aim was not only to explain the prosperity of the nation, but also “to supply the state or commonwealth with a revenue sufficient for the public services.”. Like Quesnay, Smith believed the state was necessary. Indeed, he was convinced that national wealth could only be increased through division of labour in “a well-governed society”, in which he singled out three crucial functions of government: the military, the judiciary and other public services such as provision of infrastructure. These are public goods—producers cannot exclude anyone from consuming them. For Smith, such public goods had to be paid for by the state; some sort of taxation was therefore necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David Ricardo was perhaps the most anti-government of the classical economists. Although the title of his &lt;em&gt;The Principles of Political Economy and Taxation&lt;/em&gt; contains a key activity of government (taxation), he never considered how taxation could allow government spending to encourage production and hence value creation. For Ricardo, taxes are the ‘“portion of the produce of land and labour, placed at the disposal of government” to spend on areas such as education. If these expenditures are too high, he writes, the capital of the country is diminished, and “distress and ruin will follow”. Ricardo never asks, as Smith did, whether some taxes are necessary to help capitalists carry out production. He assumes infrastructure—the judiciary and so on—as a given. In effect, Ricardo narrows the production of economic value strictly to the private sphere. Admiring Ricardo’s rigorous analytical arguments, in comparison with Smith’s more fluid and interdisciplinary philosophical and political approach, economists followed him and excluded government from the productive sector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Marx’s view of government, meanwhile, derived from his materialist view of history, whereby the organization of society (including government structures) reflects the economic system (which he called the mode of production) and the underlying social relations: the interaction between classes. So, in his view, under the capitalist mode of production—based on surplus value generated from exploitation of labour—government and law reflected the needs of capitalists. Marx ridiculed some followers of Smith and Ricardo for haranguing state officials as “parasites on the actual producers”, then realizing that they were after all necessary to support the capitalist system. Nevertheless Marx, like Smith before him, while stressing the necessity of some functions of the state, placed state officials in the category of unproductive labourers outside the production boundary. The capitalist class had an interest in maintaining the state in a position strong enough to guarantee the rule of law and advance their class interests—but nothing more than that: “The executive of the modern state is nothing but a committee for managing the common affairs of the whole bourgeoisie.” The question concerning Marx was what constituted the ‘right’ size of government to provide the necessary services without taking away any additional profits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the neoclassical economists broke with the labour theory of value, they did not depart from their predecessors’ view that government was necessary but unproductive. Marginal utility, as we have seen, locates value in the price of any transaction that takes place freely in the market. According to this perspective, government produces nothing: it cannot create value. And government’s main source of income is taxes, which are a transfer of existing value created in the private sector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The immensely influential Alfred Marshall was quite nuanced in his discussion of economic life in his Principles, but still recommended that economics should avoid ‘as far as possible’ the discussion of matters associated with government. He believed that government interference in, or regulation of, the market would often happen in response to attempts by vested interests to rig the market in their favour (i.e. government would be ‘captured’ by such interests)—thus only hurting a particular competitor rather than benefiting society as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To the humble citizen, however, it might not be so obvious that government does not create value. We have already seen three ways in which it does so: bailing out the banks; investing in infrastructure, education and basic science; and funding radical, innovative technologies which are transforming our lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The crucial point is that many of these activities involve taking risks and &lt;em&gt;investing&lt;/em&gt;—exactly what austerity doesn’t do—and in so doing they create value. But that value is not easily visible, for the simple reason that much of it goes into the pockets of the private sector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;_______________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt; Excerpted from “The Value of Everything: Making and Taking in the Global Economy” by Mariana Mazzucato. Published by Penguin. Copyright © 2018 by Mariana Mazzucato. All rights reserved.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 01:06:35 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The ANC is re-elected but without much enthusiasm]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/09/the-anc-is-re-elected-but-without-much-enthusiasm]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_map503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-09T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 9th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I AM WHAT I am today because of the ANC,” says Princess Kgosimang, as she walks the short distance from her house in Soweto to the polling station. The 71-year-old lists the ways her life has improved since the end of apartheid. She has a home of her own, a state pension of 1,700 rand ($118) per month and her grandchildren go to multiracial schools. While she dislikes how corrupt the African National Congress (ANC) became under Jacob Zuma, president from 2009 to 2018, she believes that his successor, Cyril Ramaphosa, can clean house. “I want to give him a chance to make amends,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On May 8th enough voters like Ms Kgosimang turned out to re-elect the party that has governed South Africa since 1994, when Nelson Mandela was elected as the country’s first black president. At the time of writing the ANC is projected to win 57% of the national vote, according to analysis by Dawie Scholtz, a psephologist. Yet this is not an enthusiastic endorsement. The ANC’s success probably relied on older black voters with memories of the struggle, rather than on younger South Africans who are fed up with corruption, inequality and a lack of jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In each of the five previous general elections since the advent of democracy the ANC won more than 60% of the vote. This will be the first time the party’s result fell below that line in a national ballot. Turnout is also down; projections suggest just 65% of the registered electorate voted, compared with 73% in 2014. It is a long way from 1994, when turnout was near universal, with millions of non-white South Africans waking up before dawn to line up for their first opportunity to vote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Ramaphosa’s supporters will argue that 57% is a decent result. They will point to the 54% of the vote the ANC got in local elections in 2016, arguing that the party’s performance would have been much worse under a different leader. That is most likely true —and their case will be stronger if the ANC can hold on to its majority in Gauteng, the country’s most populous province. (That result was too close to call at the time of writing.) But it is also apparent that the president has not been able to reverse the downward trend in the ANC’s performance at national elections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not that the results were especially encouraging for the two main opposition parties: the Democratic Alliance (DA) and the Economic Freedom Fighters (EFF). Though it will retain majority control of the Western Cape province, which it has governed since 2009, the DA seems to have made little progress nationally since 2014, when it won 22% of the vote. It is projected to win a marginally lower share this time around, according to Mr Scholtz. Another model devised by the Council for Scientific and Industrial Research predicts it will get 24%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early indications suggest that although the DA increased its share of the black electorate, it lost votes among white Afrikaans-speaking South Africans. These probably went to the Freedom Front Plus party, which may win about 500,000 votes or around 3% of the total. That would represent its best ever showing and a tripling of support since 2014, a reflection of its voters’ concern about policies such as the expropriation of land without compensation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That policy has been championed by the EFF. The populist black-nationalist party is projected to win about 10% of the vote, up from 6% in 2014, and may yet hold the balance of power in Gauteng. Nevertheless its projected tally is a few percentage points below what some polls had suggested—a reflection perhaps of low turnout among young black South Africans, a group that has gravitated towards the EFF.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though the official final tallies will not be declared until the weekend, attention is already turning to what the results mean for reform under Mr Ramaphosa, whose inauguration is scheduled for May 25th. South Africa is in a perilous state. The official unemployment rate is 27%, debt to GDP has more than doubled over the past decade to 56%, and Eskom, the state-owned utility, struggles to keep the lights on. South Africans are increasingly frustrated that no one has yet been prosecuted for corruption during the era of “state capture” under Mr Zuma, when a corrupt family dictated government policies and the appointment of cabinet ministers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Ramaphosa has slowly begun to repair the country’s institutions. He has said some sensible things about the economy. But he has been constrained by his own party, many of whose members have been “deployed” into state-owned companies or the civil service and fear for their jobs, should the president prove serious about sacking the inept and prosecuting the corrupt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will be a lot of commentary about whether the ANC’s share of the national vote gives Mr Ramaphosa a mandate for reform. More important, though, is whether he is willing to use fully the considerable powers of the South African presidency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will be two early clues. The first is the size of his new cabinet. South Africa has more than 30 cabinet ministers, a high number in global terms. A slim-downed executive would be a symbol that the president is less inclined to hand out plum jobs to buy the loyalty of incompetent comrades. The second clue will be who he appoints as ministers. If the last of Mr Zuma’s loyalists, such as Nomvula Mokonyane and Bathabile Dlamini, are removed, while wise hands such as Tito Mboweni and Pravin Gordhan, are retained, then this will be a promising sign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twenty-five years after the end of apartheid, the political centre in South Africa has just about held. But the initial results suggest that it is fragile. Parties on the far left and right have picked up voters, while millions more disillusioned South Africans stayed at home. It is Mr Ramaphosa’s task to restore their faith in democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 01:06:34 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>