<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[What Narendra Modi should do next, China’s pigs at risk, and confronting a history of slavery in Brazil]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/23/what-narendra-modi-should-do-next-chinas-pigs-at-risk-and-confronting-a-history-of-slavery-in-brazil]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-23T18:00:12Z&quot;&gt;May 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A SELECTION of three essential articles read aloud from the latest issue of The Economist. This week, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/25/what-narendra-modi-should-do-next&quot;&gt;India&lt;/a&gt;’s ruling Bharatiya Janata party has won a second landslide victory&lt;/strong&gt;. The prime minister, &lt;strong&gt;Narendra Modi&lt;/strong&gt;, should make better use of his latest triumph. Can &lt;strong&gt;China&lt;/strong&gt;, home to half the world’s pigs, curb the epidemic of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/china/2019/05/25/african-swine-fever-hits-china-home-of-half-the-worlds-pigs&quot;&gt;African swine flu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (06:28)? And&lt;strong&gt; Brazil &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;b&gt;faces painful disagreement over how to commemorate its history of &lt;/b&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/05/25/for-some-in-brazil-commemorating-slavery-is-vital&quot;&gt;slavery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (12:24). Runtime: 23 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-may23rd2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 02:41:28 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The race to become Britain’s next PM]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/23/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_woc777.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-23T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- data-infographic-js=&quot;/2019/tory-leadership/js/bundle.js&quot; data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/tory-leadership/css/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/tory-leadership/css/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE UNOFFICIAL &lt;/small&gt; race to succeed Theresa May as leader of the Conservative Party, and thus prime minister, has been going on ever since her disastrous election performance two years ago. On May 16th it moved up a gear when senior Tory backbenchers met Mrs May and extracted a promise that if, as expected, she fails in her fourth attempt to pass her Brexit bill in the House of Commons early next month, she will outline a timetable for her departure. The upshot is that 10 Downing Street is likely to have a new occupant this summer.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The man most fancied to succeed her, Boris Johnson, a former foreign secretary and prominent Brexiteer, had earlier that day thrown his hat in the ring. “Of course I’m going for it,” he told an audience of insurance brokers in Manchester. Expect more candidates to break cover over the course of the next few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Betfair Exchange, a gambling website, has been tracking punters’ predictions on the next Tory leader. According to the wisdom of the crowd, a handful of candidates stand out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p &gt;Source: Betfair Exchange&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Adrian Wooldridge, our political editor, assesses the chances of the leading Conservative politicians hoping to take the top job in this short film
&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ychDrZ2QzlE&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 23:40:11 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China is surprisingly carbon-efficient—but still the world’s biggest emitter]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/25/china-is-surprisingly-carbon-efficient-but-still-the-worlds-biggest-emitter]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_gdc901.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190525_GDC901_emissions/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;W&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;ITH ITS&lt;/small&gt; four-tiered smog warnings and lethal dumps of toxic waste, China has become Exhibit A for the environmental costs of economic development. Its growing meat consumption and reliance on fossil fuels have also made it a focus for people worried about climate change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In one sense, China’s reputation as the bellows of “hothouse Earth” is overblown. Since 1850 countries with a &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; per head of $12,000-16,000 in 2019 dollars have produced a population-weighted average of 10.6 tonnes of carbon dioxide-equivalent gases per person per year. In 2016 China’s &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; per head was $14,000, and it emitted just 9.3 tonnes per person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, China pollutes far less per person than Western countries did at the same stage of development. When America, France, Britain and Germany had incomes similar to modern China’s, they relied on inefficient power stations and cars, and spewed out 16.6 tonnes per person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The combination of China’s huge population and rapid &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; growth has nonetheless made it the world’s biggest emitter of carbon. China is predicted to produce 16bn tonnes of greenhouse gases in 2030—four times the entire world’s output in 1900.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To prevent the stock of greenhouse gases in the atmosphere from reaching levels likely to cause disastrous warming, China must do better than merely beating the past records of richer countries. Instead, it will need an unprecedented decline in emissions per head—at least to the more carbon-efficient level of similarly rich Latin American economies, and ideally onto the trajectory of poorer Asian giants like India and Indonesia, which rely less on heavy industry and manufacturing. Those countries, perched at the sweltering latitudes where farmers will be most hurt by climate change, must in turn work out how to reach upper-middle-income status without replicating China’s emissions path.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To their credit, Chinese authorities, spurred by public concern about air pollution, have prioritised green policies, such as switching from coal-fired power stations to renewable sources and setting up an emissions-trading system. China’s annual rate of emissions growth has fallen from 9.3% in 2002-11 to 0.6% in 2012-16. The waning of its cement-intensive construction boom should slow emissions further. But it will take more than incremental gains to stave off severe warming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/source.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/source.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p &gt;Sources: Climate Action Tracker; Climate Watch; University of Groningen Growth and Development Centre; UN Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/20190525_GDC901_emissions/fix.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190525_GDC901_emissions/fix.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Graphic detail&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Not-so-cold comfort&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 21:40:25 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Once Upon a Time...in Hollywood” is entertaining but empty]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/23/once-upon-a-timein-hollywood-is-entertaining-but-empty]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_BKP512.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-23T12:07:18Z&quot;&gt;May 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EVERY ONE of Quentin Tarantino’s films has been a love letter to pop culture in general and to cinema in particular, but none of those odes has been as explicit or as gushing as “Once Upon a Time...in Hollywood”. A two-and-three-quarter-hour tribute to Tinseltown, the film is a loosely bound anthology of vignettes extolling the charms of the dream factory as it was in 1969: the cars, the clothes, the on-set camaraderie. It’s a sleepy and ultimately happy comedy—too happy, perhaps, given that it stirs fact and fiction together, and features the Charles Manson cult and the murder of Sharon Tate. Mr Tarantino is so deeply in love with the movie business that he can’t peer at its dark side for long before returning to its sunlit swimming pools and studio backlots. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The film begins with a fun black-and-white clip of an actor and his stunt double being interviewed in the 1950s. The actor is Rick Dalton (Leonardo DiCaprio), the earnest, buffoonish star of a hit TV series about a sharp-shooting bounty hunter in the Wild West. The stunt double is Cliff Booth (Brad Pitt), Rick’s easy-going best friend. When the audience sees the duo again, a decade has passed—and what a difference a decade makes. Rick has been reduced to humiliating cameo appearances on variety shows. Cliff, meanwhile, hasn’t had any stunt work for a while, but he sticks by Rick as his driver, handyman and drinking buddy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their bromance is the heart of “Once Upon a Time...in Hollywood”, although it might have been more affecting if it was clearer what Cliff got out of it. After he has chauffeured Rick back to his house in the hills every evening, he gets out of the actor’s Cadillac, gets into his own battered car and drives back to his trailer to feed his dog and eat food out of a packet. He shows no sign whatsoever of resentment, and no desire for companionship that isn’t provided by a dog or an employer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is typical of the film’s mellow mood. Early on, an agent (Al Pacino) tries to persuade Rick to make spaghetti westerns in Italy, but he has to be the kindest and most honest agent who has ever been portrayed on screen. Roman Polanski (Rafal Zawierucha) moves in next door to Rick with his starlet wife, the aforementioned Tate (Margot Robbie). There is a whisper that Tate’s ex, Jay Sebring (Emile Hirsch), is planning to steal her away, but Mr Tarantino doesn’t elaborate: the director prefers simply to gaze at Tate as she strolls around in her white mini-skirt and boots. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The film’s most interesting and unsettling conceit is that the ranch where Rick and Cliff once shot their TV show is now occupied by Charles Manson and his brainwashed acolytes, and Cliff suspects the ranch’s owner (Bruce Dern) has been kidnapped—or worse—by the interlopers. But, again, Mr Tarantino prefers to see the funny side of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He has no truck with the pitch-black cynicism of “Mulholland Drive”, “The Player” and all of the other great films about the scandals, exploitation and sheer craziness of La La Land. Indulging in dewy-eyed nostalgia with all of his usual obsessive attention to detail, Mr Tarantino lets the good times roll instead. And when the inevitable orgy of gory violence finally begins, even that is nowhere near as horrifying as you might fear. Mr Tarantino’s film is entertaining, of course, in its rambling, jokey way, but it doesn’t have much to say except that things often work out better in the movies than they do in real life. An escapist homage to the escapism industry, “Once Upon a Time...in Hollywood” is as much of a fairytale as its title implies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Once Upon a Time...in Hollywood” will be released in America on July 26th and in Britain on August 14th&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 21:40:24 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“A re-election of a kind that no one has won in India before”—Narendra Modi&#x27;s landslide]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/23/a-re-election-of-a-kind-that-no-one-has-won-in-india-before-narendra-modis-landslide]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/bjp1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-23T11:30:51Z&quot;&gt;May 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NARENDRA MODI&amp;#x27;S &lt;/strong&gt;BJP party appears to have secured a convincing re-election victory. What will that mean for India and the region? Also, we look back on &lt;strong&gt;the life of Bob Hawke, a former Australian prime minister&lt;/strong&gt; who convinced the world that his country deserved a prominent place in global politics. And, why &lt;strong&gt;Silicon Valley’s latest obsession is optimising &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/18/sleepless-in-silicon-valley&quot;&gt;sleepy time&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Runtime: 21min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/repeatperformance-india-selection&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 21:40:23 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A bleak view of the future]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/bartleby/2019/05/23/a-bleak-view-of-the-future]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_FNP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-23T09:57:40Z&quot;&gt;May 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ARE millennials really different from preceding generations? Bartleby tends to be cynical about such claims, recalling how the youthful idealism of his own peers was tamed by parenthood and the need to pay the mortgage. But a new survey from Deloitte, the accountancy firm, suggests that millennials, defined as those born between January 1983 and December 1984, are feeling particularly gloomy. The survey interviewed 13,416 people across 42 countries (with between 200 and 500 people in each nation, ranging from Argentina to Turkey).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The survey found that climate change was their biggest worry, with 29% concerned about the issue, followed by income equality at 21% (respondents were asked to pick three issues from a list of 20). That said, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://ceepr.mit.edu/files/papers/2019-006.pdf&quot;&gt;separate research&lt;/a&gt; by MIT found that American millennials travel more miles in cars than baby boomers and are just as keen on car ownership; concern about climate change does not automatically translate into lifestyle changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Millennials seem to have turned very pessimistic about the global economy, with only 26% expecting the situation to improve in the next 12 months; that compares with 45% last year. Just over half expect their personal finances to deteriorate. Only 22% expect the social and political climate in their countries to improve, down from 33% in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to business, the proportion of millennials who feel that the sector has a positive impact on society has dropped to 55%, from 61% in 2018. Almost two-thirds of those polled think that business have no ambition beyond wanting to make money. In contrast, millennials think businesses should place a higher priority on generating jobs and producing high-quality goods and services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many millennials are unhappy with their jobs. The survey says 49% plan to quit within the next two years, up from 38% in 2017. (Of course, younger workers are naturally more footloose than their elders.) Dissatisfaction with pay is the biggest factor, followed by a lack of opportunities to advance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What about the gig economy, which many assume will provide a lot of work for this generation (although it &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2018/10/04/worries-about-the-rise-of-the-gig-economy-are-mostly-overblown&quot;&gt;currently provides just 1% of paid employment &lt;/a&gt;in America)? Here their views are mixed. While 48% think that &amp;quot;gig workers have a better work/life balance than those in full-time jobs&amp;quot;, 49% think &amp;quot;the employment rights of gig worker are not respected or protected&amp;quot; and 60% think they are only used to reduce costs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, there is mixed evidence that &amp;quot;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/01/24/companies-can-appeal-to-workers-and-consumers-with-liberal-messages&quot;&gt;woke capitalism&lt;/a&gt;&amp;quot; may work, if only in the negative. More than a quarter of millennials said they had backed away from an organisation because of its political position, or that of its leader; only around a sixth said they had been positively attracted by a company&amp;#x27;s position. Sending an illiberal message may drive workers and consumers away. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 21:40:22 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Across the rich world, an extraordinary jobs boom is under way]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/briefing/2019/05/23/across-the-rich-world-an-extraordinary-jobs-boom-is-under-way]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_fbd001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-23T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE SECOND &lt;/small&gt;volume of “My Struggle”, Karl Ove Knausgaard’s enormous, maddening, brilliant autobiographical novels, contains some depressing life advice. “If I have learned one thing,” he sighs, “it is the following: don’t believe you are anybody. Don’t bloody believe you are somebody…Do not believe that you’re anything special. Do not believe that you’re worth anything, because you aren’t.” We like to tell ourselves that we deserve our successes, Mr Knausgaard’s book suggests, yet they are largely the product of forces over which we have no control. When he wrote those words he probably was not thinking about the boasts of politicians in the &lt;small&gt;OECD&lt;/small&gt;, a club mainly of rich countries, about their jobs markets. But he might as well have been.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Unemployment numbers best in 51 years. Wow!” tweeted Donald Trump, America’s president, last month. Theresa May, the British prime minister, bragged in February that “employment is at a near-record high and unemployment at a near-record low.” The month before, Scott Morrison, Australia’s prime minister, crowed that “more than 730 jobs were created every day last year under our government.” Around the same time his Japanese counterpart, Shinzo Abe, let it be known that “the employment rate for young people is at a level surpassing all previous records.” Hence the swagger of politicians, who believe that they are special. But they are not. Jobs abound because of forces that largely have nothing to do with them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC091.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC091.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC091.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC091.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC091.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC091.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC091.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC091.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC091.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC091.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;And abound they do. Across the &lt;small&gt;OECD&lt;/small&gt; a jobs bonanza is under way. In the past five years the group has added 43m jobs. The unemployment rate—the number of people looking for work as a share of the total labour force—is at its lowest in decades (see chart 1). Not every member can celebrate. Unemployment in Italy, Spain and Greece remains higher than before the financial crisis of 2008-09. America’s rate of labour-force participation is still well off its all-time high. But most can. In 2018, the employment rate among people of working age was the highest ever in Britain, Canada, Germany, Australia and 22 other &lt;small&gt;OECD &lt;/small&gt;countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC086.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC086.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC086.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC086.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC086.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC086.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC086.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC086.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC086.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC086.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The boom is broad based. Unemployment among unskilled workers and the young is tumbling, as is long-term joblessness. The share of people working part-time because they cannot find jobs with longer hours remains higher than it was just before the financial crisis of 2008-09 but has fallen sharply since 2013 (see chart 2). America’s Bureau of Labour Statistics produces perhaps the widest official measure of unemployment, which includes involuntary part-timers as well as those who have dropped out of the labour force but nonetheless want to work. It is currently well below its long-run average.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;A good job, too?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one can argue about the scale of the jobs boom. But it has become a shibboleth at either end of the political spectrum that the quality of jobs on offer has nosedived. Driving Uber taxis or delivering meals are not really jobs at all, the argument goes. It is true that what Mr Trump regards as “jobs”—traditional, male-dominated occupations, such as those in manufacturing—have withered. Between 1995 and 2015 such middle-skilled jobs fell as a share of &lt;small&gt;OECD &lt;/small&gt;employment by ten percentage points. Next month sees the publication of a book by David Blanchflower of Dartmouth College, and previously a member of the Bank of England’s monetary-policy committee, called “Not Working: Where Have All the Good Jobs Gone?”. Perhaps the growing difficulty of finding stable, well-paid employment in academia and journalism explains why the popular discourse about modern labour markets is so gloomy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The despondency might be justified were not popular perceptions about the world of work so obviously wrong. Consider the notion that work is ever more precarious. In fact, official estimates of America’s gig economy, whereby short-term freelance work is accessed through online market places, put it only at about 1% of total employment. Temporary employment may be a little higher than it was in the 1990s, yet the rate has been falling for a decade. In France the share of new hires given long-term permanent contracts recently reached an all-time high of 50%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The belief that people increasingly flit from job to job is also not borne out by fact. Over the past two decades the share of &lt;small&gt;OECD &lt;/small&gt;workers who have been in their job for less than a year has hovered around 20%, with no clear trend up or down. The demise of jobs for the middlingly skilled has not proved a disaster either. Although it has meant that low-skilled jobs have risen as a share of &lt;small&gt;OECD &lt;/small&gt;employment they have done so to a far lesser extent than high-skilled ones, which have boomed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until recently a missing piece of the puzzle was wage growth. Economics textbooks say that times of low unemployment go hand in hand with juicy pay rises as employers compete harder for staff. Yet for much of the post-crisis period the “Phillips curve” appeared broken, with falling unemployment in 2014-16 failing to translate into higher wages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The relationship has started to rekindle. As unemployment has continued to fall wages are at last accelerating. A broader measure of whether work pays, where the total of all compensation is expressed as a share of national income, is rising in many rich countries, including America and Britain. Pay is still increasing more slowly than might have been expected given the tightness of the labour market. For that, blame weak productivity growth. And it is wrong to conclude that workers are ever more exploited. The incidence of “low pay”—workers who earn less than two-thirds of the median—has been falling for two decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Red-hot labour markets do not solve every problem. Malaga’s restaurants are buzzing and its streets are clean. You would hardly know that the Spanish city’s average unemployment rate over the past five years has been close to 30%. The one sign that there may be lots of people with not much to do is the number of gaming arcades. The rough sleepers and empty lots of San Francisco scream of a city with an unemployment problem; in fact the rate is 2.6%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Others make deeper criticisms of the rosy jobs numbers. Shouldn’t societies aspire to work less, rather than more? People who do not need to engage in wage-labour can indulge in other, more fulfilling activities. David Graeber, an anthropologist, goes further. In “Bullshit Jobs”, a book published last year which has become akin to a holy tract for millennial socialists, he claims that a big chunk of modern employment is pointless and soul-sucking. “Huge swathes of people, in Europe and North America in particular, spend their entire working lives performing tasks they secretly believe do not really need to be performed,” he argues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is hard to dismiss the feeling that drudgery is the price Japan has paid for an average unemployment rate over the past half-century of just 3%, the lowest in the &lt;small&gt;OECD&lt;/small&gt;. At the baggage-collection area of Haneda airport, a woman spends her day straightening suitcases after they are placed on the conveyor belt. At an empty bar in Tokyo’s fashion district a world-beating gin martini (the addition of a single drop of orange bitters is a revelation) is mixed by three people, who then stand around as it is drunk. Mr Graeber would surely argue that this is less a sign of social progress and more that capitalism has conspired to turn people into drones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But societies benefit from strong labour markets. More workers means more people paying income tax and fewer receiving benefits. Studies suggest that the unemployment rate is positively correlated with rates of property crime and even with violent crime. Having a job gives people a sense of purpose which is also good for all sorts of social outcomes, including mental and physical health. And being in work makes another, better job easier to get. Capitalism has not been able to tell many good-news stories of late. This is one of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reason for the strength of the &lt;small&gt;OECD&lt;/small&gt;’s labour market is a puzzle, however. In recent years many governments have loaded employers with extra costs, even as it is becoming ever easier to replace people with robots. A study in 2013 by Carl Benedikt Frey and Michael Osborne of Oxford University concluded that 47% of jobs in America were at risk of being automated. Rules have proliferated on equal pay, anti-discrimination, health and safety, and maternity and paternity leave. Across 24 &lt;small&gt;OECD &lt;/small&gt;countries for which there are long-run data, the value of the minimum wage has risen from 44% of full-time median earnings in 2000 to 50% today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;Hives of industry&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why are labour markets so buoyant? This is in part a cyclical phenomenon. Economic growth tends to push unemployment down. The recovery from the financial crisis is a decade old. In part because of appropriately lax monetary policy, America is about to achieve its longest-ever period of economic expansion. Meanwhile, lingering uncertainty related to the financial crisis and the rise of populism may mean that firms are keener on hiring staff than on devoting large amounts of capital to investment, which is harder to undo. The post-crisis period has also been characterised by rapid growth in the service sector, which is more labour-intensive than industry. For all these reasons it is no surprise that unemployment is relatively low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But not this low. In October 2013 the &lt;small&gt;IMF &lt;/small&gt;made economic forecasts for advanced economies for the following five years. On the assumption that annual &lt;small&gt;GDP &lt;/small&gt;growth would average 2.4%, they concluded that by 2018 the rate of unemployment would be 6.9%. It turned out that the &lt;small&gt;IMF &lt;/small&gt;was too optimistic on growth and too pessimistic on unemployment, which by 2018 had fallen to around 5%. That suggests it is not only a cyclical phenomenon. Long-term structural changes to demography, technology and policy play an equally significant role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take demography. The &lt;small&gt;OECD&lt;/small&gt; is ageing. Young people on average are more likely to be registered as unemployed than their elders, in part because they are less skilled but also because older folk who lose a job may retire and thus drop out of the labour force. Several studies draw a link between more young people and higher unemployment. In the 1980s, a time of relatively high joblessness, 25% of the rich world’s working-age population was aged 15 to 24. That has since fallen to around 17.5%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demographic change, in other words, means that today’s unemployment rate is not directly comparable with those of the past. By one estimate, had America’s demographic structure in 2000 remained the same today, the current rate of unemployment would be around 0.5 percentage points higher. Oxford Economics, a consultancy, finds results for the euro zone that are similar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet tumbling unemployment is about much more than statistical trickery. The second big factor, technological change, is genuinely strengthening labour markets. Better tech improves the “matching” of employers with potential employees. Not long ago those hiring put an advert in a local newspaper or spread the word by mouth. Now employers can shoot from the hip, posting vacancies on a slew of jobs websites. In the ten years to 2016 the cost of filling a vacancy fell by 80% in real terms. And candidates are more likely to spot a job that suits them. A study in 2011 by Peter Kuhn and Hani Mansour found that using the internet to look for a job reduced the time spent unemployed by about a quarter. &lt;small&gt;OECD&lt;/small&gt; countries with high worklessness are often those where online job searching is less common. Only 40% of unemployed Italians do it, compared with over 95% of South Koreans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gig economy, even if it is relatively small-scale, also raises employment by creating work that would not otherwise exist. In the past fixing a tap would have been a &lt;small&gt;DIY&lt;/small&gt; job; now with the tap of a screen it is possible to pay someone else to do it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;Work in progress&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A series of small, incremental changes to policy over many decades is the third factor behind a jobs boom for which the current crop of politicians are so keen to take credit. Governments have offered carrots and sticks. Carrots include making it easier for women to combine work and family. In many countries rights for part-time workers have been strengthened and parental leave made more generous, with the state often bearing the cost. Mr Abe’s economic-reform package includes providing more day-care centres for children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC067.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC067.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC067.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC067.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC067.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC067.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC067.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC067.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC067.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBC067.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such policies can have a large impact on labour-force participation, particularly for women, suggests research by Francine Blau and Lawrence Kahn, published in 2013. Female employment rates have been edging up across the &lt;small&gt;OECD &lt;/small&gt;for decades. While in America female employment has since fallen, across the &lt;small&gt;OECD &lt;/small&gt;as a whole the pace of growth has quickened (see chart 3).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another carrot is education. The share of &lt;small&gt;OECD &lt;/small&gt;workers with some form of higher education has risen from 22% in 2000 to nearly 40% today. These workers are more likely to be in employment than poorly qualified folk. Higher education usually instils a superior work ethic and such workers have more transferable skills.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Governments have wielded the stick, too. Many have reduced the power of trade unions and collective-bargaining agreements. That may have made wages more responsive to market conditions. A larger share of workers appears to be experiencing nominal wage reductions than was the case a few decades ago. Receiving a pay cut is unpleasant and embarrassing. But if bosses can trim pay during bad times, they are less likely to fire workers. Wages in Japan move down almost as easily as they do up. An unusually large share of workers’ take-home pay is made up of bonuses, which can be withheld fairly easily during times of economic trouble. In Japan’s hospitality sector in 2009, workers’ end-of-year bonuses were cut by over 40%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In countries that have failed to update old-fashioned labour practices, the cost of doing so has been high. In Italy nearly 350 national industrial agreements cover the vast majority of firms and formal employees. They take little account of regional differences in the cost of living and productivity. That prices many workers in the poor south out of the labour market. Spain’s collective-bargaining agreements are often rigid in the face of changing conditions. In 2008-09, when a building bust pushed the economy into recession, nominal wages in construction rose by 5%. Bosses had little choice but to shed staff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Governments have also made it difficult to live off handouts. In 2001 a single childless person earning the average wage, who then became unemployed for a year, would have received benefits worth 48% of previous earnings. By 2018 that had fallen to 41%. Would-be recipients of benefits face ever-tougher eligibility tests. Over the past two decades the number of Britons receiving jobless benefits, as a share of those out of work, has fallen from 80% to 50%. That may, in turn, have made wages more flexible. Workers will take wage cuts if necessary in order to avoid unemployment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190525_FBD002_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBD002_0.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBD002_0.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBD002_0.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBD002_0.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBD002_0.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBD002_0.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBD002_0.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBD002_0.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FBD002_0.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reforms such as these are harsh and their implementation has often been botched. Yet they can have a big effect on jobs. In one paper Marcus Hagedorn, Iourii Manovskii and Kurt Mitman look at what happened in America in 2013, where the time for which some people could claim unemployment benefit fell from 73 weeks to 25. They estimate that the benefit cut led to the creation of some 2m jobs in 2014 about two-thirds of total employment growth that year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;No end to the grind&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The strength of the labour market calls into question gloomy predictions about the future of work—that increasingly sophisticated computers will consign growing numbers of workers to a life of enforced idleness. Messrs Frey and Osborne could still be proved correct at some point in the future. Accelerating wage growth will certainly persuade more companies to automate jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the lesson of the past half-millennium is that technological change complements jobs rather than destroys them. Sky-high employment rates today suggest that nothing has changed. And there is plenty of evidence pointing in the direction of more improvements. The current period of economic expansion seems to have further to go. If there is a lesson from the 1960s, when unemployment in some &lt;small&gt;OECD&lt;/small&gt; countries fell as low as 1%, it is that there remains more scope to reduce underemployment and inactivity. Mr Knausgaard finds room for some practical advice amid the detailed accounts of his struggles: “So keep your head down and work.” If everyone follows it, the rich world’s jobs market could have more surprises in store.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Briefing&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Working it&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 21:40:21 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Should Germany borrow to invest?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/23/should-germany-borrow-to-invest]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_fnp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-23T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;O&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;UTSIDE THE&lt;/small&gt; headquarters of the German Taxpayers’ Federation in Berlin, a display tracks the public debt in real time. Now displaying a total of just under €2trn ($2.2trn), it has been ticking down since early 2018. Germany’s public-debt ratio, expected to be 58% of &lt;small&gt;GDP &lt;/small&gt;in 2019, is as much the envy of other rich countries as its engineering prowess. Thanks to rising labour-market participation, says Michael Hüther of the German Economic Institute, a think-tank, tax revenues per head reached their highest level ever, in real terms, in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even so, Germany’s fiscal policy is becoming a subject of debate. Olaf Scholz, the finance minister, has warned that the “fat years” are over. Economic growth is projected to slow this year, reducing the tax take. If he is to meet Germany’s stringent fiscal rule, he must rein in public spending.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em &gt;S&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em &gt;chuldenbremse&lt;/em&gt; (debt brake) was enshrined in the constitution in 2009, when the financial crisis was expected to swell public debt beyond 80% of &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt;. It restricts the federal-government deficit to no more than 0.35% of &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; a year unless a downturn hits; any overshoot beyond that must be made up in better times. (The debt brake also affects states’ finances: from 2020, they will be forbidden to run structural deficits.) Some economists, though, are asking whether the rule is a good one. Pointing to Germany’s rock-bottom interest rates and crumbling infrastructure, they argue that the country needs more debt-financed investment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190525_FNC104.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FNC104.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FNC104.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FNC104.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FNC104.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FNC104.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FNC104.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FNC104.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FNC104.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190525_FNC104.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Germany’s government debt is in such high demand that, at some maturities, investors are willing to pay to lend it money. Yields on ten-year bonds turned negative in May, as investors spooked by the trade war between America and China, and by Italian politicians’ hints that they would break the euro zone’s fiscal rules, sought safety. On May 9th the yield on Germany’s ten-year government bonds slipped below that of Japan’s (see chart).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At such attractive rates the case for borrowing for projects that could boost growth seems obvious. Public investment, at 2.3% of &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt;, lags behind the euro-zone average and barely covers depreciation. Mr Hüther was once a proponent of the debt brake. But in a recent column in the &lt;em &gt;Sü&lt;/em&gt;&lt;em &gt;ddeutsche Zeitung&lt;/em&gt;, written with Jens Südekum of the Heinrich-Heine University Dusseldorf, he argues for a return to a “golden rule”, which allows for investment to be financed by debt. The debt brake was supposed to spare future generations from being saddled with today’s borrowing. But by limiting investment, they argue, it penalises future generations instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, the government may have been overzealous in its application of the rule. Catarina Midoes and Guntram Wolff of Bruegel, a think-tank, find that since 2010 officials, when drawing up budget plans, have consistently come up with predictions for tax revenues that turn out to undershoot reality. That has had the effect of restraining public spending.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In part, the forecasting errors reflect the fact that the economy has beaten expectations over the past decade, resulting in unexpectedly high tax revenues. But the researchers speculate that the debt brake may also have led to a “surplus bias”, with forecasters being deliberately cautious for fear of breaking the rule. (The finance ministry, however, says that the analysis does not consider the possible influence of tax-policy changes or one-off effects.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not everyone agrees that the debt brake has led to a squeeze on capital spending. Officials in the finance ministry point out that government investment has grown at 7% annually in recent years, outpacing nominal &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; growth. Bottlenecks prevent plans from turning into reality, meaning that investment cannot rise much more. Clemens Fuest of the Ifo Institute for Economic Research points out that €8bn allocated to public projects by the federal government in recent years has not yet been spent. Public planners are in short supply and the building industry is close to capacity. &lt;small&gt;NIMBY&lt;/small&gt;ism has held up the redevelopment of a railway network in Stuttgart and a third runway for Munich’s airport.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Political appetite to release the debt brake seems limited. Though the finance ministry’s new chief economist, Jakob von Weizsäcker, is receptive to fresh ideas, Mr Scholz is still keen to balance the books. Even so, there is nothing stopping the government from dismantling other barriers to investment. More of it would, after all, boost the future tax take—thus making it less likely that the government would need to slam its foot on the debt brake further down the line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Finance and economics&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Black books&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 21:40:20 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The rich world is enjoying an unprecedented jobs boom]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/23/the-rich-world-is-enjoying-an-unprecedented-jobs-boom]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190525_LDD003_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-23T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;E&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;VERYONE SAYS &lt;/small&gt;work is miserable. Today’s workers, if they are lucky enough to escape the gig economy and have a real job, have lost control over their lives. They are underpaid and exploited by unscrupulous bosses. And they face a precarious future, as machines threaten to make them unemployable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is just one problem with this bleak picture: it is at odds with reality. As we report this week (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/briefing/2019/05/23/across-the-rich-world-an-extraordinary-jobs-boom-is-under-way&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Briefing&lt;/a&gt;), most of the rich world is enjoying a jobs boom of unprecedented scope. Not only is work plentiful, but it is also, on average, getting better. Capitalism is improving workers’ lot faster than it has in years, as tight labour markets enhance their bargaining power. The zeitgeist has lost touch with the data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In America the unemployment rate is only 3.6%, the lowest in half a century. Less appreciated is the abundance of jobs across most of the rich world. Two-thirds of the members of the &lt;small&gt;OECD&lt;/small&gt;, a club of mostly rich countries, enjoy record-high employment among 15- to 64-year-olds. In Japan 77% of this group has a job, up six percentage points in six years. This year Britons will work a record 350bn hours a month. Germany is enjoying a bonanza of tax revenue following a surge in the size of its labour force (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/23/should-germany-borrow-to-invest&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;). Even in France, Spain and Italy, where joblessness is still relatively high, working-age employment is close to or exceeds 2005 levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rich-world jobs boom is partly cyclical—the result of a decade of economic stimulus and recovery since the great recession. But it also reflects structural shifts. Populations are becoming more educated. Websites are efficient at matching vacancies and qualified applicants. And ever more women work. In fact women account for almost all the growth in the rich-world employment rate since 2007. That has something to do with pro-family policies in Europe, but since 2015 the trend is found in America, too. Last, reforms to welfare programmes, both to make them less generous and to toughen eligibility tests, seem to have encouraged people to seek work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to the jobs boom, unemployment, once the central issue of political economy, has all but disappeared from the political landscape in many countries. It has been replaced by a series of complaints about the quality and direction of work. These are less tangible and harder to judge than employment statistics. The most important are that automation is destroying opportunities and that work, though plentiful, is low-quality and precarious. “Our jobs market is being turned into a sea of insecurity,” says Jeremy Corbyn, leader of Britain’s Labour Party.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Again, reality begs to differ. In manufacturing, machines have replaced workers over a period of decades. This seems to have contributed to a pocket of persistent joblessness among American men. But across the &lt;small&gt;OECD&lt;/small&gt; as a whole, a jobs apocalypse carried out by machines and algorithms, much feared in Silicon Valley, is nowhere to be seen. A greater share of people with only a secondary education or less is in work now than in 2000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is also true that middle-skilled jobs are becoming harder to find as the structure of the economy changes, and as the service sector—including the gig economy—expands. By 2026 America will have more at-home carers than secretaries, according to official projections. Yet as labour markets hollow out, more high-skilled jobs are being created than menial ones. Meanwhile, low-end work is becoming better paid, in part because of higher minimum wages. Across the rich world, wages below two-thirds of the national median are becoming rarer, not more common.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for precariousness, in America traditional full-time jobs made up the same proportion of employment in 2017 as they did in 2005. The gig economy accounts for only around 1% of jobs there. In France, despite recent reforms to make labour markets more flexible, the share of new hires given permanent contracts recently hit an all-time high. The truly precarious work is found in southern European countries like Italy, and neither exploitative employers nor modern technology is to blame. The culprit is old-fashioned law that stitches up labour markets, locking out young workers in order to keep insiders in cushy jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere, the knock-on benefits of abundant work are becoming clear. As firms compete for workers rather than workers for jobs, average wage growth is rising, pushing up workers’ share of the pie—albeit not as fast as the extent of the boom might have suggested. Tight labour markets lead firms to fish for employees in neglected pools, including among ex-convicts, and to boost training amid skills shortages. American wonks fretted for years about how to shrink disability-benefit rolls. Now the hot labour market is doing it for them. Indeed, one attraction of the jobs boom is its potential to help solve social ills without governments having to do or spend very much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nonetheless, policymakers do have lessons to learn. Economists have again been humbled. They have consistently underestimated potential employment, leading to hesitant fiscal and monetary policy. Just as their sanguine outlook on finance in the 2000s contributed to the bust, so their mistaken pessimism about the potential for jobs growth in the 2010s has needlessly slowed the recovery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The left needs to accept that many of the criticisms it levels at capitalism do not fit the facts. Life at the bottom of the labour market is not joyous—far from it. However, the lot of workers is improving and entry-level jobs are a much better launch pad to something better than joblessness is. A failure to acknowledge this will lead to government intervention that is at best unnecessary and at worst jeopardises recent progress. The jobs boom seems to be partly down to welfare reforms that the likes of Mr Corbyn have vociferously opposed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The right should acknowledge that jobs have boomed without the bonfire of regulations that typically forms its labour-market policy. In fact, labour-market rules are proliferating. And although the jury is out on whether rising minimum wages are harming some groups, such as the young, they are not doing damage that is large enough to show up in aggregate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The jobs boom will not last for ever. Eventually, a recession will kill it off. Meanwhile, it deserves a little appreciation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Leaders&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;The great jobs boom&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 21:40:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Theresa May’s failed premiership is over]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/23/theresa-mays-failed-premiership-is-over]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190525_LDP002_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-23T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HERESA MAY&lt;/small&gt; has devoted her time in Downing Street to a single task: getting Britain out of the European Union. In November she cleared the first hurdle when she signed a draft Brexit deal with her opposite numbers in Brussels. But its terms were so much worse than those she had promised at home that she has been unable to get the deal through Parliament. &lt;small&gt;MP&lt;/small&gt;s have rejected it three times, by crushing margins. Under pressure from her party, Mrs May has promised to quit if she fails on her fourth and final attempt. Even though the vote is not due until next month, it became clear this week that the deal was indeed doomed when her last-ditch attempt to win over doubters backfired spectacularly and triggered the resignation of a senior minister (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/23/another-british-prime-minister-is-destroyed-by-the-europe-question&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;). At the same time, the Conservative Party is set to take a drubbing in European elections at the hands of Nigel Farage and his new Brexit Party. Britain will soon have a new prime minister.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Historians may be a fraction kinder to Mrs May than today’s commentators. But the prime minister’s ineptitude has rendered the fiendishly hard Brexit project almost impossible. Faced with the many painful trade-offs that Brexit entails, Mrs May refused to accept that compromise was necessary until too late—after others’ positions had hardened and compromise was defined as losing. Many Leavers now believe that a perfect, costless version of Brexit exists, which they are being denied only through some mix of incompetence and conspiracy. At the same time many Remainers, seeing the government constantly in retreat, believe that Brexit could yet be cancelled altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This polarisation is Mrs May’s legacy—and it will bedevil her successor. In the aftermath of the referendum, nearly three years ago, many Brexiteers might have accepted a deal in which Britain left the single market and ended free movement, with temporary membership of the customs union as the only tie. Most now see such an outcome as an intolerable betrayal (never mind that some of them still seem unsure what a customs union actually is). In the same way, Remainers might once also have been satisfied by the prospect of a customs union, so long as it was tied to a vote in Parliament on whether to hold a second referendum. But when Mrs May belatedly offered such things this week, it was dismissed by all sides as inadequate. The scope for compromise has drastically narrowed from where it stood in 2016. Talks with the Labour opposition and indicative votes among &lt;small&gt;MP&lt;/small&gt;s on possible Brexit options have gone nowhere, in large part because they were initiated so late in the day. Mrs May inherited a divided country which urgently needed to be coaxed back together. Her approach has driven its two tribes still further apart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She has no cards left to play. A change of leader might give new momentum to talks in Westminster, which have stalled in the past few weeks, despite the &lt;small&gt;EU’&lt;/small&gt;s urging of Britain to get on with it. Boris Johnson, the favourite among the Conservative Party members who will choose the next leader, represents a dangerous gamble for the country (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/22/choosing-boris-johnson-as-prime-minister-would-be-a-dangerous-gamble&quot;&gt;Bagehot&lt;/a&gt;). But he may be more capable than Mrs May of the political and ideological flexibility that will be required to get Britain out of the trap in which it has placed itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one should assume that Mrs May’s exit will solve Britain’s Brexit problems. Mr Johnson proposes to renegotiate the withdrawal agreement, but the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; is sure to refuse him. At home, most Leave-voters detest the current deal so vehemently that they would rather quit with no deal at all (another dreadful legacy of Mrs May, who spent two years saying Britain could prosper with no deal, before admitting that she was wrong). Upstart parties on both the Leave and Remain sides are tugging Labour and the Tories towards the extremes. The possibility of cross-party agreement seems more remote than ever. And as the chances of no deal edge up, the pound is sliding. Mrs May has had a wretched time in office. Her successor will find it no easier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Leaders&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;The end of the road&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 21:40:18 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>