<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[What happens when antibiotics no longer work?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/29/what-happens-when-antibiotics-no-longer-work]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/the_world_ahead_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-29T16:40:13Z&quot;&gt;Apr 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN THIS edition of “The world ahead” podcast we examine a possible future where antibiotics no longer work. What causes antimicrobial resistance and what can be done to remedy it? And in a related scenario, we examine technology&amp;#x27;s potential to address the global shortage of medical staff. Anne McElvoy hosts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theworldahead/theworldahead-whenthedrugsdontwork&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1409838532?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/77TqNrVfHv2kK633eQPk4t&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZXdvcmxkYWhlYWQ&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=208475&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Economist-The-world-ahead-p1143184/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:06:33 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The genomics revolution for good and ill]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/04/29/the-genomics-revolution-for-good-and-ill]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_OPP510.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-29T14:52:28Z&quot;&gt;Apr 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SEX IS how humans propagate. But developments in genetic engineering might change this one day. “We are, in the future, going to have sex for most of the wonderful reasons that we have sex now: for fun, for pair-bonding, to connect with other people, to give meaning to our lives. But increasingly we are going to do it less and less for procreation,” says Jamie Metzl, the author of a new book on genetics, “Hacking Darwin.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Metzl was speaking on &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s Babbage podcast on technology and science. Today, during in vitro fertilisation, it is possible to screen embryos for genetic disorders. Tomorrow it may be feasible to look for—or even add—new traits. (An excerpt from Mr Metzl’s book is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/04/25/how-genetic-engineering-will-reshape-humanity&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.) The podcast raised questions of technology, ethics and society. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistbabbage/babbage-thegeneticrevolution&quot; width=&quot;500&amp;amp;quot;&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Listen on: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id508376907?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/0BCUrdrOb3tvfIwazeLBUH&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWVjb25vbWlzdGJhYmJhZ2U&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=142124&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Economist-Babbage-p401958/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Genomic technologies are going from research lab to commercial service quickly, notably in America, which has permissive regulations. Steven Hsu, the cofounder of Genomic Prediction, discusses how his company already screens for Down’s Syndrome and is planning to test for other disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet this may just be the start. As more traits are detectable through genetic testing, parents may be able to choose among traits in their natural embryos. But some would go further, and tinker with DNA to produce certain traits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gulzaar Barn, a philosopher at King’s College, London, is uneasy with this. On the podcast, she argued that society should be cautious before accepting genetic enhancement as a good thing, since it undermines the idea that we are all equal despite our genetic or individual differences (be it looks or intelligence, and so on).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Less controversially, basic genomic technologies are used to cure disease. Eric Topol is a doctor and author of several books on technology and health care (including “Deep Medicine,” recently &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/03/23/a-doctors-hopes-for-digital-medicine&quot;&gt;reviewed&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;em&gt;The Economis&lt;/em&gt;t). He looks forward to using genomics to tailor therapies around individual needs. “Instead of this kind of dumbed-down approach, where we treat people without knowing much more about them, we will have a far greater handle at many levels,” he tells us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After talking to scientists, businesspeople, philosophers and doctors, the Babbage programme turned to the world of the arts and culture for the final word. We spoke to Ella Road, the 27-year-old playwright of “The Phlebotomist” (ie, someone who takes blood for medical testing). It recently concluded a run in London. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the play, people are rated for their genetic makeup. She argues on the podcast that her futuristic play isn’t far from the world of today, where people are rated on social media all the time and society accepts wide inequalities. You can read a scene from the play &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/04/26/the-genetic-data-dystopia-we-may-face?fsrc=gp_en&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This episode of Babbage was produced as part of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s Open Future initiative, which makes the case for freedom, rights, technology and diversity in the 21st century. You can read more on the topics at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/openfuture&quot;&gt;Economist.com/openfuture&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And if you enjoy the Babbage podcast, please subscribe to the show or rate us (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://podcasts.apple.com/gb/podcast/babbage-from-economist-radio/id508376907&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;) and share it on social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:06:32 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why do some airports hide their buses?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/gulliver/2019/04/28/why-do-some-airports-hide-their-buses]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190330_WBP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-28T14:39:34Z&quot;&gt;Apr 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;ALWAYS ON THE lookout for a bargain, Gulliver takes great pride in using public transport when he travels abroad. Journeys between airports and city centres are no exception. Most of the time finding the cheapest route takes no more effort than logging onto an airport’s websites or opening a navigation app such as Google Maps. Sometimes, however, airports are not co-operative, trying their best to shove visitors onto convenient but overpriced transport links. Arlanda Airport near Stockholm, the capital of Sweden, is by far the worst offender Gulliver has encountered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Passengers arriving at Terminal 5, which handles most of Arlanda’s international flights, are presented with clear signage to its train and bus stations. The train station is served by the Arlanda Express, a high-speed rail link that covers the 40km stretch to Stockholm Central Station in just 20 minutes. Many business travellers swear by the service for its speed and convenience. But with standard one-way fares costing 295 SEK ($31), those paying for their own ticket may feel less happy about the price. An alternative is offered by Flygbussarna, a private bus company, which does the journey by road in 40 minutes. One-way tickets purchased from its drivers cost 119 SEK–by no means an exorbitant amount, but not exactly a steal either.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;A quick visit to Arlanda’s website gives the strong impression that these are the only two options. But there are in fact more than that. Three commuter buses also connect the airport with Märsta Station, 20 minutes from Arlanda. From there you can take a 40-minute train to Stockholm Central. Because the entire journey can be made within a 75-minute window, passengers only need to buy a single ticket. That costs just 32 SEK if you invest in a prepaid swipe card, or 45 SEK if you do not.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;That one can reach Stockholm city centre for nearly one-tenth the price of the Arlanda Express is nothing exceptional. The price difference is roughly comparable to that at London’s Heathrow Airport between the Heathrow Express, an overground rail service which is Britain’s most expensive train per mile, and the cheap-as-chips London Underground system. Local buses are also well signposted at its terminals. What is exceptional at Arlanda, however, is the lengths to which it has gone to hide the very existence of the cheaper commuter bus services. As well as excluding them from its website, the airport diverts passengers away from its own bus station.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Instead, people arriving at Terminal 5 must ignore the signage and go upstairs to the departures level before waiting at an unmarked stop. (The actual signpost has been placed so far away from the doors of the terminal that bus drivers pay no attention to it and hardly stop there.) Alternatively, local buses also stop at a nearby office complex—another option that requires passengers to ignore all the airport’s signage to find the buses there.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Gulliver appreciates that the public-private partnership which built the Arlanda Express in the 1990s–at a mind-blowing cost of 6bn SEK–wants to recover at least part of its investment. That is why passengers are also hit with a 120 SEK “station access fee” if they attempt to take slower commuter trains to Stockholm. But free competition between different modes of transport is good for travellers as it spurs efficiency and helps keep a lid on fare levels. Both Arlanda and the City of Stockholm risk losing footfall to other cities if their visitors feel ripped off every time they arrive at the airport.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:06:31 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China-America trade talks, and more from our daily podcast]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/29/china-america-trade-talks-and-more-from-our-daily-podcast]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/the_intelligence_62.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-29T11:23:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMERICAN NEGOTIATORS will be in Beijing this week to finalise a trade deal. What’s left to be agreed, and what are the sticking points? Also, America’s shale boom has given it leverage in international oil markets. How will it use its power? And we look at a foul-smelling Egyptian delicacy that has the potential to kill. Runtime: 21 min.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/thestraininspain-anelectionlooms&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 19:07:48 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spain’s Socialists win the election, but need to find allies]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/29/spains-socialists-win-the-election-but-need-to-find-allies]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_EUP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BACK LAST May when he filed the censure motion that brought him into office, Pedro Sánchez brushed off demands for an immediate election. With less than a quarter of the seats in Congress, he governed for ten months through a mix of significant gestures—in particular a big rise in the minimum wage—and symbolic acts, such as starting the process of moving the remains of Franco, the former dictator, to a less prominent location.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His reward came on April 28th when his Socialist party won a general election with 123 seats, gaining 2m more votes and 38 more seats compared with the last ballot in 2016. That is well short of a majority, however, so the Socialists will need allies to govern in the 350-seat Congress. But on paper at least, Mr Sánchez may be able to find them on either left or centre-right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The election increased the fragmentation of what was once a two-party system in Spain. The right paid a price in lost seats for its splintering into three. The formerly dominant conservative People’s Party (PP) lost more than half of its seats. Ciudadanos, a formerly liberal but now more right-of-centre party, came within 220,000 votes of the PP. The hard right, in the shape of Vox, a newish ultra-nationalist party, entered Congress for the first time since 1982. But with only 24 seats and 10.3% of the vote, it fell short of many forecasts. The spectre of Vox, indeed, probably helped Mr Sánchez to mobilise his voters. A high turnout of 76% on a warm spring day helped the Catalan separatists too, who won 22 seats, up from 17.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We’ve sent a message to Europe and the world that you can defeat reaction [and] authoritarianism,” Mr Sánchez told a cheering crowd outside the Socialist headquarters in Madrid. He will now face two big tasks: to fulfil his promise of a fairer society when economic recovery is slowing, and to try to defuse Catalan separatism. First he will have to marshall a majority in Congress. “From our ideas on the left, we will extend our hand to all political forces [who operate] within the constitution,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One option, and perhaps the likeliest, is to join forces with Podemos, a further-left outfit with 42 seats (down from 71), the moderate Basque nationalists and assorted regional parties. Pablo Iglesias, Podemos’s leader, has been pressing for a formal coalition—a first in Spain’s post-Franco era. This would echo Portugal’s largely successful government. But such an assemblage will be able to govern only if it can rely on the abstention of Catalan separatists on big votes. Catalan opposition was the reason why Mr Sanchez’s failed to pass his budget in February, leading to the early election. And forming such a coalition may be tricky anyway. Many Socialist voters will recoil at Podemos’s commitment to an independence referendum in Catalonia. The Socialists do favour dialogue with the separatists, but a referendum is not currently on offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A stronger, but politically even more difficult, option would be a coalition with Ciudadanos. Albert Rivera, the party’s leader, explicitly ruled that out during the campaign and did so again on election night, saying that he would lead the opposition. Mr Rivera wants a hard-line approach to Catalan separatism, not dialogue as Mr Sánchez advocates; he also sees an opportunity to displace the PP as the dominant force on the centre-right. For their part, Socialist activists listening to Mr Sánchez outside party headquarters chanted “Not with Rivera”. The private sector and many centrists will urge both men to reconsider. But Mr Sánchez is unlikely to announce any decision until after municipal, regional and European elections on May 26th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the entry of Vox and a stronger Catalan separatist contingent, the new Congress is likely to be a rowdy and ill-tempered body, when Spain needs the moderation and concord Mr Sánchez is pledged to seek. The election leaves the Spanish right with a difficult task of rebuilding. Unless the PP does much better next month, its new leader, Pablo Casado, is likely to be forced out. He chose to tack right, trying to echo rather than challenge Vox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the Socialists, whatever happens next, this was their first victory since 2008 and a personal triumph for Mr Sánchez, who was briefly ejected as party leader in 2016-17. The days of absolute majorities in Spain are over for the time being. But Spain’s prime minister has delivered a rare good result for European social democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 19:07:47 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Military spending around the world is booming]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/international/2019/04/28/military-spending-around-the-world-is-booming]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_BLP511.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-28T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE WORLD is arming itself to the teeth. That is the conclusion of a new report published on April 29th by the Stockholm International Peace Research Institute (SIPRI), a think-tank. Global military spending last year rose to $1.8trn, says SIPRI—the highest level in real terms since reliable records began in 1988, during the cold war, and 76% higher than in 1998, when the world was enjoying its “peace dividend”. Military spending as a share of global GDP has fallen in recent years, but that offers little reassurance in a world of rising geopolitical tension.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The spending boom is driven, above all, by the contest between America and China for primacy in Asia. Start with America. In 2018 it raised its already-gargantuan defence budget for the first time in seven years, ending an era of belt-tightening imposed by Congress. The boost reflected the Trump administration’s embrace of what it calls “great power competition” with Russia and China—requiring fancier, pricier weapons—in place of the inconclusive guerilla wars it had fought since 2001.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America’s military heft has no equal. Its outlay of $649bn (in 2017 dollars) was almost as large as the next eight countries combined, by SIPRI’s reckoning. Even that did not satiate the Pentagon’s appetite. It got $716bn this year (in current dollars, as counted by the Department of Defence) and hopes for a staggering $750bn in 2020—an annual increase larger than the defence budgets of almost all of its NATO allies. That includes nearly $10bn for cyber operations, a 10% year-on-year boost; over $14bn for space, a 15% jump; and the biggest budget request for shipbuilding in two decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_WOC807.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190504_WOC807.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190504_WOC807.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190504_WOC807.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190504_WOC807.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190504_WOC807.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190504_WOC807.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190504_WOC807.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190504_WOC807.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190504_WOC807.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;China is far behind. It spends somewhere between a quarter and two-fifths of what America does (the precise amount is unclear, say experts, because Chinese spending is so opaque). Nor is its military expenditure growing at a 10% clip, as it did on average in the years between 2000 and 2016. But it has risen relentlessly for a quarter-century, completely changing the balance of power in Asia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Between 2009 and 2018, America’s defence spending fell by 17% in real terms whereas China’s grew by 83%—accelerating under President Xi Jinping and outpacing every other big power. “No one has ever presided over anywhere close to this level of Chinese military development in Chinese history before Xi,” notes Andrew Erickson, a professor at the US Naval War College. Its navy has been a particular beneficiary. Between 2014 and 2018, China launched naval vessels with a total tonnage exceeding that of the entire Indian or French navies, notes IISS, another think-tank. Even so, the country’s defence spending is still smaller as a proportion of GDP than that of any other top-five country: 1.9% to America&amp;#x27;s 3.2%. That means it has room to grow, should the geopolitical mood darken.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Military reforms that Mr Xi introduced in 2015, including a slimming down of the army and reorganisation of the command structure along American lines, are also likely to have given China more bang for its yuan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In response, China’s regional rivals have opened their purses, too. India now outspends every European country. South Korea’s annual increase in 2018 was the highest since 2005. And Japanese spending is set to surge in the next five years, with new offensive weapons breaking old pacifist taboos. All in all, Asian military spending makes up 28% of the world’s total, up from 9% in 1988.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Europeans, having hollowed out their armed forces after the cold war, are getting their act together. In 2018 NATO’s European allies raised military spending by 4.2% in real terms, according to IISS. Poland, which is particularly anxious about next-door Russia, boosted spending by 8.9%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were European spending to be lumped together, the continent would be the world’s second-largest military power, outspending Russia fourfold. In practice, Europe’s hodge-podge of duplicated, mismatched equipment (Europeans use 17 types of tanks to America’s one) and continued dependence on America in key areas—such as moving troops and refueling warplanes—mean that its armed forces are far less than the sum of their parts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet not everywhere is piling up arms. Military spending in Africa shrank for a fourth consecutive year in 2018, by 8.4%, driven by big falls in Angola, Algeria and Sudan, says SIPRI. Protests in the latter two countries, with armies under pressure to hand over power to civilians, might cause bloated military budgets to be squeezed further.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Middle East also seems to be cooling off after years of frenzied arms-buying. Though SIPRI lacks data for Qatar and the United Arab Emirates (UAE), two of the biggest customers for Western arms companies, and for war-torn Yemen and Syria, spending in the rest of the region fell by 1.9% in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That trend seems likely to continue. Saudi Arabia, the region’s biggest fish, which sets aside a huge 8.8% of GDP for defence, will slash its military spending by 9.1% this year. Iran, its rival, plans even bigger cuts of its own—though the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps (IRGC), which has done most of the recent fighting in places like Syria, got a hefty raise, as did the intelligence ministry, which has been bumping off dissidents abroad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most interesting contraction is, however, in Russia. “Can they count?” President Vladimir Putin asked of his Western rivals in February. “I&amp;#x27;m sure they can. Let them count the speed and the range of the weapons systems we are developing”. But despite the theatrical flaunting of new missiles, and NATO’s impressive rearmament to the west, SIPRI calculates that Russia’s defence budget actually shrank by 3.5% in 2018—putting it outside the top five for the first time in over a decade. This may be the result of a weakening rouble. But Russia’s long military spending spree seems to be drawing to a close. That is a sobering thought for Mr Putin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 08:05:43 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Ebola outbreak in Congo is getting worse]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/04/28/the-ebola-outbreak-in-congo-is-getting-worse]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_blp903.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-28T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE GREATEST fear of most health workers battling Ebola is catching the deadly virus, which makes people gush blood from every orifice. But to Dr Richard Valery Mouzoko Kiboung, an epidemiologist from Cameroon working with the World Health Organisation (WHO), violence was also a pressing worry. Dr Mouzoko was stationed in Butembo, a city in the east of the Democratic Republic of Congo and the centre of an Ebola outbreak that was detected nine months ago. The area around it is in effect a war zone, home to over 100 militias. Locals misunderstand and distrust health workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On April 19th gunmen burst into a meeting of the local Ebola response team that he led. The attackers took everyone’s phone, then started shooting. Two people were wounded. Dr Mouzoko was killed. Hours later a group of people armed with machetes tried to set fire to an Ebola treatment centre at a hospital in nearby Katwa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The violence is part of a trend. In February and March several clinics were attacked, leading Médecins Sans Frontières, a medical charity, to pull its staff from the area around Butembo. A car carrying experts from the WHO was ambushed and damaged by men with sticks. Machete-wielding attackers slashed the head of a health worker responsible for safely burying Ebola victims, so that their corpses do not infect new victims. Congo “is as complex and as volatile an environment as I&amp;#x27;ve seen,” says Mike Ryan, who directs the WHO’s health-emergency programme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_MAM908.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190427_MAM908.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190427_MAM908.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190427_MAM908.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190427_MAM908.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190427_MAM908.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190427_MAM908.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190427_MAM908.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190427_MAM908.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190427_MAM908.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The WHO and other responders appeared to be getting a handle on the outbreak in January, but the violence has set their efforts back. The virus has infected nearly 1,400 people and killed nearly 900. In April the WHO said there was a very high risk that Ebola would spread, including to neighbouring countries such as Uganda, Rwanda and Burundi. Those countries have been asked to start vaccinating health workers and watch out for the virus. The WHO says that more work is also needed in mapping the movement of people, such as workers and refugees, across borders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus, the head of the WHO, says it is becoming difficult to persuade his staff to go into the field. He is visiting Butembo to try to calm his workers and analyse the situation. He is now expecting a rise in the number of cases of Ebola. “Whenever there is an attack it slows down the response, and the number of cases immediately increases as the virus gets the advantage and continues unabated,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Locals, whose basic needs have long been neglected, resent the massive deployment of resources just to fight the virus. Earlier efforts by the police and armed forces to compel people to take preventative measures alienated the local population. Some even imagine that the government is using Ebola to exterminate the Nandes, the biggest ethnic group in the region, or that the emergency was manufactured to keep people from voting in elections last year. The idea that Ebola does not actually exist has been spread by some groups for political advantage, says Dr Tedros, who described it as “playing with fire”. Though he says local leaders have agreed to deliver the same message about the dangers of Ebola.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The WHO has thus far declined to declare the outbreak a public-health emergency of international concern, its loudest alarm bell. The means of controlling Ebola are well understood from previous outbreaks. These include quickly and safely burying victims, tracing the contacts of those infected and vaccinating people in affected areas. Dr Tedros says he has agreed to increase vaccination coverage as soon as possible. There is also discussion of using a different type of vaccine that could be administered to many more people than the one currently in use. But it is almost impossible to do any of this unless health workers can be kept safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 06:08:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling with style]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/04/28/struggling-with-style]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_WBP503_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-28T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;SUMMER’S ARRIVAL in the northern hemisphere brings the arrival of a dilemma that plagues every office worker. What does a casual dress code mean in practice? The happy medium between looking like Kim Kardashian or Hagrid the giant is hard to pin down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs has just implemented a “flexible dress code” although the executive memo noted gnomically that “casual dress is not appropriate every day”. Besuited corporate clients might not take kindly to investment-banking advice delivered by someone wearing a tank top and ripped jeans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It makes sense that banking would be one of the last bastions to fall to the advance of casual workwear. You want the people who look after our money to appear sober and respectable. For similar reasons, bank headquarters have deliberately been built in a grandiose style to emphasise the institution’s financial solidity and historical roots. Depositors might hesitate about handing over their savings to people working under a railway arch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For men, the move to casual dress seems entirely positive. Few people will mourn the demise of the tie, a functionally useless garment that constricted male necks for a century. The tie’s origins date back to the 17th century when mercenaries hired by Louis XIII of France wore a form of cravat. The modern version of the tie emerged in the 1920s and was popularised by Britain’s Edward VIII who, when not flirting with the Nazis, developed the Windsor knot. It became standard office wear for the next six decades. In the 1990s ties started to go out of fashion because technology titans and hedge fund managers refused to wear them—and were rich enough to ignore social convention. As a prank, Mark Zuckerberg, the Facebook founder, once turned up at a meeting with a venture capitalist in his pyjamas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The jacket, by contrast, is a much more useful garment, replete with pockets to house wallets, spectacle cases and travel passes (or, these days, mobile phones). So the default work garb for men, when meeting clients, is jacket, open-necked shirt and dark trousers (denim excluded).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On days without meetings, men can slob out in t-shirts (though not too garish) and jeans, and no one will think the worse of them. Arriving in shorts or without socks is another matter entirely. But dressing in the morning is a quick-and-easy process. Steve Jobs was famous for wearing the same outfit—black turtleneck, jeans and sneakers—every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what works well for men does not apply as easily to women. Karl Stefanovic, an Australian TV presenter, wore the same blue suit every day for a year and no one noticed. By contrast, his female co-presenters received constant comment on their appearance. Even the Duchess of Cambridge (Kate Middleton) gets snarky comments when she wears the same clothes twice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women’s workwear seems to have become less formal over time. A survey by Euromonitor found that sales of women’s suits fell by 77% in America between 2007 and 2016. But many women worry that they will be judged as unprofessional (unlike their male colleagues) if their clothes are deemed to be too scruffy, or too revealing. It can also be tough choosing clothes that are suitable for both inside and outside conditions. Air-conditioning systems in offices are often designed to suit the male metabolic rate, which can cope with colder temperatures than the female body. The result may be that women have to bring an extra layer to wear within the office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for formal meetings, although men have abandoned the tie, many women feel obliged to wear high heels. These give many women a sense of empowerment and femininity (not to mention extra height). But in health terms, heels can seem like the Western equivalent of the ancient Chinese practice of foot-binding: bad for women’s feet, ankles and backs and designed to limit their mobility. Britain’s Parliament held a debate after a woman was sent home from her job as a receptionist for refusing to wear high heels (it was inconclusive).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Companies understandably want workers who deal with the public to look respectable. No one should be expected to turn up at the office as if dressed for a wedding. Nor should workers wear clothes that wouldn’t be appropriate if visiting a prudish grandmother or a child’s teacher. The most important item to bring to work is a dose of sartorial common sense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 04:08:10 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Holy Fire at Easter features new lanterns for Ukraine]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/04/28/the-holy-fire-at-easter-features-new-lanterns-for-ukraine]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_blp902.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-28T14:16:37Z&quot;&gt;Apr 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHEN SEVEN weeks of ascetic abnegation culminate in a joyful Easter celebration, Orthodox Christians are supposed to be in amity with one another, and at peace with the world. That is more a statement of the obvious. Since a calendar reform of the 1920s, Christians of the east have been divided over when to celebrate say, Christmas; but virtually all, whether in Muscovite cathedrals or tiny Balkan villages, mark Easter on the same date (often, as this year, different from the western one) and in broadly the same style.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a style that stresses inclusivity. The service features a famous sermon by Archbishop John Chrysostom (c349-407) which invites everybody to the Easter feast, whether they have fasted rigorously or only a little or not at all: “The table is lavishly laden, let all enjoy it sumptuously!” Elsewhere in the prayers, there are exhortations like: “Let us embrace one another! Let us say…even to those who hate us, may all be pardoned in the light of the Resurrection!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Against this warm and forgiving background, people were watching closely for any slight mending of a split within the Orthodox world which has been described by one of the protagonists, the Patriarchate of Moscow, as the bitterest inter-Orthodox division for many centuries. It concerns the proclamation in January of an independent Ukrainian church, with the blessing of the Istanbul-based Patriarch of Constantinople, who traditionally enjoys “primacy of honour” in world Orthodoxy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a thundering retaliation for what it called encroachment on its canonical territory, the Moscow Patriarchate severed relations with the Istanbul-based hierarch, Bartholomew I, and told its flock not to receive the sacraments (supremely sacred church rites) in places under his authority.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In recent weeks and over Easter, there have been signs of things getting just a little bit easier, or at least of people learning to live with deep disagreement. A change at the top may help. The politician who spearheaded the creation of the Orthodox Church of Ukraine (OCU), Petro Poroshenko, lost last weekend’s presidential elections to a comic actor, Volodymyr Zelensky.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Muscovite hierarchy apparently sees this as an opportunity for a fresh start. Patriarch Kirill sent the new head of state a warm letter of congratulation and his Easter message contained no vituperation over Ukraine. As a practising Orthodox Christian, Mr Poroshenko had been passionately involved in church affairs and staked his unsuccessful election campaign on a slogan of “army, language and faith”. Mr Zelensky, who is Jewish, has less obvious interest in inter-Orthodox disputes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those disputes rumble on. Muscovites complain that parishes loyal to Kirill are being taken over improperly by Ukrainian nationalists. The OCU retorts that any transfers are voluntary. Whatever the circumstances, about 500 congregations have switched allegiance from the Patriarchate of Moscow to the OCU; that probably leaves around 11,000 communities in Muscovite hands, against nearly 8,000 for the OCU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In any case, the church which Mr Poroshenko helped to found was proud to celebrate its first Easter since receiving the Tomos, a document issued in Istanbul that certifies its independence. Perhaps a little crestfallen, the former president stood near the front as Metropolitan Epifaniy, the 40-year-old primate of the new church, led the Resurrection chants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was also the first year in which the independent Ukrainian church participated in one of the most spectacular Easter rituals that bind the Orthodox world together. As soon as the “Holy Fire” symbolising the Resurrection is kindled in the Church of the Holy Sepulchre in Jerusalem, usually on Saturday afternoon, the flames (or rather lanterns kindled from the flame) are swiftly transported to Orthodox communities near and far. Palestinian Christians drum the fire through their streets, while planes whisk flickering lamps to places like Greece, Cyprus, Russia—and, as of 2019, Ukraine. It was brought to Saint Michael’s Cathedral in Kiev by a group of 30 volunteers, including some war veterans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Istanbul, meanwhile, Patriarch Bartholomew solemnly prayed for all the other leaders of Orthodox churches, including Moscow’s Kirill and Kiev’s Epifaniy, as he led the four-hour overnight service. Mr Zelensky was reported to have headed to Turkey for a short holiday but he was not to be seen at the Patriarchate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other ways, though, he seems to have entered the paschal spirit. He had upset the leaders of the new Ukrainian church by waggishly comparing their beloved Tomos, or certificate of religious freedom, with a thermos, which in Slavic languages as well as English refers to a humdrum device for keeping drinks at a stable temperature. But over the weekend, leaders of the OCU said the new President had apologised for his joke and they had warmly forgiven him; they wished him well with his presidency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 02:06:46 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Who will win “Game of Thrones”?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/04/28/who-will-win-game-of-thrones]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_WOC556.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-28T14:52:55Z&quot;&gt;Apr 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article contains plot details of season eight of “Game of Thrones”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“WHEN YOU play the game of thrones, you win or you die. There is no middle ground.” Cersei Lannister’s binary prediction, made eight years and 62 episodes ago during the first season of TV drama “Game of Thrones”, is looking prescient. With just four episodes left, a major battle looks set to wipe out many of the show’s remaining characters. And not all survivors would have much chance of taking a seat upon the Iron Throne as the ruler of Westeros when the final season ends, according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://markets.predictwise.com/entertainment/game-of-thrones&quot;&gt;bookmakers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early front-runner Bran Stark, no stranger to falling, has plummeted from favour with bettors, while his sister Sansa’s chances have nearly doubled over the past two episodes. A new “battle of the bastards” is taking place between Gendry and Jon Snow in third and fourth place, even as the latter’s true heritage starts to cause problems with his beloved aunt. And as is fitting for a show with a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/prospero/2017/07/24/what-is-the-moral-compass-of-game-of-thrones&quot;&gt;meandering moral compass&lt;/a&gt;, the two players who most want to win, Cersei and Daenerys Targaryen, have little hope, at least if the wisdom of crowds is to be believed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;More on “Game of Thrones”:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.1843magazine.com/culture/the-daily/game-of-loans&quot;&gt;The economics of “Game of Thrones&lt;/a&gt;”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.1843magazine.com/culture/the-daily/how-to-win-the-game-of-thrones&quot;&gt;How to win the “Game of Thrones”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/prospero/2016/06/27/women-rule-westeros-how-strange&quot;&gt;Women rule Westeros. How strange&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:06:49 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>