<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Are extraterrestrials extra patriotic?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/07/04/are-extraterrestrials-extra-patriotic]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_WOC365.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN THE FINAL scene of “Independence Day”, a blockbuster film from 1996, Captain Steve Hiller (Will Smith), having saved the world from alien annihilation, watches as exploding debris from a UFO mothership lights up the sky, just in time for the American holiday. Turning to his stepson, he says with a smile, “Didn’t I promise you fireworks?” For Americans, such pyrotechnic displays are an important Fourth of July tradition. Can the same be said for UFOs?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps. According to the National UFO Reporting Centre (NUFORC), an American non-profit organisation that has collected reports of unidentified flying objects since 1974, UFO sightings tend to spike on July 4th. Between 1995 and 2018, around 2% of all sightings recorded by NUFORC fell on this date; seven times more than would be expected by chance. What explains this strange phenomenon?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hollywood may be partly to blame. In the two years before the release of the Will Smith flick, NUFORC recorded an average of seven UFO sightings on July 4th (eight in 1995 and six in 1996). In 1997, a year after aliens burst onto the big screen, there were 74—more than ten times as many. Traditions of the July 4th holiday may also help explain the spike. Independence Day is typically spent outdoors. Heavy alcohol use is not uncommon. Intoxication may cause some to confuse celebratory fireworks with alien aircraft.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_WOC367.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190706_WOC367.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190706_WOC367.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190706_WOC367.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190706_WOC367.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190706_WOC367.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190706_WOC367.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190706_WOC367.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190706_WOC367.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190706_WOC367.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;UFO sightings cannot be blamed entirely on drunkenness. They often have earthly explanations. Some of the biggest spikes in reported UFO sightings in recent years have later been explained by meteors, missiles or debris from satellites re-entering the atmosphere. Or so the government would have you believe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 03:40:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ari Aster returns with “Midsommar”]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/07/04/ari-aster-returns-with-midsommar]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BKP508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-04T17:19:40Z&quot;&gt;Jul 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE NEW wave of high-class horror rolls on with “Midsommar”, a sinister, slow-burning film by Ari Aster, which is being hailed by many critics as one of the best of the year. Following the director’s acclaimed debut, “Hereditary”, Jordan Peele’s “Get Out” and “Us”, John Krasinski’s “A Quiet Place” and Luca Guadagnino’s “Suspiria”, “Midsommar” is a horror movie with crossover potential. It has the resonant themes, painstaking cinematography and Oscar-worthy acting to pull in viewers in the mood for a prestigious drama; but it will also appeal to those who just fancy seeing close-ups of good-looking youngsters being mutilated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The film’s star, Florence Pugh, is especially impressive. A British actress best known for indie dramas (“The Falling”, “Lady Macbeth”), Ms Pugh is as expressive when she is glaring silently as when she is collapsing in a fit of racking sobs. The reason for these sobs is that the sister and parents of her character, Dani, are killed in the film’s opening minutes: like “Hereditary”, “Midsommar” explores grief. Dani’s passive-aggressive dolt of a boyfriend Christian (Jack Reynor) isn’t much help, and he blames her for his neglectful behaviour as well as for her own woes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before the deaths, Christian had been planning to break up with Dani but, more out of cowardice than compassion, he decides in the circumstances to let her tag along on his boys’ holiday to northern Sweden. His American graduate-student buddies (Will Poulter and William Jackson Harper) are not too pleased, but his Swedish friend Pelle (Vilhelm Blomgren) reassures Dani that she is more than welcome. He has invited them all to a nine-day solstice festival in the woodland commune where he grew up, and he seems suspiciously sure that Dani will fit right in. On arrival, she agrees. The ancient rites and the perpetual sunshine in Pelle’s remote enclave may be disorientating, but the white-robed tribespeople are warm and beatific, and the psychotropic mushrooms they hand out turn the meadows into rippling oceans of wild flowers. It is quite a while before Dani learns how much trouble she is in. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Too long, perhaps. As anyone who has seen Robin Hardy’s British cult classic “The Wickerman” (1973) will know, things never end well for outsiders who poke their noses into an isolated community’s pagan festivities—sex and ritual sacrifice are usually involved—and “Midsommar” comes to much the same conclusion as that film, or indeed any other folk-horror mystery. The difference is that it takes 140 minutes to get there. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not that Mr Aster wastes the time. A lot funnier than “Hereditary”, “Midsommar” is in part a cheerful comedy about bickering Americans who are befuddled by the customs and cuisine of a foreign country. The screenplay floats some provocative ideas about the sense of belonging offered by religions, however anachronistic and illogical they may appear. There are so many odd little details scattered throughout the gorgeously designed film that it never stops being intriguing. The runic inscriptions and the pictographs on the barn walls are all very well, but why is there a live bear locked in a wooden cage?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet as well-crafted as “Midsommar” is, viewers still have to wait an hour before anything unpleasant happens in the commune. When it does happen, it is so unpleasant that it is hard to believe that Dani and the others would not run for the hills, instead of shrugging and going along with the programme of solemn al fresco meals and exhausting maypole dances devised by their hosts. Many viewers will go along with it, too, though others will feel that Mr Aster is cheating. Given that two of his characters are anthropology students who ask the commune’s elders about their myths and traditions, they seem oddly incurious about the more brutal practices. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nor do they seem to care that their friends keep disappearing without trace, or that there is a locked-up bear in the vicinity. The careless plotting means that “Midsommar” is ultimately more frustrating than frightening. It gives viewers plenty of time to appreciate its myriad artistic touches, but also to notice how ridiculously implausible it is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Midsommar” is screening in Britain and America now&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 01:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Conservatism&#x27;s crisis, hard truths from Shell&#x27;s boss and insects become fish food]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/07/04/conservatisms-crisis-hard-truths-from-shells-boss-and-insects-become-fish-food]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-04T16:40:28Z&quot;&gt;Jul 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A SELECTION of three essential articles read aloud from the latest issue of The Economist. This week, the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/07/04/the-global-crisis-in-conservatism&quot; data-tegid=&quot;08hrcro5f43n94sfe0n8qp9g599565ol&quot;&gt;global crisis in conservatism.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Royal Dutch Shell’s boss delivers some hard truths on &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/07/06/shells-boss-delivers-some-hard-truths-on-oil-and-climate-change&quot;&gt;oil and climate change&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (10:18). And, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/07/06/beetles-and-flies-are-becoming-part-of-the-agricultural-food-chain&quot;&gt;insects become fish food&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (18:00). Runtime: 27 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-july4th2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id313848583&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/3a5n4DoT1xrV5rgBWBPxnR&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWVjb25vbWlzdGVkaXRvcnNwaWNrcw&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=18376&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/Politics/The-Economist-Editors-Picks-p987585/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jul 2019 01:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[If everyone had voted, Hillary Clinton would probably be president]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/07/06/if-everyone-had-voted-hillary-clinton-would-probably-be-president]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-06T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-cfg=&quot;main-content:width:full&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-cfg=&quot;latest-updates:position:-1&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span data-cfg=&quot;article:right-rail:display:none&quot;&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190706_GDC414voting1/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;C&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;LOSE OBSERVERS&lt;/small&gt; of America know that the rules of its democracy often favour Republicans. But the party’s biggest advantage may be one that is rarely discussed: turnout is just 60%, low for a rich country. Polls show that non-voters—both people uninterested in voting and those blocked by legal or economic hurdles—mainly belong to groups that tend to back Democrats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What would change if America became the 22nd country to make voting mandatory? To estimate non-voters’ views, &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; used the Co-operative Congressional Election Study (&lt;small&gt;CCES&lt;/small&gt;), a 64,600-person poll led by Harvard University. The survey includes demographic data such as race and age, as well as participants’ recollections of whom they voted for and verified records of whether they voted. In general, voters and non-voters from similar backgrounds had similar opinions. Using a method called “multilevel regression and post-stratification”, the relationships between demography and vote choices can be used to project state-level election results—and to estimate what might have happened in the past under different rules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190706_GDC414_bars/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Non-voters are relatively uneducated, young and non-white.The first of these traits predicts conservatism, but the others point to liberalism. If everyone voted, 30% of voters in the 21 most competitive states would not be white, up from the actual figure of 25%. As a result, in a typical cycle Democrats would add 50 electoral-college votes—enough to reverse the result in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If voting were universal, parties would not benefit from whipping their bases into a frenzy. Instead, they would need to court swing voters, pushing policies towards the centre. That centre, however, would sit to the left of its current position, putting the brunt of the adjustment on Republicans. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Sources: Co-operative Congressional Election Study; Census Bureau; YouGov; &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Graphic detail&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;The silent near-majority&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 21:40:01 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Russia is back on the stage of great nations”—Putin’s PR push]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/07/04/russia-is-back-on-the-stage-of-great-nations-putins-pr-push]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_blm509.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-04T11:40:09Z&quot;&gt;Jul 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/13/what-ivan-golunovs-ordeal-reveals-about-russia&quot; data-tegid=&quot;01eibs9tdu2eksffnkd6gbrfna8p5v6o&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;RUSSIA&amp;#x27;S PRESIDENT&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is glad-handing in Italy, where his anti-liberal roadshow resonates. But Mr Putin’s is a twisted vision of liberalism, and at home many of his compatriots see through the ruse. We examine the “Swedish model” of&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/15/the-idea-of-criminalising-prostitutes-clients-is-spreading&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt; prostitution laws&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, and how the approach endangers &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/19/the-push-to-decriminalise-sex-work-in-new-york&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;sex workers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. And, the push to make &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/06/20/cleaning-up-nuclear-waste-is-an-obvious-task-for-robots&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;robots&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; that can handle environments like the melted-down Fukushima Daiichi power plant. Runtime: 23 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/e81f0263-c97b-4051-bb73-f6f516aee11c&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 20:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How a victim of the Cultural Revolution mastered economics]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/07/04/how-a-victim-of-the-cultural-revolution-mastered-economics]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_FND000_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE STUDENTS&lt;/small&gt; embarking on an economics doctorate at the University of California, Berkeley, this autumn face a daunting obstacle: Econ &lt;small&gt;201A&lt;/small&gt;, a course in microeconomic theory inflicted on all new recruits. Over 16 weeks they must acquaint themselves with some of the most formalised parts of economics, including Houthakker’s Axiom, the Slutsky matrix and Afriat’s Theorem. According to one instructor, between five and seven class members (out of 20 to 25) usually receive a grade of &lt;small&gt;B&lt;/small&gt;- or worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But anyone losing heart should take inspiration from a past student, Weijian Shan. He tried the course in 1982 after becoming one of America’s first &lt;small&gt;P&lt;/small&gt;h&lt;small&gt;D&lt;/small&gt; students from communist China. As he recounts in “Out of the Gobi”, his memoir published earlier this year, he had not taken a mathematics class beyond the age of 12. His faculty adviser, Janet Yellen, who would later chair the Federal Reserve, and George Akerlof, who would later win a Nobel prize, worried that the difficulties of Econ &lt;small&gt;201A&lt;/small&gt; would be “insurmountable”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shan, however, had already surmounted more than most. After his schooling was cut short in 1966 by the Cultural Revolution, he was “sent down” to the countryside, like millions of other city kids. He joined a Construction Army corps in the Gobi desert, trying to create farms out of salty clay in a “place that birds don’t care to shit”. They dug ditches, made bricks and harvested wheat, three of the four most tiring things in the world, according to one squad member. (The fourth was sex, which they were spared.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His march to Berkeley was long. He arrived in the Gobi knowing only a few sayings and slogans in English (“Long live Chairman Mao”). But in 1975 he was chosen by his peers and bosses to study the language in Beijing. He won nomination only after first ingratiating himself with his company by memorising the official rules and referee signals of volleyball, which made him a respected referee of platoon matches. The English he learnt in Beijing helped him win an Asia Foundation scholarship to study in America after it restored formal diplomatic ties with China in 1979. Having earned an &lt;small&gt;MBA &lt;/small&gt;in a year at the University of San Francisco, he embarked on his &lt;small&gt;P&lt;/small&gt;h&lt;small&gt;D&lt;/small&gt; at Berkeley’s business school.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his study of economics Mr Shan had one or two things going for him. Economics is the science of scarcity, a subject with which he had intimate acquaintance. Deep in the Gobi, a day’s walk from their settlement, half a box of matches could cost 50kg of potatoes. When Americans dismiss something as “bullshit”, Mr Shan recalls the patties of cow dung they used to treasure as fuel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The construction corps taught him other economic concepts, such as “value-added” and its opposite: their company turned 750,000kg of seeds into just 70,000kg of grain. He experienced the power of the division of labour. Even with the utmost industry his team could make only 200 bricks per person in a day if they each mixed, moulded and moved the materials. But by dividing those tasks between them they could make two-thirds more. He also learnt the value of capital. His platoon could have made 20,000 bricks per day with a simple mixing machine, but no one would provide the 3,000 yuan (about $1,300 at the official exchange rate) to buy it. Mr Shan wonders if he was the first hard labourer with “such a burning desire to be exploited by capital”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;The pigshed academy&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shan’s educational resurgence was nonetheless remarkable. Even by 1990 just 0.4% of Chinese born in 1951-55 held a university degree (see chart). The Cultural Revolution was like a mad natural experiment, depriving some people of a university education for reasons unrelated to their ability. Their loss has thus helped economists calculate the worth of a college education, which is otherwise difficult to estimate because college-goers are often more able than other people, even before they get there. According to a study in 2015 by John Giles of the World Bank, Albert Park of the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, and Meiyan Wang of the Chinese Academy of Social Sciences, about three-quarters of the returns to college in China reflect the skills and credentials that universities confer. But a quarter reflects the intrinsic abilities of the people they admit. Mr Shan’s education yielded a rich harvest. But he was also an unusually good seed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_FNC332_1.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190706_FNC332_1.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190706_FNC332_1.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190706_FNC332_1.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190706_FNC332_1.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190706_FNC332_1.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190706_FNC332_1.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190706_FNC332_1.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190706_FNC332_1.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190706_FNC332_1.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;One benefit of university is guidance. Mr Shan’s efforts to educate himself in the desert lacked system or direction. He retreated to a pigs’ kitchen, where vegetable roots, skins and leaves were boiled, to read whatever he could find: an aviation magazine, Mao’s speeches, a pesticide manual. For this reason, he feels his “little house of knowledge is built on sand”. (The vastly more privileged students of today can also struggle to study systematically, because of the surfeit of claims on their attention. Their houses can be dangerously top-heavy.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shan enjoyed Econ &lt;small&gt;201A&lt;/small&gt;, eventually. But he had to abandon his first attempt, returning only after taking the mathematics class that Ms Yellen and Mr Akerlof had recommended. The maths textbook was over 400 pages long. He read it seven times. “I would have enjoyed studying in a more leisurely manner,” he writes, but “I had so much ground to make up.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He followed his &lt;small&gt;P&lt;/small&gt;h&lt;small&gt;D&lt;/small&gt; with a brief stint at the World Bank and a longer one as a professor at Wharton Business School. He founded the &lt;em&gt;China Economic Review&lt;/em&gt; (which in 1990 published an article by a 32-year-old Yi Gang, now head of China’s central bank), then entered finance, becoming a big shot in private equity at Newbridge Capital. During long negotiations in hotel conference rooms he would marvel at the luxury of round-the-clock room service. His colleagues would tell him to shut up and gain some weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the Cultural Revolution ended in 1976 and reforms began, Mr Shan, like his country, had a lot of potential—and a lot of ground to make up. Since then they have both been compelling examples of convergence. When capital, of the human or physical variety, is scarce, the returns to investment can be high. And after the rigours of the past both were accustomed to the deferred gratification that heavy investment requires. The man who eventually mastered Econ &lt;small&gt;201A&lt;/small&gt; is an economics lesson in himself.&lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Finance and economics&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Yellen’s unlikeliest student&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 20:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A warlord’s offensive against Tripoli is flagging]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/07/04/a-warlords-offensive-against-tripoli-is-flagging]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_MAP008.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;N TRIPOLI&lt;/small&gt;, the capital of Libya, children play on the beach, cafés buzz late into the night and the manager of a beauty parlour reports that laser treatments, hair-removals and nose-jobs are on the rise. “War hasn’t put off custom,” says Kherea Dughman. About 15km (9 miles) away a rebel army is fighting to take the capital. But after eight years of civil war, Libyans have become inured to the rumble of artillery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There have been several attempts to stabilise Libya since the overthrow in 2011 of Muammar Qaddafi, its former dictator. In 2016 the &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt; installed a “government of national accord” (&lt;small&gt;GNA&lt;/small&gt;) in Tripoli. But it is beholden to the militias in the west that back it. Khalifa Haftar, the head of the self-styled Libyan National Army (&lt;small&gt;LNA&lt;/small&gt;), controls the east and much of the south, including Libya’s largest oilfields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Talks arranged by the &lt;small&gt;UN &lt;/small&gt;to broker a peace between them in April were upended by Mr Haftar, who launched a surprise attack on the capital just after the &lt;small&gt;UN &lt;/small&gt;secretary-general had arrived. Mr Haftar has little interest in negotiating a settlement. The 75-year-old former general thinks Libya is not yet ready for democracy and that it needs a strongman—himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Haftar returned from exile in America after Qaddafi’s fall and raised a force of perhaps 20,000 fighters. They would, his supporters repeatedly promised, clear the capital of the chaos of “terrorist militia” rule. His sneak-attack was intended to snatch Tripoli swiftly. But three months on his forces are being pushed back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Militias that had previously fought each other have rallied against Mr Haftar. On June 26th they captured Gharyan, cutting his supply line to the south (see map). That leaves his troops over 1,000km from their main base at al-Rajmah. Whereas the defenders of Tripoli can go home and shower at the end of a day of fighting, Mr Haftar’s troops are in the desert. The tribes backing him are reluctant to send more men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Haftar, though, has powerful friends. Saudi Arabia, Egypt and the United Arab Emirates (&lt;small&gt;UAE&lt;/small&gt;) provide arms, fighter jets and money to pay recruits. They see Mr Haftar as an ally in their counter-revolution against the popular, and often Islamist, uprisings the Arab spring unleashed in 2011. And they view Libya’s oil, territory and ports as strategic assets that they want to keep out of the hands of their regional foes, Turkey and Qatar. With their support, Mr Haftar hopes to battle on just as he did in Benghazi, Libya’s second city. He took it in 2017 after three years of fighting, but only by destroying and depopulating it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkey and Qatar, meanwhile, have sent weapons and armoured trucks to reinforce Tripoli. Both say they are buttressing the forces of democratic and popular change. They have also supported armed groups who share their Islamist ideology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Foreign intervention risks turning a civil war into a regional one. In June Mr Haftar’s men threatened to strike all Turkish vessels in Libyan waters. It detained six Turkish sailors and released them only after Turkey threatened military action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt; Security Council is too divided to restrain the parties. Libya’s former colonial rulers, France and Italy, have backed opposing sides, fuelled by their oil interests. (Total, a French company, has most of its fields in the east; Italy’s oil giant, Eni, is concentrated in the west.) Russia, which favours autocrats across the region, has thrown its support behind Mr Haftar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America, which could be an umpire, acts like a bystander. Since Barack Obama’s presidency, it has opted to “lead from behind”. Donald Trump phoned to congratulate Mr Haftar—a naturalised American citizen—when it seemed his offensive would be successful. America, which had supported calls for a ceasefire in the &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt;, abruptly threatened to veto them. Since Mr Haftar’s offensive has failed Mr Trump’s interest seems to have waned in another of what he once called the Middle East’s “stupid wars”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the conflict, the dinar has stabilised. Oil production is near its post-2011 peak of 1.1m barrels a day and at current prices could earn Libya $27bn this year. In the current fighting both camps are avoiding anything that might damage the oilfields because revenue from them pays the salaries of armed groups on each side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Mr Haftar tries to regain the initiative, however, that could change. Although he controls most of the fields, a &lt;small&gt;UN &lt;/small&gt;embargo on non-government sales prevents him from boosting his own coffers while shrinking those of the government. Previous efforts to sell oil independently were thwarted by America, but Mr Haftar is thought to be mulling trying again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He may also become more destructive. Since losing Gharyan he has stepped up his bombardment of Tripoli. Fighting has already destroyed one airport and threatens a second. On July 3rd an attack killed 44 African migrants in a detention centre on the edge of Tripoli. Power lines and the pipes bringing water are also vulnerable to attack. Electricity is down to nine hours a day. Schoolchildren complain it is too hot to prepare for exams. More than 100,000 people have left the capital’s outlying suburbs for the city centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most people in Tripoli want a government able to collect the rubbish and put an end to the militias’ extortion and turf wars. (“It’s like taming wildcats in a circus,” is how a government official describes governing Tripoli.) Some may have once welcomed the order that Mr Haftar promised to restore. But his bombardment has punctured such hopes. His flamboyant uniforms, his nepotistic promotion of his sons and backing from the former regime’s henchmen stir fears of a second Qaddafi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, the horror goes on. Field hospitals and ambulances ferrying the wounded have come under attack. A nurse camped in a school with her children, after the shelling destroyed her home, begs for relief. “Why don’t they both just go away,” she sobs. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Middle East and Africa&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Siege on the Mediterranean&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 20:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Boris Johnson may reverse Britain’s embrace of sin taxes]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/07/04/boris-johnson-may-reverse-britains-embrace-of-sin-taxes]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BRP003.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;C&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;ONSIDERING THEY&lt;/small&gt; call themselves Conservatives, Britain’s recent leaders have been unusually willing to meddle with individual choices. Plastic straws are to be banned, over concerns about pollution of the oceans. A tax on plastic bags, introduced in 2015, may double under plans currently out for consultation. The Tories have also expanded so-called sin taxes on unhealthy behaviour. Worried about bulging obesity levels, last year the government introduced a tax on sugary drinks, which led manufacturers to change their recipes or raise their prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some would like the nanny state to be stricter still. Jamie Oliver, a celebrity chef, wants to tax milkshakes. Professor Dame Sally Davies, England’s chief medical officer, is due to deliver in September a report that is likely to recommend more taxes on unhealthy foods. The Institute for Public Policy Research, a leftish think-tank, recently called for more food taxes and for sweets, crisps and soft drinks to be sold in plain packets, as cigarettes already are. Some environmentalists support a meat tax.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On July 3rd Boris Johnson, the probable next prime minister, announced as part of his campaign for the Tory leadership that he would take a different approach. He promised no new sin taxes until his government had studied whether existing ones—including long-standing taxes on alcohol and tobacco—work, and whether they disproportionately hurt the poor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Awkwardly, the answer to both questions is probably that they do. Although the Johnson campaign cites a dissenting study, on the whole there is good evidence that sin taxes change people’s behaviour. In the case of alcohol and tobacco, for example, economists tend to find that a 1% increase in prices is associated with a 0.5% decline in sales. But because poor people tend to spend a higher proportion of their income than others on things deemed sinful, such taxes hit them hardest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Johnson’s plans are likely to go down well with the Conservative Party members whose votes he is courting. Health campaigners may be less impressed. On the same day as his announcement, a report by Cancer Research &lt;small&gt;UK&lt;/small&gt; found that obesity caused more cases of cancer than tobacco in Britain. As for targeting the poor, advocates for sin taxes sometimes argue this is in fact an advantage of the policies, because the poor will disproportionately reap the promised health benefits of having their behaviour changed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This ignores their associated loss of personal choice, however. It also misses a point that Mr Johnson understands very well: the thing about sinful behaviour is that it is often pleasurable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Britain&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Boris eyes the nanny&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 20:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OPEC’s predictable deal cannot conceal its long-term difficulties]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/07/04/opecs-predictable-deal-cannot-conceal-its-long-term-difficulties]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_FNP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE MEETING&lt;/small&gt; of the Organisation of Petroleum Exporting Countries (&lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt;) in Vienna on July 1st and 2nd was, in some respects, a snooze. The deal announced by &lt;small&gt;OPEC &lt;/small&gt;and its allies was the continuation of one struck late last year. For at least another nine months, daily production will remain 1.2m barrels below last October’s level. But behind the predictability giant problems loom, for the oil market and for &lt;small&gt;OPEC &lt;/small&gt;itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America and Iran, an &lt;small&gt;OPEC &lt;/small&gt;member, are flirting with war. The decline in Venezuela’s production has steepened since January, when America announced sanctions against &lt;small&gt;PDVSA&lt;/small&gt;, its national oil company. Escalating conflict in Libya could cause production there to plummet as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, oil producers are more concerned about weakening demand than tight supply. The price of Brent crude climbed to $74 a barrel in late April, after President Donald Trump said he would not extend waivers to sanctions on Iranian exports. It then plunged in May as inventories built up, investors fretted about the trade war and government-bond yields tumbled in America and Europe. The announcement on June 29th that America and China would resume trade talks has helped, but a deal is far from certain. Faced with shaky economic indicators, &lt;small&gt;OPEC &lt;/small&gt;is keen to avoid a market awash with oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_FNC350_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But &lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt;’s decision to trim output points to further uncertainties within the alliance. The first is how long it will be willing to continue losing market share to America. In 2014, as American oil flowed freely, &lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt; declined to curb output, hoping that slumping prices would teach gung-ho American oilmen a lesson. The ensuing crash pained petrostates and wildcatters alike. But shale production has roared back—last year America produced more crude than any other country—and &lt;small&gt;OPEC &lt;/small&gt;has become reluctant to let prices dive again. The result is that &lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt;’s share of global production has dipped, from 42.2% in 2016 to 39.2% in March, and America’s has risen, from 10.9% to 14.5% (see chart).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second question is whether Saudi Arabia and Russia will start to feel the pain of production cuts more acutely. Sinking output in Venezuela and Iran has helped &lt;small&gt;OPEC &lt;/small&gt;to keep a lid on supply even as American output has risen. Wood Mackenzie, an energy-research group, estimates that America (excluding Alaska and Hawaii) will pump 1.2m more barrels of crude a day this year than it did in 2018. Iran will pump 1m fewer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That helps explain why, despite cutting production somewhat, Saudi Arabia accounts for almost as much of the global market as it did in 2016. Russia has been even more protected. That year it agreed to work with &lt;small&gt;OPEC &lt;/small&gt;to stabilise the oil price. Its influence in the Middle East has grown and it has helped shape &lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt;’s decisions, big and small. On June 29th Vladimir Putin, Russia’s president, said that he had agreed with Saudi Arabia to extend &lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt;’s production cuts, making the imminent meeting in Vienna seem all but redundant. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russia has given up relatively little in return. In most months its output has exceeded the level it had agreed with &lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt;. (May was a rare—and possibly unintended—exception: an important crude pipeline suffered contamination.) In March its share of the global market was higher than in 2016. “By doing only a little, they got quite a lot,” says Martijn Rats of Morgan Stanley, a bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;OPEC &lt;/small&gt;and Russia look set to continue co-operating. The meeting in Vienna included a charter to formalise &lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt;’s partnerships with non-members. But there is a limit to how much further output in Venezuela and Iran can fall. If oil prices remain low, Saudi Arabia and Russia may face an uncomfortable choice: let prices dip or cut production more steeply, thereby losing market share and propping up American shale. This month’s meeting was straightforward. Future ones may be less so. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Finance and economics&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Making the cut&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 20:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EU leaders’ arduous deal on top jobs may yet fall apart]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/07/04/eu-leaders-arduous-deal-on-top-jobs-may-yet-fall-apart]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_EUP002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;E&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;MMANUEL MACRON&lt;/small&gt; is a lucky man. His rivals and opponents have a habit of doing themselves harm. In the French presidential election in 2017 his main centre-right rival was consumed by a corruption scandal. Earlier this year anti-government &lt;em&gt;gilets jaunes&lt;/em&gt; protesters surged then faded in part because disorganisation and public-relations mistakes took their toll. And this week Mr Macron obtained something close to a dream outcome in the allocation of big European jobs. Once again this was largely thanks to others’ mistakes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After three days of talks the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;’s leaders (minus Theresa May of Brexiting Britain) agreed to nominate Ursula von der Leyen, Germany’s defence minister, to the presidency of the European Commission, the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;’s executive. A moderate Christian Democrat close to Angela Merkel, Mrs von der Leyen shares some of Mr Macron’s federalist inclinations. Also, she did not run in the recent European election campaign as a &lt;em&gt;Spitzenkandidat&lt;/em&gt; or “lead candidate” for the commission job—a convention that the French president wants to kill off. The presidency of the European Central Bank (&lt;small&gt;ECB&lt;/small&gt;) goes to Christine Lagarde, the French head of the &lt;small&gt;IMF &lt;/small&gt;who, like Mr Macron, is on the doveish side of Europe’s economic debates. The presidency of the European Council, the group of &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; heads of government, goes to Charles Michel, Belgium’s liberal prime minister and a Macron ally. The final appointment sees Josep Borrell, a veteran Spanish social democrat, as the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;’s high representative for foreign affairs and security policy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Macron is delighted with the outcome,” observes Mujtaba Rahman of the Eurasia Group, a consultancy. He points out that the result was less Mr Macron’s design than the product of others’ errors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first was made last November, when the European People’s Party (&lt;small&gt;EPP&lt;/small&gt;), the group of centre-right parties, picked Manfred Weber, a Bavarian member of the European Parliament, as its lead candidate. The &lt;small&gt;EPP&lt;/small&gt; came first in the European Parliament elections that took place from May 23rd to 26th, which under the &lt;em&gt;Spitzenkandidat&lt;/em&gt; convention would have made Mr Weber the prime candidate for the commission. But he has no executive experience, little profile outside Brussels and his native Germany and a reputation for making excuses for Hungary’s authoritarian government. Moreover, the &lt;small&gt;EPP&lt;/small&gt; lost seats, along with its traditional partners in the centre-left Socialists and Democrats (&lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;small&gt;D&lt;/small&gt;) group. Mr Weber was too contentious a figure for the newly fragmented parliament to settle on his candidacy, or on a single alternative. Although Mrs Merkel, the &lt;small&gt;EPP&lt;/small&gt;’s most powerful leader, backed her compatriot, other leaders objected to him at a summit on June 20th. Unable to reach a deal, the leaders postponed their talks to June 30th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was Mrs Merkel who made the second mistake. In discussions with Mr Macron and the prime ministers of Spain and the Netherlands, the German chancellor agreed to a compromise whereby Frans Timmermans, the &lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;small&gt;D&lt;/small&gt;’s lead candidate and a Dutch vice-president of the commission, would take the commission presidency, with Mr Weber becoming president of the parliament and a liberal running the council. Mrs Merkel’s colleagues in the &lt;small&gt;EPP&lt;/small&gt;, such as Leo Varadkar of Ireland, objected that the parliament job was too puny a prize for coming first. The leaders of eastern states and Italy, too, dislike Mr Timmermans for his record of tough action against illiberal abuses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The summit on June 30th dragged on into July 1st. By breakfast it was clear that neither Mr Timmermans nor Mr Weber could command the necessary support. Leaders suspended the talks until the following morning, when Mr Macron floated the idea of Mrs von der Leyen. Acceptable to Mrs Merkel, the rest of the &lt;small&gt;EPP&lt;/small&gt;, the easterners and to left-of-centre governments, she was the tolerable candidate exhausted leaders could accept. With a German heading for the commission, Mr Macron could press for a Frenchwoman at the &lt;small&gt;ECB&lt;/small&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the package did not inspire universal approval. Some, especially in the &lt;small&gt;EPP&lt;/small&gt; and &lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;small&gt;D&lt;/small&gt;, complain that Mrs von der Leyen lacks a democratic mandate, having not campaigned as a &lt;em&gt;Spitzenkandidat&lt;/em&gt;. Her struggles to modernise the armed forces cause some to question her competence: “Germany’s weakest minister”, sneered Martin Schulz, a German former president of the European Parliament. Other objections have also bubbled up. All four of the big jobs settled at the summit go to western Europeans at a time of heightened tensions between easterners and westerners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of which makes support for the package in the parliament uncertain. In votes on the parliament’s own presidency on July 3rd &lt;small&gt;MEP&lt;/small&gt;s from the “grand coalition” of moderate pro-&lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; parties—the &lt;small&gt;EPP&lt;/small&gt;, &lt;small&gt;S&amp;amp;D&lt;/small&gt; and liberals—splintered as some social democrats backed the Green candidate and easterners in the &lt;small&gt;EPP&lt;/small&gt; backed a Czech from a more right-wing group. David Sassoli, an Italian social democrat supposedly supported by the grand coalition, won with only 345 of its 442 votes, and no others, meaning that he does not enjoy a majority among the parliament’s 751 members.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That may suggest that Mrs von der Leyen is also not guaranteed the majority she needs to secure the commission presidency. That vote is due to take place between July 15th and 18th. If she fails, leaders will have to return to the drawing board. They might then turn to Margrethe Vestager, the liberal competition commissioner who was a &lt;em&gt;Spitzenkandidat&lt;/em&gt; in all but name and fairly widely acceptable. Otherwise the options are few.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if she does succeed, what sort of a commission president will Mrs von der Leyen make? It is true that after five years of her as defence minister, the German armed forces are still plagued by equipment shortages and technical faults. German opposition parties are holding an investigation into her extensive and expensive use of consultancies. Yet her job is known as a graveyard of careers for good reason—the problems long predate her tenure—and Mrs von der Leyen has done well to survive in it. Multilingual and instinctively Atlanticist, she is respected by &lt;small&gt;NATO&lt;/small&gt; colleagues for having fought for budget increases for Germany’s armed forces and presiding over expanding German military missions in places like Mali and Lithuania. She has recently warned against European complacency about China’s rise and intentions. Addressing &lt;small&gt;MEP&lt;/small&gt;s in Strasbourg on July 3rd she struck a conciliatory tone in comments in German, French and English.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There may have been better candidates for the commission job—for example, Ms Vestager—but there were certainly far inferior ones. Likewise, Ms Lagarde, Mr Michel and Mr Borrell are all competent figures. The Spaniard will be the most heavyweight person to hold the foreign-policy role since its creation in 2009. Europe runs on compromises like this one. It could do worse. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Europe&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;The Leyen’s share&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 20:39:55 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>