<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[The race to become Britain’s next PM]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/31/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-31T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 31st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;

&lt;figure data-infographic- data-infographic-js=&quot;/2019/tory-leadership/js/bundle.js&quot; data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/tory-leadership/css/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/tory-leadership/css/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HERESA MAY&lt;/small&gt; has announced that she will step down as leader of the Conservative Party on June 7th. She will remain as prime minister until her successor is chosen. Nominations for the Tory leadership will close in the week beginning June 10th, followed by several rounds of voting among MPs, a process that will last until the end of the month. The MPs will then send two names to party members who will make the final choice. The result of their vote will be announced before parliament rises for summer. 
&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure data-infographic- &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Betfair Exchange, a gambling website, has been tracking punters’ predictions on the next Tory leader. According to the wisdom of the betting crowd, a handful of candidates stand out. But there is only one clear frontrunner.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure data-infographic- &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adrian Wooldridge, our political editor, assesses the chances of the leading Conservative politicians hoping to take the top job in this short film
&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ychDrZ2QzlE&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Source: Betfair Exchange&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 23:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“When They See Us” is a heartrending portrait of the Central Park Five]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/31/when-they-see-us-is-a-heartrending-portrait-of-the-central-park-five]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_BKP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-31T15:20:50Z&quot;&gt;May 31st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EARLY IN the first episode of “When They See Us”, a detective responding to the news that a jogger has been found beaten and raped at 11pm in New York’s Central Park asks: “What was she &lt;em&gt;doing&lt;/em&gt; there?” The line captures the assumptions that governed white New Yorkers’ behaviour in April 1989, when the city’s murder rate was seven times higher than it is now, and sensible folk did not venture into the park after dark. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By the time the viewer hears that line, they know that Ava DuVernay, who directed the four-part Netflix series, intends to take this story as it was told by the city’s media at the time, and turn it inside out. She starts not with the jogger in the park, but earlier that afternoon, with the boys who will be wrongfully convicted—strolling through Harlem with their families, joking about baseball and school. Viewers see their innocence first, so that they can watch the machinery of a racist justice system destroy it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Films based on true stories often exaggerate the contemporary notoriety of events for dramatic effect. In the Central Park jogger case this is unnecessary: it dominated New York’s public consciousness. With the victim, an investment banker, in an unresponsive coma, police launched a dragnet across Harlem. The press was filled with lurid accounts of “wilding”, described as a Harlem fad in which adolescent boys roamed the park in packs, seeking targets. The city was about to get its first black mayor, crime and the crack epidemic were at their peaks, and the feminist “Take Back the Night” movement was demanding harsher prosecution of sexual assault.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The case was overseen by a flamboyant, press-hungry assistant district attorney, Linda Fairstein (played by Felicity Huffman). Ultimately four black and one Latino boy between the ages of 14 and 16 were convicted of committing the attack together. But there was no physical evidence, the boys’ confessions were inconsistent and black protesters called it a stitch-up. They were right. In 2002 Matias Reyes, a serial rapist serving a life sentence, confessed to the crime, and the convictions were voided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190601_bkp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190601_bkp505.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190601_bkp505.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190601_bkp505.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190601_bkp505.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190601_bkp505.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190601_bkp505.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190601_bkp505.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190601_bkp505.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190601_bkp505.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms DuVernay’s series is a powerful counterpoint to “The Central Park Five”, the documentary released in 2012 by Ken and Sarah Burns. The documentary enjoys an advantage: it can simply raise questions about crucial issues such as what the police did to coerce confessions, or whether the boys were involved in other crimes that night (including attacks on cyclists and another jogger). Ms DuVernay must pick a version, and she sides firmly with the boys. They are depicted as innocents, caught up in an after-dark romp, who had the bad luck to get arrested. The police coach the boys to invent their confessions and beat them when they hesitate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This loyalty to the protagonists is both the strength and the weakness of the series. It allows the film-makers to depict the boys’ family and community lives with tremendous empathy and sophistication. Antron McCray’s relationship with his ex-convict father (portrayed by Michael Kenneth Williams, who played Omar in “The Wire”) is a heartbreaking mix of love and resentment. In prison, Yusef Salaam forms religious bonds with other Muslim prisoners, while the baby-faced Kevin Richardson struggles for guidance. But the commitment to the Five’s perspective leaves the film with unconvincing, cardboard-thin characterisations of its villains: the police and prosecutors. Ms Fairstein’s careerist zeal is never quite sufficient to explain her malevolence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The series is also dead set on eventually granting the Five redemption. This leaves it strangely reluctant to probe the permanent damage their incarceration wrought. It edges in that direction in the final episode, which focuses on Korey Wise, who (unlike the other four) was 16 at the time of his arrest and thus committed to the adult rather than the juvenile system. Ms DuVernay shows how Mr Wise’s isolation and beatings at the hands of other inmates drove him to the edge of madness. But once the real rapist confesses to the crime, Mr Wise is depicted as having overcome adversity. In fact, many who know Mr Wise describe him as wracked by post-traumatic stress, unable to escape his ruined adolescence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Appropriately, the series repeatedly cuts in historical footage of Donald Trump, then a billionaire celebrity with political ambitions, who helped whip up hysteria against the Central Park Five and took out a full-page newspaper advertisement calling for them to receive the death penalty. But that is just one way in which the case echoes into the present. For a viewer who was living in the city during Mr Wise’s trial, the horror of watching “When They See Us” is the intimation that America has transcended none of its history of racist injustice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“When They See Us” is available on Netflix from May 31st&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 22:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“The party is in a tricky position”—China’s trade-war rhetoric]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/31/the-party-is-in-a-tricky-position-chinas-trade-war-rhetoric]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_blm507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-31T11:15:30Z&quot;&gt;May 31st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS PRESIDENT &lt;strong&gt;Donald Trump threatens new tariffs&lt;/strong&gt; on Mexican goods, retaliatory ones between&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/30/the-trade-war-and-finance&quot;&gt; China&lt;/a&gt; and America&lt;/strong&gt; are starting to bite. That puts China’s party leaders—and their hardening nationalist message—in a tricky spot. We examine how &lt;strong&gt;the global &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/28/airlines-would-like-to-see-boeings-737-max-back-in-the-air&quot;&gt;grounding&lt;/a&gt; of Boeing’s 737 MAX&lt;/strong&gt; planes might change air-safety regulation. And a visit to &lt;strong&gt;Venice’s Biennale, where &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/15/in-venice-a-library-of-exile-reflects-on-displacement-and-language&quot;&gt;immigration&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/05/18/climate-change-strikes-the-venice-biennale&quot;&gt;climate change&lt;/a&gt; are taking centre stage&lt;/strong&gt;. Runtime: 22 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/protectionistracket-trade-warrhetoric&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 20:40:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump vows to use tariffs to punish Mexico for migrants]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/31/donald-trump-vows-to-use-tariffs-to-punish-mexico-for-migrants]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_usp506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-31T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 31st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;SEVERAL ADVISERS to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mexico’s secretary for foreign affairs, Marcelo Ebrard&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;, receive phone notifications each time President Donald Trump sends a tweet. Phones—and alarm bells—were surely ringing on May 30th, when Mr Trump delivered his threat &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;to apply a 5% tariff on all imports from Mexico. Unless the Mexican government takes action “to dramatically reduce or eliminate the number of illegal aliens crossing its territory into the United States”, the tariff is to go into effect on June 10th, and to increase each month until October 1st, reaching a maximum of 25%.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;The trigger for the threat was not entirely clear. It could have been Mr Trump’s desire to shift attention away from news coverage of Robert Mueller, who said on May 29th that his investigation could not charge the president with a crime because to do so would have been unconstitutional; or it could have been meant in response to a video the president tweeted the day before, of more than 1,000 “illegal aliens” crossing into the United States. It could even have been data on the recent rise in the number of people apprehended at the border with Mexico: from 51,000 in April 2018 to 109,000 in April this year. (That figure should decline over the coming months, if it follows the usual seasonal pattern.)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mr Trump’s statement accompanying the tweet was angry, strewn with capital letters and exclamation marks. “&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Gang members, smugglers, human traffickers, and illegal drugs and narcotics of all kinds are pouring across the Southern Border and directly into our communities. Thousands of innocent lives are taken every year as a result of this lawless chaos,” the statement reads. “It must end NOW!”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; This kind of fear-mongering has always been central to Mr Trump’s political appeal. At the launch of his presidential campaign, in June 2015, he rode down a gold escalator in Manhattan to denounce Mexicans “bringing drugs...They’re bringing crime...They’re rapists.” That rhetoric has worked well for Mr Trump in the past and may do so again.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Still, this approach may not produce all the results that Mr Trump desires. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Maintaining America’s current levels of border enforcement requires the co-operation of Mexico’s government, which Mr Trump’s bellicosity does not make more likely to be forthcoming. And the &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;“crisis” is in part the result of an increase in families from Central America seeking asylum, not the gang members, smugglers and human-traffickers that Mr Trump rails against. The Mexican administration has already increased its efforts to deport Central Americans from Mexico. Creating a regional economic-development plan to tackle the root causes of Central American migration, as Mexico’s president, Andrés Manuel López Obrador, has said he would like to do, cannot be done quickly or by any one country alone.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;But a reduction in border crossings may not be the primary objective here: if the numbers go down, the president may claim victory and take it as proof that he can push around other countries. If the numbers do not go down, then he gets to keep the hordes of lawless Latinos as an issue in 2020. Most likely, given the president’s inattention to facts, he may claim both of these things to be true at the same time.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;As with most of Mr Trump’s trade policies, the move displays all the finesse of an elephant attempting embroidery. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mexican lobbyists were under the impression that Robert Lighthizer, the United States Trade Representative, had been sidelined. Earlier proposals for tariffs have come with some sort of process or consultation, with Congress or the public. This one set a ten-day deadline and appears to include neither. Mick Mulvaney, the White House chief of staff, explained that this was not a trade dispute but “part of an immigration problem”.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;If the tariffs are enacted, both national economies will suffer. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Two-thirds of American imports from Mexico are between related parties, where one partner owns at least 10% of the other, so any tariff will cause problems along tightly integrated supply chains. A working paper by Alonso de Gortari of Princeton University published on May 27th estimated that America contributed 30% of the value of its imports of manufactured products from Mexico. Carmakers are particularly vulnerable&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;—&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;just as demand in America is softening anyway. The experience of tariffs so far suggests that the heaviest burden will be on American importers. A depreciating peso could soften the blow for them—if they can renegotiate contracts to reap the benefits of the lower currency.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;In response to the threat, the peso fell against the dollar by around 2%, making Mexican exports fractionally more competitive. Futures capturing the expected value of the S&amp;amp;P 500 stockmarket index sank by around 0.9%. Yields on American government debt dipped, too, a sign of investors seeking a haven. The damage could spread beyond the direct economic hit, if it reduces the likelihood of passing the USMCA (the United States-Mexico-Canada Agreement), a trade deal between the three North American heavyweights. Chuck Grassley, an influential Republican senator, called the threat “a misuse of presidential authority”, and has noted that tariffs would “seriously jeopardise” the USMCA’s prospects. Embarrassingly, both Mr Lighthizer and his Mexican counterpart had sent a draft of the deal to their respective legislatures for approval that same day.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;The damage could go further. Mr Trump was supposed to stop threatening Mexico with tariffs once it had agreed to the USMCA. Now he appears to have pocketed that agreement, and to have used the same threat to try squeezing out a separate batch of concessions. All this while the Trump administration attempts to force unrelated concessions from the Chinese, the European Union and the Japanese. They will surely ask: what is the point of conceding to a negotiator who does not keep his word?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 18:40:10 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is America losing its appeal for brainy foreigners?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/30/is-america-losing-its-appeal-for-brainy-foreigners]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_USP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-30T19:38:27Z&quot;&gt;May 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT IS A truism of American politics that the interests of the less educated, like high-school graduates, need better protection. Ahead of next year’s presidential race, President Donald Trump and many would-be Democratic candidates talk up the concerns of blue-collar, industrial workers. Joe Biden, the front-runner to take on Mr Trump, recently launched his campaign from a union hall in Pittsburgh. Mr Trump’s anti-trade policies, his vow to restore American manufacturing strength, and his rallies in industrial cities of the Midwest, suggest prosperity depends most on creating more jobs for the lower skilled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet America—like every advanced economy—increasingly needs to attract the most highly educated talent possible. The high-skilled, who tend to congregate with other high-skilled people, usually in cities and universities, are more likely to be wealth creators, in finance or creative industries and well-placed to exploit new technology. Entrepreneurs, university graduates and others with demonstrable talent are in high demand. How a country attracts and keeps the highest-skilled migrants, therefore, is a measure of its likely future strength. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Historically, America has far exceeded rival countries in appealing to brainy foreigners and putting them to work, for example in how it gets foreigners into employment after they graduate from its universities. But under Mr Trump that crown is slipping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The OECD, a think-tank for mostly rich countries, this week spelled out America’s problem. In pure terms of attractiveness to the high-skilled around the world, the authors of a new report say that America still ranks as the most popular place. Across seven indicators the think-tank studied for its measure of “talent attractiveness”--including unemployment levels, tax rates, gender equality, how easy it is for the family of a talented individual to settle and more—America still stands out as the most tempting destination for the brainy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But on a second set of indicators the country fares worse. These include whether an applicant is likely to be denied a visa, how tight quotas are for the highly skilled, and the time and hassle involved in getting an application processed. Count in those considerations and America’s appeal to the most talented international workers falls sharply. The OECD ranks America behind several other rich countries, including Australia, Sweden, Switzerland, New Zealand, Canada and Ireland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such rankings can be disputed, and the rush of people who would like to study and work in America is not going to dry up. But the gush might slow. The numbers of international students present in America have already been declining in the past couple of years, for example. The Immigration and Customs Enforcement department counted a 2.7% fall in student numbers this spring (it found just under 1.2m foreign students in the country in March). It is likely that Mr Trump’s talk of “America First”, his hostility towards Muslims, plus his threats to tighten visas that are popular with Indian applicants, do little to make America a more appealing place for foreign talent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump’s proposal early in May to rejig America’s immigration system to focus it more on letting in skilled workers who can meet the needs of the economy—and less on family reunification or the acceptance of refugees—might address some of the concerns raised by the OECD. But that immigration plan is unlikely to become law. It looks unfeasible, given opposition to it from both Democrats in Congress (because it does nothing to accommodate DREAMERS, migrants who came to America as children illegally and have been allowed to stay) and some conservative Republicans (because it isn&amp;#x27;t harsh enough, for example, towards refugees).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America has long prospered by attracting foreign talent. But any sign that the country is becoming less attractive to skilled foreigners, as the OECD suggests, could mean that America will pay a price down the road.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 10:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Britain&#x27;s constitutional time-bomb, extreme weather in the Midwest and 30 years since Tiananmen]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/30/britains-constitutional-time-bomb-extreme-weather-in-the-midwest-and-30-years-since-tiananmen]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-30T16:50:49Z&quot;&gt;May 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A SELECTION of three essential articles read aloud from the latest issue of The Economist. This week, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/30/britains-constitutional-time-bomb&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Britain’s constitutional time-bomb&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Brexit is already a political crisis—sooner or later it will become a constitutional one too. Also, how &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/06/01/floods-and-storms-are-altering-american-attitudes-to-climate-change&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;floods and storms in the Midwest&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; are altering American attitudes to climate change (9:24). And, 30 years after the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/china/2019/06/01/many-chinese-know-little-about-the-bloodshed-in-beijing-30-years-ago&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tiananmen Square massacre&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, many Chinese know little about the bloodshed (18:07). Runtime: 26 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-may30th2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:40:47 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why England start the Cricket World Cup as favourites]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/05/30/why-england-start-the-cricket-world-cup-as-favourites]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_BLP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-30T11:32:50Z&quot;&gt;May 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE GRASS has been cut, the squares prepared. The advertising posters are up and 95% of the 800,000 tickets have been sold. The 12th Cricket World Cup begins in England this week and will conclude, somewhat laboriously, in a final on July 14th. Each of the ten teams will play each other in a round-robin league, with the top four in the table qualifying for the semi-finals. As usual, the matches are one-day internationals (ODIs), in which each team gets 50 overs (or 300 balls) with the bat—longer than the T20 format, which gives each side 20 overs, but shorter than Test matches, which last five days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of fixtures and the increasingly aggressive batting tactics used by most teams makes it likely that more international runs will be scored in the next month than in any that came before. But another historic milestone also looms on the horizon. The English, who invented the game but have never won the World Cup, might finally break that duck. Bookmakers reckon they are the favourites, with roughly a 30% chance of victory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For most of the tournament’s 44-year history, the “Poms” (as they are called by their Australian tormentors, who have won it five times) have been useless. They last reached a final in 1992. At the previous tournament in 2015, the only teams they managed to beat were lowly Scotland and Afghanistan. They were eliminated at the earliest opportunity. Their defeat by hosts New Zealand was one of the most comprehensive sporting losses imaginable, with the Kiwis surpassing England’s paltry 123 runs in just 12 overs and two balls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But during the past four years England have focused relentlessly on avenging themselves at the tournament. Shortly after the debacle in 2015, the England and Wales Cricket Board (ECB) appointed Trevor Bayliss, a head coach who specialises in cricket’s short formats. Mr Bayliss threw out the core of the old squad and rebuilt the team in the image of Eoin Morgan, its Irish-born captain and one of its most aggressive batsmen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Bayliss’s changes have been twofold. The first has been to pick hard hitters who were previously considered too inconsistent. At the top of the order are Jonny Bairstow and Jason Roy, who drifted around the edges of the England set-up before 2015, but have now matured into the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://stats.espncricinfo.com/ci/engine/stats/index.html?class=2;filter=advanced;orderby=fow_run_rate;partnership_wicketmax1=1;partnership_wicketval1=partnership_wicket;qualmin1=10;qualval1=fow_innings;template=results;type=fow&quot;&gt;fastest-scoring opening pair in ODI history&lt;/a&gt;. Supporting them in the middle order is Ben Stokes, a brawny all-rounder who was omitted from the last World Cup squad after a poor run of form with the bat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The coach’s second change has been to encourage the batsmen who survived his cull in 2015 to swing even harder for the boundary rope (see chart, above). Alongside Mr Morgan, the core of the side is now occupied by Jos Buttler, one of cricket’s most innovative hitters, and Joe Root, the Test captain, who offers something of a cooler head. In the last four years, all three have scored their runs at least 10% more quickly (on a per-ball basis) than they did in the previous four years. Where England once considered a total of 300 runs a good score, the team now looks for 350 or more. It was a measure of how eagerly the players bought into Mr Bayliss’s philosophy that in June 2015, just two months after the World Cup, they beat New Zealand 3-2 in an ODI series, registering scores of 408, 365 and 350.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the start of this World Cup, England hold the number-one ranking in ODI cricket and the world record for the highest score (481 against Australia last year). In 2019 so far they have scored boundaries—six runs if the ball is hit over the rope without bouncing, four runs if it touches the turf—40% more frequently than the average ODI team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of which raises the question: why doesn’t every team wield the willow so aggressively? The answer is that doing so carries considerable risk, because hitting with reckless abandon increases the chance that a shot will be caught by a fielder, resulting in a wicket. England have enough capable sloggers in the team, including several bowlers, to get away with this perilous strategy most of the time. But occasionally it backfires spectacularly, with every single batsman getting himself out. In the last year England have endured the two biggest defeats in their history. In October their total of 132 runs was 219 less than Sri Lanka managed in their innings, and in March the West Indies passed England’s score of 113 in just 12 overs and one ball. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even more worrying for English fans is a dearth of top-notch bowlers. Whereas the country has five of the world’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.icc-cricket.com/rankings/mens/player-rankings/odi/batting&quot;&gt;20 highest-rated ODI players with the bat&lt;/a&gt;, it only has two of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.icc-cricket.com/rankings/mens/player-rankings/odi/bowling&quot;&gt;top 20 with the ball&lt;/a&gt;: Chris Woakes and Adil Rashid. But although they both take a lot of wickets they also give away lots of runs. In fact, England’s bowlers are so leaky that the ECB has relaxed the eligibility criteria in order for Mr Bayliss to select Jofra Archer, a Barbadian who has a British passport but has only lived in the country for three years. He bowls more quickly than any of England’s other options, and has honed his skills by playing in T20 leagues around the world. The hosts will need him to translate that success to ODIs if they are to win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The real sultans of swing and spin are India. The team is synonymous with Virat Kohli, its captain and the world’s highest-rated batsman. But they are most dangerous with the ball in hand, since the squad contains three of the eight best bowlers at the competition: Jasprit Bumrah, a seamer with an unusual number of tricky variations and the courage to use them, and Kuldeep Yadav and Yuzvendra Chahal, two wrist-spinners who move the ball unpredictably off the pitch. The flat wickets that the hosts have prepared might make the World Cup a run-fest, with some commentators expecting the first ever score of 500. But India will do better than most in restraining their opponents’ hitting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia offer the other main threat to England’s hopes. The defending champions have endured a dismal couple of years, exacerbated by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/game-theory/2018/03/28/a-ball-tampering-row-consumes-australia&quot;&gt;the suspension&lt;/a&gt; of former captain Steve Smith and his deputy, David Warner. The pair were caught rubbing the ball with sandpaper to make it swing more in the air, an offence that is beyond the pale in cricket, but have now served their bans. They were roundly booed by English spectators in a warm-up game against the hosts on May 25th, an unusual occurrence in the sport—and promptly scored 159 runs between them while guiding their team to victory. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps England will be able to pile 400-odd runs on their old rivals later this month, when it really counts. But there would be no sensation more familiar for cricket fans than the Poms self-destructing and the Aussies spoiling the party.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:40:46 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mitch McConnell says he would confirm a Supreme Court nominee in 2020]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/30/mitch-mcconnell-says-he-would-confirm-a-supreme-court-nominee-in-2020]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_USP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-30T10:14:10Z&quot;&gt;May 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHEN ANTONIN SCALIA died suddenly in 2016, Mitch McConnell, the Senate majority leader, wasted no time staking out the Republican position on the conservative jurist’s successor. Hours after news broke of Mr Scalia’s demise, Mr McConnell declared that “the American people should have a voice in the selection of their next Supreme Court justice”. With nearly nine months to go before the presidential election, he told America that his legislative chamber would take no action on any Supreme Court nominee named by Barack Obama. “This vacancy”, he announced, articulating a broad principle, “should not be filled until we have a new president.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was an aggressive move. The constitution gives presidents the power to nominate federal judges, including Supreme Court justices, and the Senate’s “advice and consent” are necessary before they take their seats. But Mr McConnell took the unprecedented step of building a blockade around Scalia’s seat rather than give a hearing to Merrick Garland, the moderate chief judge of the District of Columbia Circuit Court of Appeals nominated by Mr Obama. After stonewalling Judge Garland for the remaining 11 months of Mr Obama’s term, the Republican Senate avidly took up Donald Trump’s nominee, the highly conservative Neil Gorsuch. He was confirmed on April 7, 2017.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;McConnell’s gambit proved to be a thorough success: instead of a Democratic president replacing one of the court’s most right-wing justices with a left-leaning judge, Mr Scalia’s seat was filled with a 49-year-old originalist who would safeguard the conservative majority. But would the new principle of demurring on Supreme Court nominations in presidential election years stick? The former chair of the Senate Judiciary Committee, Iowa Republican Charles Grassley, said in 2018 that he would honour the 2016 rule and refuse to preside over a Supreme Court confirmation hearing were the shoe to be on the other foot in 2020. &amp;quot;If I’m chairman, they won’t take it up&amp;quot;, Mr Grassley said, “because I pledged that in 2016”. Mr Grassley’s replacement as chair, Lindsey Graham, has echoed this promise. “If an opening comes in the last year of President Trump’s term and the primary process has started”, Mr Graham said in 2018, “we’ll wait until the next election”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the past, Mr McConnell has hedged when asked if he agrees with the current and former Judiciary Committee chairs. But on May 28th, at a talk to the Chamber of Commerce in Paducah, Kentucky, his home state, the senator made his position clear. “If a Supreme Court justice dies next year, what would you do?”, he was asked. Mr McConnell took a long sip of iced tea and smiled: “oh, we’d fill it”, he said, to laughter. As important as questions of policy are, he said, “what can&amp;#x27;t be undone is a lifetime appointment to a young man or woman who believes in the quaint notion that the job of a judge is to follow the law. That’s the most important thing we’ve done for the country.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chuck Schumer, the Democratic minority leader in the Senate, took to Twitter to accuse the majority leader of hypocrisy. In response, Mr McConnell now says his no-hearing rule applies only when the Senate and White House are controlled by different parties. However he tries to justify the change of policy, Mr McConnell seems unfazed by charges of inconsistency. If a Supreme Court vacancy opens up before the 2020 election, Mr McConnell will promptly fill it. Principle seems to count for little. But votes count, and he has 53 to the Democrats’ 47.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:40:45 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How the European elections will shake up domestic politics]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/01/how-the-european-elections-will-shake-up-domestic-politics]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_eud002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;T WILL TAKE&lt;/small&gt; weeks for the results of the European elections to take effect; the parliament does not convene until July. But in some countries events moved swiftly. Within days of the vote a chancellor was forced from office, a snap election called, a de facto leader sent to prison and some party chiefs left fighting to survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ruling Christian Democratic Union (&lt;small&gt;CDU&lt;/small&gt;) and its Bavarian ally took first place in &lt;strong&gt;Germany&lt;/strong&gt;, but with a record low score of 29%. The Greens surged into second place with over 20% of the vote. A poor national result for the far-right Alternative for Germany masked a strong showing in the country’s east, where the party came first in two of three states that will hold elections in the autumn. The biggest losers were the Social Democrats (&lt;small&gt;SPD&lt;/small&gt;), the &lt;small&gt;CDU&lt;/small&gt;’s coalition partner, who slumped to 16% and lost a separate election in the city-state of Bremen for the first time in over 70 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Germany’s coalition is tattered but holding, for now. Yet a febrile mood has taken hold inside the ruling parties. Andrea Nahles, the embattled &lt;small&gt;SPD&lt;/small&gt; chairwoman, has decided to flush out any internal foes by putting her leadership of the parliamentary group up for early election. But Annegret Kramp-Karrenbauer, leader of the &lt;small&gt;CDU&lt;/small&gt;, managed to distract from the &lt;small&gt;SPD&lt;/small&gt;’s woes by appearing to suggest that YouTube commentators should be subject to regulation during election campaigns, exposing her to charges (which she denied) of opposing free speech. Inside the &lt;small&gt;CDU&lt;/small&gt; some wonder if the gaffe-prone Ms Kramp-Karrenbauer has what it takes to succeed Angela Merkel, her mentor, as chancellor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere it was a mixed night for governing parties. The results in &lt;strong&gt;Italy &lt;/strong&gt;reversed the roles of junior and senior partner in western Europe’s only populist government. Matteo Salvini’s nationalist Northern League doubled its tally from last year’s general election to 34% of the vote; the anti-establishment Five Star Movement (&lt;small&gt;M&lt;/small&gt;5&lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt;) crashed from 32% to 17%. The opposition centre-left Democratic Party beat expectations to take second, with 23%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The League’s triumph could tempt Mr Salvini, the deputy prime minister, to force an election and dump the &lt;small&gt;M&lt;/small&gt;5&lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt; in favour of a coalition with other right-wing parties. But after the result he said that his loyalty to the existing arrangement had “never been in question”. The bigger doubts are over the &lt;small&gt;M&lt;/small&gt;5&lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt;. With the whip firmly in his hand, Mr Salvini has called for measures at which the &lt;small&gt;M&lt;/small&gt;5&lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt; has balked, including immigration controls, infrastructure schemes and more autonomy for Italy’s rich north. Alarmingly for Brussels, the League leader also urged a tax-cutting stimulus. Italy already risks breaching euro-area budget-deficit limits, and the European Commission is reportedly preparing to begin disciplinary proceedings. But a defiant Mr Salvini said he had been given “a mandate calmly to revisit old and outdated parameters”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;strong&gt;Austria&lt;/strong&gt; the election provided only brief respite for Sebastian Kurz, the young head of the ruling conservative People’s Party (&lt;small&gt;öVP&lt;/small&gt;), amid a scandal that has shattered his government. On May 18th Mr Kurz ejected his coalition partner, the far-right Freedom Party, after a tape from 2017 surfaced showing its leader, Heinz-Christian Strache, promising government contracts to a woman he believed was related to a Russian oligarch. Perhaps benefiting from disillusionment with Mr Strache’s party, the &lt;small&gt;öVP&lt;/small&gt; went on to win a record 35% of the vote. But one day later Mr Kurz’s government was toppled in a confidence vote. A caretaker government will take office before elections in September, in which Mr Kurz will hope to resume where he left off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;Not as bad as it seemed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emmanuel Macron, the &lt;strong&gt;French &lt;/strong&gt;president, will have been disappointed to lose to Marine Le Pen’s National Rally (formerly the National Front), which took 23% of the vote. Yet the outcome was far from devastating. Despite 28 weeks of &lt;em &gt;gilets jaunes &lt;/em&gt;(yellow jackets) protests, and Ms Le Pen’s efforts to turn the election into a referendum on Mr Macron, she ended up with a slightly lower score than in 2014. Less than a percentage point separated the two lists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps most importantly, the result confirmed the upending of politics that Mr Macron brought about when he seized the presidency in 2017 with a new party, En Marche. The mainstream parties on the left (Socialists) and right (Republicans) together scored less than 15%. The only impressive gains came from the Greens, who took 13%. Mr Macron will now seek to reboot his presidency. He promises that policymaking will become more “human”, but also to stick to reform plans for pensions, unemployment benefits and the public sector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nationalists struggled in the &lt;strong&gt;Nordics&lt;/strong&gt;, especially Sweden and Denmark, against socialists and liberals. In the &lt;strong&gt;Netherlands &lt;/strong&gt;the Labour Party secured a surprise win on the back of an energetic campaign by Frans Timmermans, a candidate to run the European Commission. But hard-right Flemish separatists did well in a general election in &lt;strong&gt;Belgium&lt;/strong&gt;, held on the same day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;strong&gt;Poland&lt;/strong&gt; the ruling populist Law and Justice (&lt;small&gt;P&lt;/small&gt;i&lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt;) party won 45% of the vote, putting it in good stead to win a general election due in the autumn. The European Coalition, an ad hoc group of anti-&lt;small&gt;P&lt;/small&gt;i&lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt; parties led by the centrist Civic Platform (&lt;small&gt;PO&lt;/small&gt;), will struggle to remain united after taking a disappointing 38%. With other parties in trouble, the &lt;small&gt;P&lt;/small&gt;i&lt;small&gt;S-PO&lt;/small&gt; rivalry will continue to dominate Polish politics. But &lt;small&gt;P&lt;/small&gt;i&lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt;, under its leader Jaroslaw Kaczynski, is setting the agenda with generous handouts and popular slogans. &lt;small&gt;PO&lt;/small&gt; and others are struggling to find a coherent pitch to voters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a dreadful election for Liviu Dragnea, head of &lt;strong&gt;Romania&lt;/strong&gt;’s ruling Social Democrats (&lt;small&gt;PSD&lt;/small&gt;). Voters at home and abroad turned out in droves against a government widely perceived as corrupt. The &lt;small&gt;PSD&lt;/small&gt; took just 23% of the vote, and 80% of Romanians backed a referendum opposing the government’s judicial reforms. A day after this drubbing Mr Dragnea, the architect of laws designed to reduce penalties for corruption that sparked huge protests, was handed a three-and-a-half-year prison sentence for abuse of office. With Mr Dragnea’s career surely over, the opposition will now seek to turf his party from office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Centrists enjoyed modest success elsewhere in central Europe. In &lt;strong&gt;Slovakia&lt;/strong&gt; a coalition backed by Zuzana Caputova, a liberal who won March’s presidential election, came first. Viktor Orban’s Fidesz won half the vote in &lt;strong&gt;Hungary&lt;/strong&gt;, though two small opposition parties did better than expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond &lt;small&gt;MEP&lt;/small&gt;s, &lt;strong&gt;Spaniards &lt;/strong&gt;also chose 12 regional governments and 8,131 mayors. A month after winning a general election, Pedro Sánchez’s Socialists took 33% of the vote in the European election, confirming them as comfortably the largest party. The results were also a relief for Pablo Casado, the new leader of the conservative People’s Party (&lt;small&gt;PP&lt;/small&gt;). After a drubbing in the general election Mr Casado tacked towards the centre, winning 20% and hanging on to Madrid’s regional government. Other parties struggled. Ciudadanos, a centre-right outfit, slid to 12%. The far left and right faded. The two wings of the Catalan separatist movement secured 49% of the vote in the region. But legal troubles may prevent their two &lt;small&gt;MEP&lt;/small&gt;s from taking up their seats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Sánchez still needs to build a parliamentary majority. Albert Rivera, Ciudadanos’s leader, will face pressure to stop his veto of deals with the Socialists in protest at their conciliatory approach to the Catalan problem. Weeks of haggling lie ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;The next to go?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alexis Tsipras, &lt;strong&gt;Greece&lt;/strong&gt;’s prime minister, called a snap election for July after his left-wing Syriza party suffered a crushing defeat at the hands of the centre-right New Democracy (&lt;small&gt;ND&lt;/small&gt;). Nationalist voters punished Syriza for Mr Tsipras’s biggest achievement: resolving a 28-year dispute over the name of Greece’s northern neighbour, now known as North Macedonia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;ND&lt;/small&gt; looks set to win the general election. That will reassure other euro-zone governments worried about Greece sticking to its post-bail-out reform plan, after Syriza embarked on a burst of pre-election spending. But Kyriakos Mitsotakis, &lt;small&gt;ND&lt;/small&gt;’s leader, may struggle to form a coalition. And Mr Tsipras is unlikely to go into docile opposition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Europe&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Winners and losers&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 21:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Papua New Guinea’s prime minister has resigned]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/01/papua-new-guineas-prime-minister-has-resigned]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_asp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;P&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;OLITICAL TRANSITIONS&lt;/small&gt; are rarely plain sailing in Papua New Guinea (&lt;small&gt;PNG&lt;/small&gt;). The country’s prime ministers like to cling to office regardless of mass desertions of their political allies to their opponents’ side. Its parliamentary speakers defy the rules to keep their jobs. Governments sometimes put pressure on the judiciary and office of the governor-general to help them stay in power. So it was in 2011 during the political turmoil that eventually resulted in Peter O’Neill taking over as &lt;small&gt;PNG&lt;/small&gt;’s prime minister. And so it has been again recently, as he has fought to keep his job. Finally, on May 29th, he tendered his resignation to avoid the humiliation of defeat in an impending vote of no-confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While in office Mr O’Neill presided over a boom in the export of minerals. A $19bn project, launched in 2014, involved the extraction of liquid natural gas in the Southern Highlands, a province. It is the biggest ever private-sector investment in &lt;small&gt;PNG&lt;/small&gt;. But Mr O’Neill’s opponents say it has brought little benefit to local people. Paul Flanagan, a former treasury official in &lt;small&gt;PNG&lt;/small&gt;, says the country’s living standards have been falling in the past five years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A no-confidence motion against Mr O’Neill was originally due to take place in February. But he avoided it by declaring a three-month suspension of parliament. In April discontent grew over another natural-gas deal, worth $13bn, with ExxonMobil, Total and Oil Search, a local firm in which the government has a big stake. Some politicians alleged that its terms were too opaque, and appeared to favour the foreign companies. Some of Mr O’Neill’s cabinet colleagues agreed. First the finance minister, James Marape, resigned. Others soon followed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On May 7th Mr O’Neill suspended parliament for another three weeks. When it reconvened it became clear that he could no longer stem the tide. By resigning before the no-confidence motion, Mr O’Neill allowed ministers and pro-government legislators to regroup behind Mr Marape as his replacement. Mr Marape won the resulting election by 101 votes to eight. He is unlikely to push for big changes in policy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia may have reason to miss Mr O’Neill. He won much favour there for accepting unwanted seekers of asylum in Australia, many of them from war-afflicted regions, on a remote island. Other countries will wonder how the leadership change in &lt;small&gt;PNG&lt;/small&gt; will affect their interests. Both China and America have been trying to court favour there to strengthen their influence in a region of strategic importance. They have been pouring money into infrastructure. America has pledged to help rebuild a mothballed naval base.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Mr O’Neill’s departure will be little mourned at home. He came to power in 2011 pledging to fight corruption. There has been little progress. His remote, mountainous country remains mired in poverty. Nearly 90% of its 8m citizens live in rural areas. Many of them are subsistence farmers with negligible access to state services. His successor faces a colossal challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Asia&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;A departure unmourned&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 21:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>