<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Greater access to abortion may have reduced America’s crime rate]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/27/greater-access-to-abortion-may-have-reduced-americas-crime-rate]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_woc138.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-27T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 27th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ANTI-ABORTION POLICIES are on the rise in America. Influenced mainly by objections from religious conservatives, legislators in states such as Georgia, Ohio and Alabama have passed new laws limiting the practice. In some instances, the new regulations go so far as to ban abortions even in cases of rape or incest—a measure supported by just 11% of voters, according to Morning Consult, a pollster. Restricting access to abortions means that more parents who don’t want to raise children would be forced to do so. Recent research suggests this could reverse decades of progress made on curbing crime in America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a paper published in 2001, the economists John Donahue and Steven Levitt credited the legalisation of abortion across America with much of the subsequent reduction in crime in the country. They argued that violent crime in states where abortion had been banned before 1973 was 15-25% rarer in 1997 than it would have been had abortion remained illegal. The study was politically explosive, and widely criticised. Many sceptical scholars sought to poke holes in its methods, including one group who discovered an “inadvertent but serious computer programming error” (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2005/12/01/oops-onomics&quot;&gt;see article&lt;/a&gt;) underlying its findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly two decades later, Messrs Donahue and Levitt have returned to the subject, and present new evidence that bolsters their original claim. In a new working paper circulated by the National Bureau of Economic Research, they attribute a whopping 45 percentage points of the total 50% decline in crime since 1990 to legal abortion. Their primary evidence is that crime fell much faster in states where more abortions were performed than it did in those where the procedure was rarer. In the early 1990s violent crime was about 50% more common in states with relatively high abortion levels than it was in those where abortion was infrequent. By 2014, crime rates in the two groups of states had converged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors argue that this statistical association reflects an underlying causal relationship. Armed with a cache of annual state-level data on abortions, crime rates and other factors—including economic conditions, welfare payments, access to firearms and alcohol consumption—they seek to isolate the impact of abortion on violent crime, after controlling for other variables that also affect crime rates. With all other factors held constant, they find that an increase in the abortion rate of 100 per 100,000 births leads to a 10-20% reduction in crime. Past studies have also shown that children born to women who wanted an abortion but did not receive one were much more likely to become criminals and had poorer life prospects than those who were born to parents ready and willing to raise them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 05:41:09 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The great jobs boom]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/28/the-great-jobs-boom]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/jobsboom.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-28T19:00:21Z&quot;&gt;May 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The received wisdom is that work is becoming low-paid and precarious, with jobs lost to automation and the gig economy. The data say otherwise. What does the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/23/the-rich-world-is-enjoying-an-unprecedented-jobs-boom&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;jobs boom in the rich world&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; mean for the global economy? Also, will &lt;strong&gt;Alibaba’s plans to list in Hong Kong&lt;/strong&gt; start a corporate shift away from Wall Street? And, &lt;strong&gt;the role of clearing houses&lt;/strong&gt; in averting financial crises. Philip Coggan hosts. Runtime: 20 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-justthejob&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 02:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why seaplanes are so dangerous]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/gulliver/2019/05/28/why-seaplanes-are-so-dangerous]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_BLP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-28T15:51:59Z&quot;&gt;May 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;ON MAY 13TH the pilot of a seaplane flying over Alaska steered to give a better view of a waterfall, just as he had done on many flights before. This time, he saw a flash on his left—and crashed into another plane. Both aircraft plunged into the sea, killing six people. The following week another seaplane crashed in Alaska with two more fatalities. America’s National Transportation Safety Board (NTSB), the government agency that is investigating the accidents, has warned that seaplanes, which are able to take off and land on water, may no longer be a safe form of transport. It has asked the Federal Aviation Administration, a regulator, to upgrade its rules about seaplanes, which currently fall far short of safety regulations for other commercial aircraft.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Seaplanes used to be the main form of air transport before the second world war, during which America and Europe were carpeted with concrete runways suitable for large passenger jets for military reasons. But it is not just weaker regulation that makes these sorts of planes dangerous today. The lack of a runway on solid ground is also a problem—one of the reasons they fell out of favour seven decades ago. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;The most exhaustive study of seaplane accidents on water, published by the Canadian government in 1994, found that over two-thirds of fatalities were caused by drowning, rather than the crash impact itself. As the report noted, “had these accidents occurred on land, a large percentage of them might have been non-fatal.” This is because it is difficult to safety evacuate a seaplane on water. The report found that only 8% percent of occupants of these planes were able to escape easily, compared to 26% that escaped with difficulty. Nearly half did not escape at all. Comparisons with accidents involving land-based aircraft are particularly stark. The same report found that for this type of plane, only 0.2% of nose-over or nose-down accidents on take-off or landing were fatal, compared to 10% for seaplanes.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;There are several reasons for this. Seaplanes often flip upside during a crash landing, something which is relatively rare on land. Passengers who are scared of jumping in the water can block escape routes. For those that do escape, help takes longer to organise and arrive than on land. And icy water, which can cause hypothermia, can kill otherwise unharmed passengers. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Pressure to fly these aircraft in less than ideal weather is also a problem. Float planes, as they are also called, are often chartered by cruise lines, particularly in Alaska, as a quick way to give passengers a tour of the landscape. But cruise lines want to ensure these flights start and end on time so their passengers do not delay the ship setting sail. As a result, the NTSB has found that some seaplane pilots feel pressured by tight cruise-ship schedules to carry out excursions even when conditions are dangerous. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;But a regulatory crackdown on seaplanes looks likely to run into political resistance in America. Alaska is particularly reliant on seaplanes. Most of the American state is inaccessible by road and the tourism industry there is heavily reliant on seaplanes to get visitors around. Alaskans are also six times more likely than the average American to own a plane. Seaplanes are likely to be around for some time yet. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 02:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Airlines would like to see Boeing’s 737 MAX back in the air]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/28/airlines-would-like-to-see-boeings-737-max-back-in-the-air]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_woc124.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-28T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A YEAR AGO at Farnborough Air Show, Dennis Muilenburg, boss of Boeing, beamed as orders for its new 737 MAX jetliner rolled in. At next month’s Paris Air Show he will be less upbeat. In March regulators around the world grounded the plane, after two of them crashed within five months, killing 346 people. On May 23rd aviation regulators were due to convene in Dallas to review Boeing’s application to unground the MAX, now that it says it has fixed the software thought to have contributed to the accidents. Mr Muilenburg says he is “confident” that the updated plane will be “one of the safest aeroplanes ever to fly”. On May 22nd America’s Federal Aviation Administration suggested it could be a while before it is back in the air. All told, airlines have ordered around 5,000 maxes. This week Ryanair, which awaits 135 of them, said it will have to cut 1m seats from this year’s schedules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 02:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A big conviction shows Romania&#x27;s war on corruption is back on track]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/28/a-big-conviction-shows-romanias-war-on-corruption-is-back-on-track]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_eup501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-28T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE WAR against corruption in Romania has seen its ups and downs since the country joined the European Union, but on May 27th the rule of law won a big battle. Liviu Dragnea, leader of the governing Social Democratic Party (PSD), was sent to prison for three and a half years, after an appeals court upheld his conviction for keeping two party workers in fictitious jobs on the state’s payroll. His downfall will touch off a scramble for power. More important, it is a victory for elements of Romania’s judiciary that are fighting to clean up the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The conviction is the latest win for Romania’s National Anti-Corruption Directorate (DNA), an independent prosecutor’s office that has put thousands of officials and businessmen in jail. The DNA has dealt with Mr Dragnea before: in 2015 it convicted him of electoral fraud, a felony that barred him from serving as prime minister. Yet after the PSD and its coalition partners, the National Liberals (PNL), took office in December 2016, he became, in effect, the country’s most powerful politician. As head of the PSD and president of the legislature, he turned the full energy of the government towards keeping himself out of prison.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2017 the government tried to pass laws letting corrupt lawmakers off the hook by emergency decree, but backed down after huge street protests. It then turned to passing the measures piecemeal. Last year the Justice Ministry set up a unit to bring charges against prosecutors who “abused” their power, a clear attempt to intimidate the DNA. The ministry also fired Laura Codruta Kovesi, the agency’s hard-driving director.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The deteriorating situation led the European Commission to send Romania a warning. Things have been especially embarrassing since Romania currently holds the EU’s rotating presidency. But it also prompted Klaus Iohannis, Romania’s president and a good-government type, to launch a referendum asking voters whether they approved of weakening anti-corruption measures. On May 26th, the same day that most of Europe was voting for the new EU parliament, 80% of Romanian voters said no. They also dealt the PSD a huge defeat in the election, giving it just 23% of the vote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many wondered whether the court’s abrupt announcement of a verdict had something to do with the PSD’s defeat. “The people spoke, and then the judges rediscovered their courage,” said Cristian Ghinea, a newly elected MEP for the Save Romania Union (USR), an anti-corruption party. The USR and other opposition parties are readying a motion to topple the government. But Radu Magdin, a political consultant, said the coalition would probably stick together and defeat the measure out of fear that early elections would favour the opposition. The PSD, meanwhile, will try to purge officials tied to Mr Dragnea, said Oana Popescu, head of GlobalFocus, a think tank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The party will struggle to find a new leader. “The system was very personalised, like [under] the Ottomans—everything was about Dragnea. It is in collapse now. No one knows who is in charge,” said Mr Ghinea. Viorica Dancila, the prime minister, is seen as weak. Other party big-wigs, such as the mayor of Bucharest, Gabriela Firea, says she does not even want to lead the party.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many observers had worried that Romania was losing its war on corruption and going the way of Viktor Orban’s Hungary. Mr Dragnea’s sentencing has given them renewed hope. “The checks and balances in Romania worked, unlike in Hungary,” said Laura Stefan, an expert on rule-of-law issues at the Expert Forum think-tank in Bucharest. “Dragnea was not able to pass amendments to the criminal code, and he failed at the court. It shows there are limits to what you can do, even if you are the most powerful person in Romania.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 02:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The National return with a magnificent—and still melancholic—new album]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/28/the-national-return-with-a-magnificent-and-still-melancholic-new-album]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_BKP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-28T16:38:04Z&quot;&gt;May 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN MARCH the National released “You Had Your Soul With You”. Though the single was not exactly upbeat or cheery—witness the line, “You have no idea how hard I died when you left”—it was a little more up-tempo than some of the band’s previous work. Some fans wondered, and worried: would their new album be a departure from the group’s stock-in-trade brooding baritones and ballads? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I Am Easy to Find”, the band’s eighth studio album in 18 years, came out on May 17th and those fears were allayed. Not only has the National stayed in its melancholic mood (many of their early-to-mid-2000s peers have either disbanded or lightened up a little); “I Am Easy to Find” is also a magnificent LP that is both consistent with their oeuvre and subtly surprising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is not to say they haven’t changed at all since their self-titled debut album was released in 2001. They are no longer a group of guys who share a house in Brooklyn and mess around in a garage-turned-music-studio. “Take a bath and get high through an apple,” Matt Berninger, the frontman, sang in “So Far Around the Bend” (2009), along with a refrain that “now there’s no leaving New York.” But the band has left New York, and decamped to cities around the world, often with their wives and children. They spend long stretches apart to work on side projects. Some of these developments were evident on their last album, “Sleep Well Beast” (2017), on which they occasionally traded the break-up tracks for songs about the small and difficult moments in a long marriage. (Many of the band’s lyrics are co-written by Carin Besser, Mr Berninger’s wife.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I Am Easy To Find” is notable in featuring so many female voices. Gail Ann Dorsey, who collaborated with David Bowie for decades, sings on a number of tracks. She carries “Hey Rosey”, a song about dangerous and painful love, as Mr Berninger provides a melodic counterpart; the blend of their two voices makes it a nearly perfect song. Elsewhere on the album, vocalists including Sharon Van Etten, Kate Stables, Mina Tindle and Lisa Hannigan drift in and out to powerful effect. (The band’s decision to collaborate with women has strangely been attributed to #MeToo by critics, but the National credits the development to the vision of Mike Mills, a producer who has also made a short film to complement the project.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Songs like “So Far, So Fast” are experimental in a way that suits the group: strange, synth-heavy, occasionally choral. (The Brooklyn Youth Chorus sings one song in full, and appears throughout the album). Not all these forays in new directions work: the song “Not In Kansas” strives too hard to be political, and is ambling and musically stilted. But the album is memorable for gems such as “Quiet Light”, which sounds a lot like the band fans know well. Mr Berninger croons, “I’m not afraid of being alone/ I just don’t know what to do with my time” with a familiar mix of ennui and angst. The album deserves to be listened to in one sitting. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What the National has managed to maintain—both rarely and beautifully—is a mood. How to describe that mood? Perhaps in dissociated images that have only a little to do with their lyrics: New England highways in November paved with ice; candlelight and marijuana smoke; crumpled-up letters; long lonely walks in early spring; last kisses. Their mood is not so much despair as it is simply sadness, of a bittersweet, poignant and powerful kind. It is a feeling that has enough shades to keep people listening all these years on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 00:40:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Casting light on the Moon]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/05/28/casting-light-on-the-moon]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_bkp516.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-28T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Moon: A History for the Future.&lt;/strong&gt; By Oliver Morton. &lt;em&gt;Hachette; 352 pages; $16.99. Economist Books; £20&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EVERY 29 days, according to an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://science.sciencemag.org/content/267/5203/1481&quot;&gt;article published in &lt;em&gt;Science&lt;/em&gt; magazine in May 1995&lt;/a&gt;, the global temperature fluctuates by 200ths of a degree Celsius. This is because the Moon, when it is full, reflects a whole lunar surface-worth of distant sunlight onto the terrestrial night and Earth is measurably warmer than it would be at the Moon’s crescent, or even in its gibbous phase.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this, and many other imperceptible ways, the Moon has an effect on the Earth. It lights our night, it subtly prolongs our days, its gravitational tug washes our estuaries, rinses our harbours and erodes our cliffs, and it keeps the Earth’s axis of rotation on a more or less stable tilt. This stability may have made possible the sustained evolution of microbial life, then complex creatures and, finally, questioning bipeds. If the great-splat-in-the-sky theory is correct, and the Earth and Moon are the surviving products of an unimaginable traffic accident in orbit around the sun, then something of our planet now belongs to up there. We owe a lot to the Moon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Its pale face reflects humanity’s hopes and fears, and offers a faintly-marked surface on which to sketch our dreams. Fifty years ago this summer, and 240,000 miles (386,243km) from home, American astronauts began a series of brief walks on the dusty lunar surface. This period of direct contact lasted six visits during a trifling three years. The view from the Moon revealed the beauty and fragility of our own blue planet. The Apollo program was cancelled prematurely, and the wider world lost interest in the Moon. This loss was, and is, mourned by a class of enthusiasts later to be labelled “orphans of Apollo”: those who had hoped to see Apollo as the beginning of a great adventure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since then, no astronaut or cosmonaut has travelled much more than 300 miles in a vertical direction. But we can dream, and we can despatch robots to look at the lunar terrain. And one day, humans could step out onto the far side of the Moon. A vast corpus has looked back at the great fact of the Moon landings, and a vastly bigger body of science-fiction has already extended the adventure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oliver Morton, &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s briefings editor, is one of those orphans of Apollo. He has written not just a very good book about the Moon but even more admirably, a different one. It is good because it is superbly well-written and enjoyably organised. It is different because it looks beyond Apollo towards the future: the Moonbase as a technological challenge, an economic gamble and as a testbed for the much more dangerous missions to Mars. Much of the information you might hope to find—its mass, topography, petrology, orbit, the nature of its surface, what it takes to get there and the folklore it has inspired—is tautly arranged in separate chapters. The lunar role in post-Copernican discovery and the great adventures of Apollo are necessarily but freshly recounted, the latter with clever use of dialogue spoken on the Moon itself, and to mission control back on Earth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A little like Norman Mailer in his book, “Of a Fire on the Moon” (1970), Mr Morton bookends his tale with some of his own responses to the moon, space launchers and the lunar light. He brings an enviable knowledge of science-fiction literature to focus on the uneasy futures we imagine for this hostile homestead-to-be (including a prison and labour camp from which, once deported, there can be no return).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally he brings a reporter’s direct experience of encounters with tomorrow’s lunarnauts: the giants of private enterprise and innovation who may, and perhaps will, provide the impetus and the hardware for a new age of exploration and exploitation. These include Jeff Bezos of Blue Origin and Elon Musk of SpaceX. Mr Bezos is described as well-motivated. So, too, is Mr Musk, with the rider that he is “also a prick. Not an irredeemable arsehole, though he has recently looked more like one than he used to…” Really? So what? Which powerful man could not, at some time, have merited such a judgment? Even so, that mix of forthrightness and observation is part of what makes the book a pleasure to read.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;TIM RADFORD*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;*Our policy is to identify the reviewer of any book by or about someone closely connected with &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;. Tim Radford is a freelance journalist. His book “The Consolations of Physics: Why the Wonders of the Universe Can Make You Happy” is published in paperback by Sceptre this summer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 00:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Margrethe Vestager ticks all the boxes]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/charlemagnes-notebook/2019/05/28/why-margrethe-vestager-ticks-all-the-boxes]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-28T14:11:00Z&quot;&gt;May 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Editor’s note: This piece has been updated following the European Parliament elections on May 23rd-26th. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPEAN POLITICS is turning more febrile after voters in elections for the European Parliament broke the old duopoly of the two main political “families”: the centre-right European People’s Party (EPP) and old centre-left Socialists and Democrats (S&amp;amp;D).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two “big tent” groups, which have dominated the parliament since direct elections were introduced in 1979, were the biggest losers as European politics fragments. By the latest count, the two groups between them lost 87 seats in the 751-seat parliament. That, in turn, is re-opening the debate about who should run the European Commission, the powerful bureaucratic machine at the heart of the European Union, which acts as an executive, a civil service and a market regulator. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The president of the commission is nominated by national leaders, with approval from the parliament. Leaders will meet in Brussels tonight to begin discussing who should fill this and a host of senior EU jobs, among them the president of the European Council (representing leaders) and the president of the European Central Bank (ECB).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the last European elections in 2014, the parliament tried to institutionalise the idea of the Spitzenkandidat, whereby leaders would be compelled to choose the “leading candidate” for commission president selected by the parliament on the basis of who can command a majority. Under a gentleman&amp;#x27;s agreement in 2014, the S&amp;amp;D made way for Jean-Claude Juncker of the EPP, whose group was the largest. The leaders acquiesced despite misgivings by Britain and Hungary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The EPP insists that, as the largest parliamentary group (which still counts 180 seats), it should have the right again to nominate its candidate—in this case Manfred Weber, the German who leads the EPP’s parliamentary group. But foisting him on leaders will be harder this time around. To begin with, Mr Weber has no executive experience, unlike Mr Juncker, a veteran prime minister of Luxembourg. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, Emmanuel Macron, the French president, is determined to halt Mr Weber and the whole Spitzenkadidat process. To do so, he is enlisting the support Pedro Sánchez, António Costa and Mark Rutte, the prime ministers of Spain, Portugal and the Netherlands respectively. Angela Merkel, the German chancellor who secured the job for Mr Juncker last time around, nominally supports Mr Weber. But she is less dominant than she used to be, and will probably not back Mr Weber at any cost; some think she is more interested in placing a hawk at the head of the ECB.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But perhaps the biggest problem for Mr Weber is that the EPP’s cosy deals with the S&amp;amp;D (the two groups share the presidency of the parliament on a rotating basis) can no longer be easily imposed on others. The S&amp;amp;D backs Frans Timmermans, a former Dutch foreign minister serving as first vice-president of the commission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Alliance of Liberals and Democrats for Europe (ALDE), which gained 42 seats for a total of 109, also refuses to endorse Mr Weber. The Greens, who also made big gains, are critical as well. And various Eurosceptic nationalist and populist groups, notably the European Alliance of People and Nations, led by Matteo Salvini, Italy’s right-wing deputy prime minister, are determined to break the mould of European politics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Mr Weber is blocked, who else might become the commission’s president? Some are pushing for an alternative EPP figure, Michel Barnier, a former French foreign minister who ably held the 27 European states united in the negotiations with Britain over Brexit. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the case for Margrethe Vestager, the powerful competition commissioner, is growing. She ticks many of the boxes needed for a successful candidate: she can get things done, she is acceptable to the centre-right EPP and the S&amp;amp;D. More important, is championed by the Liberals and Greens, whose votes will be needed for a majority. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Vestager has served as education, interior and economy minister of Denmark, despite belonging to a small social liberal party. As a commissioner since 2014 she has applied both a liberal sense of consumer rights and an interventionist commitment to defending the little guy to the task of regulating technology giants. She has taken on tax dodgers, infringers of personal privacy and market distorters. Thrusting machos from Silicon Valley have turned up in her office berating her and come off the worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The EU in 2019 faces an array of security and economic threats. It needs a powerful, efficient leader with experience of the commission and a sense of how the world is changing. It needs a leader who can stand up for Europe and initiate legislation defending its citizens. It needs someone acceptable to left and right, north and south. Many candidates will put their names forward. Ms Vestager ticks a lot of boxes. Europe would be foolish to overlook her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 21:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Fragmentation is the main trend”—Europe&#x27;s elections]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/28/fragmentation-is-the-main-trend-europes-elections]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_blm501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-28T11:30:17Z&quot;&gt;May 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPE&amp;#x27;S VOTERS have shown they are not happy with traditional political parties. But even as the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/27/the-conservatives-and-labour-take-a-bashing-in-britains-european-election&quot;&gt;Brexit Party&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; surged in Britain, populists across the continent found elections to the European Parliament tougher than expected. And despite being &amp;quot;asset-light&amp;quot;, some &lt;strong&gt;tech companies need &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/11/how-real-estate-barons-have-ridden-the-tech-boom&quot;&gt;property&lt;/a&gt; to keep expanding&lt;/strong&gt;. That’s good news for the right real-estate investment funds. Also, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/25/big-agribusiness-wants-to-make-quinoa-more-mainstream&quot;&gt;quinoa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is the grain getting a new lease of life. Runtime: 20 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/continentalbreakfast-europeanelections&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 20:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why managers should listen to shareholders]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/27/why-managers-should-listen-to-shareholders]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_blp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-27T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 27th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ARTHUR BALFOUR was a British prime minister who did not think much of his party members. “I’d rather take advice from my valet than from the Conservative Party conference,” he said. Corporate executives, particularly in America, seem to take a similar attitude towards their shareholders, believing that, like children, they should be seen but definitely not heard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maybe managers should get their fingers out of their ears and start listening to their investors. That is the conclusion of a recent paper* by Clifford Holderness of the Carroll School of Management at Boston College.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In America and a few other countries, boards can issue additional shares without shareholder approval. In some countries, shareholders must approve issuance above a certain threshold. And in yet others, investors must agree before any new stock can be created. So what happens to a company’s share price when new shares are issued? Mr Holderness performed a meta-analysis of more than 100 studies of stock reactions around the world. He found that, when shareholders approved issuance in advance, the price tended to rise by an average of 2%. But when managers issued stock without shareholder approval, the share price declined by an average of 2%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The simplest explanation for this differential lies in the agent-principal conflict between executives and investors. As Mr Holderness writes, if agency conflicts did not exist, “shareholder voting on equity issuance should not matter.” However, managers may want to issue shares to fund expansion of the company, allowing them to control more assets and demand a higher salary. Investors, meanwhile, may worry about the impact of such expansion on long-term returns and dislike the dilution of their control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another sign of agent-principal conflicts are shares that are privately placed with selected investors or used to pay for takeovers. In Australia, any offering of more than 15% of the equity must be subject to shareholder approval; in America, the threshold is 20%. In both countries, there is a clustering of share issuance just below the limit; managers go out of their way to avoid asking for approval. In April Occidental Petroleum promised $10bn worth of preferred shares to Berkshire Hathaway, Warren Buffett’s conglomerate, should the oil company’s bid for Anadarko, a rival, succeed. This injection helped it avoid asking shareholders to authorise the Anadarko deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This disdain for shareholders’ views contradicts the ethos of American capitalism. The system works, it is usually argued, because companies respond to shareholder pressure and because broad share ownership gives everyone, including workers, a stake in the American dream. One of the reasons for the success of the private-equity model is that investors enjoy greater scrutiny over what managers do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But when it comes to public companies, shareholders tend to be treated like an awkward uncle at a family gathering. Their only rights are to sell their shares or to vote against the reappointment of directors. In any other field, this would be extraordinary. Imagine you appointed a letting agent to look after your house and they decided to spend lots of your money on gold taps and chandeliers. When you complain, they respond that you are only entitled to sell the house, or fire them at the end of their contract.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Managers have long grumbled that shareholders want to interfere too much. A new complaint is that socially conscious investors may insist that firms concentrate on non-financial factors, like treating workers better or cutting emissions. This concern seems ill-founded. For example, research** shows that companies voted the “best to work for” produce superior subsequent long-term returns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More generally, the majority of metastudies have found that companies with better ESG (environmental, social and governance) records improved their financial performance. Mr Holderness’s work puts the tin lid on the argument that managers should ignore investors. When it comes to shareholders, managers should remember the words of Diogenes: “We have two ears and one tongue so that we would listen more and talk less.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* “Equity issuances and agency costs: The telling story of shareholder approval around the world”, &lt;em&gt;Journal of Financial Economics&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;** “Employee Satisfaction, Labor Market Flexibility, and Stock Returns Around the World”, by Alex Edmans, Lucius Li and Chendi Zhang, European Corporate Governance Institute Working Paper 433&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 17:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>