<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Voters punish Labour and the Tories at local elections over Brexit deadlock]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/03/voters-punish-labour-and-the-tories-at-local-elections-over-brexit-deadlock]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_brp507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-03T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NOT ALL politics is local. Voters fed up with the political impasse in Westminster, nearly three years after the referendum to leave the European Union, lashed out at both the Conservatives and Labour in local elections on May 2nd. Instead, they gave their support to smaller parties that offered any sort of alternative.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By mid-morning on May 3rd, with results still coming in, a pattern had emerged. The Conservatives had performed badly across the board, losing ground in both Remain-voting areas, which balked at the Tories’ hard line on Europe, and staunchly Leave parts of the country, where voters felt the party too soft on the topic. But so had Labour, which fell back sharply in Leave-voting areas in the north and midlands. When it comes to Brexit, voters seem happy to dish out the blame equally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Where a viable third option existed, voters jumped at it. The Liberal Democrats were the main beneficiaries. By 9am the morning after the vote, they had won eight councils, mainly from the Conservatives. The Green Party also did well, picking up 40 seats, after a brief lull in the Brexit coverage pushed the environment to the top of news bulletins in the weeks running up to the vote. Independents, meanwhile, mopped up. In Ashfield, a former mining community in the midlands, the Ashfield Independents romped home with 30 of 35 seats. An independent candidate in Middlesbrough’s mayoral election hammered his Labour opponent. By 9am more than 200 independent candidates had won seats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Loyalists from the two main parties offered excuses for the poor performance. The Conservatives were defending a big haul of seats won in 2015, when local elections came at the same time as their surprise general-election victory under David Cameron. By contrast, Labour had a torrid day in 2015 and is on track for another bad one this time. The party’s defenders point out that these elections were dominated by rural seats, where Labour is weak anyway—a fact the party has no plans to change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lib Dems were quick to hail a triumph. Sir Ed Davey, the party’s home-affairs spokesman, labelled it the best result in a generation. It is true that they performed well, but the party is making up ground lost during their unhappy years in coalition with the Conservatives, rather than converting swathes to the Lib Dem faith. Between 2010 and 2015 the Lib Dems’ share of the vote in general elections fell from 23% to 8%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;John Curtice, a veteran pollster, suggested a cheap bottle of champagne or a prosecco was in order, rather than the good stuff. What it does demonstrate is that the Lib Dems are far from a spent force. The main pitch from a new pro-Remain centrist outfit, Change UK, is that the Lib Dems are fit only for the knackers; these results show that voters disagree.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Results will dribble in for the rest of the day, including from bellwether seats such as Darlington, in the north-east, and from Northern Ireland. What is clear already is that there is no Brexit dividend for either Labour or the Conservatives. Voters fed up with the two main parties have plenty of other options, whether Lib Dem or Green (both of which offer outright opposition to Brexit), or a battered, bruised and increasingly far-right UK Independence Party, which clung on to some seats despite having fallen apart institutionally. The same trend on steroids can be expected in the European election later this month, which voters have historically used to cast a protest vote and which offers an even wider array of options (neither the Brexit Party, Nigel Farage’s new outfit which currently tops the polls, nor Change UK stood in this week’s local elections). Neither Labour nor the Conservatives will see political benefit from Brexit. But other parties will.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 18:06:48 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Are states equipped to tackle partisan gerrymandering on their own?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/02/are-states-equipped-to-tackle-partisan-gerrymandering-on-their-own]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_USP510.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-02T21:48:29Z&quot;&gt;May 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;DESPITE ITS repeated refusals to curb haywire electoral maps, the Supreme Court has no great love of partisan gerrymandering. When, 33 years ago, the justices unanimously let a Republican gerrymander in Indiana &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://supreme.justia.com/cases/federal/us/478/109/#tab-opinion-1956739&quot;&gt;slide&lt;/a&gt;, they said the impact on Democrats was discriminatory but not egregiously so. When in 2004 the court decided not to strike down maps favouring Republicans in Pennsylvania, four justices &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.oyez.org/cases/2003/02-1580&quot;&gt;determined&lt;/a&gt; that gerrymandering, while nothing to celebrate, was not a matter the judiciary could police. And in 2018, challenges to devastating gerrymanders in Wisconsin and Maryland (one for each party) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2018/06/19/the-supreme-court-dodges-big-decisions-on-partisan-redistricting&quot;&gt;came up short&lt;/a&gt; on procedural grounds. Despite their demurrals, the justices seem to agree that it is poor form for politicians of one party to methodically preserve their seats with precision-engineered maps. In 2017, Samuel Alito, a conservative justice unwilling to crack down on partisan draughtsmen, nevertheless called gerrymandering “distasteful”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So when the justices &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/03/28/the-supreme-court-does-not-like-gerrymandering&quot;&gt;took up&lt;/a&gt; the matter yet again in March, several pursued a new tack. Maybe the judiciary does not need to meddle with politically tainted line-drawing, Donald Trump’s two appointees suggested in the oral arguments, because a new political awakening is fixing the problem all by itself. Justice Neil Gorsuch &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/oral_arguments/argument_transcripts/2018/18-422_5hd5.pdf&quot;&gt;launched&lt;/a&gt; this line of questioning in &lt;em&gt;Rucho v Common Cause,&lt;/em&gt; a challenge to an extreme Republican gerrymander of congressional districts in North Carolina. “We’ve heard that the court must act because nobody else can as a practical matter”, Justice Gorsuch told Paul Clement, the lawyer representing the North Carolina General Assembly. But “what’s the scope of the problem here?” Seven sparsely populated states with only one congressional district have no gerrymandering (or district lines) at all, and a handful of other states have taken redistricting out of politicians’ hands. These changes, in Justice Gorsuch’s home state of Colorado as well as in California, Arizona, Michigan, New York, Missouri, Ohio and Utah, mean that nonpartisan or bipartisan commissions, not the legislatures themselves, draw the lines. And some state Supreme Courts, notably &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2018/01/25/pennsylvanias-supreme-court-invalidates-the-states-congressional-map&quot;&gt;Pennsylvania&amp;#x27;s&lt;/a&gt;, are finding electoral maps invalid under state constitutions. “My sense”, Justice Gorsuch said, “is there’s a lot of movement in this area”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justice Brett Kavanaugh, the court’s newest member, voiced frustration with Democratic gerrymandering in his home state of Maryland. But he, too, explored the idea that the democratic process may spare the Supreme Court from stepping in. There is “a fair amount of activity going on in the states”, Justice Kavanaugh observed to Emmet Bondurant, the lawyer for the North Carolina plaintiffs. Voters are “recognising the same problem that you’re recognising” and taking action to hand map-drawing to independent commissions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Bondurant’s reply, supported later in the hearing by Allison Riggs, another lawyer arguing against the skewed North Carolina maps, was a reality check. Most states that have moved to redistricting commissions in hopes of dampening the political gamesmanship in electoral map-making have got there via ballot initiatives: amendments to their state constitutions approved by voters at the polls. But many states, including most east of the Mississippi River, do not provide for such a process, and it is distinctly unlikely that state legislatures would vote to strip themselves of the power to redistrict. Neither Republicans nor Democrats have an incentive to pass off the pen to a committee that will draw maps less favourable to them in the next decade’s elections. And moves are afoot in the Pennsylvania legislature to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.witf.org/news/2019/04/house-panel-advances-changes-in-pennsylvania-judge-elections.php&quot;&gt;gerrymander&lt;/a&gt; judicial elections in response to the state Supreme Court&amp;#x27;s crackdown on a Republican-favouring congressional map.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the face of evidence that states are not fully equipped to handle gerrymandering on their own, Justices Gorsuch and Kavanaugh waxed poetic about the wonders of the political process. Mr Clement did nothing to discourage them, mentioning that the House of Representatives recently voted for HR-1, a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.congress.gov/bill/116th-congress/house-bill/1/text#toc-H5AD53F4DB4D140C183648E0CD2DA03F9&quot;&gt;bill&lt;/a&gt; which would, among other things, force all states to transfer electoral cartography from legislatures to independent commissions. Mr Clement said this was evidence that Congress, in addition to the states, “is able to take action”. He even had a response, disingenuous though it was, to Chief Justice John Roberts’s riposte that members of Congress must be “pretty happy with the way the districting has been done”. Actually, Mr Clement replied, it is remarkable that “a majority of Congress thinks that they should pass HR-1”. He did not mention that Mitch McConnell, Republican majority leader of the Senate, has declared HR-1 dead on arrival in his chamber. Nor did he clarify that it is only Democrats in the House, not “a majority of Congress”, that wants to see HR-1 become law. (Mr Clement did mention, however, that forcing legislatures to outsource their maps might be unconstitutional.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite its limits, enthusiasm for democratic change is not entirely misplaced. “Slay the Dragon”, a new documentary film by Barak Goodman and Chris Durrance, detailing the increasingly sophisticated scourge of partisan gerrymandering in America, shows the power of grassroots organising. After conveying the frightful implications of computer-aided map-drawing, “Slay the Dragon” tells the story of Katie Fahy, a political neophyte who gets so fed up with election doping in her state of Michigan that she decides to do something about it. Ms Fahy builds Voters Not Politicians, an all-volunteer organisation to get a redistricting-reform amendment on the 2018 ballot. She gathers the required hundreds of thousands of signatures; fights a well-financed legal assault on the measure; wins victories in both federal and state court to keep the proposal on the ballot; and persuades 61% of Michigan voters to adopt the plan. The story is a remarkable example of how civic passion and pluck can make a difference. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the difficulty of replicating Michigan’s transition in most other states is a hard reality. And the Wolverine state’s success is allowing some justices to believe that the courts can sit back and let democracy take its course. Ms Fahy bristles when she hears this. But she and activists in other states with independent commissions may have more disappointments ahead. In 2015, a redistricting commission in Arizona barely survived a constitutional challenge at the Supreme Court. The decision was &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2015/07/02/one-for-the-people&quot;&gt;written&lt;/a&gt; by Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg and clinched by Justice Anthony Kennedy, who left the bench last summer. Chief Justice John Roberts&amp;#x27;s dissent accused the majority of &amp;quot;deliberate constitutional evasion&amp;quot;: Article I empowers only state legislatures to draw electoral lines, he wrote. With a more conservative Justice Kavanaugh now in Justice Kennedy&amp;#x27;s seat, and the pointed dissenter in the Arizona case now the swing justice, independent commissions—and America’s electoral democracy—remain vulnerable. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 07:06:50 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Are states equipped to tackle partisan gerrymandering on their own?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/03/are-states-equipped-to-tackle-partisan-gerrymandering-on-their-own]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_USP510.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-03T01:48:29Z&quot;&gt;May 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;DESPITE ITS repeated refusals to curb haywire electoral maps, the Supreme Court has no great love of partisan gerrymandering. When, 33 years ago, the justices unanimously let a Republican gerrymander in Indiana &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://supreme.justia.com/cases/federal/us/478/109/#tab-opinion-1956739&quot;&gt;slide&lt;/a&gt;, they said the impact on Democrats was discriminatory but not egregiously so. When in 2004 the court decided not to strike down maps favouring Republicans in Pennsylvania, four justices &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.oyez.org/cases/2003/02-1580&quot;&gt;determined&lt;/a&gt; that gerrymandering, while nothing to celebrate, was not a matter the judiciary could police. And in 2018, challenges to devastating gerrymanders in Wisconsin and Maryland (one for each party) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2018/06/19/the-supreme-court-dodges-big-decisions-on-partisan-redistricting&quot;&gt;came up short&lt;/a&gt; on procedural grounds. Despite their demurrals, the justices seem to agree that it is poor form for politicians of one party to methodically preserve their seats with precision-engineered maps. In 2017, Samuel Alito, a conservative justice unwilling to crack down on partisan draughtsmen, nevertheless called gerrymandering “distasteful”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So when the justices &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/03/28/the-supreme-court-does-not-like-gerrymandering&quot;&gt;took up&lt;/a&gt; the matter yet again in March, several pursued a new tack. Maybe the judiciary does not need to meddle with politically tainted line-drawing, Donald Trump’s two appointees suggested in the oral arguments, because a new political awakening is fixing the problem all by itself. Justice Neil Gorsuch &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/oral_arguments/argument_transcripts/2018/18-422_5hd5.pdf&quot;&gt;launched&lt;/a&gt; this line of questioning in &lt;em&gt;Rucho v Common Cause,&lt;/em&gt; a challenge to an extreme Republican gerrymander of congressional districts in North Carolina. “We’ve heard that the court must act because nobody else can as a practical matter”, Justice Gorsuch told Paul Clement, North Carolina’s lawyer. But “what’s the scope of the problem here?” Seven sparsely populated states with only one congressional district have no gerrymandering (or district lines) at all, and a handful of other states have taken redistricting out of politicians’ hands. These changes, in Justice Gorsuch’s home state of Colorado as well as in California, Arizona, Michigan, New York, Missouri, Ohio and Utah, mean that nonpartisan or bipartisan commissions, not the legislatures themselves, draw the lines. And some state Supreme Courts, notably &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2018/01/25/pennsylvanias-supreme-court-invalidates-the-states-congressional-map&quot;&gt;Pennsylvania&amp;#x27;s&lt;/a&gt;, are finding electoral maps invalid under state constitutions. “My sense”, Justice Gorsuch said, “is there’s a lot of movement in this area”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justice Brett Kavanaugh, the court’s newest member, voiced frustration with Democratic gerrymandering in his home state of Maryland. But he, too, explored the idea that the democratic process may spare the Supreme Court from stepping in. There is “a fair amount of activity going on in the states”, Justice Kavanaugh observed to Emmet Bondurant, the lawyer for the North Carolina plaintiffs. Voters are “recognising the same problem that you’re recognising” and taking action to hand map-drawing to independent commissions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Bondurant’s reply, supported later in the hearing by Allison Riggs, another lawyer arguing against the skewed North Carolina maps, was a reality check. Most states that have moved to redistricting commissions in hopes of dampening the political gamesmanship in electoral map-making have got there via ballot initiatives: amendments to their state constitutions approved by voters at the polls. But many states, including most east of the Mississippi River, do not provide for such a process, and it is distinctly unlikely that state legislatures would vote to strip themselves of the power to redistrict. Neither Republicans nor Democrats have an incentive to pass off the pen to a committee that will draw maps less favourable to them in the next decade’s elections. And moves are afoot in the Pennsylvania legislature to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.witf.org/news/2019/04/house-panel-advances-changes-in-pennsylvania-judge-elections.php&quot;&gt;gerrymander&lt;/a&gt; judicial elections in response to the state Supreme Court&amp;#x27;s crackdown on a Republican-favouring congressional map.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the face of evidence that states are not fully equipped to handle gerrymandering on their own, Justices Gorsuch and Kavanaugh waxed poetic about the wonders of the political process. Mr Clement did nothing to discourage them, mentioning that the House of Representatives recently voted for HR-1, a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.congress.gov/bill/116th-congress/house-bill/1/text#toc-H5AD53F4DB4D140C183648E0CD2DA03F9&quot;&gt;bill&lt;/a&gt; which would, among other things, force all states to transfer electoral cartography from legislatures to independent commissions. Mr Clement said this was evidence that Congress, in addition to the states, “is able to take action”. He even had a response, disingenuous though it was, to Chief Justice John Roberts’s riposte that members of Congress must be “pretty happy with the way the districting has been done”. Actually, Mr Clement replied, it is remarkable that “a majority of Congress thinks that they should pass HR-1”. He did not mention that Mitch McConnell, Republican majority leader of the Senate, has declared HR-1 dead on arrival in his chamber. Nor did he clarify that it is only Democrats in the House, not “a majority of Congress”, that wants to see HR-1 become law. (Mr Clement did mention, however, that forcing legislatures to outsource their maps might be unconstitutional.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite its limits, enthusiasm for democratic change is not entirely misplaced. “Slay the Dragon”, a new documentary film by Barak Goodman and Chris Durrance, detailing the increasingly sophisticated scourge of partisan gerrymandering in America, shows the power of grassroots organising. After conveying the frightful implications of computer-aided map-drawing, “Slay the Dragon” tells the story of Katie Fahy, a political neophyte who gets so fed up with election doping in her state of Michigan that she decides to do something about it. Ms Fahy builds Voters Not Politicians, an all-volunteer organisation to get a redistricting-reform amendment on the 2018 ballot. She gathers the required hundreds of thousands of signatures; fights a well-financed legal assault on the measure; wins victories in both federal and state court to keep the proposal on the ballot; and persuades 61% of Michigan voters to adopt the plan. The story is a remarkable example of how civic passion and pluck can make a difference. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the difficulty of replicating Michigan’s transition in most other states is a hard reality. And the Wolverine state’s success is allowing some justices to believe that the courts can sit back and let democracy take its course. Ms Fahy bristles when she hears this. But she and activists in other states with independent commissions may have more disappointments ahead. In 2015, a redistricting commission in Arizona barely survived a constitutional challenge at the Supreme Court. The decision was &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2015/07/02/one-for-the-people&quot;&gt;written&lt;/a&gt; by Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg and clinched by Justice Anthony Kennedy, who left the bench last summer. Chief Justice John Roberts&amp;#x27;s dissent accused the majority of &amp;quot;deliberate constitutional evasion&amp;quot;: Article I empowers only state legislatures to draw electoral lines, he wrote. With a more conservative Justice Kavanaugh now in Justice Kennedy&amp;#x27;s seat, and the pointed dissenter in the Arizona case now the swing justice, independent commissions—and America’s electoral democracy—remain vulnerable. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 05:11:18 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Charlottesville’s Confederate statues are still standing]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/02/why-charlottesvilles-confederate-statues-are-still-standing]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_USP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-02T20:20:51Z&quot;&gt;May 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SINCE 1924, a bronze statue of Robert E. Lee (pictured), the Confederacy’s top general and a brutal slave owner, has stood in a park in Charlottesville, Virginia. In August 2017, a crowd of white nationalists gathered in the pretty college town to protest against the city council’s plan to remove the statue. One of them drove a car into a group of counter-demonstrators, killing a young woman, Heather Heyer. President Donald Trump’s remark that there were “very fine people on both sides” of the protests was one of the lowest points of his presidency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly two years later, a legal battle over the statue of Lee and one of another Confederate general, Thomas “Stonewall” Jackson, drags on. On April 25th, a judge ruled that the city council could not take the statues down because of a Virginian law that forbids authorities other than the state government from removing war memorials. While, “some people obviously see Lee and Jackson as symbols of white supremacy,” Richard E. Moore, a circuit judge wrote, and “others see them as brilliant military tacticians or complex leaders at a difficult time”, their views are irrelevant; the statues are war memorials and thus protected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Opponents of the statues are understandably concerned. Don Gathers, former chairman of the city commission that recommended removing the statues, said he feared the ruling would embolden white supremacists, “to think they had won and to come back to Charlottesville”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The battle over Charlottesville’s Confederate statues echoes similar ones elsewhere. Since 2015, when a white supremacist, fond of posing for photos with the Confederate flag, slaughtered nine black churchgoers in South Carolina, there has been a concerted push to remove monuments to the Confederacy from public places across America. Proponents of the removal of such monuments point out that the majority of them were erected long after the Civil War, during the Jim Crow era of the early twentieth century. This, it is argued, makes them less war memorials than symbols of a defiant and reborn white supremacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their defenders often argue that, notwithstanding the spirit in which they were raised, the monuments are part of America’s heritage. This argument has been broadly successful. According to the Southern Poverty Law Centre, an advocacy group, over 100 Confederate symbols including flags and place names, have been removed from public places, but over 1,500, including over 700 monuments, remain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is largely due to state laws, like Virginia’s. When in early 2017 Charlottesville’s city council voted to remove the statue of Lee, the Monument Fund, a local group, sued, citing a law, passed in 1904—in Richmond, capital of the Confederacy—against the removal of war memorials. After Ms Heyer’s murder, the council also voted to remove a statue of Jackson (erected in 1924) and the Monument Fund updated its lawsuit to include that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other states have passed such laws more recently. In 2004, Mississippi passed a law banning the removal of monuments. It was followed in 2015 by North Carolina. In 2016 Tennessee made it more difficult for the state legislature to approve monuments’ removal. In 2017, Alabama passed legislation protecting memorials that had stood on public property for 40 years or more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In some cases, novel ways have been found around these laws. In Memphis, Tennessee, several Confederate statues came down after the city sold the two public parks in which they stood to a non-profit organisation for a mere $1,000 each. On other occasions the laws have been flouted. Last year protestors toppled “Silent Sam” a statue of a Confederate soldier at the University of North Carolina; the university chancellor then had the monument carted away before she resigned. The laws are also being challenged in the courts, sometimes with more success than in Virginia. In January, a judge in Alabama ruled that the state law violated the rights of citizens opposed to Confederate monuments; the attorney-general has said he will appeal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Charlottesville, the legal wrangling will continue. As well as arguing that the statues of Lee and Jackson are not war memorials, the city council points out that the law did not originally apply to cities like Charlottesville, only to counties. (It was amended in 1997 to include cities.) The judge has yet to rule on that but the case may end up in the state’s Supreme Court.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That legal battle aside, Charlottesville is likely to remain in the news. Last month Joe Biden, the current frontrunner for the Democratic nomination for president, made the violence there a central part of his official campaign launch. In his announcement video the former vice-president chastised Mr Trump for praising the white supremacists who chanted, “the same anti-Semitic bile heard across Europe in the 30s”. The president’s words, Mr Biden went on, “stunned the world and shocked the conscience of this nation”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In response, Mr Trump said he was defending those who had opposed the removal of the statue of Lee. “If you look at what I said, you will see that that question was answered perfectly,” Trump told reporters. “And I was talking about people who went because they felt very strongly about the monument to Robert E. Lee, a great general. Whether you like it or not, he was one of the great generals.” Mr Biden disputed this. “Hatred was on the march, and he knew it,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 05:11:17 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Caster Semenya’s case sets a big precedent for women’s sport]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/05/02/caster-semenyas-case-sets-a-big-precedent-for-womens-sport]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_IRP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-02T19:16:38Z&quot;&gt;May 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FEW ATHLETES have been as blessed and cursed as Caster Semenya. All that the 28-year-old South African runner has ever done is run as fast as her legs could carry her—fast enough to win back-to-back Olympic gold medals over 800 metres, and to triumph in each of the last forty 800-metre races that she has entered. But her extraordinary body has also been the subject of ridicule, speculation and censure. In 2009, when she breezed to a World Championship title as an 18-year-old, the International Association of Athletics Federations (IAAF), the sport’s governing organisation, announced that it was investigating whether she might be intersex—an umbrella (and misleading) term for people with a wide range of developmental conditions affecting the genitalia and gonads. To protect her privacy, the IAAF never published its findings. But it has spent the ensuing decade fighting a regulatory battle against Ms Semenya, about whether she must meet certain hormonal criteria to compete as a woman. On May 1st the Court of Arbitration for Sport (CAS), the highest legal body in sport, ruled against her in a decision that will have wide-ranging implications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The court allowed the IAAF to impose a limit of 5 nanolitres of testosterone per litre of blood (nmol/L) on runners with certain intersex conditions that increase naturally occurring testosterone. The ruling covers women’s races between 400 metres and a mile. That testosterone threshold is far below the normal male range of 8-30 nmol/L, but considerably above the normal female range of 0.1-1.8 nmol/L. To continue racing over 800 metres, Ms Semenya would have to undergo hormone therapy, which can increase the risk of cardiovascular disease, along with other nasty side effects. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The direct impact of the court’s ruling might actually be quite small. Ms Semenya has undergone hormone therapy before, when the IAAF introduced a testosterone limit of 10 nmol/L for women across all track-and-field events in 2011. The court suspended that rule in 2015, when Dutee Chand, an Indian sprinter with abnormally high testosterone levels, disputed that there was proof that women like her received an unfair advantage in all athletic events. The IAAF has spent the ensuing years gathering data on the question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Its researchers presented to the court an analysis of results at past athletics championships, which showed that women with high levels of testosterone did disproportionately well in middle-distance events. They did not find such evidence for most other competitions. The court therefore allowed the IAAF to impose a tougher 5 nmol/L limit, but only for those particular races. Ms Semenya is one of a handful of runners affected. Rather than undergoing another bout of hormone therapy, which knocked about 4% off her 800-metre time, she could simply switch to the 5,000-metre race. The event is not covered by the new rules, and she won it at the South African Athletics Championships on April 26th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Only a few runners will have to make immediate career choices after the court’s decision. But the precedent set by the IAAF’s ruling could affect female athletes in every sport. It is by far the most prominent and detailed ruling that the court has delivered regarding biological sex, and it is a potentially far-reaching one. From now on, the CAS will almost certainly use testosterone levels to determine who should be allowed to compete in women’s events. These tests will apply not only to intersex athletes, but also to trans women, who were born male but identify as women. The International Olympic Committee (IOC) had already introduced a testosterone limit of 10 nmol/L for trans women in all sports in 2016, replacing its previous requirement for athletes to have undergone genital-reconstruction surgery. It is now considering reducing the limit to 5 nmol/L. This rule change has not been tested at the court, but after Wednesday’s precedent it looks likely to stand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;A binary code&lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How to distinguish between men and women? If sports administrators want to maintain separate competitions for different sexes, any attempt to draw a firm biological distinction between them will miscategorise some people. That leaves them with two options. The first is to pick a binary physical characteristic, such as having—or not having—testes or a Y chromosome, a typical (but not universal) biological marker for males. The second is to pick a physical characteristic that exists on a spectrum, such as endogenous testosterone levels, and to set a threshold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first approach might seem more robust. Officials at the Olympics used chromosome testing to verify athletes’ sex between 1968 and 1996. But it turns out that some women who possess both Y chromosomes and testes receive no performance-enhancing effects from them. Maria José Martínez-Patiño, a Spanish hurdler, was kicked off the national athletics team (and shunned by her colleagues and boyfriend) after failing a verification test in 1985. Three years passed before geneticists could prove that her body was insensitive to testosterone, and that her intersex condition thus conferred no athletic advantage. The IAAF subsequently stopped chromosome testing, but not soon enough for Ms Patiño to save her career.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her case was extremely rare. Various estimates suggest that the share of intersex people in the general population ranges from 0.05% to 1.7%, depending on how broadly the concept is defined. But those figures include conditions that neither raise questions about a person’s biological sex nor confer any conceivable sporting advantage (as in Ms Patiño’s case). Over time, officials have decided that they are unwilling to exclude people who fall into this category. Their approach now is to include people in women’s sports unless they demonstrably have an unfair competitive advantage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This has led governing bodies to the second option: picking a physical characteristic that exists on a spectrum. Scientists generally agree that testosterone is the best candidate. The hormone drives the development of male characteristics from puberty, such as bigger muscles, sturdier bones and less fat. Ross Tucker, a sports scientist who advised Ms Semenya on the case, has shown that the gap between boys’ and girls’ running times grows wider once they become teenagers, as males experience this physiological boost. In adulthood, the fastest men run about 10% faster than women. The discrepancy is even bigger for some other field events, such as javelin and pole vault. It is no coincidence that anti-doping bodies ban competitors from juicing up on testosterone artificially.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One advantage of setting a testosterone threshold is that athletes such as Ms Patiño, who produce lots of it without any benefit, can lower their levels without affecting their performance. But this approach also poses lots of problems. Working out where the threshold should be is tricky. Defining femaleness on a sliding scale means that trans women, as well as intersex athletes, can qualify after hormone therapy. That is unlikely to undo all the sporting advantages of a testosterone-charged puberty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lack of reliable data complicates things further. Whereas the hormone-induced gap between male and female performance is obvious, the correlation between testosterone levels and athletic prowess within the tiny group of elite female competitors is weak. This is a select group of highly unusual people who have a similar biological and sporting profile. (Some trans women have erroneously used the weakness of this correlation within a small sample to claim that testosterone does not matter at all across the two sexes, which Mr Tucker strongly disputes.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So measuring the advantages of abnormally high testosterone levels among women is tricky, which could explain why the IAAF struggled to find any sign of such effects in most of the events that it studied. The organisation’s analysis might also have had methodological flaws. It compared women whose testosterone levels are in the top third of the range against those in the bottom third, when it might be more enlightening to look at the farther extremes of the range instead. And Mr Tucker was one a trio of independent researchers who found that the IAAF’s figures were riddled with errors, such as athletes who had been double-counted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It takes an extraordinary person, such as Ms Semenya, to demonstrate just how potent testosterone can be in women’s sport. A by-product of her first experience with hormone therapy is that we know roughly how much it hindered her performance: by 4%. But whether that is an appropriate adjustment is purely subjective. Ms Semenya thinks it is unfair: “I just want to run naturally, the way I was born,” she says. Sports officials have ultimately come to an arbitrary decision. The IAAF’s 10 and 5 nmol/L thresholds were largely based on estimating the maximum level that a non-intersex woman could naturally reach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The law of comparative advantage &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The guesswork becomes even sketchier for combat and contact sports, because measuring the performance of a wrestler or rugby player is much harder than timing a runner. Bone structure is also more important in these games, which gives anyone who develops a stronger skeleton at puberty a permanent advantage, regardless of how much hormone therapy they later go through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most controversial cases in these sports have involved trans women, rather than intersex ones. Such “transitioning” is a broad process that may include declaring oneself to be a woman, or undergoing hormone therapy or genital reconstruction surgery (transition goes the other way, too).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fallon Fox, an American mixed-martial arts fighter, was pilloried by commentators and other combatants when she revealed in 2013 that she had undergone gender-reassignment surgery. One male fighter called her a “lying, sick, sociopathic, disgusting freak”. She last appeared in the ring in 2014. Hannah Mouncey, a trans woman who had represented the Australian men’s handball team before changing gender and switching to the women’s team, was barred from the women’s Australian Football League in 2017. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reliable data about the change in performance for trans women are just as scarce as for intersex ones. Joanna Harper, a scientist who is also a trans runner, and who appeared as a witness for the IAAF in Ms Semenya’s case, has conducted one of the few studies to date. Her research covered eight non-elite endurance runners who competed first as men, then as women. She found that their slower times after hormone therapy put them in roughly the same position within women’s races as they had achieved within men’s. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the data are far too scant to say that this pattern holds for all athletes in every sport. If a handful of trans women fare better in elite women’s events than they did in men’s—suggesting that they have maintained an unusually large athletic advantage, even after hormone therapy—then sports administrators could find that the testosterone threshold creates a bigger quandary than chromosome tests did. Rather than cruelly ending the career of a few athletes such as Ms Patiño, they could reduce the chances of victory for a large number of women who would struggle to beat disproportionately successful trans competitors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Harper points out that there has been no deluge of trans women gaming the system. The trans athlete who has come closest to dominating an individual sport is Laurel Hubbard, a New Zealander who held junior national weightlifting records as a man and then became an international contender as a woman. In 2017 she finished second in the World Championships, and was leading at the Commonwealth Games in 2018 before an elbow injury. It was only in 2016 that trans women could compete in women’s events without having undergone genital-reconstruction surgery—which only a small proportion of trans people do. Not a single trans athlete has yet competed in the Olympics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nonetheless, the possibility remains that the testosterone threshold could allow several pretty good male competitors to reign supreme after transitioning to become women. Many women worry that such champions are imminent. Some trans women accuse them of scaremongering. Only the passage of time and collection of more data will prove who is right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regardless of what happens, the court’s ruling on Ms Semenya’s case confirms that the definition of what it means to be female in sport will from now on be set on a sliding scale. If anybody thought that the decade-long dispute would clarify the matter, they were wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 04:08:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jihadism in Africa, a Democratic rethink of foreign policy, and what showbiz can teach drug companies]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/02/jihadism-in-africa-a-democratic-rethink-of-foreign-policy-and-what-showbiz-can-teach-drug-companies]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-02T17:15:24Z&quot;&gt;May 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A selection of three essential articles read aloud from the latest issue of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;. This week, the fight against jihadists is moving to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/04/the-wests-new-front-against-jihadism-is-in-the-sahel&quot;&gt;Africa&lt;/a&gt;. Despite Western help, governments in the Sahel are struggling to beat back violent extremists. Next, the Democrats and American &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/04/foreign-policy-after-donald-trump&quot;&gt;foreign policy&lt;/a&gt;—could radical rethinkers emerge? (12:43). And, Netflix and pills—why the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/04/the-antibiotic-industry-is-broken&quot;&gt;drugs industry&lt;/a&gt; should take inspiration from the entertainment industry (23:38)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-may2nd2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 01:07:51 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“America and China are spending enormous sums on defence”]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/02/america-and-china-are-spending-enormous-sums-on-defence]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/china_navy_day.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-02T10:02:01Z&quot;&gt;May 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;GOVERNMENTS THE world over are beefing up &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/international/2019/04/28/military-spending-around-the-world-is-booming&quot;&gt;defence spending&lt;/a&gt;—chief among them America’s and China’s. But some of the usual big military spenders are actually shrinking budgets. May Day protests in France took a violent turn this year, and that complicates President Macron’s efforts to calm an already protest-prone populace. And academics have been trying to determine which English-speaking country produces the most &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/30/who-are-the-biggest-bullshitters&quot;&gt;bullshit&lt;/a&gt;. Runtime: 21min.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/buythebullet-globaldefencespending&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 23:07:09 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg wants to build WeChat for the West]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/02/mark-zuckerberg-wants-to-build-wechat-for-the-west]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_wbp001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;N HIS SPARE&lt;/small&gt; time Mark Zuckerberg likes to run. In 2016 Facebook’s boss pledged to cover 365 miles (587km) that year and, ever the overachiever, completed the challenge by July. He does not practise martial arts, but his almost discomfiting poise could lead you to mistake him for a master of something like aikido. That would be appropriate, for in his professional life Mr Zuckerberg is trying to turn his opponents’ energy against them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When in early March he announced that Facebook would follow a “privacy-focused vision for social networking”, complete with encrypted messages that even the firm cannot peer into, observers interpreted this as a defensive move. Some discerned a belated response to outrage over privacy abuses on the world’s largest social network. Others saw the plan to knit together its instant-messaging services, chiefly Messenger and WhatsApp, as a way to make the company harder to break up, as some American politicians demand. Others still spied a ruse to escape liability for violent user content, now that Facebook would no longer be able to read any of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All three rationales probably played a part. Yet the firm’s “privacy pivot” is perhaps better seen as an aikido-like redirection of detractors’ momentum. Mr Zuckerberg’s speech at his firm’s annual developer conference in San Jose on April 30th suggested as much. Far from retreating, he is limbering up for a new contest—to reinvent social networking, this time around messaging. “The future is private,” he declared grandiosely. Though he might not admit it in public, he seems keen to turn Facebook into a Western version of WeChat, the Chinese messaging app whose array of mobile services, from payments to filing court paperwork, has made it ubiquitous in China—even if his recent pledge to store user information only in countries that respect the rule of law is an implicit admission that he has given up on the Chinese market, where Communist minders insist that Western firms must keep all data locally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;Older. And wiser?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook’s core business is maturing, as its boss clearly sees. Its operating margins—42%, excluding $3bn set aside to cover an expected fine by America’s Federal Trade Commission for privacy violations—remain the envy of the tech world (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/02/american-technology-firms-mixed-results&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;). In the latest quarter revenue grew by 26% compared with the previous year, exceeding $15bn. But user growth is slowing. In some rich countries, especially European ones, it is flat. The young prefer social media which are more “intimate” and “ephemeral”, like Snapchat, which pioneered “stories”, messages and pictures that disappear after 24 hours—and which Facebook aped. More than 500m users of Instagram, Messenger and WhatsApp now post stories every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Zuckerberg expects migration from the online “town square” to a digital “living room” to continue; stories may soon outnumber posts on Facebook’s newsfeed. The plan is to build it around WhatsApp, which already offers secure texting. It would let users find each other, pay digital and offline shopkeepers, or purchase a cornucopia of online services—perhaps one day using Facebook’s own currency. In time, the thinking goes, it may become as indispensable to Westerners as WeChat is in China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some elements of the new platform already exist; WhatsApp is testing a payment service in India. Others, such as new shopping features on Instagram, were launched in San Jose. All this falls short of a full-blown business plan. But the contours of Mr Zuckerberg’s vision are taking shape. The 34-year-old is proceeding more cautiously than in Facebook’s early years, when he was guided by the now infamous injunction to “move fast and break things”—but no less deliberately.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is just as well, for “platform shifts” are tricky. Microsoft did not see smartphones coming and Facebook itself almost missed the rise of mobile apps. To succeed, it must clear a number of hurdles. The first is technical. Facebook wants an Instagram user to be able to send a note directly to a friend on WhatsApp. Creating a common phone book for these services, with a combined total of 2.7bn users and different source codes, presents a knotty problem for programmers. Chris Cox, one of Mr Zuckerberg’s top lieutenants, is rumoured to have left the company in March because he did not think it could be done (this week Mr Cox attributed his departure to “artistic differences” with his boss).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second challenge is economic. WeChat could become the platform of choice on smartphones because China had no dominant app stores. Facebook must contend with incumbents such as Apple and Google. Since you can’t sell microtargeted adverts against encrypted messages your algorithms cannot see, the new platform will need a fresh way to make money. For all its ubiquity, WeChat is no cash cow (Tencent, its owner, makes most of its revenue from online games). Maintaining Facebook’s fat margins would require new revenue sources, such as charging businesses to contact users or taking a cut of any purchases, as credit-card issuers do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, there are the entwined issues of privacy and competition. Mr Zuckerberg accepts that a lot of people dismiss Facebook’s sincerity here—his recent article in the &lt;em &gt;Washington Post&lt;/em&gt;, imploring governments to regulate social media, notwithstanding. It will continue to collect plenty of data. Integrating these, and the underlying apps, could in turn enable Facebook to convert its dominance in public social networking into power over private messaging. This reminds seasoned competition regulators of Microsoft’s attempts to bundle its operating system with a web browser in the mid-1990s in a bid to control cyberspace. With the internet’s rise, the stakes today are bigger: no country wants one firm to become society’s de facto operating system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since its services cost nothing, Facebook says, it is not gouging users. It could argue that a single dominant social network is easier to police than lots of smaller ones and has greater financial and technical capacity to keep users safe from harmful content. And it would be a bulwark against WeChat, which might otherwise become a force outside China—bringing the Chinese surveillance state with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, Mr Zuckerberg’s &lt;em &gt;Washington Post&lt;/em&gt; article looks like a bid to broker a 21st-century version of the Kingsbury Commitment of 1913, when &lt;small&gt;AT&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;T&lt;/small&gt;, then America’s telephone monopoly, accepted government oversight and agreed to spin off some of its businesses in exchange for not being nationalised or broken up. The difference is that, unlike &lt;small&gt;AT&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;T&lt;/small&gt;, Facebook’s reach extends beyond America and spans a growing range of industries, from advertising to finance. It must grapple with politicians, regulators and rivals. If enough opponents gang up at once, even the most gifted aikido master may struggle to fend them off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Finance and economics&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Mark Zuckerberg’s WeChat moment&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 22:06:33 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Satellite data shed new light on North Korea’s opaque economy]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/04/satellite-data-shed-new-light-on-north-koreas-opaque-economy]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_gdc101_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;

&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190504_GDNorthKorea/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;V&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;IEWED FROM&lt;/small&gt; space at night, North Korea looks like the recently released first image of a black hole: an abyss, ringed by the brilliant glow of South Korea, China and Russia, from which nothing can escape. But the Hermit Kingdom does emit a bit of light, which orbiting satellites detect. And nocturnal luminosity is one of the few reliable sources of information about the country. It implies that North Korea’s economy is poorer, more volatile and more vulnerable to weather than formerly thought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Night lights are a strong proxy for economic activity. A new paper by the &lt;small&gt;IMF&lt;/small&gt; finds that they explain 44% of the variation in countries’ &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; per person—as close a tie as that between a person’s height and hand size. In places where records are poor or manipulated, night lights offer an alternative measure of output. One study found that among countries with similar luminosity, autocracies reported &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; growth 15-30% higher than democracies did.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Nowhere are good economic data rarer than in North Korea. The most detailed numbers come from South Korea’s central bank, which derives them from figures on production volumes of various goods. When adjusted for the cost of living in a developing Asian economy, the bank’s most recent estimate of North Korea’s annual &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; per person is enough to buy goods and services that would cost $2,500 in America.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190504_GDNorthKorea_Chart/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The picture painted by night lights, however, is even grimmer. In 2013 a group of scholars compared luminosity and &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; within rural China, obtaining an equation to estimate economic output from light. A forthcoming paper by World Data Lab, a startup, and a team of researchers applies this formula to North Korea. It yields a standard of living that would cost $1,400 a year in America, making North Korea one of the world’s ten poorest countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The data also suggest that the economy has been unusually volatile. In 2013-15 luminosity fell by 40%. That implies a 12% reduction in &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt;, including 19% in the capital region, Pyongyang. Since 2016, however, the country has brightened again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190504_GDNorthKorea_Pyongyang/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;International sanctions are unlikely to have produced this darkening. They were made stricter in 2016-17, just as luminosity rose. A drop in the prices of North Korean exports, like coal, may have played a part.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the main cause was probably weather. North Korea relies on hydropower, and in 2015 it was parched by a drought. The Bank of Korea also reckons that electricity, gas and water output fell by 13% in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The economy may not have shrunk as much as the dimming suggests. Recessions caused by power cuts could disproportionately reduce lighting. Many North Koreans own solar panels, which power daytime activity not shown in night lights. And state buildings, whose illumination is a political choice, make up much of the capital’s glow. As with physics inside a black hole, no one knows what economic laws apply within North Korea’s eerie silhouette.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nonetheless, a 40% drop in luminosity indicates a serious recession. And this year the government has admitted publicly that heatwaves, floods and drought have caused a dire food shortfall. The regime appears much better prepared to weather trade sanctions than the wrath of nature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p data-interactive-source=&quot;&quot; &gt;Sources: World Data Lab in collaboration with the NOMIS Foundation, Vienna University of Economics and Business, and the International Institute for Applied Systems Analysis; Earth Observation Group, NOAA NCEI; “Illuminating economic growth”, by Yingyao Hu and Jiaxiong Yao, IMF working paper, April 2019&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/gd-north-korea/css/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/gd-north-korea/css/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Graphic detail&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;When the lights go out&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 21:06:20 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Xiaomi’s founder loses a billion-yuan bet]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/02/xiaomis-founder-loses-a-billion-yuan-bet]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_wbp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;N 2013 BUSINESS&lt;/small&gt; folk gathered in Beijing to honour Chinese “Economic Figures of the Year” were treated to an unexpected twist. One of the winners, Lei Jun, ventured that in five years the sales of Xiaomi, the smartphone-maker he founded in 2010, would surpass those of Gree, a manufacturer of air-conditioners with government roots. To make things interesting Dong Mingzhu, an entrepreneur and Gree’s chairwoman with whom Mr Lei had shared an award, bet him 1bn yuan ($148m today) that her company’s turnover would stay ahead. Mr Lei accepted. Since March 19th, when Xiaomi posted revenues of 175bn yuan in 2018, corporate China has awaited the figure from Gree. On April 28th the verdict was in: it made 200bn yuan. Mr Lei was out of the money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bet looked bold for Mr Lei in 2013. Xiaomi was then making a quarter of Gree’s 120bn yuan in annual sales. The “Apple of the East”, as it was dubbed, represented a new sort of Chinese company: market-driven and spunky, not state-led and stodgy; online instead of bricks and mortar; relying on digital technology rather than mechanical engineering. By mid-2018 Xiaomi’s revenue neared 90% of Gree’s (see chart). When the firm floated on the Hong Kong stock exchange last July it was valued at $54bn. It has become the fourth-most-valuable Chinese brand, according to Brand&lt;small&gt;Z&lt;/small&gt;, a consultancy; Gree is 29th. Ms Dong herself suggested that the wager was meaningless given how different Gree and Xiaomi were.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_WBC817.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190504_WBC817.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190504_WBC817.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190504_WBC817.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190504_WBC817.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190504_WBC817.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190504_WBC817.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190504_WBC817.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190504_WBC817.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190504_WBC817.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In reality, the companies are not that dissimilar—and growing less so as China’s economy modernises. Both have boomed thanks to swelling Chinese disposable incomes. The fiercely independent Ms Dong has repeated publicly that her firm must fight for customers just as private ones like Xiaomi do. In April Gree’s largest shareholder, a regulator overseeing state-owned enterprises, said it would sell most of its 18% stake. To build an ecosystem of devices controlled by his mobile phones, Mr Lei relies on closeness to China’s manufacturing heartland, Gree’s home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They face similar challenges, too. The competition in their core markets is stiff. Xiaomi’s margins from low-cost phones are wafer-thin. Gree has lost share of Chinese air-con sales to rivals such as Haier and Midea, which are introducing more high-tech models. Xiaomi and Gree have both taken a punt on changing their original business models. Gree is selling more online. Xiaomi is opening more physical stores. To keep up with rapidly changing consumer tastes, Gree has moved into smart home appliances, as well as low-emission vehicles and chip design—areas in which Xiaomi now does business, too. Ms Dong now makes smartphones, and Mr Lei has a line of air-conditioners. Whether or not he makes good on it—gambling is outlawed on the mainland—the bet highlights the changing face of China Inc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Business&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;The billion-yuan bet&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 21:06:19 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>