<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Deaths of despair, once an American phenomenon, now haunt Britain]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/14/deaths-of-despair-once-an-american-phenomenon-now-haunt-britain]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_brp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-14T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN RECENT YEARS America has witnessed a troubling trend: a rise in what have become known as “deaths of despair”. Sir Angus Deaton and Anne Case, an academic couple both of Princeton University, have tracked an increase in the number of middle-aged whites dying from drug overdoses, suicides and alcohol-related conditions. Their work has shaped political debate in America. Now a report by the Institute for Fiscal Studies (IFS), a British think-tank, published on May 14th, suggests that something similar is taking place on the other side of the Atlantic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is one of the initial findings of a five-year review of inequality begun by the IFS, which will look at everything from income to political participation. In its scale and scope, the exercise will be on a par with the Mirrlees Review, a gargantuan assessment of the tax system undertaken by the same think-tank, which issued its final report in 2011 and has been a reference point for researchers ever since. Sir Angus, who won the Nobel prize for economics in 2015, is chairing a panel of worthies overseeing the project.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BRC016.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190518_BRC016.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190518_BRC016.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190518_BRC016.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190518_BRC016.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190518_BRC016.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190518_BRC016.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190518_BRC016.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190518_BRC016.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190518_BRC016.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The analysis shows that, after steadying during the 2000s, deaths of despair among middle-aged British men have in the past eight years or so been moving in the wrong direction (see chart). In 2017 they drew level with deaths from heart disease. In part because deaths from cancer have stopped falling, overall mortality among middle-aged men is on its way up for the first time in decades. Deaths of despair among women are also rising, but less quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BRC012.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190518_BRC012.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190518_BRC012.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190518_BRC012.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190518_BRC012.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190518_BRC012.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190518_BRC012.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190518_BRC012.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190518_BRC012.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190518_BRC012.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Economists argue over what has caused the rise in deaths of despair in America. The ready availability of opioid painkillers is thought to play some part. So may economic misfortune: those with no education beyond high-school, among whom the rise has been particularly rapid, have also seen their income stagnate. However, Sir Angus and Professor Case put more emphasis on the impact of the erosion of traditional social structures, including trade unions, the church and marriage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far there is no comparable research on Britain, though the IFS is working on it. Circumstantial evidence points to some possible explanations, however. As in America, poor prescription practices may have contributed to a rise in opioid abuse (though to nowhere near the same extent). Deaths which were related to the use of opioids have risen from 800 a year in the mid-1990s to 2,000 a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Economic factors are likely to play a role too. Official data suggest that deaths of despair jumped in the mid-1980s, when traditional industries such as coal-mining were closing. The continued decline of manufacturing and the rise of service industries has probably favoured women. In 2004 the female employment rate exceeded the male rate in none of Britain’s local authorities. Now it is higher in 12. Men who no longer feel that they hold a privileged position in society may think they have little to live for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the fact that deaths from despair began rising again around 2010 points to another factor: fiscal austerity. A big tightening of welfare policy, including harsher use of sanctions against those who fail to meet job-searching requirements, has made the experience of looking for work progressively more uncomfortable—though why that should affect men more than women is not clear. Finding out what is really going on should be a priority for Sir Angus and his team. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 13:06:43 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Smartphones are driving Americans to distraction]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/13/smartphones-are-driving-americans-to-distraction]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_woc111.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-13T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EVER SINCE Apple launched the first iPhone in 2007 the small digital screen has become a ubiquitous part of life. Today in America there are some 260m smartphones in use, one for every adult. But the omnipresence of the device appears to be behind a recent increase in pedestrian deaths on America’s roads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At first glance, Americans appear to be restrained when using their smartphone while driving. One survey conducted by the Department of Transport (DoT) reckons that around 5% of drivers used their mobile phones behind the wheel in 2017. DoT researchers arrive at this figure by observing drivers’ mobile-phone use in situ at randomly allocated stopping places. By contrast Zendrive, a startup, employs software that is able to remotely track drivers’ use of their mobile phones. Using data on 60bn journeys taken in 2018 Zendrive reckons that the true rate of smartphone use behind the wheel may be as high as 60%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To what extent is distracted driving causing people to crash more frequently? Data released by the DoT last month suggest that over the past five years smartphones have caused just 2,105 fatal crashes (1.2% of the total). But there is reason to believe that this figure undercounts the true toll as not all police agencies are able to report the true cause of a crash. About 20% of the victims of distracted-driving fatalities are not drivers or passengers, but other road users such as pedestrians and cyclists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While cars have become progressively safer thanks to airbags, side-impact bars and the like, pedestrians remain just as vulnerable to reckless driving. Their vulnerability appears to be demonstrated in the data. Between 1994 and 2009 the rate of deaths on American roads fell by an average rate of 2.6% for motor-vehicle users and by 3.2% for pedestrians. However, since 2009, while deaths from those in vehicles have flat-lined, pedestrian deaths have risen steadily. They are now 36% higher than their 2009 rate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not all these deaths can be attributed to smartphone use and distracted driving. Higher sales of SUVs, which are bigger and more deadly vehicles, are partly to blame, too. And it is likely that some of the pedestrians who are killed are distracted by their smartphones when they should be focused on safely crossing the street. Whatever the proximate cause, a back-of-the-envelope calculation by &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; finds that if pedestrian deaths had continued their secular decline since 2009 an additional 20,000 deaths could have been averted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As things stand just 18 states in America ban the handling of mobile phones while driving. North Carolina is the latest state to be considering a ban and evidence suggests that it would save lives. Research published last month finds that states that banned texting-while-driving reduced emergency-room visits from car crashes by 4%, equivalent to 1,600 fewer ER visits per state per year. The more Americans focus on the road ahead, the safer everyone will be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 02:09:23 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[An apartment scandal embarrasses senior Bulgarian officials]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/13/an-apartment-scandal-embarrasses-senior-bulgarian-officials]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_eup503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-13T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FEW BULGARIANS who walk by the Letera, a new luxury apartment building in Sofia, can read the texts inscribed on its facade. They are written in the Glagolitic alphabet, a medieval ecclesiastic script. This is part of the building’s aesthetic, a sort of religious-nationalist elitism. The advertising video on its website is a tribute to early Slavic Christianity, featuring cowled monks in the mist. Over the entrance, the 91st psalm offers protection for the righteous from their enemies: “He who dwells in the secret place of the Most High, abideth in the shadow of the Almighty.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tsvetan Tsvetanov (pictured, right), the owner of the Letera’s penthouse, may wish he dwelt in a somewhat more secret place. In late March, Mr Tsvetanov, the second most powerful figure in the ruling GERB party, was revealed to have obtained his apartment in a complicated exchange that valued it at about €250,000 ($280,000), perhaps a quarter of the going rate. He denies any wrongdoing, but has resigned as GERB’s parliamentary leader. He is still chairman of the party’s campaign committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since then nearly a dozen other highly placed government officials have been found to have received cut-price apartments in various buildings around Sofia. Many have stepped down, including the former justice minister. Even the chairman of the government anti-corruption commission is under investigation, for failing to declare that his top-floor loft included his building’s entire 186-square-metre roof terrace. (He claimed it was shared by all the residents, though it can be reached only from his apartment.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The “apartments scandal” has infuriated Bulgarian citizens, even though the sums involved are far smaller than in other corruption affairs, such as the billion-dollar collapse of the politically connected Corporate Commercial Bank in 2014. “The thing about this story is that you can touch it,” explains Polina Paunova of Svobodna Evropa, the Bulgarian branch of Radio Free Europe, which first reported the scandal. Unusually for eastern Europe, about 90% of Bulgarians own their homes, so property is an emotional subject—especially with values going up: housing prices rose 35% in Sofia between 2015 and 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The media have become obsessed by details of unlisted balconies and private elevators, but the real implications go much deeper. The most difficult problem for corrupt politicians is justifying cash holdings that vastly exceed their salaries, explains Nikolay Staykov of the Anti-Corruption Fund, a watchdog that collaborated with Svobodna Evropa to uncover the scandal. Property transactions provide ways to launder such money, such as declaring a purchase at the lowest plausible value, and then reselling it to a friendly party at the highest plausible price.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scandal involves powerful commercial interests as well. The Letera was built by Arteks, a developer that is also building a 34-storey apartment tower that would be the tallest in Sofia. That project, the “Golden Century” building, is opposed by neighbourhood groups. More important, it may not be legal: its construction permit, granted in 2007, expired in November 2017. The company contends that amendments to the construction code passed by parliament in January 2017, when Mr Tsvetanov was leader of the GERB fraction, retroactively granted it an extra three years. Mr Tsvetanov says that when he was negotiating to buy his apartment from Arteks, he was not aware of the problem with the Golden Century’s permit, and that in any case the amendments do not apply. Arteks’s lawyers say they do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since they joined the European Union in 2007, Bulgaria and Romania have been subjected to special monitoring by the European Commission to check that they are making progress against corruption. Romania established an independent prosecutor’s office that convicted thousands of officials, but has since backtracked and last year fired the prosecutor. Bulgaria, meanwhile, has been evasive from the start. The current government anti-corruption commission, formed in early 2018, is the third iteration: earlier versions accomplished little, and were dissolved under EU pressure for reform. With its commissioner now under investigation, the new version is just as compromised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boyko Borisov, Bulgaria’s prime minister for most of the past ten years, is a canny operator who has his party entirely in his grip. His position is not under threat. But the apartments scandal has pushed GERB’s popularity below that of the rival Socialist Party in some polls, and it may have wrecked Mr Borisov’s ability to deliver one of his campaign promises: ending the EU special monitoring programme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Mr Tsvetanov is defending himself by trumpeting his role as an advocate for Bulgaria’s planned purchase of F-16 fighter jets from America. Like the others accused in the apartment scandal, he hopes the words of the psalm hold true: “No evil shall befall you, nor shall any plague come near your dwelling.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 02:09:22 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[From the Catholic faith&#x27;s European heartland, a cry of female protest]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/05/13/from-the-catholic-faiths-european-heartland-a-cry-of-female-protest]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BLP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-13T17:25:00Z&quot;&gt;May 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ACROSS MANY parts of the Christian world, soothing and well-worn sermons were preached on May 12th about the indispensable role of women in upholding the faith: it was, after all, Mother’s Day in many countries. But in Münster, a bastion of German Catholicism, a somewhat different female voice was raised. Catholic women in that city have been co-ordinating a nationwide, week-long “strike” to back their demand for greater female participation in the life of the church, and other reforms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The protest, which involves staying away from Mass, holding outdoor services and withdrawing voluntary labour from church institutions, has been dubbed “Maria 2.0”. Its banner is a picture of the Virgin Mary with her mouth sealed by sticking-plaster, implying that she has been unfairly silenced. Organisers say the strike, which ends on May 18th, has won support in 100 locations across Germany, and messages of solidarity from other Teutonic places like Austria and Switzerland. “Many words [on this subject] have been exchanged and then disappeared into thin air, and now it is time for a different kind of protest,” one of the prime movers, Andrea Voss-Frick, told a local broadcaster. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The women want quicker progress to a reasonable gender balance in the management posts that are open to lay people; they have been promised a 30% quota by 2023. More controversially, they want their gender to be admitted to the “ordained ministry”. This ultimately means becoming priests, and at a minimum implies being accepted to the slightly lower but still important rank of deacon. They want the rule requiring priests to be celibate to be scrapped. One of their complaints against the celibate male priests who now dominate the church is that even where they are not directly responsible, they have mismanaged and covered up the problem of clerical abuse of minors.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The protest has thrown into sharp relief some dilemmas faced by Catholicism in the prosperous Western places which used to be the faith&amp;#x27;s principal locus, before the centre of gravity started shifting to the developing world. Given that the Catholic faith is a global body with a single leader, the German Catholic church cannot act unilaterally over sensitive matters like ordination and gender, but it cannot ignore pressure from its most dynamic members either. As Thomas Bremer, a professor of ecumenical theology at Münster University puts it: “[The protests are] an indication of the common mood in the mainstream Catholic church in Germany and the bishops will have to relate to it somehow....[given that] the people who took part in these actions, or sympathised, are also the ones who are most active in the church and keep its structures alive.&amp;quot;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nobody, however, should expect a revolution. Pope Francis all but admitted last week that the church’s internal deliberations over female deacons (let alone female priests) were deadlocked. He said a commission which has been examining whether there had been such a thing as ordained deaconesses in the early church had failed to reach any agreed conclusion. Conservatives (including the most conservative of Germany&amp;#x27;s bishops) argue that ordained female deacons clearly did not exist in the early Christian era, and they should not exist now, because that would imply rejecting God&amp;#x27;s revelation to the world through Jesus Christ and his immediate followers. Indeed at least one German bishop has taken the hard-line view that early Christianity differed from other religions of its time in not having female celebrants of its most important rites. This implies that the male monopoly was a conscious choice, not just a cultural reflex. Francis has assured traditionalists that he takes their arguments seriously, but he has cited the shift in Catholic thinking over the death penalty (from conditional acceptance to total rejection) as an example of how “divine revelation” can find new interpetations in a changing world. But that kind of logic is exactly what conservatives find flawed in the current pontiff&amp;#x27;s thinking, and some are determined to restrain his reforming instincts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The immediate reaction of senior German Catholics to the week-long protest has laid bare the church’s internal divisions . The two mainstream organisations of Catholic women have voiced understanding for the protest. The Bishops’ Conference has expressed willingness to give a sympathetic hearing but lamented the form of protest chosen. At least one bishop, Franz-Josef Bode, and many ordinary priests have said the protest is on balance something to be welcomed. Germany, however, still has plenty of conservative prelates. One, Bishop Rudolf Voderholzer, has said it is a waste of time and energy to consider any changes to the celibate male priesthood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;German-speaking Europe is emerging as an arena for intra-Catholic conflict. Although declining, the German Catholic church is not in freefall, as it seems to be in other parts of western Europe, such as France and even Ireland. In 2017, the number of Catholics in Germany inched downwards by 270,000 to 23.3m but they remain the country&amp;#x27;s largest religious group. Among, for example, upwardly-mobile Catholics born to Irish or east European parents in England, the typical response to abuse scandals or other disappointments has been to give up on the church. In Germany, a significant percentage of Mass-goers, including some well-educated and articulate women, are determined to stay and fight for change. This will not be the last cry of protest from women in the Catholic church. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 01:08:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A new podcast shows why some obituaries need sound as well as words]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/13/a-new-podcast-shows-why-some-obituaries-need-sound-as-well-as-words]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BKP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-13T13:00:21Z&quot;&gt;May 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHEN AUDREY HEPBURN died in 1993, newspapers’ obituaries often mentioned the unusual lilt of her voice. The &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; noted that she spoke with the “trace of a European accent”, “a hint of mischief”. Cecil Beaton, in the &lt;em&gt;Telegraph&lt;/em&gt;, described her “singsong cadence that develops into a flat drawl ending in a child-like query”: he thought it had “the quality of heartbreak”. The &lt;em&gt;Los Angeles Times&lt;/em&gt; said that “her melodic, hard-to-place accent and haunting beauty captivated audiences and helped win her the Academy Award as best actress”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clearly Hepburn’s voice was part of her charm, but its precise sound is hard to capture on the page and hard for the reader to imagine. That is why, 26 years later, Mo Rocca has retold Hepburn’s story, this time in a different medium. On his new podcast, “Mobituaries”, the journalist dedicates 40 minutes to the movie star, tracing her life from her birth in Belgium in 1929, through her film career to her humanitarian work. The episode is interspersed with clips from “Funny Face” and “Breakfast at Tiffany’s”; there is room for her dreamy, melancholic rendition of “Moon River” (pictured). The voices of those who knew her, or who admired her work, are also included. The late Nora Ephron is recorded in an interview from 2011 gushing over Hepburn’s grace and beauty, saying that “there was no one like her, ever”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Free from the demands of the news agenda, “Mobituaries” eulogises individuals, characters and things (one episode contemplates “Neanderthals: death of a human species”; another “Death of a tree: roots of a rivalry”). It is experimental in form—each episode is an unusual blend of interviews, animated discussion, clips and music—and a way for Mr Rocca to explore subjects that intrigue him. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He is astute when picking those subjects. Only a podcast, for instance, could demonstrate the skill of Vaughn Meader, an impersonator of John F. Kennedy. The episode considers Meader’s rise to fame, what his career was like during the 12 months of Kennedy’s presidency, and what happened after the assassination in November 1963. It includes clips from “The First Family”, a hit album which launched Meader to stardom, as well as snippets of later interviews where he expressed exasperation—sadness, almost—at being asked to do “the voice”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Musicians, too, are a natural fit for the airwaves and Sammy Davis Jr., a talented singer and impressionist, is eulogised in the fifth episode. The featured interviewees maintain that it was the emotion Davis conveyed in his music that made his performances so special. The listener hears it for themself: Mr Rocca juxtaposes clips of the same song, performed first by Davis and then by another artist. The difference is surprising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere, Mr Rocca pursues more abstract discussions. An episode on deaths in sitcoms focuses on three types of death: the death of love for a character, a change of actor playing a character and the death of a character within the plot. Mr Rocca explores the phenomenon of “Chuck Cunningham syndrome”, whereby a character simply disappears (named after a figure in “Happy Days” who suffered that fate), with Alan Sepinwall, chief television critic for &lt;em&gt;Rolling Stone&lt;/em&gt;. Clips of dialogue from a number of shows support the discussion, but it is interviews that allow the listener to understand the impact of such passings. Lila Garret, a writer on “Bewitched”, laments that they had to replace actor Dick York due to his poor health. Decades on, Jamiee Foxworth expresses disbelief at her character being written out of “Family Matters” in 1992. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of this is to say that the written obituary has been left behind—a writer’s career, for example, is best weighed up in words, and the ambiguity of language can be useful—but Mr Rocca shows how some stories are enriched by sound. It makes for compelling listening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: The Economist, as well as running an obituary every week in print, also features them on occasion in “The Intelligence”, our daily podcast&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 21:05:50 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The IMF has agreed to break Pakistan’s fall. Again]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/13/the-imf-has-agreed-to-break-pakistans-fall-again]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_fnp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-13T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt; FAMILIARITY, THEY say, breeds contempt. Few countries are as familiar with the IMF as Pakistan. The over-indebted country of 200m people has obtained 21 loans from the fund, as many as Argentina. On May 12th this familiarity deepened further. The country’s government, led by Imran Khan, a former cricket star who heads the Pakistan Tehreek-e-Insaf party, said it had reached a deal with the IMF’s staff to borrow another $6bn over three years. The agreement now awaits formal approval from the fund’s bosses in Washington, and the support of other international lenders, including the World Bank and the Asian Development Bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The loan will relieve Pakistan’s dollar shortage but do little to improve the IMF’s standing in the country. In return for its money, the fund expects the government to raise tax revenues and utility prices—and to let the currency fall, if need be. That will help narrow Pakistan’s wide trade and budget deficits. But it will also curb growth and increase inflation in the short term. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The full agreement has not yet been published. But some details have been released and others leaked to the local press. Pakistan must cut its budget deficit (before debt service) to 0.6% of GDP next fiscal year (which starts in July) from the deficit of over 1.7% that the IMF expects for this year. To meet this goal, the government has reportedly promised to remove tax breaks worth about 350bn rupees ($2.5bn or 1% of GDP) next year and to raise the price of gas and electricity. It has pledged to give the central bank, the State Bank of Pakistan, more autonomy in its fight against inflation (which has increased sharply to over 8%). It will also let market forces dictate the rupee’s exchange rate, which has been devalued by over 18% against the dollar in the past year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To ease the public’s pain, the IMF will allow the government to spend more on welfare schemes, such as a cash-transfer scheme named after Benazir Bhutto, a former prime minister who was assassinated in 2007. But her son, Bilawal Bhutto Zardari, who now leads her party in opposition, seems unimpressed. After the government this month appointed a former IMF official to head the country’s central bank, Mr Bhutto Zardari accused it of surrendering Pakistan’s autonomy. “How can IMF negotiate with IMF?” he asked. A cartoon in the &lt;em&gt;Friday Times&lt;/em&gt;, a local news weekly, showed Christine Lagarde, head of the fund, sitting across the negotiating table from herself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In truth, Mr Khan’s government tried hard—perhaps too hard—to keep its distance from the fund. Instead of agreeing a deal as soon as it came to power in August 2018, it turned for help to friendly powers instead, including Saudi Arabia (which gave $3bn and deferred a similar amount of oil payments), the United Arab Emirates ($3bn) and China, which added another $2.2bn. China is investing heavily in Pakistan’s roads, ports and power plants, building what has been called the China-Pakistan Economic Corridor (CPEC). Some view this lending with suspicion, seeing Pakistan as a victim of China’s “debt-trap diplomacy”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such an assessment seems premature. CPEC spending may have contributed to the increase in Pakistan’s imports (the country’s current-account deficit exceeded 6% of GDP in the year to June 2018). But because this outflow of import spending was presumably matched by an inflow of Chinese capital, it cannot have been responsible for the dangerous dwindling of Pakistan’s foreign-currency reserves over the past year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was instead the result of Pakistan’s own macroeconomic muddle. The previous government pursued both an over-valued exchange rate, which was too strong for Pakistan’s beleaguered exporters, and imprudent fiscal spending, which was too strong for Pakistan’s feeble revenue-raising powers. The dollars provided by Pakistan’s allies in China and the Gulf have temporarily alleviated this problem of falling reserves. But solving it was always going to require policy reforms, which are difficult for bilateral allies to demand or monitor. Better to leave those tasks to the IMF.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not that the IMF will find it easy. Pakistan is a regular taker of the fund’s loans but not a diligent follower of its advice. Many of the reforms it has promised in the latest agreement have been pledged repeatedly before, including widening the tax net, rationalising utility prices and respecting the central bank’s autonomy. When push comes to shove, Pakistan’s governments have been reluctant to follow through, afraid of losing the support of powerful, but lightly taxed, domestic constituencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For their part, the IMF’s staff have been reluctant to cut Pakistan off, for fear of the upheaval that would ensue. “Governments have tried to ‘game’ the IMF, and achieved partial success each time,” write Ehtisham Ahmad and Azizali Mohammed, two former IMF advisers, in their history of the pair’s relationship. Pakistan’s public might dislike the IMF less, if they knew how frequently their leaders disregard it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 21:05:49 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“The president is the fount of all patronage”—Philippine mid-term elections]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/13/the-president-is-the-fount-of-all-patronage-philippine-mid-term-elections]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20199518_blm501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-13T11:30:32Z&quot;&gt;May 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PERSONALITIES, NOT policies, will determine poll results in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/11/the-philippines-mid-term-elections-will-tighten-the-presidents-grip&quot;&gt;Philippines&lt;/a&gt; today, where elections are underway to fill some 18,000 government jobs. Candidates who support the firebrand president, Rodrigo Duterte, such as his daughter, are likely to do well. Also, why is it that as the need for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/04/antibiotics-biotech-firms-are-struggling&quot;&gt;antibiotics&lt;/a&gt; increases, incentives to produce them are diminishing? And a trip to the tiny &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/05/11/a-groundbreaking-show-on-delos-mixes-classical-and-contemporary-art&quot;&gt;Greek island&lt;/a&gt; of Delos for an unusual meeting of modern art and protected antiquity. Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/sparetherodrigo-philippineelections&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 19:06:46 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How Manchester City came to rule English football]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/05/12/how-manchester-city-came-to-rule-english-football]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-12T22:52:14Z&quot;&gt;May 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIFTEEN YEARS ago, if you had told English football fans in a pub that Manchester City, Liverpool and Tottenham Hotspur would one day be the dominant forces in the Premier League, they would have told you to make the pint in your hand the last one for the day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2004 Spurs finished 14th in the table and Man City 16th. Liverpool, in their 14th consecutive year without a league title, ended up fourth. But they were still far behind the then ruling triumvirate: Arsenal, who had just recorded the competition’s first unbeaten season in more than a century; Chelsea, who had just been bought by Roman Abramovich, a Russian oligarch; and Manchester United, who had bagged 8 of the previous 11 titles. Between 1996 and 2011, these three clubs were the only ones to win the Premier League.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, however, fans of the Gunners, the Blues and the Red Devils must worry that they might not get their hands on the trophy again for many years. The new sultans of the Premier League are Manchester City, who on May 12th sealed their fourth title in eight seasons—to the delight of Abu Dhabi’s royal family, who purchased the club in 2008. If City have become arguably the best team in English football history, collecting a record 100 points from a possible 114 last season and 98 this time around, then Liverpool are a close second. Liverpool’s finishing total of 97 points this season would have won them the title in any other year, but that is little consolation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liverpool can still look forward to the final of the Champions League, Europe’s most prestigious tournament, on June 1st. Their opponents will be Tottenham—who are some way behind them in the league, but have finished in the top four for a fourth consecutive season, a feat matched only by Manchester City. What has allowed the new trio to dominate English football?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Big money is a big part of the answer. Manchester City’s spending spree between 2008 and 2012 included £520m ($675m) of transfer fees, more even than Mr Abramovich splurged in his first four years at Chelsea. Liverpool were rescued from the brink of bankruptcy in 2010 by Fenway Sports Group (FSG), an American company which also owns the Boston Red Sox, a baseball team. Since purchasing the club for a mere £300m, FSG has spent heavily. Estimates from 21st Club, a football consultancy, suggest that Liverpool pay over £300m in players’ wages and transfer fees every year, roughly as much as Mr Abramovich does (see chart below). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But spending on players is only part of the answer. Football’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/game-theory/2018/11/30/rich-clubs-are-bullying-footballs-administrators-into-submission&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Financial Fair Play rules&lt;/a&gt; penalise clubs if they spend more than they earn. In fact, Manchester City spend only 8% more per year on players than do Manchester United, the richest club in the world, yet  achieve vastly superior results. Spurs have managed to overtake Arsenal, their north London foes, even though they spend 20% less on their squad than the Gunners do. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The secret of the new trio’s success is not lavish spending, but wise investment. The leading trio have learned from the mistakes made by most other English clubs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teams in the Premier League are much richer than their counterparts in Europe’s “big five” leagues in Spain, Germany, Italy and France. According to Deloitte, a consultancy, nine of the 20 clubs with the largest annual revenues are English. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This wealth owes much to a combination of luck and shrewdness. The lucky part is that the league has always had at least three teams competing for the title, unlike the eternal duopoly of Barcelona and Real Madrid in Spain, and the near-monopoly of Bayern Munich in Germany, Juventus in Italy and Paris Saint-Germain in France. The shrewd bit is English clubs’ energetic marketing abroad, both in arranging pre-season tours and attracting foreign sponsors. Today, Asian fans are more likely to follow English clubs than those elsewhere. More Americans watch the Premier League than all other European leagues combined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But English teams have squandered much of this wealth in the transfer market. When 21st Club plotted European teams’ spending on players against their results on the pitch (see the chart above), 16 of the 20 Premier League teams sat below the trendline. In the last ten years, an English side has won the Champions League only once. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This profligacy has two causes. The first is differential pricing, an economic phenomenon in which a seller charges different customers different rates for the same good. European clubs know that Premier League sides are flush with cash, so demand greater transfer fees, reckons 21st Club. English clubs have spent, on average, 80% more than their rivals for the same level of talent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A second cause has been English clubs’ eagerness to poach ageing stars from elite teams, rather than nurturing talented youngsters. In 2017, when pondering the conundrum of why Europe’s richest league was so mediocre, this newspaper &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2017/09/02/the-english-are-bad-at-playing-football-but-brilliant-at-selling-it&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;noted&lt;/a&gt; that “in recent years a number of English sides have spent club-record sums on older players who are at the peak of their fame but have ended up spending half their time on the bench.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data from 21st Club show that Manchester City, Liverpool and Tottenham have now bucked this trend. Since 2016, the players they have signed up have been younger and less likely to come from Europe’s best clubs than those bought by Manchester United, Chelsea and Arsenal (see chart below). Taking a gamble on a very good player in his early twenties makes it more likely that a team will enjoy his best years, in his late twenties, especially if he becomes an extraordinary footballer. And bargaining transfer fees with a smaller club makes it more likely that an English club will secure a good deal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Manchester City adopted this strategy even though they broke their club record £55m when they bought Kevin de Bruyne, a midfielder, from Wolfsburg, a second-rate German team. Liverpool also broke their record when they purchased Mohamed Salah, an attacker, for £37m from Roma, a good (but not great) Italian side. Though both transfer fees were large, they were fairly priced: now in their peak years, Messrs de Bruyne and Salah have become their teams’ best players. Gallingly for Chelsea, both had played for the London club when they were younger, but were sold after making slow starts to their careers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tottenham have had to be even more economical, in order to finance their new stadium, which has cost £1bn to build. In fact, this year they became the first club in Premier League history not to sign a single new player during a season. That they could do so and still prosper was thanks to years of nurturing young talents from Europe’s lesser clubs, who have now matured into stars. They include Christian Eriksen (from Ajax), Son Heung-min (from Leverkusen) and Dele Alli (from lowly Milton Keynes). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whereas Manchester City, Liverpool and Tottenham fans will struggle to name a bad signing in the last three years, Manchester United, Chelsea and Arsenal have several expensive flops in their squads that they will try to sell this summer. No player has been more emblematic of this than Alexis Sánchez, a 30-year-old striker. Last year Manchester United made him the league’s highest paid player, on an annual salary of around £25m, after prising him away from Arsenal. But the ageing Mr Sánchez had already started to struggle in his final performances for Arsenal. The Chilean’s time in Manchester has been a disaster, scoring just five goals in 45 games. Chelsea’s acquisition of Álvaro Morata, a striker from Real Madrid, for a club record £60m, was equally dire. He lasted just a season. Arsenal have purchased a number of defenders who have failed to live up to their billing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hiring competence of Manchester City, Liverpool and Tottenham has allowed them to punch above their weight financially, meaning that English teams are at last able to contest the crown of European football. Whatever happens on June 1st, an English team will win the Champions League for the first time in seven years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 08:06:39 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why women’s art sells at a discount]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/05/12/why-womens-art-sells-at-a-discount]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/women2.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A ROSE painted by another name would cost more. In a new paper*, four academics show that art made by women sells for lower prices at auction than men’s, and suggest that this discount has nothing to do with talent or thematic choices. It is solely because the artists are female.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors used a sample of 1.9m transactions in art auctions across 49 countries in the period from 1970 to 2016. They found that art created by women sold at an average discount of 42% compared with works made by men. However, auction prices can be distorted by a few famous artists whose output is perceived as extremely valuable. If transactions above $1m are excluded, then the discount falls to 19%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One explanation for this gap could be that women choose different subjects. This is partly true; for example, a higher proportion of women than men paint roses (including Helen Allingham, a British watercolourist: see picture), whereas a smaller share create landscapes. But it turns out that themes that are more associated with female artists sell at a premium, not a discount. Indeed, the researchers could not explain the female discount in terms of other factors such as the size, style or medium of the paintings, or the age of the artist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In theory, another possibility could be that women are just less talented than men. To test that proposition, the authors conducted a couple of experiments. In one, they showed 1,000 people a selection of 10 lesser-known paintings and asked them to guess the gender of the artists. The respondents were right only 50.5% of the time, no better than tossing a coin. In short, the general public cannot discriminate between male and female art.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a second test, the researchers used a computer programme to generate paintings and randomly assign the results to artists with male or female names. They then asked participants to rate the paintings and ascribe a value. The experiment found that affluent individuals (those most likely to bid at auctions) attributed a lower value to works which the programme assigned to a woman. Clearly, this gap was unrelated to the artistic merit of the picture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It could be that these well-heeled observers were aware of the market discount for female artists, and applied it accordingly. But that does not solve the puzzle of why the discount arose in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two more findings imply that the difference relates to culture rather than talent. First, the academics considered the relationship between the female discount and the level of gender inequality in the countries where the auctions took place. The latter measure was based on indices (such as those compiled by the UN and the World Economic Forum) which look at factors such as educational attainment and political empowerment. For a given female artist, the average discount applied to their work was lowest in countries where women were more equal. (There are some exceptions to the rule; women’s art was highly rated in Brazil.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news is that the female discount has reduced over time. For transactions under $1m, the study calculated, the discount has dropped from 33% in the 1970s to 8% after 2010. Again, though, that only confirms the underlying prejudice—evidently ability never had anything to do with the disparity. But the reduction in the discount has another implication. As it has fallen, so the returns on women’s art have grown; since the 1970s they have been higher than for their male peers. Collectors should put aside their prejudices: as the art world’s longstanding chauvinism abates, the female of the species has become a better investment than the male.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;* “Is Gender in the Eye of the Beholder? Identifying Cultural Attitudes with Art Auction Prices” by Renée Adams, Roman Kräussl, Marco Navone and Patrick Verwijmeren&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 07:10:45 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The joy of absence]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/12/the-joy-of-absence]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_wbp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;RONALD REAGAN famously quipped that “it’s true hard work never killed anybody, but I figure, why take the chance?” Beyond a certain level, extra effort seems to be self-defeating. Studies suggest that, after around 50 hours a week, employee productivity declines sharply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that doesn’t stop some managers from demanding that workers stay chained to their desk for long periods. At the blood-testing firm Theranos, Sunny Balwani, boyfriend of the founder, Elizabeth Holmes, had an obsession with employee hours, and would tour the engineering department at 7.30pm to check people were at their desks. All those hours were wasted when the company eventually collapsed (prosecutors have charged Ms Holmes with fraud).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jack Ma, the founder of Alibaba, the Chinese e-commerce group, recently praised the 996 model, where employees work from 9am to 9pm, six days a week, as a “great opportunity”. To be fair, Mr Ma said employers should not mandate such hours. Still presenteeism is the curse of the modern office worker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will be days when you do not have much to do; perhaps because you are waiting for someone else in a different department, or a different company, to respond to a request. As the clock ticks past 5pm, there may be no purpose in staying at your desk. But you can see your boss hard at work and, more important, they can see you. So you make an effort to look busy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of this may be a self-perpetuating cycle. If bosses do not like to go home before their underlings, and underlings fear leaving before their bosses, everyone is trapped. Staff may feel that they will not get a pay rise, or a promotion, if they are not seen to be putting in maximum effort. This is easily confused with long hours. Managers, who are often no good at judging employees’ performance, use time in the office as a proxy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The consequence is often wasted effort. To adjust the old joke about the Soviet Union: “We pretend to work and managers pretend to believe us.” Rather than work hard, you toil to make bosses think that you are. Leaving a jacket on your office chair, walking around purposefully with a clipboard, and sending out emails at odd hours are three of the best known tricks. After a while this can result in collective self-delusion that it is actual work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But presenteeism has more serious consequences. It is perhaps most prevalent in Japan, where people attend the office even when they are in discomfort. In doing so, they are neither doing themselves, or their employers, any favours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As well as reduced productivity, this can mean greater medical expenses for the employer. According to a study in the Journal of Occupation and Environmental Medicine, these costs can be six times higher for employers than the costs of absenteeism among workers. To take one example, research published in the British Medical Journal found that Japanese employees with lower back pain were three times more likely to turn up for work than in Britain. As a result, those workers were more likely to experience greater pain and to suffer from depression. What could be more depressing than being in pain, and feeling trapped at work?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of this is to say that employers are not entitled to expect workers to be in the office for a decent proportion of time. Inevitably there will be a need for some (preferably short) meetings. Dealing with colleagues face-to-face creates a feeling of camaraderie, allows for a useful exchange of ideas and enables workers to have a better sense of their mutual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the grand sweep of humanity, presenteeism is a recent phenomenon. Before the industrial era, most people worked in their own farm or workshop and were paid for the amount they produced. Factories emerged because new machines were much more efficient than cottage-industry methods, and only a large employer with capital could afford them. Suddenly, workers were paid not for their output but for their time, and were required to clock in and out. But modern machinery like smartphones and laptops is portable. It can be used as easily at home as in the office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turning an office into a prison, with inmates allowed home for the evenings, does nothing for creativity that is increasingly demanded of office workers as routine tasks are automated. To be productive you need presence of mind, not being present in the flesh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 06:13:23 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>