<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[The singular genius of Pauline Kael]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/07/01/the-singular-genius-of-pauline-kael]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BKP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-01T15:38:39Z&quot;&gt;Jul 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PAULINE KAEL, the legendary film critic for the &lt;em&gt;New Yorker&lt;/em&gt;, would have turned 100 last month (she died in 2001). As part of the centenary celebrations an admiring and buoyant documentary, “What She Said: The Art of Pauline Kael”, was shown at the Edinburgh International Film Festival. The film makes it clear that Kael (pictured left) was the most influential critic in the history of the medium. And that she always will be: no other film writer can ever have the same impact she had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Partly this is because she was the funniest, the most combative, the most erudite and the most enthusiastic writer in the business (and that is the kind of hyperbole she enjoyed using herself). She expunged “term-paper pomposity” from her reviews, distancing herself from aloof “gentleman critics” by balancing her encyclopedic film knowledge with proudly subjective opinions, autobiographical tidbits, dirty jokes and remarks she overheard from other patrons in the cinema. Although her acidic wit was compared to Dorothy Parker’s, she saw herself as an outsider in New York and in the &lt;em&gt;New Yorker&lt;/em&gt;. A California rancher’s daughter, she was accused by a colleague of “trampling through the pages of the magazine with cowboy boots covered with dung”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Partly, though, Kael’s pre-eminence was a matter of timing. She was old enough to remember seeing silent movies with her parents in the 1920s, and yet she didn’t join the staff of the &lt;em&gt;New Yorker&lt;/em&gt; until 1968, when she was nearly 50. Prior to that, she had lurched from magazine to magazine, struggling to make a living. The problem was that she despised Hollywood’s big-budget crowd-pleasers, panning the likes of “The Sound of Music” as being overblown and sentimental. “American movies have never been more contemptible,” she declared in 1967, a stance that did not endear her to her editors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But 1967 was also the year when Arthur Penn’s controversially bloody “Bonnie and Clyde” was released. Most critics loathed or ignore it, but Kael was infatuated, and her 9,000-word defence of the outlaw biopic earned her a position at the &lt;em&gt;New Yorker&lt;/em&gt;. Suddenly, a generation of American film-makers was experimenting with the iconoclastic “New Wave” techniques of Europe’s auteurs—and Kael loved them. In particular, she loved the sex, the violence and the exploding heads she saw in the work of Francis Ford Coppola, Brian De Palma, Martin Scorsese and Robert Altman. There was none of that in “The Sound of Music”. And so it came about that a middle-aged single mother became a best-selling pundit by championing America’s youngest, hippest male directors. She made their careers, and they made hers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What She Said” may not be particularly iconoclastic, but it is a lively, exhaustively researched, and stunningly well edited tribute to an uncompromising talent. Written and directed by Rob Garver, the documentary compiles excerpts from Kael’s journalism (read by Sarah Jessica Parker), hundreds of film clips and snippets of interviews with figures such as Camille Paglia, Paul Schrader, Quentin Tarantino, David O Russell and others. John Boorman, an English film-maker, recalls that when Kael was at her formidable peak, directors felt as if they were “under surveillance”. Ridley Scott is still angry about her dismissal of “Blade Runner” in 1982. On a chat show in 1973 Jerry Lewis, “The King of Comedy”, said that Kael was a “dirty old broad” who “never said a good word about me.” “But she’s probably the most qualified critic in the world”, he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just think about that: a film star praising a film critic on television and assuming that the audience would know who he was talking about. It would never happen now. In the modern, fragmented, cultural landscape, cinephiles no longer queue up to buy magazines which run 9,000-word essays by their favourite critics—they harvest opinions from countless blogs, tweets and podcasts instead. In the unlikely event that a 21st-century reviewer could write as scintillatingly as Kael did, and that she had a movement as inspiring as the American New Wave to write about, most people would still have no idea who she was or what she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 23:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wanted: a new writer to cover British economics]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/07/01/wanted-a-new-writer-to-cover-british-economics]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/articles/20180224_wop001_9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; is looking to hire a staff writer to cover British economics. Journalistic experience is not necessary: the last few people to do this job had not been journalists before they arrived at the paper. The ability to write clearly and entertainingly is, however, crucial. So is the ability to spot intriguing patterns in data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We test for these things mostly by asking for a sample article, which applicants should send, with a CV to: britaineconomicsjob@economist.com. Please write up to 700 words. Your article could be on some aspect of British macro- or microeconomics, or on political economy. Four recent examples follow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The job is based in London, but the successful candidate need not be British. We welcome applications from people of all backgrounds. The deadline is August 4th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Example articles:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2017/09/02/sterlings-depreciation-has-not-led-to-an-export-boom&quot;&gt;Sterling’s depreciation has not led to an export boom&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/06/four-years-after-its-steelworks-shut-redcar-is-recovering&quot;&gt;Four years after its steelworks shut, Redcar is recovering&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/03/07/why-british-housebuilders-are-making-such-juicy-profits&quot;&gt;Why British housebuilders are making such juicy profits&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2017/10/28/higher-interest-rates-could-hit-britains-vulnerable-economy&quot;&gt;Higher interest rates could hit Britain’s vulnerable economy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 23:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America’s banks sail through the Fed’s annual stress tests]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/07/01/americas-banks-sail-through-the-feds-annual-stress-tests]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_blp903.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUMMER BRINGS examinations, both for students and for America’s banks. Each year since 2011, the Federal Reserve has set “stress tests” for the banks. They must show how much capital they have, the quality of that capital and what activities they are up to. The Fed uses this evidence to determine whether an adverse shock—economic, financial or otherwise—might put too large a dent in that capital. The tests are one feature of the post-crisis Dodd-Frank financial-reform act, and they aim to ensure that lenders have enough equity on hand should catastrophe strike again. Failure to measure up can result in the Fed curtailing a bank’s ability to distribute cash to shareholders, in the form of dividends or share buybacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On June 21st the Fed announced that America’s banks passed this year’s tests with flying colours. That paves the way for bumper payouts to shareholders. The four largest retail banks, JPMorgan Chase, Bank of America, Wells Fargo and Citigroup, plus the two biggest investment banks, Goldman Sachs and Morgan Stanley, purchased $93.1bn-worth of their own stock in 2018. That will rise to $117.9bn in 2019. Most banks have also raised their planned distribution of dividends by more than 10%. On June 27th the Fed approved these capital plans for America’s 18 largest banks (though their approval for Credit Suisse is conditional on the bank addressing what the regulator regarded as weaknesses in its plans for share repurchases and dividends).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In one way, the stress tests were tougher than ever before. The worst hypothetical shock this year included a global recession in which American unemployment rises to 10%, accompanied by sliding property prices and stressed corporate-debt markets. Even under this scenario banks would hold more capital than the Fed’s minimum requirement (although only just in the cases of JPMorgan Chase and Capital One). Randal Quarles, who oversees bank regulation at the Fed, said that “the results confirm that our financial system remains resilient”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there are fears that the Fed made the tests easier in other ways. A smaller cohort of banks—just the very biggest—was tested this year, following a roll-back of Dodd-Frank passed by Congress in 2018 which meant smaller banks need not be tested every year. And banks were also given more information about how the test would be conducted. In previous years they had received details only about the catastrophic scenarios, not about the models the Fed would use to test them. Banks had complained that this made their task akin to trying to hit a moving target in the dark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Daniel Tarullo, a former Fed governor who stepped down in 2017 and who designed the Fed’s stress tests, had been wary of divulging more information. He feared banks would rearrange their balance-sheets merely to meet the test, and argued that publishing the Fed’s models would “result in less protection for the financial system”. Mr Quarles has a different opinion. He has said the change is akin to “giving banks the textbook—not the test”. The Fed published “enhanced descriptions” of the models it uses in March.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next year the tests may be changed more radically yet. On July 9th the Fed is hosting a conference in Boston to review the stress-testing procedures. Many in the industry suspect that it will say it intends to adopt a new test, the “stress capital buffer”, alongside stress tests. Currently, passing the stress test requires that a bank’s common-equity “Tier 1” capital ratio—a measure of its equity—does not dip below 4.5% in the worst scenario the Fed examines. Proving this requires banks to outline their planned dividend repurchases and share buybacks a year in advance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A stress capital buffer would use the results of the stress test to designate a minimum common-equity Tier 1 ratio for rest of the year. The buffer would be calculated as the difference between a firm’s common-equity Tier 1 ratio at present—and what it would hypothetically fall to under the worst scenario tested. Goldman Sachs’s common-equity Tier 1 capital ratio is 13.3% at present, for example, but would be just 6.7% under the worst scenario. Its stress capital buffer would be 6.6%, the difference between the two. The total common-equity Tier 1 capital ratio the bank would need to maintain year-round would therefore be the minimum (4.5%), plus its stress capital buffer and a surcharge for being big and systemically important.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Banks with stable businesses are largely in favour of the change, as it would allow them to vary their dividends and buybacks through the year—as most companies do—rather than outlining plans in advance. But the new procedure would most affect banks that undertake risky, volatile activities, which might see their capital requirements vary wildly with the economic cycle. Although most would end up having to hold roughly the same amount of capital as now, those with large trading business, such as Goldman Sachs and Morgan Stanley, might have to raise more capital in the future. The goal might be a wise one, however. Passing one stress test is well and good, but what the Fed really wants is for them to be passed with flying colours year after year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 21:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“You smell the tear gas, you can smell the blood”—Sudan’s violent transition]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/07/01/you-smell-the-tear-gas-you-can-smell-the-blood-sudans-violent-transition]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_blm501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-01T11:23:25Z&quot;&gt;Jul 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PROTESTORS RETURNED to the streets of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/15/how-to-stop-sudan-sliding-into-war&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Khartoum&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; this weekend, again with deadly consequences. We look back to last month’s violent crackdown, and consider &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/15/a-struggle-for-power-in-sudan-could-lead-to-civil-war&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sudan’s troubled push for democracy.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;China’s swine-flu outbreaks&lt;/strong&gt; threaten hundreds of millions of pigs—but might spark long-overdue reforms in the country’s pork industry. And, we examine &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://espresso.economist.com/f540b5a543ecdae19fa0876e80f10528&quot; data-tegid=&quot;it7tqh2fprgd60k0r389v9uqnt8eu8fq&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;San Francisco’s e-cigarette ban:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; if vaping is safer than smoking, should it be stubbed out? Additional audio courtesy of Azzam al-Maryoud. Runtime: 22 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/4c027ad1-e9d0-49d9-a646-af21e44b1866&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 19:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The EU is struggling to agree on candidates for its biggest jobs]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/charlemagnes-notebook/2019/07/01/the-eu-is-struggling-to-agree-on-candidates-for-its-biggest-jobs]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_EUP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-01T08:33:02Z&quot;&gt;Jul 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NOT EVEN at the peak of the Greek debt crisis did European Union summits run on as long as the one that began in Brussels last night. Leaders gathered on June 30th to thrash out a deal on the EU’s big jobs: the presidents of the European Commission (the EU&amp;#x27;s executive), the European Council (representing leaders), the European Parliament and the High Representative for foreign affairs and security policy. The presidency of the European Central Bank, which will also soon be vacant, is also in the mix as leaders strive for regional and political balance. At the time of writing, they were still deliberating. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The blockage concerns a provisional package of appointments sketched out by the leaders of France, Germany, Spain and the Netherlands on the fringes of the G20 summit in Osaka. This would allocate the commission presidency to Frans Timmermans (pictured), a Dutch Social Democrat, the council presidency to a liberal like Charles Michel of Belgium and the parliament presidency to Manfred Weber, a Christian Democrat from Germany whose bid for the commission job has met with opposition from President Emmanuel Macron of France and others. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This accord has come under intense pressure at the summit. Leaders from the European People’s Party (EPP), the centre-right group to which Mr Weber and Angela Merkel belong, reckon the parliament presidency too puny a prize for coming first in the European elections. They want the commission. Central European governments like that of Poland also object to Mr Timmermans, who as vice-president of the outgoing commission has been a sturdy opponent of illiberalism in the region. Southerners were also aggrieved at their lack of representation—noting that the Osaka proposal would put figures from the Benelux countries in the two most powerful presidencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The objections began at the EPP’s pre-summit meeting yesterday afternoon, when leaders made known their objections to Mrs Merkel’s plan. The German chancellor left early for one-on-one consultations. All of which delayed the start of the summit&amp;#x27;s official dinner last night. Then, around 10pm, Donald Tusk, the outgoing council president, suspended the group discussion to hold a series of bilateral meetings before the leaders reconvened for breakfast at 7am.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Various packages were floated through the night. One option would see a compromise EPP figure like Michel Barnier, the EU’s chief Brexit negotiator, clinch the commission presidency. But that would break the doctrine (albeit one established only in 2014) whereby a Spitzenkandidat or “lead candidate” of a major parliamentary group during the European election campaign takes that job. Mr Weber and Mr Timmermans were both lead candidates; Mr Barnier was not. The latest permutation under discussion would send Mr Timmermans to the commission and Kristalina Georgieva, the Bulgarian head of the World Bank, to the helm of the council, with Mr Weber as parliament president and Mr Michel as High Representative. Ms Georgieva is highly rated and might satisfy the central Europeans, but has never served as a head of government—which is generally viewed as a requirement for the council job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That the allocation of posts is proving so fraught says something about the state of Europe. There was always intense horse-trading over the big jobs, but in the past it was often squared by grand bargains between France and Germany and between Christian and Social Democrats. Today’s EU is a more multi-dimensional one. The parliament and the European Council are more politically fragmented. France and Germany are at odds and in any case less powerful collectively. After the euro and migrant crises, and amid debates about liberal democracy, regional sensitivities are more raw. Mrs Merkel, once the EU’s leading co-ordinating force, is nearing the end of her time as chancellor; she seems to have misread the mood in her own EPP. The great European Rubik’s cube has more colours and layers than before. Aligning them takes time. So much so that some are already mooting a further summit on July 15th if no agreement can be reached today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 18:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How Microsoft survived creative destruction]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/30/how-microsoft-survived-creative-destruction]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_wbp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-29T16:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;LIKE AN NFL changing room, the technology industry is littered with the bodies of fallen champions, from AOL to Yahoo to Blackberry, in urgent need of rehabilitation. Ten years ago many might have expected Microsoft to end up in the same state. But the software giant has made a startling comeback, regularly vying for the title of the most valuable company on global stockmarkets, with a market capitalisation above $1trn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The story of this revival is the subject of a new case study by Herminia Ibarra and Adam Jones of London Business School (LBS). In large part, the success has resulted from a shift away from a focus on the Windows operating system and towards Azure, Microsoft’s cloud-based services offering. It involved a willingness to let Microsoft programs run on Apple and Android smartphones, something the company had previously avoided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the turnaround also required a change to the company’s culture and that is the main subject of the LBS study. The shift to cloud-based services meant that revenues would be generated in a different way. Under the old system, clients bought software under a fixed-term contract; once the sale was made, the revenue was guaranteed. Cloud services are paid for on a metered basis; revenue comes in only when customers use them. That required a new approach by the company’s sales team, led by Jean-Philippe Courtois.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shift was enormous. Around 40,000 people had to change how they did their jobs. Three elements were important. First, staff had to understand how customers were using cloud-based services, so that they could be encouraged to use them more. This required 5,000 specialist hires.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second, to permit existing sales staff to concentrate on attracting and retaining customers, they had to be relieved of some duties, such as preparing sales forecasts. Internal review meetings were reduced, including an intimidating ordeal known as the mid-year review in which senior executives grilled employees—and for which workers spent lots of time cramming like students for a test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, salespeople needed an incentive to put in the work to flog the new products, which were potentially less lucrative for them than the traditional fixed-term contracts. This involved a greater use of performance bonuses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This being Microsoft, technology chivvied the process along. A new productivity tool helped workers analyse how much time they spent in meetings or writing emails and whether they were interacting with fellow Microsoft employees or with clients. Among other things, it allowed the usefulness of meetings to be gauged: if staff were fiddling with their work smartphones, they were not listening to their colleagues and probably had better things to do than loiter in a conference room. (The test could be usefully applied to meetings at a lot more places than Microsoft.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Managers have had to change too. Microsoft is introducing a programme called “Reimagine Managers” which aims to foster an approach of coaching and caring for the staff. Technology has made some routine management tasks (like organising rotas) easier, leaving more time for more time-consuming non-routine ones, such as talking to employees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Changing a corporate culture is an enormous task, and Mr Courtois admits that it is a work in progress. Microsoft, he says, has shifted from a “fixed mindset” to a “growth mindset”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what is interesting about the Microsoft case study (which is mostly free of such management jargon) is that it highlights the practical changes needed to transform a company. Microsoft could have been a classic victim of “creative disruption”, so dependent on an existing technology (personal computers) that it failed to manage the shift to a world dominated by mobile devices. But the shift has only been successful (so far) because it has involved not just a strategic insight, but a change in approach across the workforce.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft can still trip up. Tech companies are like the Red Queen in Lewis Carroll’s “Through the Looking Glass”—constantly running to stay in the same place. IBM performed a successful shift from hardware to services in the 1990s, but has struggled to grow its revenues or lift its share price in recent years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the long run Microsoft’s fortunes may depend on whether acquisitions like LinkedIn, the career site, or GitHub, a software-development startup, prove wiser than its failed bet on Nokia’s mobile-phone business earlier in the decade. But it has already shown that, even in a big organisation, cultural change is possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Correction (July 1st 2019)&lt;/strong&gt;: An earlier version of this article had misspelt Herminia Ibarra’s name. This has been corrected. Sorry. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 18:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump and Kim Jong Un hold a border photo-op]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/30/donald-trump-and-kim-jong-un-hold-a-border-photo-op]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190706_blp902.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-30T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON THE morning of June 29th Donald Trump, America’s president, extended the most casual of invitations from his hotel room in Osaka, where he was attending a meeting of the G20 hosted by Japan. “If Chairman Kim of North Korea sees this, I would meet him at the Border/DMZ just to shake his hand and say Hello(?)!,” Mr Trump wrote on Twitter. After all, Mr Trump was already scheduled to visit the “demilitarised zone” between the two Koreas the next day, after a meeting with Moon Jae-in, South Korea’s president. Why not throw in a meeting with North Korea’s dictator, whom he had met twice before in an effort to get North Korea to abandon its nuclear weapons. Mere hours later, North Korea pronounced Mr Trump’s suggestion “very interesting”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interesting enough that, on the afternoon of June 30th, Mr Kim and Mr Trump met for the third time in just over a year. Following a tour of the South Korean side of the DMZ, which also took in a windswept guard post and a canteen where troops presented the president with a golfing outfit, Mr Trump strolled towards the dividing line in the truce village of Panmunjom. He shook hands with Mr Kim, who was waiting for him on the northern side, before stepping across the line into North Korea. The moment was heavy with symbolism: it was the first time a sitting American president had set foot in North Korea, and it came 69 years, nearly to the day, after American troops had entered the Korean war on the South’s side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During a brief chat on the northern side, Mr Trump said it was an “honour” to visit North Korea. Mr Kim appeared chuffed: “I never expected to see you in this place,” he told Mr Trump, who then invited the North’s dictator to visit the White House. Afterwards, the two stepped back across the line into South Korea, where they posed briefly for a photo with Mr Moon before retiring for talks to “Freedom House” on the southern side. Mr Moon, who needs negotiations between America and North Korea to restart in order to advance his ambitious agenda of inter-Korean economic cooperation, was effusive throughout. “The flower of peace is blossoming on the Korean peninsula,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As well as being a gift for Mr Moon, the summit was also a boon for Messrs Trump and Kim. The president’s comments during and around the meeting will have pleased Mr Kim. Mr Trump downplayed North Korea’s recent tests of short-range missiles, claiming America did not consider them missile tests. Mr Kim’s nuclear programme barely got a mention: for all the world, it looked as though Mr Trump was perfectly happy to engage with North Korea on its own terms, implicitly acknowledging the regime’s nuclear-armed status as legitimate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These comments, along with the pictures of Mr Trump stepping into North Korea and saying that he was honoured to be received by Mr Kim, are gold for the North’s domestic propaganda machine, which is bound to use them to demonstrate the great leader’s diplomatic acumen. They may go some way towards brushing up Mr Kim’s domestic image following the collapse of the pair’s previous summit, in Vietnam in February. North Korea’s failure to win relief from sanctions at that meeting seems to have so infuriated Mr Kim that he demoted his chief negotiator and is rumoured to have punished other aides. But the decision to meet Mr Trump again suggests that he still holds out hope of benefiting from continued negotiations. Mr Trump’s effusiveness about his friendship with Mr Kim is also likely to burnish the dictator’s image internationally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump, for his part, used the occasion to congratulate himself for saving the region from the devastating conflict that he claimed would be racking it had it not been for his efforts. “We are in a much different place than we were two and a half years ago,” he said. He complained repeatedly and at length about the media, whose lack of appreciation for his efforts he deemed “insulting”. He also seemed to enjoy the theatricality of the meeting, which was enhanced by its supposedly impromptu nature. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It remains unclear whether the encounter really was arranged in just 24 hours. On the one hand, the chaotic scenes at Panmunjom (including the White House press secretary getting into a fight with North Korean security officers) did not suggest extensive planning. On the other, the two leaders had been exchanging letters in the weeks leading up to the meeting, and Mr Trump had brought his entire team of nuclear negotiators along with him on his long-planned visit to Seoul. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If peace-making is taken to mean improving relations with a rogue dictatorship, the meeting certainly had some value. But it contributed very little to America’s aim to persuade North Korea to give up its nuclear weapons. In a press conference following his encounter with Mr Kim, Mr Trump told reporters that the two sides’ negotiating teams would get together in the coming weeks to arrange working-level talks. “They’ll start a process, and we’ll see what happens,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arms-control experts have been hoping for the start of that process ever since Mr Trump announced his meeting with Mr Kim in Singapore more than 13 months ago. The failure to get down to nitty-gritty talks had been taken as a sign that North Korea was not really serious about disarmament. Even if negotiators do finally start chewing over details, there is little reason to imagine that Mr Kim is ready at last to surrender his nuclear weapons. But he and Mr Trump do like a photo-op.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 17:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DMZ photo-up by Donald Trump and Kim Jong Un signals a return to nuclear talks]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/30/dmz-photo-up-by-donald-trump-and-kim-jong-un-signals-a-return-to-nuclear-talks]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190706_blp902.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-30T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON THE morning of June 29th Donald Trump, America’s president, extended the most casual of invitations from his hotel room in Osaka, where he was attending a meeting of the G20 hosted by Japan. “If Chairman Kim of North Korea sees this, I would meet him at the Border/DMZ just to shake his hand and say Hello(?)!,” Mr Trump wrote on Twitter. After all, Mr Trump was already scheduled to visit the “demilitarised zone” between the two Koreas the next day, after a meeting with Moon Jae-in, South Korea’s president. Why not throw in a meeting with North Korea’s dictator, whom he had met twice before in an effort to get North Korea to abandon its nuclear weapons. Mere hours later, North Korea pronounced Mr Trump’s suggestion “very interesting”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interesting enough that, on the afternoon of June 30th, Mr Kim and Mr Trump met for the third time in just over a year. Following a tour of the South Korean side of the DMZ, which also took in a windswept guard post and a canteen where troops presented the president with a golfing outfit, Mr Trump strolled towards the dividing line in the truce village of Panmunjom. He shook hands with Mr Kim, who was waiting for him on the northern side, before stepping across the line into North Korea. The moment was heavy with symbolism: it was the first time a sitting American president had set foot in North Korea, and it came 69 years, nearly to the day, after American troops had entered the Korean war on the South’s side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During a brief chat on the northern side, Mr Trump said it was an “honour” to visit North Korea. Mr Kim appeared chuffed: “I never expected to see you in this place,” he told Mr Trump, who then invited the North’s dictator to visit the White House. Afterwards, the two stepped back across the line into South Korea, where they posed briefly for a photo with Mr Moon before retiring for talks to “Freedom House” on the southern side. Mr Moon, who needs negotiations between America and North Korea to restart in order to advance his ambitious agenda of inter-Korean economic cooperation, was effusive throughout. “The flower of peace is blossoming on the Korean peninsula,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As well as being a gift for Mr Moon, the summit was also a boon for Messrs Trump and Kim. The president’s comments during and around the meeting will have pleased Mr Kim. Mr Trump downplayed North Korea’s recent tests of short-range missiles, claiming America did not consider them missile tests. Mr Kim’s nuclear programme barely got a mention: for all the world, it looked as though Mr Trump was perfectly happy to engage with North Korea on its own terms, implicitly acknowledging the regime’s nuclear-armed status as legitimate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These comments, along with the pictures of Mr Trump stepping into North Korea and saying that he was honoured to be received by Mr Kim, are gold for the North’s domestic propaganda machine, which is bound to use them to demonstrate the great leader’s diplomatic acumen. They may go some way towards brushing up Mr Kim’s domestic image following the collapse of the pair’s previous summit, in Vietnam in February. North Korea’s failure to win relief from sanctions at that meeting seems to have so infuriated Mr Kim that he demoted his chief negotiator and is rumoured to have punished other aides. But the decision to meet Mr Trump again suggests that he still holds out hope of benefiting from continued negotiations. Mr Trump’s effusiveness about his friendship with Mr Kim is also likely to burnish the dictator’s image internationally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump, for his part, used the occasion to congratulate himself for saving the region from the devastating conflict that he claimed would be racking it had it not been for his efforts. “We are in a much different place than we were two and a half years ago,” he said. He complained repeatedly and at length about the media, whose lack of appreciation for his efforts he deemed “insulting”. He also seemed to enjoy the theatricality of the meeting, which was enhanced by its supposedly impromptu nature. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It remains unclear whether the encounter really was arranged in just 24 hours. On the one hand, the chaotic scenes at Panmunjom (including the White House press secretary getting into a fight with North Korean security officers) did not suggest extensive planning. On the other, the two leaders had been exchanging letters in the weeks leading up to the meeting, and Mr Trump had brought his entire team of nuclear negotiators along with him on his long-planned visit to Seoul. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If peace-making is taken to mean improving relations with a rogue dictatorship, the meeting certainly had some value. But it contributed very little to America’s aim to persuade North Korea to give up its nuclear weapons. In a press conference following his encounter with Mr Kim, Mr Trump told reporters that the two sides’ negotiating teams would get together in the coming weeks to arrange working-level talks. “They’ll start a process, and we’ll see what happens,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arms-control experts have been hoping for the start of that process ever since Mr Trump announced his meeting with Mr Kim in Singapore more than 13 months ago. The failure to get down to nitty-gritty talks had been taken as a sign that North Korea was not really serious about disarmament. Even if negotiators do finally start chewing over details, there is little reason to imagine that Mr Kim is ready at last to surrender his nuclear weapons. But he and Mr Trump do like a photo-op.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 16:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Microsoft’s transformation required a change of culture]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/29/how-microsoft-survived-creative-destruction]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_wbp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-30T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;LIKE AN NFL changing room, the technology industry is littered with the bodies of fallen champions, from AOL to Yahoo to Blackberry, in urgent need of rehabilitation. Ten years ago many might have expected Microsoft to end up in the same state. But the software giant has made a startling comeback, regularly vying for the title of the most valuable company on global stockmarkets, with a market capitalisation above $1trn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The story of this revival is the subject of a new case study by Hermania Ibarra and Adam Jones of London Business School (LBS). In large part, the success has resulted from a shift away from a focus on the Windows operating system and towards Azure, Microsoft’s cloud-based services offering. It involved a willingness to let Microsoft programs run on Apple and Android smartphones, something the company had previously avoided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the turnaround also required a change to the company’s culture and that is the main subject of the LBS study. The shift to cloud-based services meant that revenues would be generated in a different way. Under the old system, clients bought software under a fixed-term contract; once the sale was made, the revenue was guaranteed. Cloud services are paid for on a metered basis; revenue comes in only when customers use them. That required a new approach by the company’s sales team, led by Jean-Philippe Courtois.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shift was enormous. Around 40,000 people had to change how they did their jobs. Three elements were important. First, staff had to understand how customers were using cloud-based services, so that they could be encouraged to use them more. This required 5,000 specialist hires.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second, to permit existing sales staff to concentrate on attracting and retaining customers, they had to be relieved of some duties, such as preparing sales forecasts. Internal review meetings were reduced, including an intimidating ordeal known as the mid-year review in which senior executives grilled employees—and for which workers spent lots of time cramming like students for a test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, salespeople needed an incentive to put in the work to flog the new products, which were potentially less lucrative for them than the traditional fixed-term contracts. This involved a greater use of performance bonuses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This being Microsoft, technology chivvied the process along. A new productivity tool helped workers analyse how much time they spent in meetings or writing emails and whether they were interacting with fellow Microsoft employees or with clients. Among other things, it allowed the usefulness of meetings to be gauged: if staff were fiddling with their work smartphones, they were not listening to their colleagues and probably had better things to do than loiter in a conference room. (The test could be usefully applied to meetings at a lot more places than Microsoft.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Managers have had to change too. Microsoft is introducing a programme called “Reimagine Managers” which aims to foster an approach of coaching and caring for the staff. Technology has made some routine management tasks (like organising rotas) easier, leaving more time for more time-consuming non-routine ones, such as talking to employees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Changing a corporate culture is an enormous task, and Mr Courtois admits that it is a work in progress. Microsoft, he says, has shifted from a “fixed mindset” to a “growth mindset”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what is interesting about the Microsoft case study (which is mostly free of such management jargon) is that it highlights the practical changes needed to transform a company. Microsoft could have been a classic victim of “creative disruption”, so dependent on an existing technology (personal computers) that it failed to manage the shift to a world dominated by mobile devices. But the shift has only been successful (so far) because it has involved not just a strategic insight, but a change in approach across the workforce.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft can still trip up. Tech companies are like the Red Queen in Lewis Carroll’s “Through the Looking Glass”—constantly running to stay in the same place. IBM performed a successful shift from hardware to services in the 1990s, but has struggled to grow its revenues or lift its share price in recent years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the long run Microsoft’s fortunes may depend on whether acquisitions like LinkedIn, the career site, or GitHub, a software-development startup, prove wiser than its failed bet on Nokia’s mobile-phone business earlier in the decade. But it has already shown that, even in a big organisation, cultural change is possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 15:40:18 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is China’s “one country, two systems” policy?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/06/30/what-is-chinas-one-country-two-systems-policy]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_CNP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-30T10:38:53Z&quot;&gt;Jun 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS of demonstrators repeatedly took to the streets of Hong Kong in June to protest against a proposed law that would allow the extradition of criminal suspects to mainland China. Their demonstrations, some of the largest in Hong Kong’s history, were instrumental in persuading the territory’s chief executive, Carrie Lam, to suspend the bill. In agitating against closer ties, Hong Kongers made use of freedoms that are denied in mainland China. What is their origin?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the late 20th century three historically Chinese territories remained beyond the control of the Chinese Communist Party: Taiwan, Macau and Hong Kong. Shortly after emerging as China’s paramount leader in 1978, Deng Xiaoping declared his ambition of achieving “reunification” with Taiwan. The island is technically the last stronghold of a government that once ruled all of China until a civil war ended in victory for the Communists in 1949, sending the defeated nationalist army into exile on Taiwan. Since then it has become a democracy, and its people increasingly identify as “Taiwanese”. Rulers in Beijing are sworn to unify the island with the mainland, if needs be by force.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deng promised Taiwan a “high degree of autonomy”, describing his proposal as “one country, two systems”. Taiwan would be allowed to retain its separate administration, capitalist way of life and even its own armed forces as long as it recognised the Communist government in Beijing as legitimate in all of China, including Taiwan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Taiwanese did not take the bait, but China used the “one country, two systems” idea when it took back Hong Kong from Britain and Macau from Portugal. Britain had secured the heart of Hong Kong in perpetuity as spoils of the 19th-century Opium Wars but the final part, the New Territories, was acquired on a 99-year lease in 1898. The Portuguese had ruled Macau since the 1500s, but eventually started withdrawing troops in 1975. With Britain’s lease expiring and Portugal abandoning Macau, China began talks with both countries in the mid-1980s to make arrangements for the return of the two territories and to decide their future political arrangements. Hong Kong and Macau were to become parts of China again in 1997 and 1999, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All parties, including China, recognised that imposing China’s political system on the two colonies would create panic and cause economic mayhem. “One country, two systems” would allow the territories to remain much as they were, with independent legal systems and police forces. Their political structures would change little, except that local “chief executives” would replace governors sent by the colonial powers. In Hong Kong, the chief executive would be elected by a 1,200-member electoral college from a pool of candidates approved by the Chinese government and would preside over a system modelled roughly on Britain’s, though with a single legislative chamber. China even promised that the chief executives would eventually be elected by “universal suffrage”, though its exact meaning in this context is unclear. The government in Beijing would be responsible for defence and diplomacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These arrangements are to last for 50 years. It is unclear what happens after 2047. In the meantime, democracy activists have been growing despondent as pro-establishment forces, some funded by Beijing, secured majorities in local councils and the territory’s legislature, and new loyalty tests were imposed on candidates for office. Frustration led to the so-called Umbrella Movement of 2014, a series of protests and sit-ins aimed at securing a promise of genuine democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In response, the central authorities doubled down on the “one country” side of the deal. In 2016 and 2017 they secured the disbarring of six legislators for disrespecting China by mangling their oaths of loyalty. This year they have changed Hong Kong’s constitution to require the passage of a law that would punish people for insulting the national anthem, mirroring a law China passed in 2017. And they have pushed to change the current, colonial-era law that specifically bars extraditions to China. The proposed bill does not cover political offences, but many fear that the Communist Party could use it to secure the extradition of people deemed offensive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though Ms Lam has suspended the extradition bill, political veterans expect the Communist Party to tighten its grip in myriad, less visible ways. The central government still praises “one country, two systems” as a great innovation. In January China’s leader, Xi Jinping, stressed the policy’s importance for securing what he called the “inevitable” unification of the mainland and Taiwan. Few in Taiwan are convinced. Recent events in Hong Kong have only increased their suspicions. Deng’s innovative solution to the problem of reunification has never faced greater scepticism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 21:26:28 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>