<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[A new podcast shows why some obituaries need sound as well as words]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/13/a-new-podcast-shows-why-some-obituaries-need-sound-as-well-as-words]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BKP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-13T13:00:21Z&quot;&gt;May 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHEN AUDREY HEPBURN died in 1993, newspapers’ obituaries often mentioned the unusual lilt of her voice. The &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; noted that she spoke with the “trace of a European accent”, “a hint of mischief”. Cecil Beaton, in the &lt;em&gt;Telegraph&lt;/em&gt;, described her “singsong cadence that develops into a flat drawl ending in a child-like query”: he thought it had “the quality of heartbreak”. The &lt;em&gt;Los Angeles Times&lt;/em&gt; said that “her melodic, hard-to-place accent and haunting beauty captivated audiences and helped win her the Academy Award as best actress”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clearly Hepburn’s voice was part of her charm, but its precise sound is hard to capture on the page and hard for the reader to imagine. That is why, 26 years later, Mo Rocca has retold Hepburn’s story, this time in a different medium. On his new podcast, “Mobituaries”, the journalist dedicates 40 minutes to the movie star, tracing her life from her birth in Belgium in 1929, through her film career to her humanitarian work. The episode is interspersed with clips from “Funny Face” and “Breakfast at Tiffany’s”; there is room for her dreamy, melancholic rendition of “Moon River” (pictured). The voices of those who knew her, or who admired her work, are also included. The late Nora Ephron is recorded in an interview from 2011 gushing over Hepburn’s grace and beauty, saying that “there was no one like her, ever”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Free from the demands of the news agenda, “Mobituaries” eulogises individuals, characters and things (one episode contemplates “Neanderthals: death of a human species”; another “Death of a tree: roots of a rivalry”). It is experimental in form—each episode is an unusual blend of interviews, animated discussion, clips and music—and a way for Mr Rocca to explore subjects that intrigue him. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He is astute when picking those subjects. Only a podcast, for instance, could demonstrate the skill of Vaughn Meader, an impersonator of John F. Kennedy. The episode considers Meader’s rise to fame, what his career was like during the 12 months of Kennedy’s presidency, and what happened after the assassination in November 1963. It includes clips from “The First Family”, a hit album which launched Meader to stardom, as well as snippets of later interviews where he expressed exasperation—sadness, almost—at being asked to do “the voice”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Musicians, too, are a natural fit for the airwaves and Sammy Davis Jr., a talented singer and impressionist, is eulogised in the fifth episode. The featured interviewees maintain that it was the emotion Davis conveyed in his music that made his performances so special. The listener hears it for themself: Mr Rocca juxtaposes clips of the same song, performed first by Davis and then by another artist. The difference is surprising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere, Mr Rocca pursues more abstract discussions. An episode on deaths in sitcoms focuses on three types of death: the death of love for a character, a change of actor playing a character and the death of a character within the plot. Mr Rocca explores the phenomenon of “Chuck Cunningham syndrome”, whereby a character simply disappears (named after a figure in “Happy Days” who suffered that fate), with Alan Sepinwall, chief television critic for &lt;em&gt;Rolling Stone&lt;/em&gt;. Clips of dialogue from a number of shows support the discussion, but it is interviews that allow the listener to understand the impact of such passings. Lila Garret, a writer on “Bewitched”, laments that they had to replace actor Dick York due to his poor health. Decades on, Jamiee Foxworth expresses disbelief at her character being written out of “Family Matters” in 1992. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of this is to say that the written obituary has been left behind—a writer’s career, for example, is best weighed up in words, and the ambiguity of language can be useful—but Mr Rocca shows how some stories are enriched by sound. It makes for compelling listening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: The Economist, as well as running an obituary every week in print, also features them on occasion in “The Intelligence”, our daily podcast&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 21:05:50 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The IMF has agreed to break Pakistan’s fall. Again]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/13/the-imf-has-agreed-to-break-pakistans-fall-again]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_fnp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-13T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt; FAMILIARITY, THEY say, breeds contempt. Few countries are as familiar with the IMF as Pakistan. The over-indebted country of 200m people has obtained 21 loans from the fund, as many as Argentina. On May 12th this familiarity deepened further. The country’s government, led by Imran Khan, a former cricket star who heads the Pakistan Tehreek-e-Insaf party, said it had reached a deal with the IMF’s staff to borrow another $6bn over three years. The agreement now awaits formal approval from the fund’s bosses in Washington, and the support of other international lenders, including the World Bank and the Asian Development Bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The loan will relieve Pakistan’s dollar shortage but do little to improve the IMF’s standing in the country. In return for its money, the fund expects the government to raise tax revenues and utility prices—and to let the currency fall, if need be. That will help narrow Pakistan’s wide trade and budget deficits. But it will also curb growth and increase inflation in the short term. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The full agreement has not yet been published. But some details have been released and others leaked to the local press. Pakistan must cut its budget deficit (before debt service) to 0.6% of GDP next fiscal year (which starts in July) from the deficit of over 1.7% that the IMF expects for this year. To meet this goal, the government has reportedly promised to remove tax breaks worth about 350bn rupees ($2.5bn or 1% of GDP) next year and to raise the price of gas and electricity. It has pledged to give the central bank, the State Bank of Pakistan, more autonomy in its fight against inflation (which has increased sharply to over 8%). It will also let market forces dictate the rupee’s exchange rate, which has been devalued by over 18% against the dollar in the past year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To ease the public’s pain, the IMF will allow the government to spend more on welfare schemes, such as a cash-transfer scheme named after Benazir Bhutto, a former prime minister who was assassinated in 2007. But her son, Bilawal Bhutto Zardari, who now leads her party in opposition, seems unimpressed. After the government this month appointed a former IMF official to head the country’s central bank, Mr Bhutto Zardari accused it of surrendering Pakistan’s autonomy. “How can IMF negotiate with IMF?” he asked. A cartoon in the &lt;em&gt;Friday Times&lt;/em&gt;, a local news weekly, showed Christine Lagarde, head of the fund, sitting across the negotiating table from herself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In truth, Mr Khan’s government tried hard—perhaps too hard—to keep its distance from the fund. Instead of agreeing a deal as soon as it came to power in August 2018, it turned for help to friendly powers instead, including Saudi Arabia (which gave $3bn and deferred a similar amount of oil payments), the United Arab Emirates ($3bn) and China, which added another $2.2bn. China is investing heavily in Pakistan’s roads, ports and power plants, building what has been called the China-Pakistan Economic Corridor (CPEC). Some view this lending with suspicion, seeing Pakistan as a victim of China’s “debt-trap diplomacy”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such an assessment seems premature. CPEC spending may have contributed to the increase in Pakistan’s imports (the country’s current-account deficit exceeded 6% of GDP in the year to June 2018). But because this outflow of import spending was presumably matched by an inflow of Chinese capital, it cannot have been responsible for the dangerous dwindling of Pakistan’s foreign-currency reserves over the past year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was instead the result of Pakistan’s own macroeconomic muddle. The previous government pursued both an over-valued exchange rate, which was too strong for Pakistan’s beleaguered exporters, and imprudent fiscal spending, which was too strong for Pakistan’s feeble revenue-raising powers. The dollars provided by Pakistan’s allies in China and the Gulf have temporarily alleviated this problem of falling reserves. But solving it was always going to require policy reforms, which are difficult for bilateral allies to demand or monitor. Better to leave those tasks to the IMF.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not that the IMF will find it easy. Pakistan is a regular taker of the fund’s loans but not a diligent follower of its advice. Many of the reforms it has promised in the latest agreement have been pledged repeatedly before, including widening the tax net, rationalising utility prices and respecting the central bank’s autonomy. When push comes to shove, Pakistan’s governments have been reluctant to follow through, afraid of losing the support of powerful, but lightly taxed, domestic constituencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For their part, the IMF’s staff have been reluctant to cut Pakistan off, for fear of the upheaval that would ensue. “Governments have tried to ‘game’ the IMF, and achieved partial success each time,” write Ehtisham Ahmad and Azizali Mohammed, two former IMF advisers, in their history of the pair’s relationship. Pakistan’s public might dislike the IMF less, if they knew how frequently their leaders disregard it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 21:05:49 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“The president is the fount of all patronage”—Philippine mid-term elections]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/13/the-president-is-the-fount-of-all-patronage-philippine-mid-term-elections]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20199518_blm501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-13T11:30:32Z&quot;&gt;May 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PERSONALITIES, NOT policies, will determine poll results in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/11/the-philippines-mid-term-elections-will-tighten-the-presidents-grip&quot;&gt;Philippines&lt;/a&gt; today, where elections are underway to fill some 18,000 government jobs. Candidates who support the firebrand president, Rodrigo Duterte, such as his daughter, are likely to do well. Also, why is it that as the need for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/04/antibiotics-biotech-firms-are-struggling&quot;&gt;antibiotics&lt;/a&gt; increases, incentives to produce them are diminishing? And a trip to the tiny &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/05/11/a-groundbreaking-show-on-delos-mixes-classical-and-contemporary-art&quot;&gt;Greek island&lt;/a&gt; of Delos for an unusual meeting of modern art and protected antiquity. Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/sparetherodrigo-philippineelections&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 19:06:46 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How Manchester City came to rule English football]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/05/12/how-manchester-city-came-to-rule-english-football]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-12T22:52:14Z&quot;&gt;May 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIFTEEN YEARS ago, if you had told English football fans in a pub that Manchester City, Liverpool and Tottenham Hotspur would one day be the dominant forces in the Premier League, they would have told you to make the pint in your hand the last one for the day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2004 Spurs finished 14th in the table and Man City 16th. Liverpool, in their 14th consecutive year without a league title, ended up fourth. But they were still far behind the then ruling triumvirate: Arsenal, who had just recorded the competition’s first unbeaten season in more than a century; Chelsea, who had just been bought by Roman Abramovich, a Russian oligarch; and Manchester United, who had bagged 8 of the previous 11 titles. Between 1996 and 2011, these three clubs were the only ones to win the Premier League.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, however, fans of the Gunners, the Blues and the Red Devils must worry that they might not get their hands on the trophy again for many years. The new sultans of the Premier League are Manchester City, who on May 12th sealed their fourth title in eight seasons—to the delight of Abu Dhabi’s royal family, who purchased the club in 2008. If City have become arguably the best team in English football history, collecting a record 100 points from a possible 114 last season and 98 this time around, then Liverpool are a close second. Liverpool’s finishing total of 97 points this season would have won them the title in any other year, but that is little consolation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liverpool can still look forward to the final of the Champions League, Europe’s most prestigious tournament, on June 1st. Their opponents will be Tottenham—who are some way behind them in the league, but have finished in the top four for a fourth consecutive season, a feat matched only by Manchester City. What has allowed the new trio to dominate English football?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Big money is a big part of the answer. Manchester City’s spending spree between 2008 and 2012 included £520m ($675m) of transfer fees, more even than Mr Abramovich splurged in his first four years at Chelsea. Liverpool were rescued from the brink of bankruptcy in 2010 by Fenway Sports Group (FSG), an American company which also owns the Boston Red Sox, a baseball team. Since purchasing the club for a mere £300m, FSG has spent heavily. Estimates from 21st Club, a football consultancy, suggest that Liverpool pay over £300m in players’ wages and transfer fees every year, roughly as much as Mr Abramovich does (see chart below). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc952_0.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But spending on players is only part of the answer. Football’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/game-theory/2018/11/30/rich-clubs-are-bullying-footballs-administrators-into-submission&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Financial Fair Play rules&lt;/a&gt; penalise clubs if they spend more than they earn. In fact, Manchester City spend only 8% more per year on players than do Manchester United, the richest club in the world, yet  achieve vastly superior results. Spurs have managed to overtake Arsenal, their north London foes, even though they spend 20% less on their squad than the Gunners do. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The secret of the new trio’s success is not lavish spending, but wise investment. The leading trio have learned from the mistakes made by most other English clubs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teams in the Premier League are much richer than their counterparts in Europe’s “big five” leagues in Spain, Germany, Italy and France. According to Deloitte, a consultancy, nine of the 20 clubs with the largest annual revenues are English. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This wealth owes much to a combination of luck and shrewdness. The lucky part is that the league has always had at least three teams competing for the title, unlike the eternal duopoly of Barcelona and Real Madrid in Spain, and the near-monopoly of Bayern Munich in Germany, Juventus in Italy and Paris Saint-Germain in France. The shrewd bit is English clubs’ energetic marketing abroad, both in arranging pre-season tours and attracting foreign sponsors. Today, Asian fans are more likely to follow English clubs than those elsewhere. More Americans watch the Premier League than all other European leagues combined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But English teams have squandered much of this wealth in the transfer market. When 21st Club plotted European teams’ spending on players against their results on the pitch (see the chart above), 16 of the 20 Premier League teams sat below the trendline. In the last ten years, an English side has won the Champions League only once. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This profligacy has two causes. The first is differential pricing, an economic phenomenon in which a seller charges different customers different rates for the same good. European clubs know that Premier League sides are flush with cash, so demand greater transfer fees, reckons 21st Club. English clubs have spent, on average, 80% more than their rivals for the same level of talent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A second cause has been English clubs’ eagerness to poach ageing stars from elite teams, rather than nurturing talented youngsters. In 2017, when pondering the conundrum of why Europe’s richest league was so mediocre, this newspaper &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2017/09/02/the-english-are-bad-at-playing-football-but-brilliant-at-selling-it&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;noted&lt;/a&gt; that “in recent years a number of English sides have spent club-record sums on older players who are at the peak of their fame but have ended up spending half their time on the bench.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Data from 21st Club show that Manchester City, Liverpool and Tottenham have now bucked this trend. Since 2016, the players they have signed up have been younger and less likely to come from Europe’s best clubs than those bought by Manchester United, Chelsea and Arsenal (see chart below). Taking a gamble on a very good player in his early twenties makes it more likely that a team will enjoy his best years, in his late twenties, especially if he becomes an extraordinary footballer. And bargaining transfer fees with a smaller club makes it more likely that an English club will secure a good deal. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190518_woc005.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Manchester City adopted this strategy even though they broke their club record £55m when they bought Kevin de Bruyne, a midfielder, from Wolfsburg, a second-rate German team. Liverpool also broke their record when they purchased Mohamed Salah, an attacker, for £37m from Roma, a good (but not great) Italian side. Though both transfer fees were large, they were fairly priced: now in their peak years, Messrs de Bruyne and Salah have become their teams’ best players. Gallingly for Chelsea, both had played for the London club when they were younger, but were sold after making slow starts to their careers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tottenham have had to be even more economical, in order to finance their new stadium, which has cost £1bn to build. In fact, this year they became the first club in Premier League history not to sign a single new player during a season. That they could do so and still prosper was thanks to years of nurturing young talents from Europe’s lesser clubs, who have now matured into stars. They include Christian Eriksen (from Ajax), Son Heung-min (from Leverkusen) and Dele Alli (from lowly Milton Keynes). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whereas Manchester City, Liverpool and Tottenham fans will struggle to name a bad signing in the last three years, Manchester United, Chelsea and Arsenal have several expensive flops in their squads that they will try to sell this summer. No player has been more emblematic of this than Alexis Sánchez, a 30-year-old striker. Last year Manchester United made him the league’s highest paid player, on an annual salary of around £25m, after prising him away from Arsenal. But the ageing Mr Sánchez had already started to struggle in his final performances for Arsenal. The Chilean’s time in Manchester has been a disaster, scoring just five goals in 45 games. Chelsea’s acquisition of Álvaro Morata, a striker from Real Madrid, for a club record £60m, was equally dire. He lasted just a season. Arsenal have purchased a number of defenders who have failed to live up to their billing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hiring competence of Manchester City, Liverpool and Tottenham has allowed them to punch above their weight financially, meaning that English teams are at last able to contest the crown of European football. Whatever happens on June 1st, an English team will win the Champions League for the first time in seven years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 08:06:39 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why women’s art sells at a discount]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/05/12/why-womens-art-sells-at-a-discount]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/women2.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A ROSE painted by another name would cost more. In a new paper*, four academics show that art made by women sells for lower prices at auction than men’s, and suggest that this discount has nothing to do with talent or thematic choices. It is solely because the artists are female.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors used a sample of 1.9m transactions in art auctions across 49 countries in the period from 1970 to 2016. They found that art created by women sold at an average discount of 42% compared with works made by men. However, auction prices can be distorted by a few famous artists whose output is perceived as extremely valuable. If transactions above $1m are excluded, then the discount falls to 19%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One explanation for this gap could be that women choose different subjects. This is partly true; for example, a higher proportion of women than men paint roses (including Helen Allingham, a British watercolourist: see picture), whereas a smaller share create landscapes. But it turns out that themes that are more associated with female artists sell at a premium, not a discount. Indeed, the researchers could not explain the female discount in terms of other factors such as the size, style or medium of the paintings, or the age of the artist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In theory, another possibility could be that women are just less talented than men. To test that proposition, the authors conducted a couple of experiments. In one, they showed 1,000 people a selection of 10 lesser-known paintings and asked them to guess the gender of the artists. The respondents were right only 50.5% of the time, no better than tossing a coin. In short, the general public cannot discriminate between male and female art.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a second test, the researchers used a computer programme to generate paintings and randomly assign the results to artists with male or female names. They then asked participants to rate the paintings and ascribe a value. The experiment found that affluent individuals (those most likely to bid at auctions) attributed a lower value to works which the programme assigned to a woman. Clearly, this gap was unrelated to the artistic merit of the picture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It could be that these well-heeled observers were aware of the market discount for female artists, and applied it accordingly. But that does not solve the puzzle of why the discount arose in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two more findings imply that the difference relates to culture rather than talent. First, the academics considered the relationship between the female discount and the level of gender inequality in the countries where the auctions took place. The latter measure was based on indices (such as those compiled by the UN and the World Economic Forum) which look at factors such as educational attainment and political empowerment. For a given female artist, the average discount applied to their work was lowest in countries where women were more equal. (There are some exceptions to the rule; women’s art was highly rated in Brazil.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news is that the female discount has reduced over time. For transactions under $1m, the study calculated, the discount has dropped from 33% in the 1970s to 8% after 2010. Again, though, that only confirms the underlying prejudice—evidently ability never had anything to do with the disparity. But the reduction in the discount has another implication. As it has fallen, so the returns on women’s art have grown; since the 1970s they have been higher than for their male peers. Collectors should put aside their prejudices: as the art world’s longstanding chauvinism abates, the female of the species has become a better investment than the male.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;* “Is Gender in the Eye of the Beholder? Identifying Cultural Attitudes with Art Auction Prices” by Renée Adams, Roman Kräussl, Marco Navone and Patrick Verwijmeren&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 07:10:45 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The joy of absence]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/12/the-joy-of-absence]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_wbp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;RONALD REAGAN famously quipped that “it’s true hard work never killed anybody, but I figure, why take the chance?” Beyond a certain level, extra effort seems to be self-defeating. Studies suggest that, after around 50 hours a week, employee productivity declines sharply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that doesn’t stop some managers from demanding that workers stay chained to their desk for long periods. At the blood-testing firm Theranos, Sunny Balwani, boyfriend of the founder, Elizabeth Holmes, had an obsession with employee hours, and would tour the engineering department at 7.30pm to check people were at their desks. All those hours were wasted when the company eventually collapsed (prosecutors have charged Ms Holmes with fraud).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jack Ma, the founder of Alibaba, the Chinese e-commerce group, recently praised the 996 model, where employees work from 9am to 9pm, six days a week, as a “great opportunity”. To be fair, Mr Ma said employers should not mandate such hours. Still presenteeism is the curse of the modern office worker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will be days when you do not have much to do; perhaps because you are waiting for someone else in a different department, or a different company, to respond to a request. As the clock ticks past 5pm, there may be no purpose in staying at your desk. But you can see your boss hard at work and, more important, they can see you. So you make an effort to look busy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of this may be a self-perpetuating cycle. If bosses do not like to go home before their underlings, and underlings fear leaving before their bosses, everyone is trapped. Staff may feel that they will not get a pay rise, or a promotion, if they are not seen to be putting in maximum effort. This is easily confused with long hours. Managers, who are often no good at judging employees’ performance, use time in the office as a proxy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The consequence is often wasted effort. To adjust the old joke about the Soviet Union: “We pretend to work and managers pretend to believe us.” Rather than work hard, you toil to make bosses think that you are. Leaving a jacket on your office chair, walking around purposefully with a clipboard, and sending out emails at odd hours are three of the best known tricks. After a while this can result in collective self-delusion that it is actual work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But presenteeism has more serious consequences. It is perhaps most prevalent in Japan, where people attend the office even when they are in discomfort. In doing so, they are neither doing themselves, or their employers, any favours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As well as reduced productivity, this can mean greater medical expenses for the employer. According to a study in the Journal of Occupation and Environmental Medicine, these costs can be six times higher for employers than the costs of absenteeism among workers. To take one example, research published in the British Medical Journal found that Japanese employees with lower back pain were three times more likely to turn up for work than in Britain. As a result, those workers were more likely to experience greater pain and to suffer from depression. What could be more depressing than being in pain, and feeling trapped at work?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of this is to say that employers are not entitled to expect workers to be in the office for a decent proportion of time. Inevitably there will be a need for some (preferably short) meetings. Dealing with colleagues face-to-face creates a feeling of camaraderie, allows for a useful exchange of ideas and enables workers to have a better sense of their mutual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the grand sweep of humanity, presenteeism is a recent phenomenon. Before the industrial era, most people worked in their own farm or workshop and were paid for the amount they produced. Factories emerged because new machines were much more efficient than cottage-industry methods, and only a large employer with capital could afford them. Suddenly, workers were paid not for their output but for their time, and were required to clock in and out. But modern machinery like smartphones and laptops is portable. It can be used as easily at home as in the office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turning an office into a prison, with inmates allowed home for the evenings, does nothing for creativity that is increasingly demanded of office workers as routine tasks are automated. To be productive you need presence of mind, not being present in the flesh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 06:13:23 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Russia’s military gamble in Syria is paying off handsomely]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/12/russias-military-gamble-in-syria-is-paying-off-handsomely]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_map001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE GREAT victory train clattered across eight time zones and back before groaning into a military-exhibition ground outside Moscow last month. It pulled car after car of trophies from Syria, as well as wagon-loads of patriotism and conspiracy theories. Here was a pockmarked American-made Humvee; there pickup-trucks turned into battering-rams for suicide car-bombers. Various home-made bombs included one hidden in a can of Russian beer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amid the fanfare of military bands, veterans on the platform recounted how Russia had intervened in 2015 to stop Syria falling into the hands of jihadists, notably Islamic State (IS), who had been secretly armed by NATO. “A lot of what you’re seeing here could have been delivered directly by the Americans,” explains one guide. “It’s not just my opinion. Many think so.” Never mind that Russia fought mostly against non-IS groups, or that America did much to crush the IS “caliphate”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another display purported to show a chemical-weapons lab with barrels of precursors labelled in English—an apparent attempt to accuse rebels of using chlorine gas in Douma in 2018. Western powers blamed the regime of Bashar al-Assad and bombed Syrian air bases in retaliation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Propaganda aside, Russia is elated with its victory. It saved Mr Assad at relatively small cost to itself, became the kingmaker in Syria and returned as a power-broker in the Middle East for the first time since the dissolution of the Soviet Union. All this is gratifyingly different from the experience of America, whose invasion of Iraq turned into a bloody debacle; or of western Europeans, whose air campaign in Libya to topple the dictator Muammar Qaddafi sundered the country. Most important, breaking America’s hegemony in the Middle East shows that Russia is not merely a “regional power”, as Barack Obama once put it, but a global one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The “Syrian Breakthrough” tour revives the long tradition of &lt;em&gt;agitpoezd&lt;/em&gt; (agit-trains). Stalin, for instance, used them to show off Soviet victories against the Nazis. When the latest train arrived in Moscow, young army cadets clambered onto a tank chanting “To Berlin!” Many Russians—more than one million, according to the authorities—have come to ogle the loot. “They’re fighting not against some tribesmen shooting arrows but against people with serious technical capabilities—tanks, armoured vehicles, and mortars,” said Anton Sidorov, a salesman and veteran of the Russian navy, who brought his four-year-old son. To stop terrorism in Russia, he added, “we have to battle terrorism outside of our territory.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russia has surprised itself with its prowess. Many Russians recall how the intervention in Afghanistan in 1979 helped destroy the Soviet Union. Russia’s war in Georgia in 2008 exposed many inadequacies, not least the poor performance of the air force. Its annexation of Crimea and its undeclared war in eastern Ukraine in 2014 brought Western sanctions and isolation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The military success was much bigger than anyone expected,” says Fyodor Lukyanov, a foreign-policy adviser to the Russian government, “Russia demonstrated in Syria that it has a degree of efficiency in using military force, compared with the two previous experiences in Georgia and Ukraine. Politically, it was an even bigger surprise.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moscow has turned into a centre for Middle Eastern diplomacy. In 2017 King Salman became the first Saudi monarch to visit Russia. Binyamin Netanyahu, Israel’s prime minister, has met Vladimir Putin, Russia’s president, a dozen times since the intervention. Russian diplomats who spent decades as spectators to America’s management of the Israeli-Palestinian peace process delight in knowing that America must now watch as Russia, Turkey and Iran negotiate the future of Syria. Deaf to warnings of a looming humanitarian catastrophe, the Syrian government, backed by Russian bombers, this month resumed operations to retake the province of Idlib, the last major area still in rebel hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strikingly, Russia has been able to keep friends with all sides of the region’s bitter rivalries: Israel and Iran; Turkey and the Kurds; Saudi Arabia and Qatar. For Russian military commanders, the war in Syria has been a proving ground for new tactics and weapons, and a showcase for arms exports.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russia and Saudi Arabia struck an unprecedented deal in early 2017 to limit oil output. The so-called OPEC-plus accord has helped lift prices, which fell below $30 a barrel in 2016, to the current level above $60. In Mr Lukyanov’s view, the deal would not have been possible without Russia’s enhanced regional status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a result, there is a new swagger about Russia in the wider world. Mr Putin has used his Syrian success for advantage elsewhere. He plans to host a summit with African leaders in October, and has sent advisers and private military companies to help some of its despots. Russia is also helping to prop up the regime of Nicolás Maduro in Venezuela. These days it is America that complains of Russia meddling in its sphere of influence, not the other way around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This contest is less the product of ideological conviction than of self-interest. But if America until recently championed democracy, Russia is becoming, in effect, the foremost defender of autocracy—at least in the view of Arab rulers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kremlin-watchers reckon little of all this had been in Mr Putin’s mind when he ordered his forces into Syria. His priority had been to avert the collapse of Mr Assad’s regime, and the risk that Syria might become an exporter of jihadism to Russia. Another reason was to break out of the diplomatic isolation he faced over Ukraine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How did Russia succeed where others failed? In part, it absorbed the lessons of America in Iraq, relying mostly on its air power and on local proxies on the ground: the Syrian army, Iranian troops, Hizbullah fighters from Lebanon and others. It also drew on the experience of Arabists nurtured by the late Yevgeny Primakov, a former foreign and prime minister. “Damascus is closer to Sochi than it is to most European cities,” says one Russian think-tanker. “Russia feels a close connection to the Middle East, partly because of the legacy of the Byzantine empire.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Israel remembers that the Soviet Union had been the first country to recognise the infant Jewish state &lt;em&gt;de jure&lt;/em&gt;, and provided it with vital weapons via Czechoslovakia. Saudis note that the Soviet Union had been the first country to establish diplomatic relations with the new Saudi kingdom in 1926 (alas, the Soviet ambassador was executed during Stalin’s purges).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cynicism plays a part. Mr Putin is less troubled than Western leaders are by public opinion or civil-society groups making a fuss about Russia’s actions. He does not ask about democracy and human rights. “We have a common interest in non-intervention in our internal affairs,” notes one Arab diplomat. In the view of Arab leaders, Mr Obama forsook Egypt’s dictator, Hosni Mubarak, whereas Mr Putin stood by the vile Mr Assad. Even if Donald Trump is more partial to strongmen, they find him mercurial. “We disagree with Russia on many things,” says the diplomat. “But when Putin makes a commitment, he delivers.” Strangely, Israeli and Gulf leaders keep mum about Russia’s role in providing air power to the reviled “Shia axis”; instead, they say Russia is a counterweight to Iran’s influence in Syria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the main reason that Russia can talk to all players in the region is that it is not America. For most of them America remains the all-important protector, so their dismay is all the greater when it appears to be losing interest in them. Israeli and Gulf leaders feared betrayal when Mr Obama negotiated a deal in 2015 to limit Iran’s nuclear programme in exchange for a partial lifting of sanctions. They care much less that Russia is selling Iran civilian nuclear technology, or has set up barter deals to help Iran circumvent sanctions. If the region’s rulers are flirting with Russia, it is mostly to regain America’s commitment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amid the swelling pride in Moscow, there is also much nervousness. Russia’s land may be vast but its economy is only the size of South Korea’s. Russians’ real disposable incomes have fallen five years running. For all the shows of patriotism, support for the war is soft: according to the Levada Centre, an independent pollster, 35% do not approve of Russia’s policy in Syria, against 51% who do; most think the military operation ought to be wound up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Opinion could turn more hostile if things go wrong in Syria, which Russian officials know is all too possible. They are learning another lesson from America’s ill-begotten war in Iraq: it is easier to win a short-term military victory than create a lasting political settlement. Few outsiders want to pay to repair the damage it has wreaked. And Russia is ensnared by its local ally. Mr Assad is strong enough to resist Russian entreaties to make political concessions, but too weak to be threatened without risking his collapse. Then there are more catastrophic risks: a confrontation with Turkey over Idlib, say, or a Turkish invasion to push back Syrian Kurds, or even a war between Israel and Iran. A surprising number of Russian experts worry about the venture “collapsing like a house of cards”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short, the power that Mr Putin tries to project abroad, in the hope that it will enhance his standing at home, is brittle. The multipolar world he has sought to bring about may yet leave Russia on the sidelines; it boasts neither the military power of America nor the economic strength of China. Tellingly, few in Moscow want to see America leave Afghanistan, fearing that might destabilise Russia’s southern flank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Right now, Mr Putin may like patriots chanting “To Berlin!” The danger for him is that they may yet start crying: “Bring our boys home!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 06:13:22 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Some American carriers are installing cameras on their in-flight entertainment screens]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/gulliver/2019/05/10/some-american-carriers-are-installing-cameras-on-their-in-flight-entertainment-screens]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_BLP511.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-10T12:37:19Z&quot;&gt;May 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;FLYERS TRAVELLING ON one of America’s major airlines may soon notice a mysterious item on the back of the set in front: a small sticker under the in-flight entertainment screen. These stickers have appeared as the result of a public outcry in recent months over the unpublicised installation of video cameras on these screens on at least four airlines. The fuss began in February on a Singapore Airlines flight, when a passenger noticed what appeared to be a camera lens by her video screen. Her husband, a cybersecurity expert, tweeted a photo of it. The airline confirmed that it was a camera. On some of their planes with newer entertainment systems, the fitters of the interiors had installed devices with an embedded camera. But Singapore Airlines said that the cameras had been “disabled” and they had no plans to use them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;That did nothing to quell public anxiety, which only grew with news reports later the same month that some screens on the big three American carriers, American Airlines, Delta Air Lines and United Airlines, also had cameras on-board. In March two American senators demanded that eight American carriers disclose whether they were using cameras to monitor passengers and whether passengers were being informed. The airlines insisted that the cameras were not operational, but they scrambled to cover them up anyway. United and Delta recently began covering all the cameras on their entertainment systems. American has also announced plans to do the same.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That ought to end the panic. But it also raises the question of why people were worried about these cameras in the first place. Of course it would be wrong for airlines to spy on their customers. But the threat to privacy from this is nothing compared to the greater threat of hackers gaining access to the webcams on laptops in people’s homes, or to virtual assistants such as Amazon’s Alexa. Aircraft, particularly in economy class, are not private places. Anything a passenger says or does can be witnessed by dozens of people. It is undeniably important for airlines to protect passengers’ privacy when it comes to their personal data—and a strict legal requirement in Europe with so-called GDPR rules. But a passenger’s behaviour while sitting in an aircraft seat—snoring, or watching a low-brow movie, or maybe picking one’s nose—is just not all that private to begin with, nor is it of much interest to companies or hackers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bigger concern is what flyers would actually do with these cameras, if they became operational. The chief technology officer of Panasonic, one of the world’s biggest manufacturers of airline-entertainment systems, which recently rolled out a new generation of their devices containing cameras and microphones, told the &lt;em&gt;New York Times &lt;/em&gt;that these devices were intended to eventually allow airlines to offer seat-to-seat or plane-to-ground video calls. Imagine a plane on which half the passengers are video-chatting to friends a few rows away or relatives back home, if you want to read a book or do some work quietly. That sounds far more disturbing than any hypothetical spying. So, on second thought, it might be a good idea to keep those cameras covered up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 03:12:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why the public prefers eccentric Christians to archbishops]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/05/10/why-the-public-prefers-eccentric-christians-to-archbishops]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_BLP513.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-10T11:31:12Z&quot;&gt;May 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;CHRISTIANITY IS the world’s most popular religion, with over 2bn followers, according to the Pew Research Centre, an American think-tank. It is the historically predominant faith in most prosperous democracies. Yet over the past century, only a limited number of Christians have gained commanding respect and influence for the way they lived out their faith, in their own countries and beyond. And many—most, even—have been idiosyncratic characters who have chosen to live outside most formal structures, or at the very edge of those structures, rather than mighty hierarchs of the church. Often they were people who had the option of living conventional, secure lives but at a certain point made radically different choices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One such person was Jean Vanier, who died this week. He was a Canadian diplomat’s son who served as a naval officer, then as a professor of theology and philosophy, but was inspired to change course after seeing the dreary conditions inside an institution for men with learning difficulties near Paris. That inspired him to open a home where people with mental-health or cognitive problems would be valued and invited to contribute to the community. He promoted an ethos than turned on its head the conventional notion of what it means to be normal and successful, and the result was a movement that eventually spread to 35 countries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another strange and charismatic (in several senses) character was Brother Roger (pictured with Mother Teresa), who became a kind of monk despite being born into a French-Swiss Protestant tradition in which monasticism hardly exists. As the founder of the Taizé community in eastern France, he was somehow able to communicate with a younger generation that was abandoning formal religion in droves, but still felt a kind of spiritual thirst. Like Vanier, he died in France at the age of 90, but the end of Roger’s life, after he was stabbed by a mentally disturbed Romanian woman, was far uglier. By the time of his passing in 2005, prayer groups modelled on his community had formed across North America. If his style of spiritual guidance had a hallmark, it was a willingness to listen as well as preach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even harder to place in any box, perhaps, was Dorothy Day, a social and political activist who lived much of her life in rough areas of New York, where she rubbed shoulders with socialists, communists and hippies, while finding commonalities and differences with them all. As a founder of the Catholic Worker Movement, she declared herself a “pacifist even in the class struggle” although she professed to understand perfectly well why the poor wanted to rise up against their oppressors. It was a stance that exasperated both secular lefists and Christian conservatives, but her integrity compelled a grudging respect. For all her radicalism on economics, she adhered to Catholic teaching on sexual and reproductive issues, saying she regretted having an abortion. Utterly different as she was from the Catholic bishops of her day, she may eventually be proclaimed a saint. A process that could lead to canonising her began under Pope John Paul II in 2000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet another place on the spectrum of idiosyncratic sanctity was occupied by Mother Teresa, the ethnic Albanian nun who worked among the destitute in Kolkata and founded a missionary order that eventually spread to more than 130 countries. When she died in 1997, her labour among the “poorest of the poor” was saluted by the leaders of India and Pakistan, who were neither Christian nor in agreement about much else. She had her critics, some of whom branded her indifferent to the root causes of poverty, and opposed to the female empowerment which might have improved living standards. Some felt that she was too quick to seek the approval of the rich and powerful. But people respected her manifest indifference to her own material comfort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As one more example of holy, disinterested eccentricity, take the figure of Maria Skobtsova, the cigarette-smoking Russian nun who lived among the down-and-out in Paris in the 1930s and was eventually executed in a Nazi gas chamber in 1945. Practising the ideal of unconditional hospitality, she was critical of the ritualistic piety of some fellow members of the Russian diaspora in France, and she doubtless infuriated some of them. But she was the one who was eventually recognised as a martyr, not her pious compatriots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What all these people have in common is the fact that they embraced uncomfortable lives, even though they had experienced a relatively comfortable existence and might have held onto it. Dorothy Day was the daughter of secular middle-class Americans, her father a sports writer. Mother Teresa could have practised her monastic vocation in Ireland, a land where she lived as a young woman. Skobstova was a talented poet and well-trained intellectual who could certainly have enjoyed the secular side of life as a Russian émigré.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reputation of a “saint”, whether in the strict sense or a somewhat broader one, is a fickle thing. The spectacle of self-abnegation in a higher cause is both fascinating and to some observers, a bit suspicious. Presented with any paragon of virtue, people immediately start asking themselves what flaws this altruistic individual had, and if the flaws turn out to be rather glaring, that can come as a kind of relief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But when facing public scrutiny, mitred princes of the church are at a particular disadvantage. They must convince sceptical onlookers that the trappings of power and prestige which they  enjoy by virtue of their office are being worn with humility, and in a spirit of concern for others. (If they have personal experience of persecution, as John Paul II did under Nazism and communism, that certainly adds credibility.) But in general, today’s world, both religious and otherwise, prefers a mud-caked eccentric to a gorgeous episcopal robe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 01:07:38 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The refugee train from Sarajevo]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/news/2019/05/11/the-refugee-train-from-sarajevo]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/bihac_train.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-11T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE flyblown plaza in front of Sarajevo’s railway station is called “Srebrenica Genocide Victims Square”. The echoey, empty station is like a cathedral. When Sarajevo, Bosnia’s capital, was at the heart of the former Yugoslavia it bustled. Now only 11 trains a day depart, and 11 arrive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To understand quite how sad a state of affairs this is, compare it to the central station in Zagreb, the capital of neighbouring Croatia. Its population is, admittedly, 40% larger than Bosnia’s. Yet Zagreb’s station has more than 16 times as much rail traffic, not counting trains serving the city’s suburban stations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was a time when you could get from Sarajevo by train to most of Europe. But in the last few years financial disputes have cut Bosnian railways off from the rest of the world. Now you can’t even take a train from here to Croatia, let alone farther away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have come to Sarajevo station to catch the train to Banja Luka, now the capital of the Serb part of Bosnia-Hercegovina. Its government denies that a genocide took place in Srebrenica, where Bosnian Serb soldiers killed some 8,000 Bosniak (Bosnian Muslim) men and boys in 1995, towards the end of the Bosnian war.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Most Bosnians have lost the habit of train travel. “You are mad” said friends when I said I was taking the train: it will be disgusting and the toilets will be clogged. They don’t know that it is as modern a train as you will find anywhere in Europe. The rolling stock was delivered from Spain in 2010 and then parked in a siding until 2016, when tracks and infrastructure was finally upgraded to take them.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The first railway to Banja Luka, which connected it to Croatia, was laid by the Ottomans in 1872. Then came the Austro-Hungarians and finally the Yugoslavs. The link to Sarajevo—built by prisoners of war and communist youth brigades, including thousands of foreigners—was completed only in the early 1950s. During the Bosnian war the railways stopped running, except for small sections.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;When the train pulls in to Sarajevo, only one door is unlocked for passengers to get on. “That way” says the conductor pointing right. “What about that way?” I ask. “Migrants” he says brusquely, but if I &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; want to sit with them that would be my choice. The migrants take the train on to Bihac, from where they try to sneak past border guards get to Croatia and then deeper into the EU. I am not here to write about them, but I join them anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Opposite me is Morsal, 26 years old. She is travelling with her two-year-old daughter, who was born in a refugee camp in Serbia. Morsal explains that she used to be a policewoman in Afghanistan. She shows me a picture of a woman surrounded by white cloth and has something white on her mouth. It takes me a few seconds to realise that the subject is lying in a coffin. Morsal had received a call from a man who warned her to quit the police; a week later four men burst into her home and shot her 16-year-old sister dead, thinking it was Morsal. Within hours Morsal began her flight via Pakistan, Iran, Turkey, Bulgaria, Serbia and now Bosnia.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Next to me is Asal, her parents and little brother. They are Iranian Kurds and for 15 years Asal’s father had been a member of an underground Kurdish political group. The Iranian security services discovered it, two members were executed and the family fled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last October Serbia ended a brief period of no-visa requirements for Iranians, but not before there had been an influx of asylum-seekers. “Did you fly to Serbia?” I ask. “No, we came with the mafia,” says a deadpan Asal. She is only 11-years old and speaks fantastic English.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;I have little doubt that Asal and Morsal will flourish in, and contribute to, any country that takes them in. I cannot say the same about a group of Algerian men in our carriage. One, who sports a top-knot, says his father is in France but he cannot get a visa to go there because, he chortles, he has been in jail four times “for fighting and that sort of thing”.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;At Banja Luka only one door opens, again. For some reason three of the migrants try to get off here. They are greeted by Bosnian Serb policemen who bark the equivalent of “Oi! Where do you think you are going?” No Muslim refugees are allowed off here.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;I ask the train crew why they separated the migrants from the other passengers, who are a mix of Bosniaks, Serbs and Croats. Answer: “Because they complain that the migrants smell.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I immediately remembered the many refugees of the Yugoslav wars: Bosniaks who flopped exhausted into Croatia, one night in 1992, having been driven out by Bosnian Serbs; Serbs who had fled Croatia to Banja Luka on their tractors; and Croats going the other way on theirs to get away from Serbs. “Have all of you actually &lt;em&gt;forgotten&lt;/em&gt; that this was you not so long ago?” I want to ask them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bosnian activists have helped the refugees. But for many Bosnians, regardless of ethnicity, the bitterness that lingers, almost a quarter of a century after the end of the war, seems to have squeezed out any sense of sympathy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:31:50 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>