<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[A Muslim appeal for Saudi Arabia to show mercy]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/06/02/a-muslim-appeal-for-saudi-arabia-to-show-mercy]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_blp902.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-02T18:40:14Z&quot;&gt;Jun 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;With all world religions, there are strains between the ancient heartland and the periphery. A Catholic campus in the American Mid-West feels different from the cloisters of the Vatican; the Buddhism embraced by Californian beach-goers lacks the rigour of a monastery in Thailand or Tibet. But in Islam, tensions of this kind, and the way they are resolved, can literally be a matter of life or death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 80 respected scholars and teachers of the Muslim faith, from many countries but mostly Anglophone ones, have lent their names to a plea to the Saudi authorities. It urges the kingdom to spare the lives of three well-known figures in the world of Islam. The trio have been incarcerated on “terrorism” charges since 2017. They had refused to back the kingdom’s diplomatic and economic blockade of neighbouring Qatar, at a time when this was  becoming a litmus-test of loyalty and securing the support of prominent and mildly independent-minded imams seemed to have become a high priority for the regime. Prosecutors want the death penalty, and unconfirmed reports indicate they might be dispatched when the holy month of Ramadan ends on June 4th. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Best-known of the three is Salman al-Ouda, a religious teacher who has built up a global audience (with about 14m Twitter followers), having first gained prominence in the 1990s when he challenged the kingdom’s alliance with America against Saddam Hussein’s Iraq. In 1999 he emerged from a five-year jail term as a defender of the regime and an advocate of Sunni-Shia dialogue. For a while he was able to teach and act freely; in 2006 he attracted a big, enthusiastic audience in London.  Also facing execution are Awad al-Qarni, a preacher, academic and author, and Ali al-Omari, a popular broadcaster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what sort of people have been courageous enough to raise their voices in support of the trio, in defiance of the huge influence that Saudi Arabia and its austere brand of Sunni Islam can exercise in almost every corner of the Muslim world? For any mosque, institute or faculty that hopes one day to gain Saudi funding, backing such a document comes at a price. And in other Middle Eastern countries such as Jordan, Bahrain and Egypt, criticism of Saudi policies can end in prosecution or worse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The answer to that question provides a revealing snapshot of the state of global Islam. Virtually none of the signatories is based in a Muslim country. Yet among those who enjoy the freedom of the Western world, the theological range is remarkably broad. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To explain this, it helps to understand the categories into which Sunni Islam’s main exponents fall. There are those who follow the Muslim Brotherhood, a movement that aspires, usually peacefully, to shift both society and its governance in an Islamic direction. Then there are traditionalists, those less concerned with politics but who see Islam’s accumulated body of law and teaching as the only cure for the “bad theology” which inspires terrorism. A third category are Salafis who prefer to go back to the basic axioms of faith and life laid down by Muhammad and his immediate successors; some Salafis are aligned with the Saudi regime, others are a bit more liberal, and some are ruthless jihadists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among the people now appealing for the lives of the incarcerated trio, there are plenty of Brotherhood-minded scholars. One would expect that, given the poisonous standoff between the Saudis and the perceived Brotherhood stronghold of Qatar, the country which the trio had impertinently refused to condemn. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But more surprisingly, the appeal was initiated by traditionalist scholars, a camp which enjoys the respect of Western governments because of its eloquent critique of terrorism. The traditionalists don’t often intervene directly in earthly affairs, particularly when it comes to Saudi Arabia; this is a rare exception.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The document’s prime movers include Faraz Rabbani, a popular Muslim teacher of south Asian origin who studied for a long time in Jordan and Syria before settling in Canada. That is a classic traditionalist profile. Also on the list are some liberal Salafis, a couple of non-Muslims who are respected scholars of Islam and at least one Shia Muslim. Given the rifts within the Muslim world--especially since the Arab Spring, which triggered murderous feuds between Brothers, Salafis and traditionalists--it is quite impressive to see such a diverse list of names on a single piece of paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, there are some striking gaps. Some of the most prominent figures in Western-based Islam are absent from the list, although their students and mentees do appear, possibly with their mentors’ discreet permission. (Lecturers from one of the West’s leading seminaries, Zaytuna College in California, are on the list but its founder, Hamza Yusuf, is not.) British signatories include Sulaiman Gani, a south London imam who forced ex-prime minister David Cameron to apologise for calling him extremist. But the leaders of Britain’s biggest mosques are noticeably missing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever the exact line-up, the appeal enjoys the approval of Mr al-Ouda’s American-based son, Abdullah, an academic scholar now based at Georgetown University. He believes the document carries real moral power, exactly because it challenges the Saudis’ claimed monopoly on Muslim wisdom. “The Saudi government is always concerned about its Islamic authority, they want to tell the West that they alone have the legitimate authority to speak about Islam.” It was in that spirit, he noted, that the kingdom in recent days hosted a conference with the paradoxically-chosen topic of “moderate Islam”, organised by the Saudi-backed Muslim World League.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jonathan Brown, an American signatory and convert to Islam who is a professor at Georgetown, said he hoped the appeal would lay bare the counter-productiveness of Saudi Arabia’s current policy. For as long as they were at liberty, the independent but broadly loyal views of teachers like Mr al-Qarni and Mr al-Ouda were a kind of advertisement for the kingdom’s fractionally loosening atmosphere. Capital punishment would have the opposite effect. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It remains hard to predict whether the executions will take place; there has been no official verdict yet. But events could unfold quickly.  If they do happen, the diverse luminaries of Western-based Islam will come together not in polite supplication but in quiet horror. (Western governments, to judge by their reaction to some recent executions, including that of 37 “spy suspects” and protesters in April, will express disapproval but not too loudly.) Meanwhile the gap between centre and the periphery will yawn wider than ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 03:40:01 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Charity begins at work]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/02/charity-begins-at-work]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190601_wbp504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE REPORT was devastating. The working environment at the organisation was described as “toxic”, there was widespread bullying of staff, a bunker mentality among senior management and 39% of employees developed mental or physical health issues as a result of their work. An investment bank or a technology firm in Silicon Valley? No. This was Amnesty International, a human-rights charity. Five managers have just left the organisation following the report’s findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Workplaces create their own hierarchies regardless of whether the aim of the operation is to help people or make money. Two female partners at KPMG, an accountancy group, recently left out of concern at the behaviour of a male colleague. Coming from a family of teachers, Bartleby can attest that school staff rooms are beset by bitter rivalries. Universities are famous for their internecine disputes, as captured in the adage that “academic politics are so vicious precisely because the stakes are so small.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Amnesty, the problem was not with staff motivation. The report, by the KonTerra group, a consultancy, makes clear that many employees regarded their job as a “vocation or life cause” that provided them with “a compelling sense of purpose and meaning”. But that commitment proved to be a double-edged sword.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, in the eyes of workers, managers believed the importance of the NGO’s work was so great that they did not need to listen to staff concerns. Employees, the higher-ups seemed to conclude, “should be grateful for being able to work at Amnesty”. Second, workers found it difficult to set healthy boundaries on their hours (or their tolerance of a toxic climate) owing to a deeply held belief in their mission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One cause of stress was a process called the Global Transition Programme (GTP) which moved the staff away from headquarters and closer to the abuses they covered. Workers felt that their views about these transfers were not seriously considered and that the implementation of the programme was rushed. As a result, employees found their work patterns disrupted, even as some moved to high-risk locations. Concerns came to a head when Gaëtan Mootoo, a long-term employee, committed suicide, leaving a note blaming work pressures. Another staff member committed suicide shortly afterwards, although inquries found no evidence that the death was work-related. The tragic incidents led to the commissioning of the report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what went wrong? On the surface, Amnesty seemed to offer services to help employees cope with stress. Staff were eligible for five counselling sessions, and an external reporting service for whistle-blowing had been created. Programmes were developed to train leaders and to help staff support their colleagues. But these efforts were described as “ad hoc, reactive and piecemeal”. In a survey 85% of employees said they had not been given enough guidance to support the well-being of their colleagues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The problem clearly came from the top. If senior management is not committed to a caring atmosphere, no amount of discussion groups or special programmes will make things better. &lt;br/&gt;A certain amount of stress at work is inevitable. Most organisations are hierarchical. Deadlines are a part of life, as is uncertainty over whether individual projects are going to succeed. But workers who are stressed and fearful are unlikely to stay in their jobs or be productive in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many managers derive a lot of their status from their oversight role. That is, in part, why organisations create such roles: they can reward high-achieving employees with a title, as well as with extra money. But power is seductive. Peter Cappelli, a scholar of human resources at the Wharton School in Philadelphia, says that toxicity arises when “the boss acts like a dictator and actively punishes people who articulate different views or express disagreement.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Amy Edmondson of Harvard Business School explained in her book, “The Fearless Organisation”, the ideal is to create an atmosphere of “psychological safety” where workers can speak their minds. Managers need to learn the art of “respectful inquiry”, where they ask employees questions and listen intently to the answers. The bosses at Amnesty may have listened to the political dissidents whose causes they were championing. But they clearly weren’t listening to their staff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 01:40:16 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The leader of Germany&#x27;s Social Democrats resigns]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/02/the-leader-of-germanys-social-democrats-resigns]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A PALL of uncertainty hangs over German politics after Andrea Nahles resigned as leader of the Social Democratic Party (SPD), the junior coalition partner, on June 2nd. Ms Nahles, an SPD veteran who has served in previous governments, will step down from both the party chairmanship and the presidency of its parliamentary caucus. She also said she would leave the Bundestag, without naming a date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Nahles’s departure, long forecast in some SPD circles, was hastened by a week of grim news for the party. On May 26th the SPD sank to a dismal 15.8% in the European elections, down by 11.5 percentage points on its 2014 result, and lost the city-state of Bremen for the first time in seven decades. A recent poll put it at just 12%, less than half the score of the surging Greens. As rumour swirled and party barons plotted, Ms Nahles sought to flush out her internal enemies by putting her leadership of its parliamentary group up for early election. But although no candidates emerged to challenge her, the continued disquiet convinced Ms Nahles that, as she said this morning, she “no longer had the support required to carry out her duties”. Something had to give.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Nahles’s resignation reignites questions over the future of Germany’s “grand” coalition, which unites the SPD with Angela Merkel’s centre-right Christian Democratic Union and its Bavarian sister party, the Christian Social Union. This awkward marriage has been on the rocks from almost the moment it was established, in March 2018. A string of political missteps and poor election results has only strengthened the hand of those in the SPD base who always believed the party would decline further in government and needed a spell in opposition. This afternoon both Mrs Merkel and Annegret Kramp-Karrenbauer, the CDU leader, urged the SPD to find a successor for Ms Nahles quickly. They said their party remained committed to the coalition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The SPD’s woes will hardly end with Ms Nahles’s defenestration. The party’s quarrelsome bench is thin on potential replacements. Beyond a parade of ex-leaders who continue to offer views, solicited or otherwise, Olaf Scholz, the vice-chancellor and finance minister, is the only SPD figure with a national profile, and he has plenty of foes himself. More difficult state elections lie ahead, in Germany’s east. The Greens continue to eat into the party’s voter base. And at the end of the year, a half-time review clause in the coalition agreement provides the SPD’s coalition sceptics with a formal platform to agitate for departure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The case against leaving nonetheless remains strong. The SPD is enjoying some policy success in government, in areas such as arms-exports and immigration. Triggering an election - the likely consequence of walking out - would probably wipe out large swathes of its representation in the Bundestag. Under the gaffe-prone Ms Kramp-Karrenbauer the CDU looks more vulnerable than it has for years. Yet the implicit promise of rejoining the CDU/CSU was that the SPD could renew itself in government. That has patently not held. Now the question is whether Germany’s coalition can.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 01:40:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s state visit to Britain]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/02/donald-trumps-state-visit-to-britain]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190601_brp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even before arriving in London on June 3rd for a three-day state visit, President Donald Trump stirred controversy, weighing in with views on potential successors to Theresa May as prime minister. The visit itself will be an extravaganza of protests and pomp. It will also be a test of how “special” the relationship between America and Britain can remain in the face of serious strains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The president is coming at a febrile time in British politics. Mrs May is about to step down as Conservative party leader, and once Mr Trump leaves she will trigger the formal start of the race between at least a dozen candidates to replace her. Like the Tories, the Labour Party took a pounding in the recent European elections; it is also beset by allegations of anti-Semitism. The country’s divisions over Brexit look deeper than ever. In such circumstances a typical visiting head of state would strive to rise above it all with tact and diplomacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not Mr Trump. On his previous working trip to Britain as president last July he embarrassed Mrs May with an interview in the Sun newspaper in which he criticised her position on Brexit and praised Boris Johnson, who had just resigned as foreign secretary. True to form, this time Mr Trump told the Sun shortly before his arrival that Mr Johnson, now front-runner in the race to be prime minister, would be “excellent” as leader. Once again he criticised Britain’s negotiating strategy for Brexit: “the UK allowed the European Union to have all the cards.”&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;As last time, too, protesters will be out in force, probably again with a giant inflatable of a baby Trump in a nappy. A few prominent figures are flagging their opposition to the visit—peevishly, critics say—by turning down their invitation to attend a state dinner on Monday. They include the Liberal Democrats’ leader, Vince Cable, and Labour’s Jeremy Corbyn, who object to Britain rolling out the red carpet for a “misogynist and racist”. The Speaker of the House of Commons, John Bercow, is also staying away—and did not invite the president to address Parliament (something Barack Obama, Bill Clinton and Ronald Reagan did).&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Despite the sense of déjà vu, this visit is a bigger deal than last year’s, in two respects. First, tensions are simmering between the two countries over issues that go to the core of their relationship. One is Iran. America has pulled out of the nuclear accord with Iran and is ratcheting up sanctions against it. Now it is twisting European allies’ arms over their efforts to enable trade to flow with the help of a new payments system called Instex. The Treasury last month warned the Europeans that efforts to circumvent sanctions could have “severe consequences, including a loss of access to the US financial system”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America is also warning its close ally about its possible use of 5G technology from Huawei, a Chinese telecoms giant with a well-established presence in the country. Last month Mike Pompeo, America’s secretary of state, warned that relying on Chinese 5G kit might put intelligence-sharing at risk. “What can Her Majesty’s government do to make sure sensitive technologies don’t become open doors for Beijing’s spymasters?” he said in a speech in London last month. “Insufficient security will impede the United States’ ability to share certain information with trusted networks.” British diplomats have long tended to downplay talk of the special relationship with America—except when it comes to security. Any erosion of trust on intelligence-sharing would be deeply damaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump will no doubt make his views clear on these issues, but he will also be determined to wallow in the pageantry of a state visit. That is the second reason why this time is different: such things are grand occasions. He is bringing not just the First Lady but all his four adult children to meet the Queen.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;So there will be warmth amid the wariness. The visit will culminate in events to mark the 75th anniversary of the D-Day landings, a reminder of what Britain and America can achieve when they stand shoulder to shoulder. Mr Trump likes the fact that Britain is one of a handful of NATO allies that meets the target of spending 2% of GDP on defence. Jeremy Hunt, the foreign secretary and another would-be prime minister, has said he favours a decisive increase in defence spending (“I think that’s great,” Mr Trump told the Sun). And with his characteristic modesty Mr Trump professes to love Britain: “I don’t imagine any other US president was closer to your great land.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:41:25 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Does Santa Claus speak Danish, English or Russian?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/06/01/does-santa-claus-speak-danish-english-or-russian]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190601_amp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;THERE ARE three reasons why Thomas Nast, the 19th-century American illustrator who created the twinkly grandfather image of Santa Claus, decided to place his workshop at the North Pole. The location was cold enough for the reindeer that pulled his sleigh; it was sufficiently remote so that curious children could not contemplate a visit; and it lay in neutral territory, allowing Santa to be an international goodwill ambassador. The last will not be true for much longer. Three states—Russia, Denmark and Canada—are claiming that the seabed and subsoil at the top of the world are part of their countries’ extended continental shelf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;The claims come under the 1982 UN Convention on the Law of the Sea, an international treaty that all the states with Arctic coastlines, except the United States, have ratified (the US says it will abide by it). The treaty states that the first 12 nautical miles from a country’s shore are territorial waters, meaning the country has exclusive rights above and below the waters, and to the airspace. Countries can also claim up to 200 nautical miles from shore as an exclusive economic zone, giving them rights to marine life in the waters and minerals on or under the seabed. This zone can be further extended if the country can prove, using a wide range of scientific evidence, that the seabed is an extension of the country’s continental shelf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Russia, Denmark (on behalf of Greenland), and now Canada on May 23&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;rd&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; have duly filed lengthy reports with the Commission on the Limits of the Continental Shelf, a body set up under the treaty to study the scientific evidence gathered with much blood, sweat and frozen tears. Although the polar ice cap is shrinking because of global warming, large parts of the ocean remain ice-bound for most of the year. To peer at the seafloor, scientists used icebreakers (although even a nuclear-powered one could not penetrate an area north of Greenland), and set up perilous, temporary camps on drifting ice floes. Colleagues on shore did a deep dive into history, trying to establish what was happening in the Arctic before and after dinosaurs roamed the earth. How underwater ridges and mountains formed millions of years ago can help determine which land mass they should be connected to today.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;The commission decides whether the science backing a claim is robust. Russia was told to do more work on its 2001 submission, which it refiled in 2015. But the body does not resolve disputes. Countries must negotiate an agreement on overlapping claims. And there are many. The Arctic is the smallest ocean, about 14m square kilometres; it accounts for just 4.3% of the world’s total water surface compared with 46.6% for the Pacific Ocean. The bit that does not fall within some country’s exclusive economic zone is only 2.8m square kilometres. Within that area, Russia is claiming 1.2m square kilometres, Denmark almost 1m and Canada 1.2m. All three claim large parts of the 1,800km-long Lomonosov ridge, which divides the Arctic Ocean into two main basins; and all three claim the geographic North Pole.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Anywhere else on Earth this would look like a recipe for armed conflict. A steady drumbeat of stories about the militarisation of the region creating to a new cold war in the Arctic lend support to that idea. Russia has been forthright about its ambitions. It made a big deal of planting a titanium Russian flag on the seabed at the North Pole in 2007. Yet armed conflict over rival claims is unlikely for two reasons. First, relations between countries and communities in the Arctic, although strained since the Ukraine crisis of 2014, remain cordial for the most part.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;The template for co-operation was set in 1996 when the eight countries with Arctic coastlines set up an inter-governmental forum called the Arctic Council, where they and indigenous peoples could co-operate on matters affecting the region. The sharp remarks made by Mike Pompeo, the American secretary of state, on the fringes of last month’s meeting of Arctic Council ministers in Finland were a break from this trend. (He criticised, among other things, Russia’s and Canada’s claims to control sea routes in the High North.) More in keeping with it was the presence of Russian lawmakers at a meeting in May of Arctic parliamentarians in Ottawa, even though Chrystia Freeland, Canada’s foreign minister, is banned from visiting Russia because of her strong denunciation of its actions in the Ukraine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Co-operation is most evident in the scientific domain. To collect its data, Canada conducted joint surveys with Denmark, Sweden and the United States, with which it has an overlapping claim in the western Arctic. The scientists who posed for a photo at the North Pole in 2016 displayed the flags of 14 countries. Russia, Denmark and Canada could have blocked the commission from studying a rival’s claim, but each gave the required permissions and have remained in close contact throughout. Harold Brekke, a former commissioner from Norway, was cited as a special advisor on all three submissions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;The prospect of a resource war looks equally flimsy. The US Geological Survey made headlines in 2008 when it estimated that the Arctic region contained 30% of the world’s undiscovered gas and 13% of its undiscovered oil. But most of the known or suspected reserves are within the 200-mile limit of national exclusive economic zones. Those found further out would be uneconomic to exploit because of the hostile environment and the distance to the ports and pipelines connecting the north to markets farther south. Commercial fishing in the high seas of the Arctic is already banned under an agreement signed in 2017 by the eight Arctic states plus China, Japan, South Korea and the European Union. As Andreas Osthagen, of the Fridtjof Nansens Institute in Norway, told the High North News, “there is very little to fight over’’.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Laying claim to the North Pole appears to be more a matter of prestige than economic potential. A hefty backlog at the commission means the matter will not be settled soon. Canada estimates it will be another decade before its submission is dealt with. The three countries have made their respective cases and now face what may seem like an interminable wait—a bit like children feel while waiting for Santa Claus at Christmas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 01:40:46 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A judge prevents the closure of Missouri’s only abortion clinic]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/31/a-judge-prevents-the-closure-of-missouris-only-abortion-clinic]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_USP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-31T23:36:56Z&quot;&gt;Jun 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 2008 Missouri had five abortion clinics. Today the state, which has 6m inhabitants—more than 1m of whom are women of child-bearing age—has one. On May 31st, a judge intervened to prevent that clinic, in the city of St Louis, from losing its licence to provide abortions. Were that to happen, and it yet may, Missouri would become the only American state since 1973—when the Supreme Court declared abortion a constitutional right—to have no abortion provider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The clinic, which is run by Planned Parenthood, is threatened with closure because the state’s Department of Health and Senior Services (DHSS) has refused to renew its licence, which expires at midnight on May 31st. It had refused, said Governor Mike Parson at a televised press conference this week, because of a “series of deficiencies” it had found at the clinic. These ranged, he said, from [largely unspecified] concerns about patient safety to the clinic’s failure to comply with licensing procedures. Among those he cited the fact that of seven doctors who work at the clinic only two had agreed to be interviewed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Planned Parenthood, the biggest provider of abortions in America, strongly refuted the suggestion the clinic was improperly run. In a lawsuit launched on May 28th it said that it had responded to every demand made by the DHSS. It described the department’s request to interview all the doctors who worked there as “inappropriate and suspicious”. The DHSS, it said, had “suggested this interrogation could lead to criminal proceedings…but refused to explain why or how”. Withholding the licence was another move in the state’s long-term effort to &amp;quot;restrict abortion access and deny Missourians their right to choose abortion”. It asked for a temporary restraining order against the state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On May 31st, the judge, Michael Stelzer of Missouri Circuit Court in St Louis, granted that. But the reprieve may only be temporary. He scheduled another hearing for June 4th. “Today is a victory for women across Missouri but this fight is far from over”, said Leana Wen, the president of Planned Parenthood, in a statement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Missouri does seem to be exceptionally keen on stopping women from having abortions. Last week Mr Parson, a pro-life Republican, signed a law banning abortions after the eighth week of pregnancy. More than a dozen states have introduced similar bills banning abortion from the moment a heartbeat is detectable, which often happens before a woman realises she is pregnant. In six states such “heartbeat” bills have been passed. The most recent was Louisiana where on May 30th the Democratic governor, John Bel Edwards, bucked his party’s line to sign a heartbeat ban into law. Earlier this month Alabama passed an even more draconian law banning all abortions at any stage of pregnancy. This, like several heartbeat bills, has no exceptions for pregnancies that result from rape or incest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because these laws flatly violate &lt;em&gt;Roe v Wade&lt;/em&gt;, the 46-year-old Supreme Court ruling which says abortion is legal until a fetus is viable, at around 24 weeks, they being are struck down in the courts. The lawmakers behind them hope that one case or another will make it to the Supreme Court where the new conservative majority will then use it to overturn &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The threat to close Missouri’s last clinic is an example of a more insidious attempt to prevent abortion. Since 1992, when the Supreme Court in its &lt;em&gt;Planned Parenthood v Casey&lt;/em&gt; ruling said states could not impose an “undue burden” on women seeking an abortion, pro-life activists have tested the limits of that by introducing regulations designed to impede access to abortion. Missouri has been at the vanguard of that effort. It has imposed a 72-hour waiting period between consultation and abortion—which is costly and stressful for women who have to travel long distances to get to St Louis—and strict limits on the use of insurance to cover abortions.  The state also insists on intrusive pelvic examinations for medical abortions, which gynaecologists say are unnecessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2018, Missouri lost its second-to-last abortion clinic after it was unable to meet another state requirement—securing “admitting privileges” at a nearby hospital. Many hospitals do not allow doctors who work elsewhere to admit patients, not least because it is considered unnecessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the success of such regulations and other fiddly licensing requirements is inarguable. Missouri is one of at least six states that have only one clinic left. “We are waking up to the effects of these regulations because the attack on &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt; has become so obvious”, says Mary Ziegler, a professor at the Florida State University College of Law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Autumn Katz, a lawyer for the Centre for Reproductive Rights, says that in most cases clinics have chosen to close before being stripped of their licences. “We have seen this so many times: states enforcing intentionally opaque licensing rules in an arbitrary manner that is designed to close clinics”, she says. Missouri’s case is a reminder, she adds, that states do not need to make abortions illegal to stop them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 08:40:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The struggle to reduce the “motherhood penalty”]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/31/the-struggle-to-reduce-the-motherhood-penalty]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190608_woc174.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-31T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 31st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE “MOTHERHOOD PENALTY”—the sharp decline in earnings that women suffer after giving birth—is one of the principal causes of the gender pay gap. It often locks women into lower incomes for the rest of their careers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Governments around the world have sought ways to reduce the opportunity cost of having children, and that cause it to be shared more evenly between men and women. A new &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://conference.iza.org/conference_files/SUM_2019/karunanethy_k28091.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;working paper&lt;/a&gt; examines the impact of the introduction of paid maternity leave in Switzerland 15 years ago. It is a rare comprehensive study of the impact of such policies. It finds that the policy did appear to shrink the motherhood penalty—but by a disappointingly small amount.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In September 2004 Swiss voters approved in a referendum a new law that required the government to pay mothers 80% of their previous salary for 14 weeks after giving birth, up to a cap of SFR196 ($196) per day. The benefit is funded by a tax on payrolls of 0.45%, split equally between employers and workers. It also protects women against losing their jobs for 16 weeks after their babies are born. Eligibility requirements are strict. To qualify, women must have worked for at least five months of their pregnancy, and still hold a paid job on the day they give birth. Nonetheless, the law’s passage made Switzerland the last country in Western Europe to guarantee paid maternity leave, and left the United States as the world’s only high-income economy without such a policy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The policy has had modest success. The working paper compares mothers&amp;#x27; average wages before and after the introduction of paid maternity leave. Surprisingly, the study found that maternity leave actually reduced first-time mothers’ average earnings by 4% one year before giving birth. However, it also led to a faster recovery in salaries, such that mothers’ wages four years after giving birth were 2% higher than they had been before the policy was enacted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors propose one benign explanation for the apparent negative pre-natal impact on earnings: the introduction of maternity leave could have led some women to join the labour force in low-paid jobs before pregnancy, so lowering average earnings. Nonetheless, the overall post-natal impact of the law, although positive, seems surprisingly small. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/01/28/how-big-is-the-wage-penalty-for-mothers&quot;&gt;Previous research&lt;/a&gt; from Nordic countries suggests that better paternity leave and a change in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2018/01/26/the-roots-of-the-gender-pay-gap-lie-in-childhood&quot;&gt;social norms&lt;/a&gt; regarding the division of child-rearing and housework can help narrow the gap, for instance, by allowing women to return to work sooner and so suffer a shorter interruption to their careers. Men might need to work harder at home, so that mothers can draw level at work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 04:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[With Sudan’s street-fighting women]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/31/with-sudans-street-fighting-women]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190531_cdd001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-31T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 31st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON APRIL 23rd I stood amid throngs of Sudanese as a train carrying hundreds of people arrived in the heart of Khartoum. The carriages were crammed with passengers from Atbara, the town where anti-government demonstrations had begun five months earlier. They had come to join the swelling ranks of protesters against military rule. As we watched these reinforcements arrive, a fellow journalist remarked that the scene reminded him of Russia in 1917. (He’s an old hand but I don’t think he was there.) More than a century ago Vladimir Ilyich Lenin arrived in Russia on a train from Switzerland, intent on seizing power for the Bolsheviks. Yet, train aside, it is an inapt parallel. For unlike Lenin’s coup d’etat, what I saw in Sudan was peaceful, joyous and leaderless.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Less than a fortnight earlier, on April 11th, civilians had forced Sudan’s army into ending the 30-year reign of the dictator, Omar al-Bashir, who is indicted by the International Criminal Court for war crimes and genocide. That was not enough, however, to end the sit-in. In the weeks after Mr Bashir’s ouster ordinary Sudanese kept up pressure on the junta to cede power. More than a month after my visit, the protestors remain dug in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On my first day in Khartoum, I went to the sit-in with Abbas, a member of the Sudanese Professionals Association (SPA), a coalition of trade unions that has spearheaded the protests. It was midnight, and the 40-degree heat of the day had mercifully waned. As we walked among those on the streets Abbas explained that: “There was an atmosphere of darkness, now there is hope.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like many Sudanese, Abbas was still processing the demise of a figure that seemed immovable. He still spoke of President Bashir’s rule in the present tense. Osman Mirghani, a local journalist, explained: “After 30 years of dictatorship nobody thought the regime could be removed.” Day after day, young Sudanese had shown incredible courage to occupy the demonstration site. Dozens were killed by security forces before the army itself turned on Mr Bashir.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Abbas took me on a tour he pointed to places where his comrades had been shot. By now, though, the area seemed more like a festival than a warzone. Small groups of students were singing a capella. Abbas translated the lyrics: “We have questions for Bashir”, went one. A “mobile mosque” shone a spotlight on those kneeling to pray. Children waited at stalls to have their faces painted with the colours of the Sudanese flag. Job done, their parents would hoist them on their shoulders so they could take a look at the vast crowds. “All of these kids believe one thing,” said Abbas, “the power of peaceful protest to bring down the regime.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since most of those at the sit-in were under 30 years old, and since this is 2019, smartphones were everywhere. There was a feedback loop between the online and offline worlds: protesters at the sit-in would take photos and post them on Facebook, which would encourage friends to come down to the site; or they would take videos and have them broadcast on the screen by the main stage. All this intensified the feeling of being part of history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During the week I was in Khartoum the days fell into a familiar pattern: I would spend the daylight hours trying to figure out what was going on between the civilian and military negotiators, then in the evening I would return to the sit-in. As Africa Correspondent for The Economist I cover 50-plus countries, and I am forever trying to quickly understand the spirit of a place. It is often easy to get trapped in air-conditioned offices getting the official spiel, when the real happenings are out on the street. This is especially true in times of flux. But by returning to the sit-in every night I was able to track the protesters’ views of what was happening in the corridors of power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I left awestruck by the determination of young Sudanese. One evening I sat down on a patch of grass to talk to three women who had been coming to the protests for weeks. “At the start we were lying to our parents about going here,” explained Eman Suliman, a 23-year-old engineer (who lives at home). Now their mothers and fathers support them. “They don’t have the energy to come but they feel the injustice,” said Ms Suliman. How long will you stay here? I asked. “We Sudanese have big reserves of endurance,” answered Nuha Elamien, a doctor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Sudanese women the sit-in seemed to be a site of particular catharsis. Under Mr Bashir women were harassed for wearing the “wrong” clothes or being on the street alone. Roan Kheir, a 23-year-old who returned from studying in England to join the protests, recalled when she was interrogated outside a cake shop for having the temerity to wear short sleeves. She listed many reasons why she came back to protest: corruption, an economy that makes it hard for young people to start a family, and solidarity with Sudan’s persecuted ethnic groups. But “female inequality” was critical. Civilian rule, she hoped, would allow more young Sudanese to live how they choose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the protest I noticed many young couples holding hands. Such public displays of intimacy may have been dangerous under the old regime. In protests in Cairo in 2011 there were reports of sexual assaults. Here in Khartoum, though, the atmosphere struck me as different, more wholesome. In some ways it resembled the Tiananmen Square protests in China in 1989, where young couples were unofficially married at the sites of sit-ins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the partial exception of Tunisia, most of the mass protests that came under the banner of the Arab spring of 2011 ultimately failed. When one side has the guns and the other has placards, the former usually wins. President Bashir was nearly toppled in 2013. But this time he was overwhelmed by the sheer weight of protestors, fortified by the knowledge that twice before, in 1964 and 1985, Sudan’s dictators had been swept away by people power. The army has now been forced at least to share power, a testament to the resilience of ordinary young Sudanese. It has yet to be seen whether the generals are willing to hand over completely to civilian rule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Talking to Abbas after the Atbara train passed I wondered aloud whether the mood was too celebratory, too soon. He said, politely, that I should not confuse elation of with a sense of a job completed. “We Sudanese”, he said, “we cover pain with joy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 02:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Populism can be beaten back by libraries. Really]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/05/31/populism-can-be-beaten-back-by-libraries-really]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_OPP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-31T17:56:00Z&quot;&gt;May 31st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANY IDEAS have been put forward to explain the rise of populism in the West: economic insecurity, a backlash against immigration and fake news, to name but a few. Another on the list might be the lack of shared spaces where people from different walks of life can meet and mingle. If politics has become tribal, perhaps that is a result of people being walled off from others—in some cases literally—eroding the sense of commonality and community.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is the intriguing message of a recent book by Eric Klinenberg, a sociologist at New York University and the author of “Palaces for the People: How Social Infrastructure Can Help Fight Inequality, Polarization, and the Decline of Civic Life” (Crown, 2018). The title comes from a phrase used by Andrew Carnegie, an American steel baron of the early 20th century, to describe the thousands of public libraries he helped build with his donations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To Mr Klinenberg, social infrastructure is the public spaces which bring people together so that bonds can form. In his book, he documents how it produces benefits ranging from economic growth to better governance, at a time when social media seem to pull people apart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Below, &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s Open Future initiative is publishing an excerpt from the book on what the design of university campuses means for the ethos of students and the wider community. It is followed by a short interview with Mr Klinenberg on social infrastructure in the 21st century, and in particular, libraries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*   &lt;span &gt; &lt;/span&gt;*   &lt;span &gt; &lt;/span&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Designing college campuses—and community&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Excerpted from “Palaces for the People” by Eric Klinenberg (Crown, 2018)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Designing campuses that promote learning and community building may be a relatively new priority in public education circles, where resources are scarce, but it has always been a central concern of universities, which play an outsize role in modern societies. The late Richard Dober, a renowned scholar at Harvard and MIT who designed college campuses throughout the world, estimated that, as of 1992, about 40% of the American population had spent at least one year as a full-time student on one of the nation’s 3,500 or so college campuses. “Campus design is a civic art that resonates with meaning and significance for our culture,” he wrote. “The Greeks had their agora, the Romans their Forum, the Middle Ages their cathedral and town square, the Renaissance their palaces and enclaves for the privileged, and the 19th century their centres of commerce, transportation and government. The campus is uniquely our generation’s contribution to communal placemaking and placemarking.” When designed well, it should “promote community, allegiance, and civility, while at the same time encouraging diversity in discourse and vision.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp502.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp502.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp502.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp502.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp502.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp502.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp502.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp502.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp502.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The time we spend on college campuses shapes our ideas about what we want to pursue and who we want to become. It changes our social networks and work opportunities. It breaks down ethnic and religious divisions, leading to what we once called “mixed marriages” between people who’d otherwise never form families together. And even as a growing number of people on both sides of the political spectrum express concern that colleges—and particularly partisan student groups—have become inhospitable to civil debate about controversial topics, there’s no better institution to prepare us for civic life in democratic societies, giving us the tools we need to understand difference, evaluate evidence, and engage in reasoned dialogue with people who don’t share our perspectives or values.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This hasn’t always been the case. Many of the earliest European universities were designed to solidify social boundaries, not open them. In “Campus: An American Planning Tradition”, the Stanford professor Paul Turner recounts that the first universities, in Bologna and Paris, were part of the city, and students typically lodged with their families or with townspeople. As universities developed, local entrepreneurs built halls and hostels for the students. But many school administrators disliked this arrangement, as did the aristocratic parents of university students, and universities began to erect gates and walls to separate their sacred grounds from the profane communities in which they had been embedded. New College, at Oxford, built the first enclosed quadrangle that housed all university functions in 1379. Many schools followed, giving rise to the model of the college as a segregated residential community as well as an educational institution where students studied, largely in private rooms, under the direct tutelage of a learned instructor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turner identifies several reasons for the use of the enclosed quadrangle in British colleges, from efficient land use in crowded towns to the influential tradition of the cloistered monastery. “Simply from an architectural point of view,” he writes, “the monastic and collegiate ‘programmes’ were nearly identical: the housing of a community of unmarried men and boys, with space for sleeping, eating, instruction, and religious services.” The walls that divided the college campus from the town served defensive purposes, protecting students and faculty not only from occasional wars and local conflicts but also from townspeople. “The early histories of Oxford and Cambridge abound in incidents of town-gown antagonism leading to fighting, warfare, and murder on both sides,” Turner reports. “The ability to close off a college at a few gate-points also gave college authorities the advantage of greater control over the students, a concern that was a major factor in the growth of the collegiate system.” By 1410, Oxford required all students to live in colleges rather than in the town, and that policy remains intact, albeit only for freshmen, today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oxford and Cambridge opened up in other ways, however. In the 16th century, when a graduate of Cambridge named Dr. John Caius raised concerns about the health risks of confining students to stagnant, foul air, the university built its first three-sided courtyard. (Some attribute the form to rising fashions in France’s new chateaux.) Whatever its origin, Turner writes, the new, open campus spaces “suggested a more sympathetic and less defensive attitude toward the world outside the college.” So too did the schools’ push to reform admissions policies. During the 17th century, the great British universities made their first efforts to incorporate local, non-aristocratic children, and a larger proportion of the general population entered higher education than at any time except the twentieth century. These trends influenced the first American colleges, which were more accessible and expansive than anything in the Old World. […]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp505.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp505.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp505.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp505.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp505.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp505.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp505.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp505.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp505.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the beginning, the architects of America’s universities rejected the monastic model that influenced European institutions, and designed them to be deeply social places. The primary motivation was intellectual. American campus architects wanted to build universities where knowledge from different fields would circulate freely, across academic domains and into the world as well. The intellectual life they promoted was never meant to be contained or disciplined. They aimed for cross-pollination, and the campus—its classrooms, libraries, dormitories, and dining halls—was an instrument of convergence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;American campus designers were also intent on building new communities, and they had novel ideas for fostering social ties. Harvard was but one of many American schools to organize student life around colleges, each with its own spaces for dining, studying, and fraternising. Princeton developed dining societies, which later became eating clubs, as the foundation for college social activities. Students played a role in creating campus culture too. In 1776, five men at the College of William and Mary started a new student society, Phi Beta Kappa, which eventually added chapters at universities across the country, becoming the first intercollegiate fraternity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fraternities whose agenda was more social than academic are, of course, another hallmark of American universities. […] Both as organisations and also as physical places, fraternities are an exemplary form of exclusive social infrastructure. The residential houses often contain dining facilities, indoor and outdoor recreational areas, bars, common rooms for entertainment, and ample party space, all of which encourage members to anchor their lives around them. Since most fraternities select people with similar backgrounds and interests—ethnicity, race, religion, class, or often sports (and occasionally academics)—joining one is an effective way to avoid the diversity and difference a university offers. Members gain brothers and sisters, but too often lose the chance to be part of something greater.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[…]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fraternities are not the only divisive social infrastructures on college campuses. American universities rarely built the kind of high walls that protected colleges at Oxford and Cambridge from the communities around them, but many schools, particularly those in cities, have buttressed their exclusive admissions standards with elaborate physical and organisational systems that separate students and faculty from neighboring people and places perceived as dangerous. Today, large campus security operations reinforce these perceptions at universities throughout the country, and make the distinction between insiders and outsiders especially sharp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conventionally, college administrators and city planners think of “town/gown” divisions as especially bad for residents, not students, because they’re the ones excluded from campus amenities and stuck dealing with a raucous population of young people who haven’t learned to be good neighbors. But universities that cut themselves off from surrounding communities also hurt students, giving them a false sense of superiority and depriving them of opportunities to learn from their neighbors and develop the civic skills that they—and all of us—urgently need.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;______________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Excerpted from “Palaces for the People: How Social Infrastructure Can Help Fight Inequality, Polarization, and the Decline of Civic Life.” Copyright © 2018 by Eric Klinenberg. Used with permission of Crown. All rights reserved.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*   &lt;span &gt; &lt;/span&gt;*   &lt;span &gt; &lt;/span&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: What is social infrastructure?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Eric Klinenberg&lt;/strong&gt;: Social infrastructure is the set of physical places that shape our interactions. The most democratic and accessible social infrastructure are classic public goods, such as libraries, schools, parks, and playgrounds. Community organisations and commercial gathering places can be social infrastructure, but if they are exclusive, they tend to foster divisiveness by promoting in-group solidarity rather than collective wellbeing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: Can you tie the rise of populism and fraying of a democratic ethos in America to a decline in social infrastructure? Conversely, will more or better social infrastructure help America&amp;#x27;s politics?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Klinenberg&lt;/strong&gt;: Shared spaces give us a chance to recognise our commonalities and establish mutual respect. Shared activities, whether in public gathering places, pubs or union halls, facilitate solidarity, even across group lines. My book tells the story of my Jewish great-grandfather, who immigrated from Prague to Chicago in 1890 and quickly discovered that participating in American democracy meant learning to live and co-operate with members of ethnic groups he had never encountered in Europe. In recent decades, we have taken away the common ground that made this cooperation possible. We have built a more competitive and segmented society, and these conditions nurture the dangerous forms of populism that flourish today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp503.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp503.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp503.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp503.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp503.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp503.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp503.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp503.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190601_opp503.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: Is the type of social infrastructure needed in the digital age different or the same as in the past?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Klinenberg&lt;/strong&gt;: After the 2016 election, Mark Zuckerberg wrote a public letter claiming that Facebook would be a crucial social infrastructure that reinvigorates democracy. But since then, we have learned that social media is doing much more to promote hate, propaganda and division than to generate the “meaningful communities” that Zuckerberg promised. If you want to know what kind of social infrastructure tech leaders really value, take a close look at the campuses they have developed in Silicon Valley: Offices designed for serendipitous encounters between members of different teams. Cafeterias with communal tables and free food. Athletic fields, walking paths, roof gardens, party spaces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why? Because they want their employees to enjoy being at work so much that they won’t want to leave. And, as Mr Zuckerberg knows better than anyone, the way to do that is not to get employees to use social media more often. It is to design and build the best social infrastructure that money can buy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: How can government best support the creation of social infrastructure? Should they build and maintain it, or encourage the private sector to provide it? Does it need a new philanthropist to built new &amp;quot;palaces for the people&amp;quot;?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Klinenberg&lt;/strong&gt;: Public-private partnerships have always played an important role in building America’s social infrastructure. Andrew Carnegie, after all, donated money to construct nearly 1,700 public libraries in America, on the condition that local governments take over all the costs of running and maintaining them. Carnegie’s generosity came at a time when there was no federal income tax. Imagine how many more “palaces for the people” America could have built had it simply imposed a fair tax on him and other successful industrialists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today I fear we are heading in a similar direction, cutting taxes for the most affluent people and hoping that their philanthropy will help solve our problems, whether it is student debt or social infrastructure. Unfortunately, philanthropy is always partial, selective and unequally distributed. The only way we will get comprehensive social infrastructure is if it is a public good that government provides.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: Who does social infrastructure well? Who can America learn from?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Klinenberg&lt;/strong&gt;: America has a lot to learn about social infrastructure. After all, our president’s biggest infrastructure idea is the wall, which is the most anti-social infrastructure project one can imagine, I often point to the Netherlands as a leader in integrating social infrastructure into climate adaptation and mitigation strategies. The Dutch have learned to build parks, plazas and playgrounds that double as flood-management systems, so that investments in ecological security improve the quality of everyday social life, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Japan has built social infrastructure into its transit infrastructure system. In Tokyo the stations are largely underground and protected from the kind of inundation that New York’s endured during hurricane Sandy. They are also clean, well-maintained and enlivened by all variety of commercial activities. Several stations are now social destinations—a far cry from what we experience in New York, where the transit experience has become a war of all against all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: I want to probe more about social infrastructure’s answer to populism, authoritarianism, post-truth and the open society—not simply social cohesion, which is its first-order effect... There is something far deeper here. What is it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Klinenberg&lt;/strong&gt;: I think the answer is closely tied to my discussion of libraries. Libraries play an especially important role in promoting democratic culture—and challenging authoritarianism—because of the way they are staffed, managed and programmed. They are radically inclusive. They are governed by professionals who abide by powerful vocational norms: pursuing knowledge with the best tools at our disposal; being non-judgmental; respecting the dignity of all persons; maintaining privacy; treating everyone, regardless of social class, race, ethnicity, age, ability or citizenship status as equals. If, on one side of the battlefield, demagogues and tech titans are pushing us towards a post-truth era, on the other, librarians are pushing back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But I fear that we are starving our libraries just when we most need them. In New York, the so-called &amp;quot;progressive&amp;quot; mayor, Bill De Blasio, wants to cut millions from the library budget, which could mean shuttering vital branches on weekends. In Ontario, Canada, the provincial government of Doug Ford is slashing the Library Services budget in half. If you don&amp;#x27;t think this matters, visit your local library this week and witness all the extraordinary things happening there. Every time a library closes its doors our society becomes a little less open, our democracy a little more vulnerable. If we don&amp;#x27;t reinvest in libraries, and in social infrastructure more broadly, what will keep us from the dark age that so many people fear?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: Right. But in a digital age when information can exist in multiple places at once and people can organise online, do we really need these physical forms of social infrastructures or libraries? When I raised this in an earlier question, you chided Mark Zuckerberg for his failings. And he is an easy target. But what of digital social-infrastructure done well? Can you imagine what a 21st-century social infrastructure ought look like? After all, I think you are going to need to, because the library budget is going to get slashed and Zuck isn&amp;#x27;t going away...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Klinenberg&lt;/strong&gt;: I don&amp;#x27;t have to imagine 21st-century social infrastructure. I just saw it, on my visit to the Oodi Library in Helsinki (pictured at the top of this page). It is a library that feels like a spaceship in the center of a bustling metropolis. It has open, light, airy spaces for reading and writing. It has rooms for all kinds of collaborative work, from video gaming to podcasting and sewing. It has rooms for community meetings, a theatre, affordable food and lots of programming. What is more, it is open everyday, from 8am to 10pm on weekdays and nearly as long on weekends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But places like Oodi exist outside of Scandinavia, too. Cities across the planet have invested in new, modern libraries that are designed for 21st-century needs. Check out the brand new library in Austin, Texas, which features maker space for local techies and enormous open spaces for children and their grown-ups. Or the smaller, new, suburban libraries in Cuyahoga County, Ohio, which are bustling with activity every day and evening—author readings, 3D printing, story-time for families, community meetings on local issues that need to get aired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are in Canada, these descriptions may remind you of the new library in Calgary. In each of these cities, residents collectively decided that a public investment in social infrastructure would generate all kinds of benefits. In Columbus, Ohio, voters decided to tax themselves for the privilege of better libraries. So I&amp;#x27;m not giving up the fight for public social infrastructure easily. And millennials, who use libraries more than any other generation—see the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2017/06/21/millennials-are-the-most-likely-generation-of-americans-to-use-public-libraries/&quot;&gt;Pew data&lt;/a&gt;—will be with me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 01:40:16 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Who will run tomorrow’s top companies?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/31/who-will-run-tomorrows-top-companies]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/edited_image.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-31T16:30:22Z&quot;&gt;May 31st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ANNE MCELVOY asks &lt;strong&gt;Ursula Burns&lt;/strong&gt; about how she became &lt;strong&gt;the first black woman to run a Fortune 500 company.&lt;/strong&gt; She explains why she now champions &lt;strong&gt;gender quotas&lt;/strong&gt;, having vehemently opposed them. And, as &lt;strong&gt;artificial intelligence&lt;/strong&gt; threatens more traditional jobs, how CEOs should &lt;strong&gt;balance protecting profits with protecting their employees&lt;/strong&gt;. Runtime: 27 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-whowillruntomorrow-stopcompanies-&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2019 00:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>