<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[On “Fleabag”, a Corbyn government and Kenneth Clarke’s tandoori moments]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/bagehots-notebook/2019/04/26/on-fleabag-a-corbyn-government-and-kenneth-clarkes-tandoori-moments]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_BRP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-26T11:47:49Z&quot;&gt;Apr 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I FINALLY GOT round to watching a few episodes of “Fleabag” to see what all the fuss is about. A few good scenes, I thought, and a magnificently disgusting character with a beard, but apart from that underwhelming. The breaking of conventions (addressing the camera, graphic sexual references, sleeping with a priest) was tediously conventional; the sentimentality, particularly about a pet hamster, was cloying….“Fleabag” and the “Fleabag”-related hype is nevertheless interesting for sociological reasons: it demonstrates the annexation of yet another area of British life by the self-worshipping upper-middle classes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Comedy used to be a pretty working-class affair. In the Victorian and Edwardian era the upper-classes (including Edward VII) went to music halls to listen to working-class songs and jokes. Many of the giants of post-war comedy such as Eric Morecambe and Les Dawson (pictured, left) came from the northern working class, their talents honed in working-men’s clubs and local talent contests. The “Carry On” films traded in seaside-postcard smut while taking pot-shots at the pretensions of the British professional classes (“Carry On Doctor” is a masterpiece of doctor-deflation).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Fleabag” is to comedy what “Coldplay” is to music: a demonstration that yet another working-class redoubt has been thoroughly conquered by the professional classes. Fleabag’s parents live in a giant house with a garden-party sized garden. Her sister is a high-flying executive. Though she’s a bit of a drop-out, she’s a drop-out in the way that only very privileged people can be: she runs a (tediously wacky) café and turns up to work when she wants to. This is as it should be. People should write about what they know and Phoebe Waller-Bridge (pictured, right), the writer of the series, is a descendant of baronets and a product of Saint Augustine Priory, a posh Catholic school. But it is yet another example of British social closure as a tiny elite takes over ever more areas of British life and then congratulates itself on how magnificently rule-breaking they are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A popular explanation for this great social closure is that the fix-is-in: a tiny clique of hyper-connected metropolitan liberals have seized control of the machinery of cultural production and then throw a few baubles to selected minorities in order to persuade everybody (including themselves) that Britain is still an opportunity society. But I worry that the explanation may be darker: as the working class contracts and looses its cultural self-confidence, so working class institutions such as working men&amp;#x27;s clubs are dying.  The modern equivalents of Les Dawson or the Carry On Team don’t have anywhere to learn their craft while the Phoebe Waller-Bridges of this world drift from independent schools to the Royal Academy of Dramatic Art convinced that they’re overturning social conventions and setting the world to rights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PEOPLE ARE finally beginning to take seriously the possibility of a government led by Jeremy Corbyn, the Labour Party leader. Mr Corbyn’s impressive performance in the last general election, in 2017, was largely written off as a protest vote: chunks of Remainer England voted for Mr Corbyn precisely because they thought that he had no hope of actually winning. Now with the Conservative Party determined to destroy itself, and Brexit-related turmoil mounting, people are getting seriously worried.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Businesses are calculating exactly what a far-left government would mean and preparing to act accordingly. Foreign powers are beginning to think seriously about what they would do if Britain were run by a man whose basic foreign policy principle is “whatever America is for I’m against”. The Israelis are terrified about the prospects of a British prime minister who has supported Hamas, a militant Islamist group in Palestine, and indulged anti-Semites in his party’s ranks. I suspect that fear of a Corbyn-led government will soon become a major force in British politics—and not just a vague theoretical fear but a real and vivid fear. People will move. Money will flee. Foreign powers will prepare for the worst.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE BRITISH political system is almost perfectly designed to make a hash of withdrawing from the European Union (EU). The system is an adversarial one: the governing party faces the opposition across a yawning divide and politicians bellow at each other. But leaving the EU demands a series of complicated compromises in the middle. The system is also designed to address a problem and move on to something else: each side states its position, parliament divides, and then you move on. But leaving the EU demands persistence above all: you have to keep worrying away at the same problem for week after week. It’s rather like using a hammer to chop down a tree. This structural problem is only going to get worse when (and if) parliament moves from the withdrawal agreement to the more laborious business of shaping our future trading relationship with the EU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kenneth Clarke, who succeeds amazingly well in combining his twin roles as Tory grandee and regular bloke, recently gave a long interview to the &lt;em&gt;Guardian&lt;/em&gt; in which he said that he repairs to the Kennington Tandoori every Tuesday evening on his own to enjoy a curry and read a copy of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;. A colleague of mine found himself having dinner in that very Tandoori last Tuesday. Sure enough Mr Clarke was sitting there, on his own in a window seat, solidly working his way through his copy of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;. When he left his place was taken by Ann Widdecombe, a former colleague of Mr Clarke’s who has just quit the Tories to join Nigel Farage’s Brexit Party. My colleague can’t be completely sure but he doesn’t think Ms Widdecombe was reading &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 22:06:17 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spain’s fractured politics, and more from our daily podcast]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/26/spains-fractured-politics-and-more-from-our-daily-podcast]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/the_intelligence_61_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-26T09:48:20Z&quot;&gt;Apr 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AHEAD OF Spain’s general election this weekend we examine its fractured political landscape. This bastion of European stability looks set for a long struggle to form a government. We also take a look at two lingering effects of Japan’s post-war policies. First, we speak to one of the victims of decades of forced sterilisation, for which the government apologised this week. And given Japan’s notorious culture of work (itself a consequence of post-war reconstruction), we note that not everyone relishes having time off to celebrate the ascension of the new emperor. Runtime: 22min.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/thestraininspain-anelectionlooms&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 19:06:20 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The French president responds to the gilets jaunes]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/26/the-french-president-responds-to-the-gilets-jaunes]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_EUP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-26T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ONLY IN FRANCE, perhaps, would the response to a social rebellion have been a three-month-long national conversation. At the Elysée Palace on April 25th, Emmanuel Macron at last presented the conclusions to his “great national debate”, which has taken him on a town-hall tour of the country and involved 2m responses from ordinary citizens. “We are above all children of the Enlightenment and it’s from debate, discussion, and the capacity to converse and contradict”, declared the philosopher-president, that solutions can be found.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As it turned out, by the time Mr Macron unveiled those solutions, many had already been leaked. His original plan to announce the measures last week was put on hold when Notre Dame cathedral in Paris caught fire. And although he declared a “new act” of his presidency, Mr Macron kept the broad contours of his domestic reform programme intact. This has focused on making France more business-friendly as well as on investing in education and training to improve opportunities and skills. To this end, the president ruled out bringing back the wealth tax, a central demand of the &lt;em&gt;gilets jaunes&lt;/em&gt; (yellow jackets) protesters, and announced further measures to cut primary-school class sizes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet Mr Macron has now spent a total of over 92 hours listening to French grievances in a series of public debates around the country. “This period has changed me,” he said, noting a sense of injustice, abandonment and lack of respect, and a suspicion of elites. Policy had to be more “human”. So no more schools or hospitals would be closed on his watch; modest pensions will be inflation-indexed; unpaid alimony payments to single parents will be enforced; and a single public-service office is to be set up to simplify dealings with the French bureaucracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Faced with a protest movement that began as a tax rebellion, Mr Macron also promised to lower the tax burden “substantially”. France currently levies a greater share of taxes—48.4% of GDP—than any other country in the European Union. He pledged to make €5bn ($5.6bn) of income-tax cuts, to be financed, or so he promised, by spending cuts and the closing of corporate-tax loopholes. A one-off concession allowing company Christmas bonuses to be paid tax-free, which the president announced last December, will be repeated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If exasperation at high taxes was part of the trigger for the &lt;em&gt;gilets jaunes&lt;/em&gt;, another was anger at the out-of-touch elite. Mr Macron offered answers on this point, too. He will cut the number of deputies by at least 25%, introduce a share (of about 20%) of proportional representation in parliament, decentralise more decision-making to local levels, and add 150 citizens to an assembly that will first look into how to subsidise greener behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps most spectacularly—and controversially—Mr Macron promised to abolish the Ecole Nationale d’Administration (ENA), his own alma mater. Paradoxically, this civil-service training college was set up after the second world war, in order to enforce the meritocratic selection of top French mandarins and put an end to the cronyism of the past. Yet today ENA has become a byword for the elite, a disconnected technocratic way of thinking, and a system that fails to recruit enough people from modest families. A commission will be set up to look into what might replace it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Macron’s announcements left plenty of unanswered questions, most notably how he will finance the extra tax cuts and spending promises. His earlier measures, themselves costing €10bn, have already pushed up the government’s budget deficit to just over the 3% limit imposed by EU rules. Mr Macron did make it clear that the French would have to work longer over their lifetimes in order to finance pensions. But promises to find savings by closing tax loopholes are a familiar fall-back for any government struggling to make credible spending cuts. As it is, Mr Macron acknowledged that he may not meet his campaign promise to trim 120,000 jobs from the mighty French civil service.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Mr Macron’s declarations lacked the planned novelty effect, there was nonetheless some surprise at the shift in presidential tone. Often criticised for his haughty governing style and arrogant demeanour, the French president this time managed to mix a touch of humility (“I can do better”) with a more chatty, less formal, even at times comic delivery. He may have been sitting beneath crystal chandeliers, but the ornate desk and monarchical manner had gone, and his seat was a modern white chair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will any of this be enough to satisfy the &lt;em&gt;gilets jaunes&lt;/em&gt; and calm the protests? For die-hard protesters preparing to return this weekend for their 24th consecutive weekly demonstration, the answer is almost certainly not. Whatever Mr Macron announced would not be enough for the radical core, some of which wants nothing less than to drive him from office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the president’s message was designed not for the extreme fringe but for those who had what he called “fair demands” from the start. The &lt;em&gt;gilets jaunes&lt;/em&gt; movement is tenacious, but is fading on the ground. There were 28,000 on the streets last weekend, down from 280,000 last November. A majority of the French now want the protests to stop, having initially sympathised with them. This is the audience that Mr Macron was speaking to. The French president will have won round neither his entrenched detractors nor his political opponents. But he may have persuaded the sceptical middle-ground that he has listened carefully, and made a genuine effort to respond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 19:06:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Democratic presidential field already looks crowded]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/26/the-democratic-presidential-field-already-looks-crowded]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/03/articles/main/20190316_woc959_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-26T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;F&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;or all&lt;/small&gt; of their divisions over policies like the Green New Deal and support for Israel, Democrats are united in their opposition to President Donald Trump. In the most recent polling from Monmouth University, a majority of voters said their most important concern was defeating him next year, whereas positions on policy came second. In these early days of the Democrats’ process for nominating a challenger, they certainly have no shortage of options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;h2 data-interactive- data-interactive-cand=&quot;joe-biden&quot;&gt;Joe Biden&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;Former Vice President of the United States&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/2020-dem-candidates/images/Biden.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Joe Biden&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Joe Biden is perhaps the favourite to win Democrats’ blessing. He tops the early primary polls—which are unreliable, but do have some predictive power—and has long been a leader in betting markets on the nomination. “Uncle Joe” offers an alluring option for the many voters pining for Obama-era politics, but also carries baggage from his long career in government. Modern progressives will look askance at his record on social and identity issues, such as busing children to integrate segregated schools and racial inequality in the criminal-justice system, and at his occasionally too-close-for-comfort interactions with women in public. He will need to cover his left flank on policy proposals, while relying on his reputation and beer-swilling persona to reassure the white working-class men who have abandoned the Democrats that he still speaks for them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a data-interactive- href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/04/25/joe-biden-provides-a-fossil-record-of-how-the-democrats-have-changed&quot; role=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Profile from Apr 25th 2019 →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;h2 data-interactive- data-interactive-cand=&quot;pete-buttigieg&quot;&gt;Pete Buttigieg&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;Mayor of South Bend, Indiana&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/2020-dem-candidates/images/Buttigieg.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Pete Buttigieg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Pete Buttigieg, the 37-year-old mayor of South Bend, Indiana, has rocketed out of obscurity with a learned intellect and hope-and-change rhetoric reminiscent of Barack Obama. He combines the perceived electability of a churchgoing, Midwestern military veteran who can speak to small-town white voters with promises of a combative approach if elected: he supports scrapping the Electoral College, packing the Supreme Court and expanding health coverage with a plan akin to Medicare for All. Mr Buttigieg is yet to spell out a detailed policy agenda, and his résumé is unusually thin for a presidential candidate. If elected, he would become America’s first openly gay president.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a data-interactive- href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/04/20/pete-buttigieg-fuses-liberalism-and-tradition&quot; role=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Profile from Apr 17th 2019 →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;h2 data-interactive- data-interactive-cand=&quot;beto-o-rourke&quot;&gt;Beto O&amp;#x27;Rourke&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;Former Representative from Texas&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/2020-dem-candidates/images/Rourke.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Beto O&amp;amp;#x27;Rourke&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Beto O’Rourke’s surprisingly close 2.6 percentage point loss to Ted Cruz in November prompted speculation that he could be destined for something larger. After an initial bout of apparently aimless online over-sharing—he even live-streamed a conversation about border policy while receiving a dental cleaning—and visits to obscure towns in middle America, he has appeared to get his groove back; as he told &lt;i&gt;Vanity Fair&lt;/i&gt; “man, I’m just born to be in it.” His words sum up his campaign rather well. Mr O’Rourke does not carry the banner of a specific group like Bernie Sanders and the Democratic socialists, or the policy heft of Elizabeth Warren, but brings some charisma and a generational contrast to the campaign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a data-interactive- href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/03/15/beto-orourke-heads-to-iowa&quot; role=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Profile from Mar 15th 2019 →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;h2 data-interactive- data-interactive-cand=&quot;bernie-sanders&quot;&gt;Bernie Sanders&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;Senator from Vermont&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/2020-dem-candidates/images/Sanders.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Bernie Sanders&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Senator Bernie Sanders is trying for a second time for the Democratic presidential nomination. After a long campaign—and, some supporters feel, a bitter defeat—versus Hillary Clinton in 2016, Mr Sanders is hoping his progressivism-first strategy can put him out in front once again. But this time, voters have plenty of options for a candidate who supports so-called “Medicare for All,” sweeping economic reforms and other such “Democratic socialist” policies. Without a clear policy agenda to set him apart, Mr Sanders might have to rely on his energy as a campaigner, which is notably good for a 77-year-old. He has been dogged by accusations that his 2016 campaign was not friendly to women or non-whites. For these reasons, he looks to start behind his mark from last cycle. Will he pull a solid second once again? Betting markets give him a good chance of winning, and for what they&amp;#x27;re worth so long before people start voting, polls give him a good shot too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a data-interactive- href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/02/19/bernie-sanders-announces-another-run-for-president&quot; role=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Profile from Feb 21st 2019 →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;h2 data-interactive- data-interactive-cand=&quot;amy-klobuchar&quot;&gt;Amy Klobuchar&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;Senator from Minnesota&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/2020-dem-candidates/images/Klobuchar.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Amy Klobuchar&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Ms Klobuchar’s entry may be seen as an opportunity for a wide breadth-over-depth approach to the primary. The Midwestern senator has an obvious advantage in hailing from a region where Democrats are keen on boosting numbers next November. Not least of the motivators for this strategy is, of course, that Donald Trump managed to flip three Rust Belt states in 2016 to give him the Oval Office. Ms Klobuchar’s appeal goes beyond her geographic advantage, however. Liberals will find much to love in her endorsement of progressive goals like automatic voter registration and reinstating climate regulations. Meanwhile, voters who switched from Barack Obama to Mr Trump will adore her stumps on corporate greed, revolving-door lobbying, and prioritisation of expanded bad-weather crop insurance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a data-interactive- href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/02/11/amy-klobuchar-declares&quot; role=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Profile from Feb 11th 2019 →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;h2 data-interactive- data-interactive-cand=&quot;cory-booker&quot;&gt;Cory Booker&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;Senator from New Jersey&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/2020-dem-candidates/images/Booker.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Cory Booker&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Some Democratic voters claim to have found a new Barack Obama in the New Jersey senator Cory Booker, and not just because he is young (for a presidential candidate) and African-American. Mr Booker, who announced his plans to run on February 1st, balances a connection to impoverished Newark, where he was a successful mayor, with an optimistic message of unity and love. He has adopted numerous left-of-centre positions (he backs Medicare for All, for example). Yet some on the left decry his ties to Wall Street and opposition of legislation that would have slashed prescription drug prices in 2017.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a data-interactive- href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/02/02/cory-booker-enters-the-race&quot; role=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Profile from Feb 2nd 2019 →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;h2 data-interactive- data-interactive-cand=&quot;kamala-harris&quot;&gt;Kamala Harris&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;Senator from California&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/2020-dem-candidates/images/Harris.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kamala Harris&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Kamala Harris occupies the top spot among market bettors, and a close third in public polling. The senator from California, who launched her campaign in mid-January, has placed a very liberal set of policy reforms at the forefront of her campaign, including support for Medicare-for-all and the so-called “Green New Deal.” Ms Harris has a knack of sounding more progressive than she actually is, a political asset at this stage. And she could do well in South Carolina, an important early state with lots of African-American primary voters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a data-interactive- href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/01/28/kamala-harris-starts-her-engine-in-the-centre-lane&quot; role=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Profile from Jan 28th 2019 →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;h2 data-interactive- data-interactive-cand=&quot;kirsten-gillibrand&quot;&gt;Kirsten Gillibrand&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;Senator from New York&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/2020-dem-candidates/images/Gillibrand.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Kirsten Gillibrand&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;New York’s Kirsten Gillibrand joined the race promising to fight for Americans like she fights for her kids. Her policy portfolio includes health care “as a right, not a privilege,” public and vocational school funding, and anti-corruption proposals to fight lobbyists and special interests in Washington. Were it not for her ties to Wall Street, the candidate Ms Gillibrand most resembles is Elizabeth Warren, though she lacks Ms Warren’s academic record on public policy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;&lt;h2 data-interactive- data-interactive-cand=&quot;elizabeth-warren&quot;&gt;Elizabeth Warren&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;div data-interactive-&gt;Senator from Massachusetts&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/2020-dem-candidates/images/Warren.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Elizabeth Warren&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Elizabeth Warren was the next Democrat to announce. The senator from Massachusetts is well known for her support for stricter financial regulation. Although her campaign rollout has been dogged by an old controversy surrounding her claimed Native American heritage, she has been winning the war of ideas in the Democratic primary. Her economic populism—a combination of support for government programmes like Medicaid and Social Security and a wealth tax—is seen by her fans as way for Democrats to win favour with white, middle-class Americans again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;a data-interactive- href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/02/09/elizabeth-warrens-unusual-brand-of-wonkish-populism&quot; role=&quot;button&quot;&gt;Profile from Feb 9th 2019 →&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/03/articles/body/20190316_WOC944.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/03/articles/body/20190316_WOC944.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/03/articles/body/20190316_WOC944.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/03/articles/body/20190316_WOC944.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/03/articles/body/20190316_WOC944.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/03/articles/body/20190316_WOC944.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/03/articles/body/20190316_WOC944.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/03/articles/body/20190316_WOC944.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/03/articles/body/20190316_WOC944.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/03/articles/body/20190316_WOC944.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There already seems to be a Democrat for everyone in 2020, and not all of the likely candidates have declared. But according to &lt;i&gt;The Economist&lt;/i&gt;’s analysis of polling in party nominations between 1980 and 2016, this early in a cycle just 17% of polls released have correctly identified the eventual party nominee. In February 2007, for example, Hillary Clinton had a 20-point lead over a young Barack Obama, who would end up winning the nomination a year and a half later in one of the closest primaries in recent memory. On the Republican side, Donald Trump had not even announced his candidacy 72 weeks before his party’s convention in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There are other ways to gauge who is ahead. Betting markets provide an opportunity for prognosticators to put real money behind their arguments, and performed admirably in predicting the 2018 midterms. According to the latest numbers from PredictIt, a popular American market, Kamala Harris has opened up a meaningful lead against all of the other currently announced candidates. However, with Joe Biden, the former Vice President, and Beto O’Rourke, who did surprisingly well in his Texas Senate race last year, not far behind, her position may deteriorate if they actually declare. In the game of presidential primaries, it is simply too early to say who might hold the winning cards.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Picture credits: AP; EPA; Reuters&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/2020-dem-candidates/css/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/2020-dem-candidates/css/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 19:06:18 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[High mid-terms turnout was driven by young and Hispanic Americans]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/04/25/high-mid-terms-turnout-was-driven-by-young-and-hispanic-americans]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_USP510.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T15:50:39Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATES performed so well in last year’s mid-term elections that pundits dubbed the cycle a “big blue wave”. By another measure, it was more akin to a 100-year flood. The final count of ballots reveals that, at 50.3%, a higher share of America’s eligible voters turned out to vote than for any mid-term election since 1914. New data from the US Census Bureau shows that this was driven especially by young people, Hispanics, and those with a college degree. These are groups that have been particularly outraged by President Donald Trump. If their political engagement continues, it could affect the outcome of the presidential election next year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mid-term elections have tended to be affairs for the politically-engaged. It requires unusual attention to politics to go out and vote for a political representative you may not have seen much of. Presidential elections, on the other hand, suck up media attention and advertising dollars from up to two years before Election Day. Over the past century, the average turnout for mid-terms has been 43%—16 percentage points lower than average turnout in presidential contests. The voters who typically cast ballots in mid-term elections have tended to be older, whiter, and better-educated than those that vote for president. This demographic portrait held true in 2018, but with some notable changes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analysis by Michael McDonald, a political scientist, of the 2018 Current Population Survey (CPS), a nationwide poll conducted by the US Census Bureau in the November following each even-year election, shows that the increase in voter turnout was large for every major demographic group. But a few groups stood out. Turnout among Americans between the ages of 18 and 29, Hispanics and those who began or completed a college degree increased 13, 16 and 13 percentage points since the last mid-terms in 2014. Whites and Americans without a college degree—groups that tend to be more loyal than not to Mr Trump—increased their turnout by 11 and 7 percentage points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Young women turned out in particularly high numbers. This is unsurprising given that the past two years have been marked by a series of women’s campaigns including the Women’s March and #MeToo movement. Among young voters, 33% of women reported voting last year, compared to 27% of men. That constitutes an increase of 16 and 13 percentage points compared to 2014 levels. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mid-term elections are often referred to as referendums on the party in power. But 2018’s referendum was most unusual. Not only was turnout exceptionally high; voters also swung left in percentages not seen since 1974. According to Catalist, a data company, compared to the 2014 election, the 18-29 age group was 24 points more Democratic; college-educated voters swung 27 points to the left while Hispanics moved 16 points. In other words, the voters that were more likely to turn out in higher numbers were also among the most likely to switch from Republican to Democratic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is bad news for Mr Trump’s 2020 campaign. If these voters stay engaged until next November the president will face a big hurdle to his re-election. Meanwhile, longer term demographic changes give Democrats more cause for cheer: America is growing younger, darker-skinned and better educated. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 04:08:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How genetic engineering will reshape humanity]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/04/25/how-genetic-engineering-will-reshape-humanity]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_OPP508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T17:17:33Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEW GENETIC technologies are exhilarating and terrifying. Society might overcome diseases by tweaking individual genomes or selecting specific embryos to avoid health problems. But it may also give rise to &amp;quot;superhumans&amp;quot; who are optimised for certain characteristics (like intelligence or looks) and exacerbate inequalities in society. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is certain is that people will be able to make decisions about their lives in ways that were impossible in the past, when we relied more on random evolution than deliberation. In the words of Jamie Metzl, we are &amp;quot;Hacking Darwin,&amp;quot; the title of his latest book. It is a thoughtful romp through new genetic technologies, with insights on what it means for individuals, society and even great-power politics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The theme draws together discrete strands of Mr Metz&amp;#x27;s diverse background. He&amp;#x27;s worked for the United Nations on humanitarian issues in Cambodia and served on America&amp;#x27;s National Security Council under President Bill Clinton. He&amp;#x27;s been an executive at a biotechnology company, a partner at large investment fund in New York and a candidate for Congress from Missouri. But perhaps even more relevantly, he is the author of two sci-fi novels on genetics, &amp;quot;Genesis Code&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;Eternal Sonata.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of &lt;em&gt;The Economist’s&lt;/em&gt; Open Future project, we asked Mr Metzl about genetic engineering, inequality and the new “liberal agenda”. Below the interview is an excerpt from his book, on the history of eugenics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*      *      *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Economist: What are the ways in which people are able to &amp;quot;hack Darwin&amp;quot; today and over the next 15 years or so?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jamie Metzl:&lt;/strong&gt; We have always fought against the inherent cruelty of natural selection, one of the two essential pillars of Darwinian evolution. We are now beginning to hack away at the second pillar, random mutation. Our growing understanding of how genes and biology function is opening the door to incredible medical applications like using genome sequencing and gene therapies to fight cancer and other diseases. But the healthcare applications of genetic technologies are only a station along the way to where these technologies are taking us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our ability to select embryos during in vitro fertilisation (IVF)—based on informed genetic predictions of both health-related traits and intimate characteristics like height, IQ and personality style—will grow over the coming years. We’ll use stem cell technologies to expand the number of eggs that prospective mothers can use in IVF and therefore the range of reproductive options for parents. We’ll deploy gene editing tools far more precise than today’s CRISPR systems to make heritable genetic changes to our future offspring. Over the coming decades, Darwin’s original concept of random mutation and natural selection will gradually give way to a process that is far more self-guided than anything Darwin could have imagined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Economist: Changing the nature of what it means to be human has huge consequences. What are the main ones?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Metzl:&lt;/strong&gt; We have internalised the idea that information technology is variable, which is why we expect each generation of our phones and computers to be better than the last. It’s harder for us to come to grips with the idea that our biology could be as variable as our IT, even though we understand intellectually that somehow we evolved from single cell organisms to complex humans over the past 3.8 billion years. Starting to see all of life, including our own, as increasingly manipulable will force us to think more deeply about what values will guide us as we begin altering biology more aggressively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_OPP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190427_OPP503.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190427_OPP503.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190427_OPP503.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190427_OPP503.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190427_OPP503.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190427_OPP503.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190427_OPP503.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190427_OPP503.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190427_OPP503.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;If we want to avoid dividing our species into genetic have and have-nots—a dangerous reduction in our diversity—or a genetic determinism that undermines our humanity, we’ll need to start living our values. But though we need to be mindful of the dangers, we must also keep in mind that these technologies have the potential to do tremendous good. Someday they might well help us avoid extinction level events like dangerous synthetic pathogens, a warmer climate, the fallout from a nuclear war or the eventual expiration of our sun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: Do we have the ethical framework to handle this? If not, what might it look like if things go wrong?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Metzl:&lt;/strong&gt; We create beautiful art, philosophy and universal concepts like human rights but wipe out millions of each other in wars and genocides and still today invest massive amounts of our collective wealth in tools of mass murder. The “better angels of our nature” remain primary drivers in our development of genetic technologies, but the dark side of human nature could also be empowered through these same tools. We need a very strong ethical and cultural framework to increase the odds that we’ll use these technologies wisely, not least because access to them will be decentralised and democratised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the positive possibilities far outweigh the negatives, it would be crazy to ignore the many ways things could go wrong. Like Icarus, we could fly too close to the sun and get burned if we hubristically assume we know more than we actually do. Our gene drives could crash ecosystems. We could use these tools to undermine our common identity as a species and social cohesion. The good news is that while the technologies are new, the values we’ll need to use them wisely are often old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: What sort of regulations need to be in place to &amp;quot;enable&amp;quot; these technologies—and what rules should &amp;quot;constrain&amp;quot; them?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Metzl:&lt;/strong&gt; Genetic technologies touch the source code of what it means to be human and must be regulated. This job is all the more difficult because the technology is racing forward faster than the governance structures around them can keep up. On both the national and international levels, we’ll need enough governance and regulation to prevent abuses and promote public safety while not so much to impede beneficial research and applications.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To avoid dangerous medical tourism, every country should have a national regulatory system in place that aligns with international best practices and the country’s own values and traditions. We also have to start developing global norms that can ultimately underpin flexible international standards and regulations. These systems must be guided by core values rather than inflexible rules because what may now seem unthinkable, like actively selecting and even editing our future offspring, will increasingly become normalised over time. We urgently need to start preparing for what is coming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: This takes the issue of human liberty to a new level (people should be free to change themselves or offspring), as well as the potential for unbridgeable inequalities (not just of wealth or life outcomes, but of capabilities encoded in oneself and family). How must the idea of liberalism adapt to address this? What does the &amp;quot;liberal agenda&amp;quot; look like for the 21st century vis-à-vis “hacking Darwin”?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Metzl:&lt;/strong&gt; If and when it becomes possible for some parents to give their children enhanced IQs, lifespans and resistance to disease, we will have to ask what this means for everyone else. Some will see these parents as first-adopters paving the way for everyone else, like the first privileged people buying smartphones. Others will call them usurpers laying the foundation for dangerously divided societies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever the case, differences within and between societies, fuelled by competition, will drive adoption of these technologies and present societies with stark choices. Too few regulations could lead to a dangerous genetic engineering free-for-all and arms race. But trying to ban genetic manipulations would increasingly require the trappings of the most oppressive police states. Some liberal societies may choose to provide a basic level of access to assisted reproduction and genetic-engineering services to everyone, not least to save the expense of lifetime care for people who would otherwise be born with preventable genetic diseases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Societies already struggling to define the balance between the parental and state interests in the context of abortion will have an even tougher time drawing this line for parent-driven assisted reproduction. But if we thought the debates over abortion and genetically modified crops were contentious, wait until the coming debate over genetically modified people arrives. If we don’t want this to tear us asunder, we must all come together in a public process to figure out the best ways forward.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*      *      *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The disgraceful history of eugenics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Excerpted from “Hacking Darwin: Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity” by Jamie Metzl (Sourcebooks, 2019)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The term eugenics combines the Greek roots for good and birth. Although coined in the nineteenth century, the concept of selective breeding and human population culling has a more ancient history. Infanticide was written into Roman law and practiced widely in the Roman Empire. “A father shall immediately put to death,” Table IV of the Twelve Tables of Roman Law stated, “a son who is a monster, or has a form different from that of the human race.” In ancient Sparta, city elders inspected newborns to ensure that any who seemed particularly sickly would not survive. The German tribes, pre-Islamic Arabs, and ancient Japanese, Chinese, and Indians all practiced infanticide in one form or another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 1859 publication of Darwin’s The Origins of Species didn’t just get scientists thinking about how finches evolved in the Galapagos but about how human societies evolved more generally. Applying Darwin’s principles of natural selection to human societies, Darwin’s cousin and scientific polymath Sir Francis Galton theorized that human evolution would regress if societies prevented their weakest members from being selected out. In his influential books Hereditary Talent and Character (1885) and then Hereditary Genius (1889), he outlined how eugenics could be applied positively by encouraging the most capable people to reproduce with each other and negatively by discouraging people with what he considered disadvantageous traits from passing on their genes. These theories were embraced by mainstream scientific communities and championed by luminaries like Alexander Graham Bell, John Maynard Keynes, Woodrow Wilson, and Winston Churchill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_OPP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190427_OPP502.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190427_OPP502.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190427_OPP502.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190427_OPP502.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190427_OPP502.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190427_OPP502.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190427_OPP502.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190427_OPP502.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190427_OPP502.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although his work was partly in the spirit of the Victorian England times, Galton was then and even more now what we would call a racist. “The science of improving stock,” he wrote, “takes cognizance of all the influences that tend in however remote degree to give the more suitable races or strains of blood a better chance of prevailing speedily over the less suitable than they otherwise would have had.” In 1909, Galton and his colleagues established the journal Eugenics Review, which argued in its first edition that nations should compete with each other in “race-betterment” and that the number of people in with “pre-natal conditions” in hospitals and asylums should be “reduced to a minimum” through sterilization and selective breeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Galton’s theories gained increasing prominence internationally, particularly in the New World. Although eugenics would later accrue sinister connotations, many of the early adopters of eugenic theories were American progressives who believed science could be used to guide social policies and create a better society for all. “We can intelligently mold and guide the evolution in which we take part,” progressive theologian Walter Rauschenbusch wrote. “God,” Johns Hopkins economic professor Richard Ely asserted, “works through the state.” Many American progressives embraced eugenics as a way of making society better by preventing those considered “unfit” and “defective” from being born. “We know enough about eugenics so that if that knowledge were applied, the defective classes would disappear within a decade,” University of Wisconsin president Charles Van Hise opined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the United States, the “science” of eugenics became intertwined with disturbing ideas about race. Speaking to the 1923 Second International Congress of Eugenics, President Henry Osborn of New York’s American Museum of Natural History argued that scientists should:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“ascertain through observation and experiment what each race is best fitted to accomplish…  If the Negro fails in government, he may become a fine agriculturist or a fine mechanic…  The right of the state to safeguard the character and integrity of the race or races on which its future depends is, to my mind, as incontestable as the right of the state to safeguard the health and morals of its peoples. As science has enlightened government in the prevention and spread of disease, it must also enlighten government in the prevention of the spread and multiplication of worthless members of society, the spread of feeblemindedness, of idiocy, and of all moral and intellectual as well as physical diseases”.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Major research institutes like Cold Spring Harbor, funded by the likes of the Rockefeller Foundation, the Carnegie Institution of Washington, and the Kellogg Race Betterment Foundation, provided a scientific underpinning for a progressive eugenics movement growing in popularity as a genetic determinism swept the country. The American Association for the Advancement of Science put its full weight behind the eugenics movement through its trend-setting publication, Science. If Mendel showed there were genes for specific traits, the thinking went, it was only a matter of time before the gene dictating every significant human trait would be found. Ideas like these moved quickly into state policies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indiana in 1907 became the first U.S. state to pass a eugenics law making sterilization mandatory for certain types of people in state custody. Thirty different states and Puerto Rico soon followed with laws of their own. In the first half of the twentieth century, approximately sixty thousand Americans, mostly patients in mental institutions and criminals, were sterilized without their acquiescence. Roughly a third of all Puerto Rican women were sterilized after providing only the flimsiest consent. These laws were not entirely uncontroversial, and many were challenged in courts. But the U.S. Supreme Court ruled in its now infamous 1927 Buck v. Bell decision, that eugenics laws were constitutional. “Three generations of imbeciles,” progressive Supreme Court justice Oliver Wendell Holmes disgracefully wrote in the decision, “are enough.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the eugenics movement played out in the United States, another group of Europeans was watching closely. Nazism was, in many ways, a perverted heir of Darwinism. German scientists and doctors embraced Galton’s eugenic theories from the beginning. In 1905, the Society for Racial Hygiene was established in Berlin with the express goal of promoting Nordic racial “purity” through sterilization and selective breeding. An Institute for Hereditary Biology and Racial Hygiene was soon opened in Frankfurt by a leading German eugenicist, Otmar Freiherr von Verschuer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eugenic theories and U.S. efforts to implement them through state action were also very much on Adolf Hitler’s mind as he wrote his ominous 1925 manifesto, Mein Kampf, in Landsberg prison. “The stronger must dominate and not mate with the weaker,” he wrote:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Only the born weakling can look upon this principle as cruel, and if he does so it is merely because he is of a feebler nature and narrower mind; for if such a law did not direct the process of evolution then the higher development of organic life would not be conceivable at all… Since the inferior always outnumber the superior, the former would always increase more rapidly if they possessed the same capacities for survival and for the procreation of their kind; and the final consequence would be that the best in quality would be forced to recede into the background. Therefore a corrective measure in favor of the better quality must intervene…for here a new and rigorous selection takes place, according to strength and health”.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the first laws passed by the Nazis after taking power in 1933 was the Law for the Prevention of Hereditary Defective Offspring, with language based partly on the eugenic sterilization law of California. Genetic health courts were established across Nazi Germany in which two doctors and a lawyer helped determine each case of who should be sterilized.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the next four years, the Nazis forcibly sterilized an estimated four hundred thousand Germans. But simply sterilizing those with disabilities was not enough for the Nazis to realize their eugenic dreams. In 1939, they launched a secret operation to kill disabled newborns and children under the age of three. This program was then quickly expanded to include older children and then adults with disabilities considered to have lebensunwertes leben, or lives unworthy of life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Making clear the conceptual origins of these actions lay in scientifically and medically legitimated eugenics, medical professionals oversaw the murder of an ever-widening group of undesirables in “gassing installations” around the country. This model then expanded from euthanizing the disabled and people with psychiatric conditions to criminals and to those considered to be racial inferiors, including Jews and Roma, as well as homosexuals. It was not by accident that Joseph Mengele, the doctor who decided who would be sent to the gas chambers at Auschwitz, was a former star student of von Verschuer at the Frankfurt Institute for Hereditary Biology and Racial Hygiene.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By the mid-1930s, the American scientific community was pulling away from eugenics. In 1935, the Carnegie Institution concluded the science of eugenics was not valid and withdrew its funding for the Eugenics Records Office at Cold Spring Harbor. Reports of Nazi atrocities amplified by the 1945–46 Nuremberg trials put the nail in the coffin of the eugenics movement in the West. Although eugenics laws were finally scrapped from the books only in the 1960s in the United States and the 1970s in Canada and Sweden, very few people were forcibly sterilized after the war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But as new technologies more recently began to revolutionize the human reproduction process and create new tools for assessing, selecting, or genetically engineering preimplanted embryos, many critics raised the specter of eugenics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[…]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The parallels between the ugly eugenics of the late nineteenth century and the first half of the twentieth and what’s beginning to happen today are not insignificant. In both cases, a science at an early stage of development and with sometimes uncertain accuracy was or is being used to make big decisions—forced sterilization of the “feeble-minded” in the old days, not selecting a given embryo for implantation or terminating a pregnancy based on genetic indications today. In both cases, scientists and government officials seek to balance individual reproductive liberty with broader societal goals. In both cases, future potential children lose the opportunity to be born. In both cases, societies and individuals make culturally biased but irrevocable decisions about which lives are worth living and which are not. These parallels offer us a powerful warning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if we collectively paint all human genetic engineering with the brush of Nazi eugenics, we could kill the incredible potential of genetics technologies to help us live healthier lives. […] That there probably is an element of eugenics in decisions being made today on the future of human genetic engineering should push us to be careful and driven by positive values, but the specter of past abuses should not be a death sentence for this potentially life-affirming technology or the people it could help.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[…]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s not that hard to imagine future scenarios when humans would need to genetically alter ourselves in order to survive a rapid change in our environment resulting from global warming or intense cooling following a nuclear war or asteroid strike, a runaway deadly virus, or some kind of other future challenge we can’t today predict. Genetic engineering, in other words, could easily shift from being a health or lifestyle choice to becoming an imperative for survival. Preparing responsibly for these potential future dangers may well require we begin developing the underlying technologies today, while we still have time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thinking about genetic choice in the context of imagined future scenarios is, in many ways, abstract. But potentially helping a child live a healthier, longer life is anything but. Every time a person dies, a lifetime of knowledge and relationships dissolves. We live on in the hearts of our loved ones, the books we write, and the plastic bags we’ve thrown away, but what would it mean if people lived a few extra healthy years because they were genetically selected or engineered to make that possible? How many more inventions could be invented, poems written, ideas shared, and life lessons passed on? What would we as individuals and as a society be willing to pay, what values might we be willing to compromise, to make that possible? What risks would we individually and collectively be willing to take on? Our answers to these questions will both propel us forward and present us with some monumental ethical challenges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Excerpted from “Hacking Darwin: Genetic Engineering and the Future of Humanity.” Copyright © 2019 by Jamie Metzl. Used with permission of Sourcebooks. All rights reserved.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 02:07:05 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[South Africa’s best bet, the right call on Huawei and a hot mess ahead for geoengineering]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/25/south-africas-best-bet-the-right-call-on-huawei-and-a-hot-mess-ahead-for-geoengineering]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T17:46:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THIS WEEK, how to stop the rot in South Africa. The liberal opposition cannot win the elections on May 8th, so the president must clean up his own party. Why Britain’s artful compromise on Huawei and 5G is a model for other countries (10:17). And geoengineering could alleviate climate change, but with politically explosive consequences (14:54).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-april25th2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id313848583&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/3a5n4DoT1xrV5rgBWBPxnR&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWVjb25vbWlzdGVkaXRvcnNwaWNrcw&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=18376&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/Politics/The-Economist-Editors-Picks-p987585/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 01:07:48 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EU workers in Britain are the most depressed about Brexit]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/bartleby/2019/04/25/eu-workers-in-britain-are-the-most-depressed-about-brexit]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_BLP508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T15:17:37Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IF YOU live in Britain, and ever turn on the TV or read a paper, it has been hard to escape from Brexit in the last three years. It has been bad enough if you are British-born. But EU citizens who are working in the UK have faced added uncertainty about their future status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gartner, a research company, has conducted weekly polls of around 300 UK-based employees to see how they have been affected. The key week was towards the end of March when the official deadline for Brexit was scheduled (it has since been postponed twice). In that week, more than half of EU workers in British experienced disgust, anger and sadness. Those feelings have subsided a little since, but are still running at about 40% of EU workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unsurprisingly, that has led EU workers to think about moving jobs. In the week starting March 7th, only 11% of them were doing so; by the week of April 8th that proportion had jumped to 24%. The proportion of footloose British-born workers saw a more modest rise from 15% to 21%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The polling also suggests that all this Brexit uncertainty is bad for productivity as well. In the week of March 25th, the average employee spent almost an hour of their working day thinking about Brexit, with EU citizens hitting nearly 70 minutes. Since then that proportion has dropped a bit, although EU citizens still spent 47 minutes worrying about the issue. Never has national navel-gazing proved so fruitless. As the Eagles once sang&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know what&amp;#x27;s been on your mind&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#x27;re afraid it&amp;#x27;s all been wasted time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 01:07:47 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Competition authorities throw out the merger of Sainsbury’s and Asda]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/04/25/competition-authorities-throw-out-the-merger-of-sainsburys-and-asda]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_BRP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT WAS BILLED as the retail deal of the decade, at a stroke creating Britain’s biggest supermarket chain—and one of Europe’s largest, too. No longer. On April 25th Britain’s Competition and Markets Authority (CMA) blocked the proposed £12bn ($15.5bn) merger between the country’s second-largest supermarket, Asda, which is owned by America’s Walmart, and the third largest, Sainsbury’s. By combining the pair’s market shares of 15.4% and 15.3% respectively, the new Sasda, or somesuch, would have leapfrogged the current market leader, Tesco, which has 27%. The merged entity would have had a turnover of about £51bn a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asda and Sainsbury’s argued that in Britain’s ruthlessly competitive retail market, the deal would have given them room to cut costs and thus offer lower prices to customers. Mike Coupe, the boss of Sainsbury’s, had claimed that prices would fall by as much as 10%. It would also have enabled the new firm to compete more effectively with Aldi and Lidl, two German discount stores that have been gobbling up market share over the past decade. Sainsbury’s and Asda must have been encouraged by a wave of consolidation in the retail world; in 2017 Tesco bought Booker, a wholesaler, for £3.7bn, and the previous year Sainsbury’s had bought Argos, a home retailer, for £1.4bn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not so fast, says the CMA. Despite promises from Sainsbury’s and Asda to sell between 125 and 150 of their stores to allow the merger to proceed, the CMA was unconvinced that the creation of such a giant was in the best interests of shoppers, or indeed of anyone other than the companies’ bosses. “Following our in-depth investigation,” explained Stuart McIntosh of the CMA, “we have found this deal would lead to increased prices, reduced quality and choice of products, or a poorer shopping experience for all of their UK shoppers.” In particular, the CMA found that the proposed price reductions were “unlikely to be realised” either online, in store or at the petrol pumps, with drivers likely to pay more at over 125 locations where Sainsbury’s and Asda currently have petrol stations close together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two supermarkets bemoaned the CMA’s decision. Many others, however, are relieved. Trade unions are happy that job cuts have been avoided. Farmers and other suppliers had expressed concern at the merger; they would probably have borne the brunt of the cost cuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The collapse of the deal leaves Sainsbury’s, in particular, in a pickle. Its share price, already significantly down over the past few years, dipped sharply on the news. Many analysts and investors had argued that Sainsbury’s management was investing too much faith and time in a merger that always looked vulnerable to the CMA’s intervention, while ignoring the company’s underlying weaknesses. In contrast, Tesco and Morrisons, the final member of Britain’s big four supermarkets, have been urgently addressing their own shortcomings. Tesco, in particular, has staged a spectacular comeback. In 2015 the company posted the biggest loss (£6.4bn) in British retail history; on April 10th it announced a 29% yearly jump in pre-tax profits, to £1.7bn. Sainsbury’s investors can only look on enviously. They will be looking carefully at the company’s annual results, due on May 1st. They may yet have Mr Coupe on toast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The CMA’s decision may also have wider implications for British business and the economy. In the past decade Britain has witnessed about $2trn-worth of mergers and acquisitions of domestic firms. Relative to the size of the economy, that is over a fifth more than in America over the same period. American economists and politicians are increasingly concerned that their economy has become too concentrated, limiting competition and eroding consumer welfare. These same concerns have been expressed in Britain, but this is the first time the CMA has blocked such a deal since its creation in 2014. The merger’s quashing could yet prove to be an important moment in the reform of Britain’s over-concentrated economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 01:07:46 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EU workers think about the Brexit exit]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/bartleby/2019/04/25/eu-workers-think-about-the-brexit-exit]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_BLP508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T15:17:37Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IF YOU live in Britain, and ever turn on the TV or read a paper, it has been hard to escape from Brexit in the last three years. It has been bad enough if you are British-born. But EU citizens who are working in the UK have faced added uncertainty about their future status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gartner, a research company, has conducted weekly polls of around 300 UK-based employees to see how they have been affected. The key week was towards the end of March when the official deadline for Brexit was scheduled (it has since been postponed twice). In that week, more than half of EU workers in British experienced disgust, anger and sadness. Those feelings have subsided a little since, but are still running at about 40% of EU workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unsurprisingly, that has led EU workers to think about moving jobs. in the week starting March 7th, only 11% of them were doing so; by the week of April 8th that proportion had jumped to 24%. The proportion of footloose British-born workers saw a more modest rise from 15% to 21%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The polling also suggests that all this Brexit uncertainty is bad for productivity as well. In the week of March 25th, the average employee spent almost an hour of their working day thinking about Brexit, with EU citizens hitting nearly 70 minutes. Since then that proportion has dropped a bit, although EU citizens still spent 47 minutes worrying about the issue. Never has national navel-gazing proved so fruitless. As the Eagles once sang&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know what&amp;#x27;s been on your mind&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#x27;re afraid it&amp;#x27;s all been wasted time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:07:21 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>