<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[The promotion curse]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/16/the-promotion-curse]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_wbd001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-16T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IS YOUR promotion really necessary? Many workers focus their hopes on climbing the hierarchy of their organisations. The prospect of higher pay helps to explain their ambition, but so does the greater status that comes with each successive title.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This scramble can often end in disappointment. The Peter principle, developed by Laurence Peter for a book published in 1969, states that workers get promoted until they reach their level of incompetence. It makes perfect sense. If you are good at your job, you rise up the career ladder. Eventually, there will be a job you are not good at and at that point your career will stall. The logical corollary is that any senior staff members who have been in their job for an extended period are incompetent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is another problem with chasing the promotion chimera. In a recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://voxeu.org/article/promotions-and-peter-principle&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt; for VoxEU, the records of almost 40,000 salespeople across 131 firms were studied by Alan Benson, Danielle Li and Kelly Shue. They found that companies have a strong tendency to promote the best sales people. Convincing people to buy goods and services is a useful skill, requiring charisma and persistence. But, as the authors point out, these are not the same capabilities as the strategic planning and administrative competence needed to lead a sales team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research then looked at what happened after these super-salespeople were promoted. Their previous sales performance was actually a negative indicator of managerial success. The sales growth of workers assigned to the star sellers was 7.5 percentage points lower than for those whose managers were previously weaker performers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scott Adams, the cartoonist, described this problem in his book, the “The Dilbert Principle”. In his world, the least competent people get promoted because these are the people you don’t want to do the actual work. It is foolish to promote the best salesperson or computer programmer to a management role, since the company will then be deprived of unique skills. That’s how the workers in the Dilbert cartoon strip end up being managed by the clueless “pointy-haired boss”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bartleby is not an expert at climbing the greasy pole. When he was last promoted, Iraq had yet to be invaded. In part, that is because he has observed a variant on the Peter and Dilbert principles; what might be dubbed the Bartleby curse. People get promoted until they reach a level when they stop enjoying their jobs. At this point, it is not just their competence that is&lt;br/&gt;affected; it is their happiness as well. The trick to avoiding this curse is to stick to what you like doing. If you enjoy teaching, don’t be a headmaster or college principal. If you like writing articles and columns, editing other people’s work may not give you the same degree of satisfaction (let alone conducting career reviews).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another problem with pursuing frequent promotions is that it turns you into a supplicant, endlessly in search of favourable feedback from the higher corporate ranks. This can mean that you lose control of your work-life balance. In Charles Handy’s new book, “21 Letters On Life And Its Challenges”, the veteran management theorist recalls a moment of epiphany when working for Shell, an oil giant. “In exchange for the promise of financial security and guaranteed work, I had sold my time to complete strangers with my permission for them to use that time for their own purposes,” he writes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The higher up the ladder you go, the greater the demands are likely to be on your time. The chief executive will expect you to be available on weekends; after all, that is why you get paid the big bucks. Subordinates will also feel that they are able to ask you tricky questions whenever they arise; they don’t want to take decisions that are above their pay grade. If you are in charge of a geographical region, you may spend much of your time on planes, visiting the corporate troops. And when you are not travelling, your day will be filled with meetings. At the end of the day, you will have been extremely busy, but with a nagging feeling that you have achieved nothing of substance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So that shiny promotion may not be for everyone. Beware the curse of overwork and dissatisfaction. Some people like to devote their whole lives to their job and be at the centre of events. It is best to let them get on with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 04:40:16 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The gift of overcoming barriers eludes the world’s Orthodox Christians]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/06/15/the-gift-of-overcoming-barriers-eludes-the-worlds-orthodox-christians]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_blp904.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-15T16:24:56Z&quot;&gt;Jun 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SCORES OF millions of Orthodox Christians will on June 16th mark the feast of Pentecost. This celebration centres on the moment when, according to church tradition, the Holy Spirit bestowed upon the disciples of Jesus Christ the mysterious power to communicate across language barriers. Each member of the multicultural crowd that gathered in Jerusalem is said to have heard the Apostles speaking in his or her own tongue. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately the ability to communicate successfully across other barriers, whether geopolitical or simply personal, is currently eluding the Christians of the East, or at least their hierarchs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The global split which opened within Orthodox Christianity six months ago over church jurisdiction in Ukraine shows no sign of healing. The dire state of diplomatic relations among regional powers is certainly not helping. The Patriarchate of Moscow abruptly severed relations with the Istanbul-based Ecumenical Patriarch, Bartholomew I, after he recognised the existence of an independent Ukrainian church. The split has left the 12 other self-ruling Orthodox churches in an awkward position of having to choose between the two Patriarchates, and the tension has ricocheted across the Orthodox world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far, no church has followed the Ecumenical Patriarchate in fully recognising the Ukrainian body, nor has any followed Moscow in completely severing ties with Patriarch Bartholomew. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Moscow Patriarchate, which hews close to the presidency of Vladimir Putin and at times defends it from popular protest, regularly pours scorn on its counterpart in Istanbul for acting as a stooge of American diplomacy. That America’s State Department supported the right of Ukrainians to organise their own independent church only added to Moscow’s fury. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, the Muscovite attacks oversimplify the position of the ancient Istanbul-based see, which must keep a delicate balance between many different earthly powers in order to survive as a tiny Christian enclave in a Muslim country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But in the coming weeks, the Ecumenical Patriarch’s profile in the Western and Anglophone world will certainly rise. The average age of his most visible representatives will plunge by nearly 40 years as younger clerics take over Greek-Orthodox sees in New York, London and Sydney. Mike Pompeo, President Donald Trump’s secretary of state, has invited Patriarch Bartholomew to America in July to give a speech on the environment. The choice of topic will come more naturally to the guest, a staunch greenie, than to the host.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of an apparent effort to counter-balance Muscovite influence in the Orthodox world, Patriarch Bartholomew has in recent weeks visibly mended his relations with the Archbishop of Athens, Ieronymos, by patching up their arcane quarrels over church jurisdiction in parts of Greece. That paved the way for Archbishop Ieronymos to join the primate of the new Ukrainian church, Epifaniy, and many other Bartholomew-minded hierarchs at celebrations in Istanbul of the Ecumenical Patriarch’s personal feast-day on June 11th. To judge by the reaction on social media, this innocent-seeming event caused much fury in the Muscovite camp and much pleasure in the opposing one. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile in Ukraine, ecclesiastical disputes roll on in an often bizarre way. Controversy swirls around 90-year-old Filaret Denysenko, a veteran and still-vigorous player in the high politics of Orthodoxy since the Soviet era. Having narrowly failed to become Patriarch of Moscow, he led a breakaway Ukrainian church in 1992 and was duly defrocked and disgraced by his erstwhile colleagues in Moscow, some of whom he had helped to consecrate as bishops.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since then the nonagenarian has styled himself the Patriarch of Kiev, a title that few people outside Ukraine recognise. In recent months, he has voiced bitter disappointment over the fact he was not put in charge of the newly-established Orthodox Church in Ukraine, and he has openly challenged the authority of 40-year-old Epifaniy, who was once his close aide. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In their handling of these inter-Ukrainian squabbles, the hierarchs in Istanbul feel they have trodden a careful line. They recognised Filaret as a valid cleric with the rank of retired bishop, which was enough to incur Muscovite rage, but they flatly rejected his claim to the title of Patriarch. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To all this, organs of the Muscovite media that are close to church thinking have reacted in a surreal way. While still snubbing the claims of “Mr Denysenko” to have any kind of clerical status, they report with gleeful satisfaction on the lively old man’s campaign to undermine his young successor. To anyone used to the relatively vertical structure of the global Catholic church, this will seem like an unseemly mess. But the story may not quite end there. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The feast of Pentecost, like every other landmark in the Orthodox calendar, will be marked by ceremonies of immense complexity, antiquity and beauty. Mastering and participating in such intricate rites can create mysterious, but also fissile, bonds between celebrants. They can quarrel suddenly, but also have sudden reconciliations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 01:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hong Kong’s leader backs down over controversial extradition bill]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/china/2019/06/15/hong-kongs-leader-backs-down-over-controversial-extradition-bill]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_blp903.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT WAS a remarkable climbdown in the face of mass protests. Just three days after suggesting that to retreat would be like spoiling a child, Hong Kong’s chief executive, Carrie Lam, announced the indefinite shelving of a proposed law that would allow the extradition of criminal suspects to mainland China. Mrs Lam now says she wants to avoid “chaos” in Hong Kong. Her U-turn came after the bill had provoked the biggest demonstration in many years, and another protest that escalated into the most violent social unrest in decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Few had expected the government to make such a concession, let alone so soon. The government had earlier planned to get the bill adopted by the Legislative Council by the middle of July, when the body is due to begin its summer break. It had described getting the law passed as “urgent”. But on June 15th Mrs Lam told reporters that the government would suspend the proceedings and would not set a deadline for resuming them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It appears that public pressure has succeeded—for now, at least—in making the government reconsider a policy that had strong backing from the Communist Party in Beijing. Protests have not always proved so successful. In 2003 the government shelved a controversial anti-subversion bill after hundreds of thousands of people took to the streets. But in 2014 protesters occupied streets in busy commercial areas for 79 days to push for democratic reform and secured no concessions. Since then many observers thought leaders in Hong Kong and Beijing had become even less inclined to give way to public opinion on sensitive political matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On this occasion, however, opposition has involved far more than the usual critics of the party’s policies in Hong Kong. Businesspeople, lawyers and foreign governments have expressed considerable anxiety about the legislation. Although the proposed bill would allow extraditions to more than 170 other jurisdictions, the protests have focused on the potential for people in Hong Kong, including foreigners there, to be sent to mainland China, where courts are explicitly under the Communist Party’s control and dissidents are jailed on trumped-up criminal charges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Opponents of the bill have been organising what they hope will be another large demonstration in Hong Kong on June 16th. They say it will go ahead despite Mrs Lam’s announcement, in order to push for the complete scrapping of the bill and to protest against what they say was the excessive use of force by the police during the outbreak of violence on June 12th. Amid reports of suspected protesters being sought among the scores of wounded in hospital, some also want Ms Lam to guarantee that there will be no prosecutions. It is telling that Mrs Lam has not retracted her claim that the unrest had been “a riot”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hong Kong’s government had argued that the main reason for introducing the bill now was to enable a suspect to be sent to face trial in Taiwan, where he is alleged to have murdered his girlfriend. The man is currently in prison in Hong Kong for a money-laundering offence and is due to be released in October. The bill would remove a provision in Hong Kong’s current law that excludes extraditions to “other parts of China”, which in Hong Kong means the mainland, as well as Macau and Taiwan. But Mrs Lam noted that Taiwan has said it will not accept the suspect’s extradition under the new law. She said that since the bill would not solve that one case, it was no longer urgent to pass it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On June 12th Liu Xiaoming, China’s ambassador to Britain, told the BBC that the government in Beijing had nothing to do with initiating the bill. At her press conference, Mrs Lam said the central authorities had supported both her efforts to introduce the bill and her decision to shelve it. But there has been widespread speculation that the central leadership has been far more actively involved. Mrs Lam owes her position to a committee of local residents that is deliberately stacked with sympathisers of the Communist Party’s policies in the territory. She would be highly unlikely to make any move on such an important matter without seeking the party’s blessing. She declined to comment on local reports that she met one of China’s most senior politicians, Han Zheng, in the Chinese border city of Shenzhen on June 14th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U-turn is a humiliation for Beijing, which has sought to tighten its grip on Hong Kong. But at least it is one the Communist Party can pin on Ms Lam rather have the Chinese president, Xi Jinping, portrayed in poor light. Even within the limits imposed by the Communist Party, Hong Kong enjoys a degree of free expression and political flexibility, which is more than can be said for mainland China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mrs Lam, for her part, deflected reporters’ repeated questions about whether she would heed the demands of protesters that she resign. There would be a precedent for doing so. Tung Chee-hwa, who was chief executive when the anti-subversion law was shelved, stepped down a few months later, apparently because of his handling of that bill. Mrs Lam said the central government had shown her “understanding, trust, respect and support”. To keep her job, she will need more such backing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 21:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Toronto Raptors’ risky bet on Kawhi Leonard pays off with a title]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/06/14/the-toronto-raptors-risky-bet-on-kawhi-leonard-pays-off-with-a-title]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_BLP510.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-14T18:54:18Z&quot;&gt;Jun 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;”FLAGS FLY forever”, they say in baseball as an explanation when teams mortgage their futures in trades in order to make one improbable run at a championship. After winning the first National Basketball Association (NBA) title in their 24-year-long history, the Toronto Raptors may need to coin a similar phrase for their sport.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly a year ago, Canada’s only NBA team pushed its chips all-in. When LeBron James, the superstar whose teams had reached the playoffs’ final round for eight consecutive years, announced he would sign with the Los Angeles Lakers, he opened the path for a new victor in the league’s Eastern Conference. The East might have seemed like a poisoned chalice, since the prize for winning it was likely to be a date in the NBA Finals with the dominant Golden State Warriors, who had won three of the past four league titles. But Toronto, undaunted, seized the opportunity, trading away DeMar DeRozan, a long-time Raptor and local fan favourite, in a deal for Kawhi Leonard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The deal was extraordinarily risky. When healthy, Mr Leonard is one of the five or so best hoopsters on Earth, and perhaps the only player in the league who could conceivably lead the league in scoring and win its Defensive Player of the Year award in the same season. However, he had missed almost the entire previous season with a mysterious injury that refused to heal itself, and alienated his old team, the San Antonio Spurs, by insisting on managing his own medical treatment. Moreover, he had only one year left on his contract, and was widely thought to be plotting a move to one of the league’s California-based franchises once he became a free agent. If he either failed to regain his previous form, or did so but then departed after a single season, the Raptors would be left with little to show for their investment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, the gamble worked out better than Toronto could possibly have expected. After resting Mr Leonard regularly during the NBA’s gruelling 82-game regular season to maintain his energy and reduce his risk of injury, the Raptors turned him loose in the playoffs. Mr Leonard rose to the occasion, delivering a performance that brought to mind the highlights of Mr James or Michael Jordan. In the decisive seventh game of the second round, he made one of the most improbable &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ChT3ewZXTfM&quot;&gt;buzzer-beating shots&lt;/a&gt; in NBA history to send the Raptors to the semi-finals. After Toronto lost the first two games of the following best-of-seven series, the Raptors’ coach, Nick Nurse, gave Mr Leonard primary responsibility for guarding Giannis Antetokounmpo, the Milwaukee Bucks’ superstar. Even though Mr Antetokounmpo stands four inches taller, Mr Leonard largely kept him in check the rest of the way, enabling the Raptors to win four consecutive games and make their first-ever Finals—as expected, against the Warriors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Betting markets gave Golden State nearly a three-in-four chance to win. But rather than rolling over meekly to the Warriors, as Mr James’s teams had done in the previous two championship series, the Raptors decisively dismantled the league’s reigning dynasty. Toronto did not even need to make use of the home-court advantage that they would have enjoyed in a hypothetical Game Seven, as they won the title on the road in the series’ sixth game, 114-110, on June 13th. The Raptors’ victory was indisputably a team effort: all seven of their regular rotation players, including Kyle Lowry, their star point guard; Pascal Siakam, a versatile, athletic forward likely to win the NBA’s Most Improved Player award; and Marc Gasol, a veteran centre whom they acquired in a trade in February, performed well. But there was no doubt about who would be named the Finals Most Valuable Player. Mr Leonard, who had already won the award once with San Antonio in 2014, amassed video-game-like statistics during the series, averaging 28.5 points, 9.8 rebounds, 4.2 assists, 2.0 steals and 1.2 blocks per game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Golden State partisans will insist that Toronto’s title comes with an asterisk, as the team lost far more in this year’s Finals than just the chance to three-peat. The team’s dynasty is built around four stars: Stephen Curry, the best shooter in NBA history; Kevin Durant, one of the league’s top overall individual scorers; Draymond Green, arguably the NBA’s best defensive forward and passing big man; and Klay Thompson, another elite long-range shooter. The team entered the series hobbled, as Mr Durant had missed all of the previous round with a calf strain. By the time it ended, the Warriors’ hopes of winning a title next season had been dimmed as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After sitting out during the Finals’ first four games, Mr Durant lasted just 12 minutes on the floor in Game Five before his right leg buckled with a torn Achilles tendon. This heel injury is the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/01/18/demarcus-cousins-is-unlikely-to-be-the-golden-state-warriors-silver-bullet&quot; data-tegid=&quot;br59nhh7vbc8mofn32lk88mks4df4uth&quot;&gt;single worst fate that can befall a basketball player&lt;/a&gt;, one that is not only expected to keep Mr Durant out for much or all of the 2019-20 campaign, but may also prevent him from ever becoming the player he once was again. And adding, well, injury to insult to injury, Mr Thompson ruptured his anterior cruciate ligament in Golden State’s final losing effort in Game Six, which will probably keep &lt;i&gt;him&lt;/i&gt; out for nearly a year as well. With both players’ contracts expiring, Golden State will have to let them go and try to sign another marquee free agent—perhaps Mr Leonard himself—to remain a serious contender.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one knows how Toronto would have fared against the Warriors at full strength. Over the course of the series, the Raptors outscored Golden State by six points per 100 possessions. Mr Durant probably improves his clubs by seven or eight points per 100 possessions relative to a typical end-of-bench player at the same position. So assuming that Mr Durant would have played around four-fifths of each game if healthy, the series might have been extremely close. Moreover, if Toronto does not deserve full credit for beating a depleted Warriors team, then the Warriors’ &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/game-theory/2015/06/18/most-valuable-loser&quot; data-tegid=&quot;idnuqjgtc3m4jm53nghd3oo91h5v1894&quot;&gt;victory over the injury-wracked Cleveland Cavaliers in 2015&lt;/a&gt; was just as questionable. Injuries are part of the game, and flags fly forever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the NBA will surely be the worse for the absences of Mr Durant and Mr Thompson in the 2019-20 season, it is probably good for the league that the Warriors’ era is drawing to a close. When Mr Durant &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/game-theory/2016/07/05/if-you-cant-beat-em-join-em&quot; data-tegid=&quot;hvoiu0s6mqs6mrgi0hbbqobu86n5cq04&quot;&gt;signed as a free agent&lt;/a&gt; with Golden State in 2016, many fans feared that the following seasons would amount to little more than suspense-free coronation ceremonies. That was, in fact, more or less what happened. Now, a whole host of exciting teams, including Houston, Philadelphia and Milwaukee, will get their chance to shine. If Mr James can lure another superstar to join him on the Lakers, then one of the NBA’s marquee franchises will get back in the hunt as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And then, of course, there are the Raptors. Now that Mr Leonard has brought Canada its first-ever NBA title, he might be tempted to build a dynasty of his own in the Great White North.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 04:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ryanair is starting to hide its brand]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/gulliver/2019/06/14/ryanair-is-starting-to-hide-its-brand]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_BLP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-14T18:02:20Z&quot;&gt;Jun 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;RYANAIR, EUROPE’S largest low-cost carrier, has long defied conventional wisdom when it comes to branding. Its garish yellow and blue livery–much like its loud-mouthed chief executive, Michael O’Leary–is an assault on the senses. While other airlines try to woo passengers with sophisticated brands, Ryanair slaps them in the face with its low prices. The strategy has served it well, appealing to a majority of short-haul flyers who prize cheap fares over other frills. Since last year, however, Ryanair has changed course. Rather than relying on just one brand, it is now diversifying. First it established an airline in Austria called Lauda, with red-and-white branding. Then it unveiled a Polish subsidiary, Buzz, with a yellow-and-black colour scheme. And earlier this week it created a Maltese-based airline, Malta Air, with red-and-white planes painted in the country’s national colours. Travellers to and from those countries no longer have to suffer the ignominy of flying Ryanair. Yet the services offered on the new airlines will be barely indistinguishable from that of their parent company. So what is Mr O’Leary up to?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The company has presented its recent moves as Ryanair “growing up”. Its biggest competitors are groups of airlines, not companies with a single brand. International Airlines Group (IAG), for instance, owns British Airways, Iberia of Spain and Aer Lingus of Ireland, while the Lufthansa Group controls the flag carriers of Austria, Belgium, Germany and Switzerland. But the similarities end there. For IAG and Lufthansa multiple brands are a necessity, not a choice. Most of their subsidiaries are ex-state-owned flag carriers that are tied inexorably to national pride. If Lufthansa retired the Austrian Airlines brand and rerouted traffic from Vienna via its hub in Munich, it would face a backlash from Austrian travellers and well as the government there. Both IAG and Lufthansa also have separate low-cost subsidiaries–Level and Eurowings–to ensure that that their no-frills services do not damage the image of their more premium brands. No such diversity exists in Ryanair’s growing stable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The establishment of subsidiaries in Austria, Poland and Malta have some other logic. Low-cost carriers have been slow to gain market share in German-speaking countries, where customer loyalty to national carriers is stronger than elsewhere. Lauda, named after Niki Lauda, an Austrian racing driver who died last month, is a uniquely appealing brand for locals. In Poland, the Buzz name bears more than a passing resemblance to Wizz Air, a rival low-cost airline, which is snapping at Ryanair’s heels in the country. In Malta, favourable employment laws could be the target. Ryanair plans to register 50 of its aircraft in the country, only 10 of which will serve the local market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there is also a more mundane explanation. The clue was the decision in February to make Mr O’Leary the chief executive of Ryanair Group. A new chief executive of Ryanair the airline will be appointed later this year. Mr O’Leary has already begun to distance himself from the airline’s marketing. He lets more affable executives on his board do the bulk of media interviews these days. It now takes customer complaints more seriously than in the past, when Mr O’Leary would tell customers who asked for a refund to “fuck off”. That is a hint that after decades of revelling in negative publicity, Ryanair’s brand has become too toxic for some of the markets it now wants to expand into. Mr O’Leary used to believe that “all publicity is good publicity”. But now perhaps even he has learnt that there is a limit to which you can take any management slogan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 03:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Iran is blowing up ships in the Gulf, says America]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/14/iran-is-blowing-up-ships-in-the-gulf-says-america]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_blp509.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-14T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE BLACK-AND-WHITE video is grainy, but what it shows is clear, claims America. An Iranian patrol boat pulls up alongside a ship called the &lt;em&gt;Kokuka Courageous&lt;/em&gt;. Iranian sailors, thought to be members of the Revolutionary Guard Corps, then remove an unexploded limpet mine from the hull of the ship. The &lt;em&gt;Kokuka Courageous&lt;/em&gt; and another ship, the &lt;em&gt;Front Altair&lt;/em&gt;, had been crippled hours earlier in “unprovoked attacks” by Iran on June 13th, said Mike Pompeo, America’s secretary of state. Iran denied it was to blame. But hardliners on both sides risk escalating the conflict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the second time in just over a month that tankers have been damaged in the Gulf. On May 12th four ships anchored off Fujairah, a port in the United Arab Emirates (UAE), had holes blown in their hulls. A preliminary investigation suggests that they were damaged by limpet mines. America blamed Iran, which issued a denial. The latest explosions caused far more damage, forcing crews to abandon both ships as they were underway. It also sent the price of oil upwards. One-fifth of the world’s supply travels through the Strait of Hormuz, an important chokepoint for international shipping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America last month dispatched an aircraft-carrier strike group to the region, citing the threat of Iran; then, in response to the attacks on ships, it also began deploying an extra 1,500 troops to bases in Qatar, Bahrain and Iraq. America’s naval vessels will probably step up their patrols. “Ordinarily the fact that the US wasn’t directly targeted and there were no casualties would give Washington some breathing room to respond,” says Michael Singh of the Washington Institute for Near East Policy, a think-tank. “However, because the free flow of energy is of such vital importance to the world economy, there is a need to show a determination to secure the straits while calming fears of a conflict.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For an idea of how things could play out some are looking to the past. The so-called tanker war between Iraq and Iran in the 1980s ravaged shipping in the Gulf. Though most attacks were from the air, the Guards honed the use of mine-planting boats—similar to the vessel captured on video on June 13th. Eventually, and with reluctance, America agreed to reflag and escort Kuwaiti vessels through the area. When that did not work, American special forces, operating from special sea barges, were sent to hunt and destroy Iranian mine-layers. That culminated in Operation Praying Mantis: a major air and naval attack on Iranian ships and platforms in 1988.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A repeat of such dramatic moves remains unlikely, for now. Only a half-dozen tankers have been the target of attacks so far, compared with hundreds in the 1980s, and the damage has been limited. With more naval forces in the region, America should be able to keep an eye on suspect ships. Air and naval patrols, to monitor Iranian vessels and hoover up their communications, will have increased. That will make it harder for would-be attackers to approach tankers without being detected. Britain’s Royal Navy also has a frigate and four specialised mine-hunting units patrolling the region, but “we’re not going to be steamrollering into that area with grey ships,” says a well-placed source.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iran has in the past threatened to close the Strait of Hormuz in response to American sanctions. Some will see the strikes against ships in the area as a veiled warning of its readiness to make good on its threat. President Donald Trump said on June 14th that if Iran were to block the strait, “it’s not going to be closed for long.” (A study published in 2008 showed that if Iran were to mine the strait, it could take America “the better part of a month&amp;quot; to re-open it.) The Iranian government, for its part, issued a statement on June 13th saying, “The US and its regional allies must stop warmongering and put an end to mischievous plots as well as false flag operations in the region.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many hardliners in the Middle East would, indeed, like to see America go to war against Iran. But the history of revolutionary Iran, including its threats to close the strait, mean that its government—or one of its factions—is the prime suspect. President Hassan Rouhani probably understands that attacking regional shipping would be to invite a Western military response. A day before the attacks he met Shinzo Abe, the prime minister of Japan, who tried to reduce tensions between America and Iran. But Mr Rouhani staked his legacy on a deal, signed in 2015, that loosened sanctions on Iran in exchange for limits on its nuclear programme. That seemed a good bet—until Mr Trump took office in America. Mr Trump’s decision to withdraw from the deal vindicated Iran’s hardliners, who have long argued that America is untrustworthy. Mr Rouhani’s popularity has plunged, and with it his control (always tenuous) over the Revolutionary Guards and other hawkish factions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iran’s supreme leader, Ayatollah Ali Khamenei, is decidedly in the latter camp. Though he gave Mr Rouhani space to negotiate the nuclear deal, his dismissive reaction to Mr Abe suggests that his patience has run out. (As it turned out, one of the ships hit in the latest attacks is operated by a Japanese company, Kokuka Sangyo.) Ideology aside, the Guards benefit from what they call the “resistance economy”. Two years ago Mr Rouhani was trying to reduce the group’s role in business. Now, with private firms sidelined, the Guards can step in as the contractor of last resort. Sanctions forced Total, the French energy giant, to pull out of a major offshore gas project; the Guards hope to take its place. The nuclear deal was a threat to the Guards’ interests, and the group has no desire to see it restored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both America and Iran seem to be calibrating their response to each other’s actions. With his economy sinking under the weight of American sanctions, Mr Rouhani has warned that Iran will abrogate parts of the nuclear accord unless other signatories—Britain, France, Germany, Russia, China and the European Union—help his country bypass the sanctions. The Guards may have drawn the conclusion that sporadic mine attacks are a deniable, low-cost and risk-free way to apply pressure on American allies, without incurring a military response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We want to get them back at the table, if they want to go back,” says Mr Trump, referring to his efforts to negotiate a new nuclear deal with Iran. But there are hardliners in America, too. Mr Trump’s hawkish national-security adviser, John Bolton, has long supported regime change in Iran, and even military action against it. In response to the attacks in May, American commanders in the Middle East are reported to have called for an increase of nearly 20,000 troops in the region. Moreover, countries such as Saudi Arabia and the United Arab Emirates have, in recent years, demonstrated a willingness and ability to take military action largely independent of America, in places such as Yemen and Libya. All sides insist they do not want war. But that may not be true of all players. And even if it were, the risk of miscalculation is growing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 03:39:55 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[British regulators seek to halt sexist ads]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/14/british-regulators-seek-to-halt-sexist-ads]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_woc261.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-14T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ARE YOU beach-body ready? London commuters may remember this question from a controversial 2015 ad on the city’s underground featuring the now-infamous words alongside a bronzed, bikini-clad model. The campaign, which sparked cries of “body-shaming” from activists, led to a protest in Hyde Park in London and a change.org petition that attracted more than 70,000 signatures. Whether the advertiser, Protein World, benefited is unclear. But protesters eventually got their way. The Advertising Standards Authority (ASA), an industry regulator, launched a review of its guidelines on gender stereotyping. The subsequent ruling, that adverts “must not include gender stereotypes that are likely to cause harm, or serious or widespread offence”, comes into force today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some consumers will welcome the changes. Whether it be teenage girls fretting over their figures or fathers struggling with everyday household tasks, 48% of women and 44% of men think there are too many outdated stereotypes in television ads (see chart). Nearly half of women and almost a third of men resent the way their gender is portrayed. Many big brands have yet to adapt. Although heterosexual couples increasingly share domestic purchasing decisions, many firms still rely on binary marketing strategies, advertising some products to women and others to men. In traditionally female-dominated sectors, such as baby products and laundry detergents, women still comprise upwards of 98% of advertisers’ intended audience. In male-dominated ones, such as automobiles, women are largely ignored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under the ASA’s new rules, advertisements depicting “harmful gender stereotypes” will be banned. This includes ads featuring people being belittled for defying outdated norms, such as a man discussing his emotions. Those that associate someone’s gender with responsibility or failure, such as a woman tidying up while her family watch television, or a man failing to change a nappy, will also be banned. Whether the ASA will succeed in implementing its rather subjective rules remains to be seen. It is certainly true that such outdated adverts are woefully out of step with modern views on equality. But as the case of Protein World makes clear, consumers can usually figure this out for themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 03:39:54 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Buy-out firms are the new banks in emerging markets]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/14/buy-out-firms-are-the-new-banks-in-emerging-markets]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_fnp509.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-14T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ENERGY PRODUCERS have long had India over a barrel. The country is the third-largest oil importer in the world, yet its pipeline density is a quarter of the global average. It aims to add 15,000km to the network by 2022, awarding projects through strict online tenders. The few groups able to qualify can hope for sweet profits—if they can first find financing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is at last becoming easier. In emerging markets, a new breed of lenders has begun acting as credit supermarkets, offering anything from working capital to multi-year debt. They look and quack like banks—but are in fact buy-out firms investing mostly rich-world money. As demand for financing surges in fast-growing countries, they will proliferate, argues Kanchan Jain of Baring Private Equity Asia. Her firm is nearing a four-year debt investment in a business that lays pipes in India.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their surge reflects investors’ continuing hunt for yield. Ultra-low interest rates since the financial crisis have depressed returns in the West, nudging institutions such as pension funds towards economies with more alluring prospects. After stocks, bonds and private equity, private credit is their latest target. Over 50 emerging-market private-debt funds closed last year, up from 14 a decade ago. They raised a total $9.4bn, a sevenfold rise since 2008. Michael Casey of Portico, an advisory firm, says fundraising volumes could easily double again without flooding the market. &lt;br/&gt;Funds are filling a void left by Western banks, which have shunned faraway borrowers since regulators asked for more capital to be held against exotic bets. Local rivals often lack firepower: the top 20 sub-Saharan banks together have less capital than one of Europe’s big lenders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors are also seeking pastures new to evade fierce competition in developed markets, where buy-out firms’ efforts to take over from banks have already reached a peak. These now manage $770bn in “alternative” debt assets. But credit supply is running ahead of demand: over $300bn raised by funds in recent years has yet to be spent. Competition for deals has crushed margins and caused a decline in “covenants”—clauses requiring borrowers to keep overall debt levels under control. Less mature markets, oddly, are starting to look safer: taking no chances, funds lending there insist on robust covenants. Borrowers also tend to be half as leveraged, and funds themselves seldom carry any debt (many do in the West).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The asset class is also winning converts away from private equity. Finding acquisition targets can be tough in emerging markets, as owners of growing businesses, often families, are loth to give up control. Exiting them is even trickier. Prospective buyers are rare and thin capital markets complicate IPOs. All this hard work erodes returns to investors, says Holger Rothenbusch of CDC Group, the British government’s overseas-investment arm. By contrast debt investments, which rarely dilute shareholders, tend to be self-liquidating. Most also produce regular cash flows. That pleases liability-driven investors like insurers. Returns can be juicy: low teens for senior loans, higher for distressed debt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are pitfalls. Lending to a company rarely gives firms a board seat, making it harder to spot problems and scold management than if funds held an equity stake. And when things do go wrong, creditors’ ability to enforce agreements or seize collateral can be weak. “I’ve had to try to bring things to an Indian court,” says a former fund manager. “It’s basically impossible.” Some try to protect themselves by booking capital offshore; others limit themselves to high-quality borrowers and sponsors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another issue is currency risk. With liabilities in dollars, most funds want to be paid in the same currency. But few companies earning in an emerging-market currency can afford to buy multi-year dollar hedges. That often restricts funds’ investable market to infrastructure projects backed by government guarantees, or companies pricing their wares in dollars, such as exporters or oil producers. To fuel a real investor frenzy, the asset class needs a stronger pipeline of deals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 03:39:53 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The agony and the ecstasy of Russian culture]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/14/the-agony-and-the-ecstasy-of-russian-culture]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_BKP510.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-14T16:38:47Z&quot;&gt;Jun 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BOOK-PRIZE ceremonies are often a bit of a let-down. Until the outcome is revealed, much of the focus is on what the seating plan and choreography suggest about the identity of the winner. After the announcement, everybody goes home. And they can be oddly unintellectual. The avowed purpose is to promote literature, but they generally feel more like horse-races than symposiums, the chatter dwelling on sales boosts rather than ideas. Not so the Pushkin House book prize, which was awarded in London on June 12th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pushkin House is a venerable London-based charity that promotes Russian culture and Anglo-Russian dialogue. In 2013 it introduced a prize for nonfiction books about Russia, written or translated into English (this blogger was one of the inaugural judges). Beginning as a modest event, these days the ceremony is conducted over a glitzy candlelit dinner at the Charterhouse, a medieval former monastery in central London. But the centrepiece is not the meal, or even the awarding of the prize, but the discussions with the shortlisted authors that punctuate the evening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Together these encapsulated why the Russian world remains so fascinating and essential a subject—the geographical and moral scale, the grotesque suffering and misrule, the bravery, the ideas and the impact on everybody else. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2018/05/19/inside-vladimir-putins-mafia-state%20%20&quot;&gt;Mark Galeotti, author of “The Vory”&lt;/a&gt;, a portrait of the Russian mafia, explained that the “the underworld is basically the dark shadow of the upper world”. He warned of “the danger of the Olympian moral perspective” of outsiders, when confronted with (for example) the turmoil of Russia in the 1990s. “Would I have broken the law?” Mr Galeotti asked, if all those round him were doing so—thus pointing up the ethical dilemmas that Russia often poses for its visitors. He elucidated the concept of the “honest thief”: a crook who doesn’t pretend to be otherwise, unlike the police and the bureaucrats. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heroism was spotlighted alongside the depravity. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2018/05/05/the-world-almost-ended-in-1983&quot;&gt;Taylor Downing, author of “1983: The World at the Brink”&lt;/a&gt;, referred to the Soviet mole in NATO who helped to avert nuclear Armageddon during a little-known cold-war near-miss. Western policymakers “knew nothing about what the [Soviet] leadership was thinking”, he reflected, just as, for all their sophisticated intelligence, they know little of the mind-sets of Iranian and North Korean leaders now. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2018/09/20/a-gripping-tale-of-cold-war-espionage&quot;&gt;Ben Macintyre, author of the “The Spy and the Traitor”&lt;/a&gt;, recalled that the tasks entrusted in London to Oleg Gordievsky, a KGB officer secretly working for Britain’s MI6, included election-meddling and the dissemination of fake news. “He’s a difficult man to like,” Mr Macintyre said frankly of his courageous subject, “but an impossible man not to admire.” Mr Gordievsky’s “nose is very slightly put out” by the poisoning of Sergei Skripal in Salisbury last year, the author confided; “he doesn’t think he’s that big a fish.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A running theme was Russia’s relationship with Ukraine—a fraternity that shaped Russian literature but has now been tragically shattered. “You cannot imagine Russian cultural history without Ukraine—and the other way around,” remarked Andrei Zorin, a professor at Oxford and one of this year’s judges. Three of the authors on the shortlist come from Ukraine; one of the books, “Maybe Esther”, is a “Russian-Polish-German history, written in German” by an author, Katja Petrowskaja, who grew up in Kiev. Another of the Ukrainians, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/03/07/the-tragedy-of-chernobyl%20&quot;&gt;Serhii Plokhy, author of “Chernobyl: History of a Tragedy”&lt;/a&gt;, described the startling ignorance that he uncovered during his research into the nuclear disaster of 1986, from operators at the power plant to Communist Party bosses. “We are living in the world of alternative facts,” Mr Plokhy lamented when, at the end of the dinner, he was declared the prize’s winner, in which “the only salvation is the book”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Humour—especially the bleak, existential kind that has been a vital survival technique in Russia for centuries—was another of the evening’s motifs, from Mr Galeotti’s deadpan accounts of his meetings with Russian gangsters, to Mr Plokhy’s view of “Chernobyl”, the hit HBO drama broadcast after his book was published. “They cut a couple of corners—like the people who constructed the Chernobyl nuclear-power plant,” Mr Plokhy said. “If only they had based the mini-series on my book, it would be perfect.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 00:40:28 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How has the LGBT movement changed in the past 50 years?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/14/how-has-the-lgbt-movement-changed-in-the-past-50-years]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_opp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-14T16:21:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ARMISTEAD MAUPIN was one of the first writers to bring gay and transsexual characters to a mainstream audience. “Tales of the city” began as a series of stories published in a San Francisco newspaper in the 1970s. In this episode of “The Economist asks” podcast, Anne McElvoy asks him about what drew him back to the setting of 28 Barbary Lane to tell a new batch of tales of queer America. Fifty years on from the Stonewall riots that sparked the LGBT civil-rights movement, Mr Maupin talks about how far there is still to go, what young gay men can never understand about his generation, and why he has finally decided to abandon his beloved San Francisco. Runtime 23 min. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-armisteadmaupin&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 23:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>