<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Britain&#x27;s constitutional time-bomb, extreme weather in the Midwest and 30 years since Tiananmen]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/30/britains-constitutional-time-bomb-extreme-weather-in-the-midwest-and-30-years-since-tiananmen]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_7.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-30T16:50:49Z&quot;&gt;May 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A SELECTION of three essential articles read aloud from the latest issue of The Economist. This week, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/30/britains-constitutional-time-bomb&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Britain’s constitutional time-bomb&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Brexit is already a political crisis—sooner or later it will become a constitutional one too. Also, how &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/06/01/floods-and-storms-are-altering-american-attitudes-to-climate-change&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;floods and storms in the Midwest&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; are altering American attitudes to climate change (9:24). And, 30 years after the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/china/2019/06/01/many-chinese-know-little-about-the-bloodshed-in-beijing-30-years-ago&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tiananmen Square massacre&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, many Chinese know little about the bloodshed (18:07). Runtime: 26 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-may30th2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:40:47 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why England start the Cricket World Cup as favourites]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/05/30/why-england-start-the-cricket-world-cup-as-favourites]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_BLP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-30T11:32:50Z&quot;&gt;May 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE GRASS has been cut, the squares prepared. The advertising posters are up and 95% of the 800,000 tickets have been sold. The 12th Cricket World Cup begins in England this week and will conclude, somewhat laboriously, in a final on July 14th. Each of the ten teams will play each other in a round-robin league, with the top four in the table qualifying for the semi-finals. As usual, the matches are one-day internationals (ODIs), in which each team gets 50 overs (or 300 balls) with the bat—longer than the T20 format, which gives each side 20 overs, but shorter than Test matches, which last five days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of fixtures and the increasingly aggressive batting tactics used by most teams makes it likely that more international runs will be scored in the next month than in any that came before. But another historic milestone also looms on the horizon. The English, who invented the game but have never won the World Cup, might finally break that duck. Bookmakers reckon they are the favourites, with roughly a 30% chance of victory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For most of the tournament’s 44-year history, the “Poms” (as they are called by their Australian tormentors, who have won it five times) have been useless. They last reached a final in 1992. At the previous tournament in 2015, the only teams they managed to beat were lowly Scotland and Afghanistan. They were eliminated at the earliest opportunity. Their defeat by hosts New Zealand was one of the most comprehensive sporting losses imaginable, with the Kiwis surpassing England’s paltry 123 runs in just 12 overs and two balls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc170.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But during the past four years England have focused relentlessly on avenging themselves at the tournament. Shortly after the debacle in 2015, the England and Wales Cricket Board (ECB) appointed Trevor Bayliss, a head coach who specialises in cricket’s short formats. Mr Bayliss threw out the core of the old squad and rebuilt the team in the image of Eoin Morgan, its Irish-born captain and one of its most aggressive batsmen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Bayliss’s changes have been twofold. The first has been to pick hard hitters who were previously considered too inconsistent. At the top of the order are Jonny Bairstow and Jason Roy, who drifted around the edges of the England set-up before 2015, but have now matured into the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://stats.espncricinfo.com/ci/engine/stats/index.html?class=2;filter=advanced;orderby=fow_run_rate;partnership_wicketmax1=1;partnership_wicketval1=partnership_wicket;qualmin1=10;qualval1=fow_innings;template=results;type=fow&quot;&gt;fastest-scoring opening pair in ODI history&lt;/a&gt;. Supporting them in the middle order is Ben Stokes, a brawny all-rounder who was omitted from the last World Cup squad after a poor run of form with the bat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The coach’s second change has been to encourage the batsmen who survived his cull in 2015 to swing even harder for the boundary rope (see chart, above). Alongside Mr Morgan, the core of the side is now occupied by Jos Buttler, one of cricket’s most innovative hitters, and Joe Root, the Test captain, who offers something of a cooler head. In the last four years, all three have scored their runs at least 10% more quickly (on a per-ball basis) than they did in the previous four years. Where England once considered a total of 300 runs a good score, the team now looks for 350 or more. It was a measure of how eagerly the players bought into Mr Bayliss’s philosophy that in June 2015, just two months after the World Cup, they beat New Zealand 3-2 in an ODI series, registering scores of 408, 365 and 350.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the start of this World Cup, England hold the number-one ranking in ODI cricket and the world record for the highest score (481 against Australia last year). In 2019 so far they have scored boundaries—six runs if the ball is hit over the rope without bouncing, four runs if it touches the turf—40% more frequently than the average ODI team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of which raises the question: why doesn’t every team wield the willow so aggressively? The answer is that doing so carries considerable risk, because hitting with reckless abandon increases the chance that a shot will be caught by a fielder, resulting in a wicket. England have enough capable sloggers in the team, including several bowlers, to get away with this perilous strategy most of the time. But occasionally it backfires spectacularly, with every single batsman getting himself out. In the last year England have endured the two biggest defeats in their history. In October their total of 132 runs was 219 less than Sri Lanka managed in their innings, and in March the West Indies passed England’s score of 113 in just 12 overs and one ball. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/game-theory/20190601_woc171.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even more worrying for English fans is a dearth of top-notch bowlers. Whereas the country has five of the world’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.icc-cricket.com/rankings/mens/player-rankings/odi/batting&quot;&gt;20 highest-rated ODI players with the bat&lt;/a&gt;, it only has two of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.icc-cricket.com/rankings/mens/player-rankings/odi/bowling&quot;&gt;top 20 with the ball&lt;/a&gt;: Chris Woakes and Adil Rashid. But although they both take a lot of wickets they also give away lots of runs. In fact, England’s bowlers are so leaky that the ECB has relaxed the eligibility criteria in order for Mr Bayliss to select Jofra Archer, a Barbadian who has a British passport but has only lived in the country for three years. He bowls more quickly than any of England’s other options, and has honed his skills by playing in T20 leagues around the world. The hosts will need him to translate that success to ODIs if they are to win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The real sultans of swing and spin are India. The team is synonymous with Virat Kohli, its captain and the world’s highest-rated batsman. But they are most dangerous with the ball in hand, since the squad contains three of the eight best bowlers at the competition: Jasprit Bumrah, a seamer with an unusual number of tricky variations and the courage to use them, and Kuldeep Yadav and Yuzvendra Chahal, two wrist-spinners who move the ball unpredictably off the pitch. The flat wickets that the hosts have prepared might make the World Cup a run-fest, with some commentators expecting the first ever score of 500. But India will do better than most in restraining their opponents’ hitting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia offer the other main threat to England’s hopes. The defending champions have endured a dismal couple of years, exacerbated by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/game-theory/2018/03/28/a-ball-tampering-row-consumes-australia&quot;&gt;the suspension&lt;/a&gt; of former captain Steve Smith and his deputy, David Warner. The pair were caught rubbing the ball with sandpaper to make it swing more in the air, an offence that is beyond the pale in cricket, but have now served their bans. They were roundly booed by English spectators in a warm-up game against the hosts on May 25th, an unusual occurrence in the sport—and promptly scored 159 runs between them while guiding their team to victory. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps England will be able to pile 400-odd runs on their old rivals later this month, when it really counts. But there would be no sensation more familiar for cricket fans than the Poms self-destructing and the Aussies spoiling the party.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:40:46 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mitch McConnell says he would confirm a Supreme Court nominee in 2020]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/30/mitch-mcconnell-says-he-would-confirm-a-supreme-court-nominee-in-2020]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_USP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-30T10:14:10Z&quot;&gt;May 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHEN ANTONIN SCALIA died suddenly in 2016, Mitch McConnell, the Senate majority leader, wasted no time staking out the Republican position on the conservative jurist’s successor. Hours after news broke of Mr Scalia’s demise, Mr McConnell declared that “the American people should have a voice in the selection of their next Supreme Court justice”. With nearly nine months to go before the presidential election, he told America that his legislative chamber would take no action on any Supreme Court nominee named by Barack Obama. “This vacancy”, he announced, articulating a broad principle, “should not be filled until we have a new president.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was an aggressive move. The constitution gives presidents the power to nominate federal judges, including Supreme Court justices, and the Senate’s “advice and consent” are necessary before they take their seats. But Mr McConnell took the unprecedented step of building a blockade around Scalia’s seat rather than give a hearing to Merrick Garland, the moderate chief judge of the District of Columbia Circuit Court of Appeals nominated by Mr Obama. After stonewalling Judge Garland for the remaining 11 months of Mr Obama’s term, the Republican Senate avidly took up Donald Trump’s nominee, the highly conservative Neil Gorsuch. He was confirmed on April 7, 2017.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;McConnell’s gambit proved to be a thorough success: instead of a Democratic president replacing one of the court’s most right-wing justices with a left-leaning judge, Mr Scalia’s seat was filled with a 49-year-old originalist who would safeguard the conservative majority. But would the new principle of demurring on Supreme Court nominations in presidential election years stick? The former chair of the Senate Judiciary Committee, Iowa Republican Charles Grassley, said in 2018 that he would honour the 2016 rule and refuse to preside over a Supreme Court confirmation hearing were the shoe to be on the other foot in 2020. &amp;quot;If I’m chairman, they won’t take it up&amp;quot;, Mr Grassley said, “because I pledged that in 2016”. Mr Grassley’s replacement as chair, Lindsey Graham, has echoed this promise. “If an opening comes in the last year of President Trump’s term and the primary process has started”, Mr Graham said in 2018, “we’ll wait until the next election”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the past, Mr McConnell has hedged when asked if he agrees with the current and former Judiciary Committee chairs. But on May 28th, at a talk to the Chamber of Commerce in Paducah, Kentucky, his home state, the senator made his position clear. “If a Supreme Court justice dies next year, what would you do?”, he was asked. Mr McConnell took a long sip of iced tea and smiled: “oh, we’d fill it”, he said, to laughter. As important as questions of policy are, he said, “what can&amp;#x27;t be undone is a lifetime appointment to a young man or woman who believes in the quaint notion that the job of a judge is to follow the law. That’s the most important thing we’ve done for the country.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chuck Schumer, the Democratic minority leader in the Senate, took to Twitter to accuse the majority leader of hypocrisy. In response, Mr McConnell now says his no-hearing rule applies only when the Senate and White House are controlled by different parties. However he tries to justify the change of policy, Mr McConnell seems unfazed by charges of inconsistency. If a Supreme Court vacancy opens up before the 2020 election, Mr McConnell will promptly fill it. Principle seems to count for little. But votes count, and he has 53 to the Democrats’ 47.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:40:45 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How the European elections will shake up domestic politics]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/01/how-the-european-elections-will-shake-up-domestic-politics]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_eud002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;T WILL TAKE&lt;/small&gt; weeks for the results of the European elections to take effect; the parliament does not convene until July. But in some countries events moved swiftly. Within days of the vote a chancellor was forced from office, a snap election called, a de facto leader sent to prison and some party chiefs left fighting to survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ruling Christian Democratic Union (&lt;small&gt;CDU&lt;/small&gt;) and its Bavarian ally took first place in &lt;strong&gt;Germany&lt;/strong&gt;, but with a record low score of 29%. The Greens surged into second place with over 20% of the vote. A poor national result for the far-right Alternative for Germany masked a strong showing in the country’s east, where the party came first in two of three states that will hold elections in the autumn. The biggest losers were the Social Democrats (&lt;small&gt;SPD&lt;/small&gt;), the &lt;small&gt;CDU&lt;/small&gt;’s coalition partner, who slumped to 16% and lost a separate election in the city-state of Bremen for the first time in over 70 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Germany’s coalition is tattered but holding, for now. Yet a febrile mood has taken hold inside the ruling parties. Andrea Nahles, the embattled &lt;small&gt;SPD&lt;/small&gt; chairwoman, has decided to flush out any internal foes by putting her leadership of the parliamentary group up for early election. But Annegret Kramp-Karrenbauer, leader of the &lt;small&gt;CDU&lt;/small&gt;, managed to distract from the &lt;small&gt;SPD&lt;/small&gt;’s woes by appearing to suggest that YouTube commentators should be subject to regulation during election campaigns, exposing her to charges (which she denied) of opposing free speech. Inside the &lt;small&gt;CDU&lt;/small&gt; some wonder if the gaffe-prone Ms Kramp-Karrenbauer has what it takes to succeed Angela Merkel, her mentor, as chancellor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere it was a mixed night for governing parties. The results in &lt;strong&gt;Italy &lt;/strong&gt;reversed the roles of junior and senior partner in western Europe’s only populist government. Matteo Salvini’s nationalist Northern League doubled its tally from last year’s general election to 34% of the vote; the anti-establishment Five Star Movement (&lt;small&gt;M&lt;/small&gt;5&lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt;) crashed from 32% to 17%. The opposition centre-left Democratic Party beat expectations to take second, with 23%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The League’s triumph could tempt Mr Salvini, the deputy prime minister, to force an election and dump the &lt;small&gt;M&lt;/small&gt;5&lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt; in favour of a coalition with other right-wing parties. But after the result he said that his loyalty to the existing arrangement had “never been in question”. The bigger doubts are over the &lt;small&gt;M&lt;/small&gt;5&lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt;. With the whip firmly in his hand, Mr Salvini has called for measures at which the &lt;small&gt;M&lt;/small&gt;5&lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt; has balked, including immigration controls, infrastructure schemes and more autonomy for Italy’s rich north. Alarmingly for Brussels, the League leader also urged a tax-cutting stimulus. Italy already risks breaching euro-area budget-deficit limits, and the European Commission is reportedly preparing to begin disciplinary proceedings. But a defiant Mr Salvini said he had been given “a mandate calmly to revisit old and outdated parameters”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;strong&gt;Austria&lt;/strong&gt; the election provided only brief respite for Sebastian Kurz, the young head of the ruling conservative People’s Party (&lt;small&gt;öVP&lt;/small&gt;), amid a scandal that has shattered his government. On May 18th Mr Kurz ejected his coalition partner, the far-right Freedom Party, after a tape from 2017 surfaced showing its leader, Heinz-Christian Strache, promising government contracts to a woman he believed was related to a Russian oligarch. Perhaps benefiting from disillusionment with Mr Strache’s party, the &lt;small&gt;öVP&lt;/small&gt; went on to win a record 35% of the vote. But one day later Mr Kurz’s government was toppled in a confidence vote. A caretaker government will take office before elections in September, in which Mr Kurz will hope to resume where he left off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;Not as bad as it seemed&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emmanuel Macron, the &lt;strong&gt;French &lt;/strong&gt;president, will have been disappointed to lose to Marine Le Pen’s National Rally (formerly the National Front), which took 23% of the vote. Yet the outcome was far from devastating. Despite 28 weeks of &lt;em &gt;gilets jaunes &lt;/em&gt;(yellow jackets) protests, and Ms Le Pen’s efforts to turn the election into a referendum on Mr Macron, she ended up with a slightly lower score than in 2014. Less than a percentage point separated the two lists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps most importantly, the result confirmed the upending of politics that Mr Macron brought about when he seized the presidency in 2017 with a new party, En Marche. The mainstream parties on the left (Socialists) and right (Republicans) together scored less than 15%. The only impressive gains came from the Greens, who took 13%. Mr Macron will now seek to reboot his presidency. He promises that policymaking will become more “human”, but also to stick to reform plans for pensions, unemployment benefits and the public sector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nationalists struggled in the &lt;strong&gt;Nordics&lt;/strong&gt;, especially Sweden and Denmark, against socialists and liberals. In the &lt;strong&gt;Netherlands &lt;/strong&gt;the Labour Party secured a surprise win on the back of an energetic campaign by Frans Timmermans, a candidate to run the European Commission. But hard-right Flemish separatists did well in a general election in &lt;strong&gt;Belgium&lt;/strong&gt;, held on the same day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In &lt;strong&gt;Poland&lt;/strong&gt; the ruling populist Law and Justice (&lt;small&gt;P&lt;/small&gt;i&lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt;) party won 45% of the vote, putting it in good stead to win a general election due in the autumn. The European Coalition, an ad hoc group of anti-&lt;small&gt;P&lt;/small&gt;i&lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt; parties led by the centrist Civic Platform (&lt;small&gt;PO&lt;/small&gt;), will struggle to remain united after taking a disappointing 38%. With other parties in trouble, the &lt;small&gt;P&lt;/small&gt;i&lt;small&gt;S-PO&lt;/small&gt; rivalry will continue to dominate Polish politics. But &lt;small&gt;P&lt;/small&gt;i&lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt;, under its leader Jaroslaw Kaczynski, is setting the agenda with generous handouts and popular slogans. &lt;small&gt;PO&lt;/small&gt; and others are struggling to find a coherent pitch to voters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a dreadful election for Liviu Dragnea, head of &lt;strong&gt;Romania&lt;/strong&gt;’s ruling Social Democrats (&lt;small&gt;PSD&lt;/small&gt;). Voters at home and abroad turned out in droves against a government widely perceived as corrupt. The &lt;small&gt;PSD&lt;/small&gt; took just 23% of the vote, and 80% of Romanians backed a referendum opposing the government’s judicial reforms. A day after this drubbing Mr Dragnea, the architect of laws designed to reduce penalties for corruption that sparked huge protests, was handed a three-and-a-half-year prison sentence for abuse of office. With Mr Dragnea’s career surely over, the opposition will now seek to turf his party from office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Centrists enjoyed modest success elsewhere in central Europe. In &lt;strong&gt;Slovakia&lt;/strong&gt; a coalition backed by Zuzana Caputova, a liberal who won March’s presidential election, came first. Viktor Orban’s Fidesz won half the vote in &lt;strong&gt;Hungary&lt;/strong&gt;, though two small opposition parties did better than expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond &lt;small&gt;MEP&lt;/small&gt;s, &lt;strong&gt;Spaniards &lt;/strong&gt;also chose 12 regional governments and 8,131 mayors. A month after winning a general election, Pedro Sánchez’s Socialists took 33% of the vote in the European election, confirming them as comfortably the largest party. The results were also a relief for Pablo Casado, the new leader of the conservative People’s Party (&lt;small&gt;PP&lt;/small&gt;). After a drubbing in the general election Mr Casado tacked towards the centre, winning 20% and hanging on to Madrid’s regional government. Other parties struggled. Ciudadanos, a centre-right outfit, slid to 12%. The far left and right faded. The two wings of the Catalan separatist movement secured 49% of the vote in the region. But legal troubles may prevent their two &lt;small&gt;MEP&lt;/small&gt;s from taking up their seats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Sánchez still needs to build a parliamentary majority. Albert Rivera, Ciudadanos’s leader, will face pressure to stop his veto of deals with the Socialists in protest at their conciliatory approach to the Catalan problem. Weeks of haggling lie ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;The next to go?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alexis Tsipras, &lt;strong&gt;Greece&lt;/strong&gt;’s prime minister, called a snap election for July after his left-wing Syriza party suffered a crushing defeat at the hands of the centre-right New Democracy (&lt;small&gt;ND&lt;/small&gt;). Nationalist voters punished Syriza for Mr Tsipras’s biggest achievement: resolving a 28-year dispute over the name of Greece’s northern neighbour, now known as North Macedonia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;ND&lt;/small&gt; looks set to win the general election. That will reassure other euro-zone governments worried about Greece sticking to its post-bail-out reform plan, after Syriza embarked on a burst of pre-election spending. But Kyriakos Mitsotakis, &lt;small&gt;ND&lt;/small&gt;’s leader, may struggle to form a coalition. And Mr Tsipras is unlikely to go into docile opposition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Europe&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Winners and losers&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 21:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Papua New Guinea’s prime minister has resigned]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/01/papua-new-guineas-prime-minister-has-resigned]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_asp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;P&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;OLITICAL TRANSITIONS&lt;/small&gt; are rarely plain sailing in Papua New Guinea (&lt;small&gt;PNG&lt;/small&gt;). The country’s prime ministers like to cling to office regardless of mass desertions of their political allies to their opponents’ side. Its parliamentary speakers defy the rules to keep their jobs. Governments sometimes put pressure on the judiciary and office of the governor-general to help them stay in power. So it was in 2011 during the political turmoil that eventually resulted in Peter O’Neill taking over as &lt;small&gt;PNG&lt;/small&gt;’s prime minister. And so it has been again recently, as he has fought to keep his job. Finally, on May 29th, he tendered his resignation to avoid the humiliation of defeat in an impending vote of no-confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While in office Mr O’Neill presided over a boom in the export of minerals. A $19bn project, launched in 2014, involved the extraction of liquid natural gas in the Southern Highlands, a province. It is the biggest ever private-sector investment in &lt;small&gt;PNG&lt;/small&gt;. But Mr O’Neill’s opponents say it has brought little benefit to local people. Paul Flanagan, a former treasury official in &lt;small&gt;PNG&lt;/small&gt;, says the country’s living standards have been falling in the past five years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A no-confidence motion against Mr O’Neill was originally due to take place in February. But he avoided it by declaring a three-month suspension of parliament. In April discontent grew over another natural-gas deal, worth $13bn, with ExxonMobil, Total and Oil Search, a local firm in which the government has a big stake. Some politicians alleged that its terms were too opaque, and appeared to favour the foreign companies. Some of Mr O’Neill’s cabinet colleagues agreed. First the finance minister, James Marape, resigned. Others soon followed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On May 7th Mr O’Neill suspended parliament for another three weeks. When it reconvened it became clear that he could no longer stem the tide. By resigning before the no-confidence motion, Mr O’Neill allowed ministers and pro-government legislators to regroup behind Mr Marape as his replacement. Mr Marape won the resulting election by 101 votes to eight. He is unlikely to push for big changes in policy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Australia may have reason to miss Mr O’Neill. He won much favour there for accepting unwanted seekers of asylum in Australia, many of them from war-afflicted regions, on a remote island. Other countries will wonder how the leadership change in &lt;small&gt;PNG&lt;/small&gt; will affect their interests. Both China and America have been trying to court favour there to strengthen their influence in a region of strategic importance. They have been pouring money into infrastructure. America has pledged to help rebuild a mothballed naval base.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Mr O’Neill’s departure will be little mourned at home. He came to power in 2011 pledging to fight corruption. There has been little progress. His remote, mountainous country remains mired in poverty. Nearly 90% of its 8m citizens live in rural areas. Many of them are subsistence farmers with negligible access to state services. His successor faces a colossal challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Asia&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;A departure unmourned&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 21:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Britain’s constitutional time-bomb]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/30/britains-constitutional-time-bomb]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190601_LDD001_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-30T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;B&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;RITONS PRIDE&lt;/small&gt; themselves on their “unwritten” constitution. America, France and Germany need rules to be set down in black and white. In the Mother of Parliaments democracy has blossomed for over 300 years without coups, revolution or civil war, Irish independence aside. Its politics are governed by an evolving set of traditions, conventions and laws under a sovereign Parliament. Thanks to its stability, Britain convinced the world that its style of government was built on solid foundations laid down over centuries of commonsense adaptation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That view is out of date. The remorseless logic of Brexit has shoved a stick of constitutional dynamite beneath the United Kingdom—and, given the difficulty of constitutional reform in a country at loggerheads, there is little that can be done to defuse it. The chances are high that Britons will soon discover that the constitution they counted on to be adaptable and robust can in fact amplify chaos, division and the threat to the union.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On June 10th, three days after Theresa May steps down as Conservative leader, the race to succeed her will formally begin (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/30/britons-are-ever-more-polarised-between-no-deal-and-a-second-referendum&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;). Some of the runners, including the favourite, Boris Johnson, vow that, unless the European Union gives them what they want (which it won’t), they will pull out of the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; on October 31st without a deal. The 124,000 members of the Conservative Party who will choose the next prime minister, an unrepresentative sample, to put it mildly, will thus take it upon themselves to resolve the question that has split the nation down the middle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Worse, Britain’s supposedly sovereign Parliament has voted against just such a no-deal Brexit on the ground that it would do the country grave harm. There will doubtless be more parliamentary machinations to stop a no-deal Brexit or force one through. The constitution is unclear on whether the executive or Parliament should prevail. It is unclear how to even choose between them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Behind this uncertainty lies the fact that Britain’s constitution is a jumble of contradictions scattered across countless laws, conventions and rules. As our Briefing this week describes, these can easily be amended, by a vote in Parliament or merely on the say-so of the controversial Speaker of the House of Commons—who this week vowed to stay in office in order to ensure that Parliament’s voice is heard. There was a time when most British lawmakers were mindful that playing fast and loose with the rules could undermine democracy. Perhaps that is why they used to practise self-restraint. But in recent decades, when liberal democracy seemed unshakable, Britain’s leaders forgot their caution. Instead, in a fit of absent-mindedness, they set about reinventing the constitution wholesale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under Tony Blair and David Cameron, the Westminster Parliament ceded power to assemblies in Scotland, Wales and Northern Ireland and to the people directly through referendums. These innovations were often well-meant and, in themselves, desirable. But nobody gave much thought to the consequences for the constitution as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The resulting mess has already stamped its mark on Brexit. The referendum endorsed leaving the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; but left the details for later. It provided a mandate for Brexit, but not for any of the very different forms Brexit can take. It is unclear how &lt;small&gt;MP&lt;/small&gt;s should reconcile their duty to honour the referendum with the duty of each one of them to act in the best interests of their constituents. Other countries avoid that mistake. Ireland holds referendums, too. But Article 46 of its constitution is clear: the people vote on a change only after a bill has passed through the Dail with the details nailed down. Britain never thought to be so sensible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brexit is itself sowing the seeds of further constitutional chaos, by threatening the integrity of the union. In the elections for the European Parliament (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/node/21764626&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;), the Scottish National Party (&lt;small&gt;SNP&lt;/small&gt;) won an increased share of the poll. Scotland voted Remain in the referendum, and the &lt;small&gt;SNP&lt;/small&gt;’s leaders can understandably claim that they have just won an enhanced mandate to leave the United Kingdom. Yet, at least one of the Tory leadership candidates is ruling out any further referendums.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Breaking up the union would be a constitutional nightmare—if only because no process for secession is laid down. Merely choosing to hold a second Scottish referendum could be fraught. Mr Johnson is loathed north of the border. Plenty of English voters are calling for a second Brexit referendum. Mrs May told the &lt;small&gt;SNP&lt;/small&gt; to wait until Brexit had been resolved. Legally, could Prime Minister Johnson hold the line against a determined Scottish campaign? It is unclear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The very act of leaving the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; would also load the constitution with fresh doubts. The Charter of Fundamental Rights, which enshrines &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; citizens’ rights in law, would no longer govern British courts. Some would-be Tory leaders, such as Dominic Raab, want to scrap domestic legislation that embeds those rights. If Parliament passed oppressive new laws, the courts might complain, but they could not stop it. Voters who moan about meddling European judges might start to have second thoughts. Cue calls for a British Bill of Rights and another fit of ill-considered constitutional innovation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And that leads to a final worry. Britain’s ramshackle, easily amended constitution is vulnerable to the radicalised politics produced by three years spent rowing about Brexit. Jeremy Corbyn and his colleagues on the hard left could not be clearer about their ambitions to revolutionise Britain. It is naive to think they would focus on the economy and public spending, but leave the rules alone. A Labour government under Mr Corbyn—or, for that matter, a Conservative government led by a populist Tory—would be constrained only by its ability to get its way in Parliament. Labour has already called for a constitutional convention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most Britons seem blithely unaware of the test ahead. Perhaps they believe that their peculiar way of doing things always leads to stability. It is indeed just possible that their constitution’s infinite flexibility will permit a compromise that gets the country through the Brexit badlands. More likely, however, it will feed claims that the other lot are cheats and traitors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brexit has long been a political crisis. Now it looks destined to become a constitutional crisis, too. It is one for which Britain is woefully underprepared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Leaders&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;The next to blow&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 21:39:55 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fragmentation comes to the European Parliament. It might improve it]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/01/fragmentation-comes-to-the-european-parliament-it-might-improve-it]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190601_EUP001_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE MOST&lt;/small&gt; eye-catching political development in Europe recently has been the surge of nationalist populism. The Brexiteers in Britain, Marine Le Pen in France and the Alternative for Germany (&lt;small&gt;A&lt;/small&gt;f&lt;small&gt;D&lt;/small&gt;) have transformed their countries’ political landscape. Italy and Poland are both governed by anti-establishment Eurosceptics. Viktor Orban’s political dominance in Hungary is undermining liberal democracy and enriching the strongman’s friends and cronies. Many European nationalists have borrowed tactics from President Donald Trump. Steve Bannon, Mr Trump’s one-time strategy chief, even toured the continent hoping to turn the five-yearly European Parliament election into a repeat of his ex-boss’s triumph in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The four-day election, the world’s second-largest democratic exercise after the Indian one, concluded on May 26th. Some 214m Europeans cast their ballots. At first glance, the results looked good for the Bannonite tendency. The Northern League of Matteo Salvini, Italy’s deputy prime minister, saw its share of the 751 seats in the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;’s legislature rise from five to 28. The Brexit Party triumphed in Britain to become the largest national party in the new chamber. Ms Le Pen’s National Rally beat Emmanuel Macron’s liberal slate to win in France. A closer look, however, reveals a more mixed pattern. The populist advance in Europe has slowed. Responsibility for that lies not with Mr Bannon, whom few of his hosts took seriously anyway, but with a broader trend: the fragmentation of the European party landscape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The three nationalist groups in the parliament gained seats overall. But their joint share rose only very modestly, from 21% to 23%, far below the one-third predicted. Without Mr Salvini’s Italian triumph they would have lost votes overall, as they did in many member states. Relative to the previous election, in 2014, Ms Le Pen in France, the hard-right Freedom Party in Austria and the nationalist Danish People’s Party all lost ground. So did Eurosceptic parties, taken collectively, in the Netherlands. In Germany the &lt;small&gt;A&lt;/small&gt;f&lt;small&gt;D&lt;/small&gt; only modestly increased its vote share, its disappointed leadership blaming a scandal in neighbouring Austria for the flop. Even in half-way-out Britain the Brexit Party—though seemingly coming from nowhere—was in fact largely cannibalising the old United Kingdom Independence Party’s vote. It is led by Nigel Farage, &lt;small&gt;UKIP&lt;/small&gt;’s former leader.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The big losers, it is true, were the two groups or families that have long dominated the European Parliament and European politics more widely: the centre-right European People’s Party (&lt;small&gt;EPP&lt;/small&gt;) and the centre-left Socialists and Democrats (&lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;small&gt;D&lt;/small&gt;). The seat tally of the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;’s unofficial “grand coalition” fell from 412 seats last time (55%) to 332 seats (44%). But it ceded these seats primarily to liberals and greens, who together gained 57 seats, or eight percentage points of the total. This shift occurred particularly in western Europe—with Mr Macron’s “Renaissance” list entering the parliament with 21 seats and Germany’s Greens doubling their share, to 21. But there were also traces of it in supposedly reactionary central Europe. In Slovakia and Romania pro-European, anti-corruption forces came first and second respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fragmentation follows the pattern of recent national elections. The decline of big-tent parties and the rise of smaller rivals have made forming governments harder. Take Spain, where a two-party system has become a five-party one and decades of stable government have given way to a spate of wobbly, short-lived governments that have struggled to pass important laws. Yet the picture at a European level is not nearly so gloomy. The European Parliament’s problem has never been its inability to marshal deals and coalitions. No party alone has ever held a majority there, and yet the assembly passes about 90% of the legislation it considers in a process of “codecision” with national governments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;An end to squishy consensus&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;What the parliament has lacked is a visible political contest. But for the first time in the four-decade history of elections to the European Parliament, turnout has risen; from 43% in 2014 to 51%. This may be explained by a combination of factors. The election of Mr Trump, no fan of the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;, and the Brexit vote have both reminded voters of the union’s vulnerability. New challenges that cross national borders, such as migration and economic disruption, have emphasised the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;’s role. Support for the union has risen and even Eurosceptic parties talk less about leaving and more about change from within. Personalities like Mr Macron, Mr Orban and Mr Salvini—and activists such as Greta Thunberg, whose youth climate strikes have swept European cities—have become &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;-wide political figures. The result is a more plural, varied legislature resting on a foundation of higher public engagement with the union.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190601_EUC141.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190601_EUC141.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190601_EUC141.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190601_EUC141.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190601_EUC141.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190601_EUC141.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190601_EUC141.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190601_EUC141.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190601_EUC141.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190601_EUC141.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In practice, three formations are possible in the new parliament. The first two are expanded grand coalitions. With either the greens or the liberals, the old &lt;small&gt;EPP&lt;/small&gt;-s&amp;amp;&lt;small&gt;D&lt;/small&gt; alliance would still wield a majority. But that would leave them vulnerable to rebellions, so a “super-grand coalition” could instead include all four parties for a solid majority of 131. Such an alliance would probably be necessary to push through big votes such as that on the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;’s next seven-year budget. But it would contain a vast ideological spectrum, ranging from quasi-Marxists on the left edge of the green bloc to hardened nationalists like Mr Orban (for now, though he may soon quit or face expulsion) on the right edge of the &lt;small&gt;EPP&lt;/small&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So yet other permutations may be needed to pass some of the legislation to come in the next European parliamentary period, which could include contentious measures like budget reforms, new common border controls, a convergence of minimum wages and a carbon tax. The &lt;small&gt;EPP&lt;/small&gt; might rely sometimes on some of the saner right-wing nationalists to forge majorities on certain economic issues where the centre-left disagrees. The &lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;small&gt;D&lt;/small&gt; might rely on the hard-left to pass social and environmental measures that lack the &lt;small&gt;EPP&lt;/small&gt;’s wholehearted support. The liberal group’s stance will probably decide a lot of measures. The anti-establishment right by contrast may be able to organise blocking minorities on certain matters—especially if Mr Salvini is able to forge a single dominant nationalist group—but it is divided and lacks the numbers to set the agenda on its own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first big test of the new arithmetic will be the parliament’s vote on the European Commission president. The candidate for the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;’s biggest job is nominated by national leaders but must secure the backing of a majority of the parliament—a first test of a super-grand coalition. It will also pit the union’s emerging left-liberal bloc, gathered around Mr Macron, against a conservative one grouped around Mrs Merkel (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/30/the-race-for-the-eus-big-jobs-gets-under-way&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;). With the decline of the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;’s two big duopolies, the Franco-German alliance and the &lt;small&gt;EPP&lt;/small&gt;-&lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;small&gt;D&lt;/small&gt; majority in the parliament, this will be a first taste of the case-by-case deals and stark political differences that are bound to become more important. The European election had been billed in some quarters as a nationalist blow to the ideal of a Europe-wide politics. Instead it may come to represent the invigoration of that ideal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Europe&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;All the colours of the rainbow&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 20:40:23 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[When picking leaders, the EU should put skill before box-ticking]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/01/when-picking-leaders-the-eu-should-put-skill-before-box-ticking]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190601_LDP002_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;S&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;EEN FROM&lt;/small&gt; afar, Europe is shrinking and ineffective. In Germany Angela Merkel’s chancellorship is winding down. Domestic woes bedevil the French president, Emmanuel Macron. Britain is leaving the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;, which is divided between east and west, north and south, liberals and authoritarians. The big centre-right and centre-left blocks are struggling, as politics fragments across the continent. If America or China wants to speak to Europe, it is less clear than ever whom they should call.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The European Parliament elections have brought yet more fragmentation, with the two main groups losing seats and their joint majority in the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;’s legislature (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/01/fragmentation-comes-to-the-european-parliament-it-might-improve-it&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;). Liberals, Greens and right-wing populists gained. The union today resembles a patchwork of ideological and regional tendencies. That makes the task of parcelling out its big jobs extra-fiddly. There are four vacancies: the presidencies of the European Commission (the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;’s executive), the European Council (its senate-like body of national leaders) and the European Central Bank (&lt;small&gt;ECB&lt;/small&gt;) as well as the “high representative” for the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;’s foreign and security policy. A convention of 2014 says the commission job should go to the “lead candidate” of the largest group in the parliament. Under an older precedent, those appointed to the top positions are meant to include representatives of all corners of the continent and of the big political families. Different permutations are lined up until, like a Rubik’s cube, everything slots into place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A more complex political landscape puts both of these conventions in doubt. The top lot in the parliament is now, as before, the European People’s Party (&lt;small&gt;EPP&lt;/small&gt;), a group consisting mainly of Christian Democrat parties. But the &lt;small&gt;EPP&lt;/small&gt; won only 24% of the seats, which hardly justifies an exclusive claim to lead the commission. And the Rubik’s routine cannot hope to capture the variety of political families and regional patterns in today’s Europe. Even if a token southerner were appointed, for example, the difference between a candidate from pro-European Spain and one from Eurosceptic Italy might be vast. If Christian Democrats, Social Democrats and Liberals all get to run things, the only slightly smaller Greens will understandably object. The cube has too many dimensions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps that is just as well. For now, more than ever, Europe’s leaders should be concentrating instead on getting the right people for the job. President Donald Trump has questioned the transatlantic alliance, tariff wars threaten Europe’s prosperity, turmoil on its borders challenges its security, digital giants from China and America are dwarfing its firms, and economic storm-clouds are once again gathering above the euro zone. Leading a more fragmented Europe through these difficulties—let alone reasserting its interests and relevance in the world—will require seasoned leadership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; may not get it. Manfred Weber, the &lt;small&gt;EPP&lt;/small&gt;’s candidate for the commission, has no executive experience and, judging by his association with Hungary’s authoritarian government, poor judgment. If he falls short, leaders may offer the &lt;small&gt;ECB&lt;/small&gt; presidency to another German, Jens Weidmann, a banker with über-hawkish views, to ensure that a German gets at least one of the top jobs. But that should not be a given. In a more meritocratic &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; the commission presidency might go to Margrethe Vestager, the dynamic (Danish) competition commissioner. Antonio Costa of Portugal, Leo Varadkar of Ireland or even Mrs Merkel, all skilled compromise-brokers, might lead the council. At the &lt;small&gt;ECB&lt;/small&gt;, a moderate like Finland’s Olli Rehn would be better than Mr Weidmann.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;True meritocracy is improbable, alas. National egos and power politics will always require some horse-trading. But as much as possible, the &lt;small&gt;EU &lt;/small&gt;should focus on substance. From the euro-zone and migration crises to the Brexit vote, the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; has had several brushes with mortality in recent years. More are doubtless to come. Its big jobs matter. Placeholders should not apply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Leaders&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Buggins belongs at the back&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 20:40:22 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why “Everybody Wants To Rule The World”, a cold-war anthem, endures]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/30/why-everybody-wants-to-rule-the-world-a-cold-war-anthem-endures]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_BKP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-30T12:29:28Z&quot;&gt;May 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT WAS a febrile year. In 1985 Ronald Reagan was sworn in as president for a second term, Margaret Thatcher entered the sixth year of her premiership and Mikhail Gorbachev took over as general secretary of the Communist Party, pledging to “do everything for our Soviet motherland to become still more rich and powerful”. There were nuclear tests and riots. Mobile-phone networks were set up, the first Nintendo home video-game consoles were launched and “Rocky IV” dominated the American box office. In the midst of all this, Tears For Fears released “Everybody Wants To Rule The World”, a jarringly cheery song about freedom, pleasure and “a lack of vision”. The tune bore some hallmarks of its era, particularly in its embrace of synth melodies and allusions to geopolitical struggles. It briefly reached the top spot on the &lt;em&gt;Billboard&lt;/em&gt; charts that summer—and the composition’s power continues to be felt. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Roland Orzabal, the band’s singer, guitarist and chief songwriter, says that he had specific crises in mind when he wrote the lyrics to his New Wave hit. He initially thought the song’s title would be “Everybody Wants To Go To War” in order to make a statement about the posturing between America and the USSR. “You still had a threat of nuclear war then,” he recalls of those cold-war tensions. “It was Russia versus America but in a very different way than the [release of] emails and underhanded methods now.” Mr Orzabal believed the song to be more cynical than hopeful, and less complex than the material he had composed for “The Hurting”, the band’s debut album that was released in 1983. He almost gave up on it, he says, but persevered at his wife’s insistence. The concept expanded, making references to clashing superpowers in the refrain but also what Mr Orzabal calls “personal dictators, like the man at work who may be dictating everything you do”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the words are general enough to speak to the anxieties of every age, and a perennial sense that “there’s no turning back”. That may help to explain why the song has been covered so many times. In recent years artists including Giorgio Moroder, Nas, Ted Yoder, Diane Birch, Trevor Horn and Robbie Williams have released versions of their own. In 2013 Lorde recorded a slow, dirge-like cover for the soundtrack of “The Hunger Games”, a dystopian film franchise. (Mr Orzabal says he listened to Lorde’s recording and thought: “Oh my God, so that’s what I was talking about. It is dark.”) This year Weezer recorded a cover for their latest, self-titled, album, and performed it live at the Coachella Music Festival with Mr Orzabal and Curt Smith, Tears For Fears’s bassist and co-founder, who sings lead vocals on the song.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Critics have grappled with the meaning and effect of these tributes, but the hit’s euphoric qualities are hard to capture in words. On Spotify, Tears For Fears’s original recording remains the most popular version, recently surpassing 250m plays. Ms Birch, who was a toddler when the song was released in 1985 but discovered it anew as a teenager, says that the emotional effect of the music is instantaneous: “When you hear the opening synth and the driving bass line, it immediately puts you in the feeling and transcends genres and time.” Gil Weinberg, a professor of musical technology at Georgia Tech, has studied the song’s structure. He identifies the track’s “tension-building chord progression and uncommon melody” as key to its appeal, but as well as that, he thinks that it has an indefinable quality that challenges other artists to replicate it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In many ways “Everybody Wants To Rule The World” resonates as loudly today as it did when it was first released. “One headline, why believe it?” could refer to fake news. Listeners are reminded that “nothing ever lasts forever” as Britain’s ties with the European Union fray (indeed, those following the Brexit negotiations likely “can’t stand this indecision” either). The line about turning “your back on mother nature” is pertinent as awareness of the climate crisis spreads. A new rivalry, between America and China, is taking hold. The juxtaposition of the foreboding verses and the sparkling instrumentation creates something rare and gripping, and it is hard to tire of the tenor vocals, high-life guitar riffs and keyboard flourishes. As the song’s enduring popularity attests, Tears For Fears certainly did not suffer from a lack of vision. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 20:40:21 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Facebook’s planned new currency may be based on a blockchain]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/30/facebooks-planned-new-currency-may-be-based-on-a-blockchain]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_fnd002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-30T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE EXCITEMENT&lt;/small&gt; among crypto-buffs is palpable. Facebook, the world’s largest social network, appears to be planning to launch a digital coin early next year. But they should not get their hopes up too high. If the firm does indeed launch what is being dubbed &lt;small&gt;FB&lt;/small&gt; Coin, GlobalCoin or Libra, it will be a tame sort of cryptocurrency—more Bitcoin 0.5 than 2.0.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook has declined to comment on the speculation, but is clearly up to something. Last year it put a highly regarded senior executive, David Marcus, in charge of a new team exploring “ways to leverage the power of blockchain technology”, which underlies cryptocurrencies. In April Mark Zuckerberg, Facebook’s boss, said at its annual shindig for developers that it “should be as easy to send money to someone as it is to send a photo”. It seems to be talking to potential partners, such as credit-card issuers and merchants, and financial regulators, such as Mark Carney, the governor of the Bank of England.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In America Facebook’s Messenger app already allows peer-to-peer transfers, but only in existing currencies and between accounts linked to bank-issued payment cards. But the new blockchain-based money would be a currency on its own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reasons abound why Facebook might want to take this step. It has to pull even with other big global apps that already offer easy payment features, such as WeChat in China. A digital coin would work in developing countries, where many people are unbanked and remittances from abroad are large (India is rumoured to be among the first countries where it will be available). If it is used for commerce, not just peer-to-peer payments, Facebook could take part of the fee that now goes to card-issuers, and charge more for ads, since buying the products touted would be quicker and simpler. It could move into services such as tipping, for which other payment systems are too pricey (at the Facebook do Mr Zuckerberg demonstrated how users could send content-creators some digital change). Data on payments would help make up for what the firm will lose in its planned “pivot to privacy”, which includes steps such as allowing users to communicate on encrypted channels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But despite the crypto-buzz, the new currency is unlikely to be a close relative of Bitcoin, says Lex Sokolin, a fintech analyst—that is, a decentralised system with no one in charge. Facebook will want to be in control to gather data, simplify administration and avoid the currency being targeted by speculators such as hedge funds. It will be a “stablecoin”, backed by established currencies such as the dollar to avoid the volatility that has bedevilled Bitcoin (which is heading back towards $9,000 after falling to little more than $3,000 last year). Regulators, fearing money-laundering or other criminal activity (as happens with Bitcoin), will surely set strict rules, perhaps capping transfers and policing their flow across borders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook is well-placed to make a go of the venture, according to Ben Thompson of Stratechery, a widely read newsletter on the tech industry. Its services now boast a total of 2.4bn monthly users. It could entice merchants with discounts if they use the new coin to buy ads, and users by paying them in it for viewing those ads—or perhaps, which would be a giant step for Facebook, even for providing data about themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet it will not have the field to itself. Similar coins already exist. Signal and Telegram, two messaging apps, are also planning digital cash. Moreover, payment cards are ubiquitous in the rich world, and easy to use online. And then there is the question of whether, for all its reach, a FaceCoin would really be welcome. Should a firm that has shown a cavalier attitude towards users’ data be trusted to deal with their money?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Finance and economics&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;FaceCoin&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 20:40:20 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>