<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Can Sara Gideon dislodge Susan Collins?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/26/can-sara-gideon-dislodge-susan-collins]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_USP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-26T19:32:28Z&quot;&gt;Jun 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUSAN COLLINS has worked hard during her four terms in the Senate for Maine to cultivate a reputation as a moderate, independently-minded Republican. The last remaining Republican in Congress from New England, once a Republican redoubt, she was among the first Republican senators to back gay marriage. In 2016 she opposed the nomination of Donald Trump. A year later, she was one of three rebel senators to sink a bill that would have killed Obamacare. And she is one of only two Republican senators who publicly support abortion rights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But maintaining her hard-won image is likely to get tougher for Ms Collins. She is only one of two Republican senators up for re-election next year in a state won by Hillary Clinton in 2016. Ousting her is critical to the Democrats’ hopes of talking the Senate. This week Ms Collins was duly presented with a formidable challenger. Sara Gideon (pictured), the Democratic speaker of Maine’s House, made it clear she would seek to undermine Ms Collins’s claim to independence and moderation by highlighting the number of times she had supported Mr Trump’s agenda.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Susan Collins has been in the Senate for 22 years,” said Ms Gideon, who has served in Maine’s legislature since 2012, in her launch video. “And at one point, maybe she was different than some of the other folks in Washington, but she doesn’t seem that way anymore.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the video, Ms Gideon highlighted Ms Collins’s vote for the Republican tax bill, alongside footage of Mr Trump warmly thanking the senator. She also—in what is already emerging as her mostly powerful line of attack—highlighted Ms Collins’s support for Mr Trump’s conservative Supreme Court picks. Last year, during tumultuous confirmation hearings for Brett Kavanaugh, who had been accused of sexually assaulting a woman as a teenager, Ms Collins appeared to be mulling a vote against him. To the fury of Democrats and women’s rights activists, Ms Collins nonetheless voted for Justice Kavanaugh and stoutly defended him in a 30-minute speech on the Senate floor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since then the anger over Ms Collins’s support for Justice Kavanaugh has focused on a different issue: abortion. Though he has not yet voted in any significant way to curtail abortion rights, Justice Kavanaugh has expressed strongly pro-life views. So has Justice Neil Gorsuch, Mr Trump’s earlier pick, whose nomination Ms Collins also supported. At a time when political hostilities over &lt;em&gt;Roe v Wade&lt;/em&gt;, the 1973 Supreme Court ruling that declared abortion a constitutional right, are more intense than ever, upholders of abortion rights worry about how both justices will vote in abortion-related cases that come before America’s highest court.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Gideon is well placed to exploit such concerns. Earlier this month, Janet Mills, Maine’s Democratic governor, signed a bill Ms Gideon had sponsored allowing health workers other than doctors to perform abortions. That will allow Ms Gideon, who has focused on access to health care as a state representative, to portray herself as a champion of the rights she claims Ms Collins has imperiled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In her video, she says that Ms Collin’s support for Justice Kavanaugh “may be paying off for her, but it’s put women’s control over their own health-care decisions in extreme jeopardy.” That is a reference to a surge in fundraising for Ms Collins that followed her vote for Justice Kavanaugh. Ms Gideon did not mention the fact that Ms Collins’s vote also sparked a successful crowdfunding campaign for whichever Democrat ends up running against Ms Collins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of this is an indication of the potency of abortion as an electoral issue. Another sign of that came this week when both NARAL Pro-Choice America, a leading abortion rights group, and Emily’s List, which promotes the candidacy of pro-choice women, both endorsed Ms Gideon. NARAL Pro-Choice America once endorsed Ms Collins; it campaigned against her after she voted for Justice Kavanaugh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before she takes on Ms Collins, Ms Gideon must see off two lesser known candidates in a Democratic primary next June: Betsy Collins, who lost the Democratic primary for governor last year, and Bre Kidman, a lawyer. She is likely to beat them both for two reasons. Firstly, unlike them, she has legislative experience. More importantly, Ms Gideon will be supported by the national Democratic machine: the Democratic Senatorial Campaign Committee has already endorsed her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 04:40:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Confessions of an accidental doom-monger]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/26/confessions-of-an-accidental-doom-monger]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_wbd000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-26T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT IS ONE of the most widely quoted statistics of recent years. No report or conference presentation on the future of work is complete without it. Think-tanks, consultancies, government agencies and news outlets have pointed to it as evidence of an imminent jobs apocalypse. The finding—that 47% of American jobs are at high risk of automation by the mid-2030s—comes from a paper published in 2013 by two Oxford academics, Carl Benedikt Frey and Michael Osborne. It has since been cited in more than 4,000 other academic articles. Meet Mr Frey, a Swedish economic historian, in person, however, and he seems no prophet of doom. Indeed, Mr 47% turns out not to be gloomy at all. “Lots of people actually think I believe that half of all jobs are going to be automated in a decade or two,” he says, leaving half the population unemployed. That is, Mr Frey stresses, “definitely not what the paper says”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what does it say? Its authors modelled the characteristics of 702 occupations and classified them according to their “susceptibility to computerisation”. This classification was, ironically, itself automated—using a machine-learning system built by Mr Osborne, which was trained using 70 hand-labelled examples. After crunching the numbers, the model concluded that occupations accounting for 47% of current American jobs (including those in office administration, sales and various service industries) fell into the “high risk” category. But, the paper goes on, this simply means that, compared with other professions, they are the most vulnerable to automation. “We make no attempt to estimate how many jobs will actually be automated,” the authors write. That, they underscore, will depend on many other things, such as cost, regulatory concerns, political pressure and social resistance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The paper was intended for an academic audience, says Mr Frey, and got “more attention than we would ever have expected”. Chinese whispers and exaggerated headlines meant the carefully caveated, theoretical and highly unlikely upper bound of 47% came to be seen by some as a firm prediction—sometimes even a target. In April striking dockworkers in Los Angeles carried placards that read “47% of American jobs are planned to be automated by 2034”. Needless to say, they are not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such misperceptions, irksome as they are to Mr Frey, are also telling. For, he says, they reflect the polarised nature of the debate about the nature of automation and the future of jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At one extreme are the doom-mongers. They warn of mass technological joblessness just around the corner. One advocate of this position, Martin Ford, has written two bestselling books on the dangers of automation. Mr Ford worries that middle-class jobs will vanish, economic mobility will cease and a wealthy plutocracy could “shut itself away in gated communities or in elite cities, perhaps guarded by autonomous military robots and drones”. The unemployed masses will subsist on a universal basic income. At the sanguine end of the spectrum, classical economists argue that in the past new technology has always ended up creating more jobs than it destroyed. Everything will work out fine in the long run, these optimists reckon, though the short term is likely to be bumpy, as it was during the Industrial Revolution, unless governments take action to smooth the transition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Frey is often assumed to be in the first camp. So plenty of people are stunned to discover that he is, in fact, closer to the second. He has now laid out his position in more detail in a new book, “The Technology Trap”. This has allowed him, he says, to put the 47% figure in “the right context”. That context is largely historical. Building on his original paper, he revisits the history of industrialisation and asks what lessons it provides today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One is that new technologies take time to produce productivity and wage gains. It was several decades before industrialisation led to significantly higher wages for British workers in the early 1800s, a delay known as Engels’s pause, after the theorist of communism who observed it. Another lesson is that, even though it eventually increases the overall size of the economic pie, automation is also likely to boost inequality in the short run, by pushing some people into lower-paid jobs. Mr Frey is concerned that automation will leave many people worse off in the short term, leading to unrest and opposition, which could in turn slow the pace of automation and productivity growth. Everyone would then be worse off in the long run. This is the titular “technology trap”. Whereas many people assume he worries about a world with too many robots, Mr Frey is in reality more concerned about a future with too few.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To avoid the trap, Mr Frey argues, today’s policymakers should take advantage of the fact that this time around it is possible to see how things might play out, and manage the transition accordingly. In particular that means making greater use of wage insurance, to compensate workers who have to move to jobs with a lower salary; reforming education systems to boost early-childhood education and support retraining and lifelong learning; extending income tax credit to improve incentives to work and reduce inequality; removing regulations that hinder job-switching; providing “mobility vouchers” to subsidise relocation as the distribution of jobs changes; and changing zoning rules to allow more people to live in the cities where jobs are being created.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Boom or gloom&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;These are all sensible suggestions. Will anyone pay attention? Messrs Frey and Osborne had an unexpected smash hit with their study. But the bestselling books on artificial intelligence, robots and automation are the bleak ones, like Mr Ford’s. In part that is because fear sells, particularly if stoked by misunderstanding, whereas pragmatic expositions of policy proposals do not—or not nearly as well. “The Technology Trap” may well ensnare doom-seekers’ attention with its ominous-sounding title. But it should ultimately hearten anyone who reads it. Provided, that is, they read it more carefully than they read Mr Frey’s earlier work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 04:40:18 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Where female footballers are more popular than male ones]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/06/26/where-female-footballers-are-more-popular-than-male-ones]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_usp002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-26T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EXCITED FANS in bald eagle baseball caps watched as the United States’ women’s football team beat Spain to progress to the quarter-finals of the World Cup on June 24th. This was no shock upset. The Stars and Stripes are the most successful side in the history of women’s football, having won the World Cup three times and Olympic gold four. This year they romped through the group stages with an aggregate score of 18-0, a total inflated by their record-breaking 13-0 drubbing of lowly Thailand. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This on-pitch success, however, is marred by controversy in court. The members of the United States women’s team marked International Women’s Day on March 8th by filing a class-action suit against their employer, the United States Soccer Federation (USSF). The suit alleged that differences in pay and employment conditions between the women’s and men’s team violate the Equal Pay Act and Title VII of the Civil Rights Act. Despite engaging in “substantially equal work”, the women’s team is paid considerably less. If each team were to play 20 friendlies over the course of a year and win them all, the women would receive $99,000 whereas the men would net $263,320, according to the filing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is common for female athletes to be paid less than men. The combined salaries of the 1,693 women playing in the top seven football leagues add up to $41.6m, just slightly less than the $41.7m salary paid to Neymar, a Brazilian forward, by Paris Saint-Germain. But football in America is unusual because the women’s team is paid less than the men, despite more people tuning in to watch them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such pay differences are permissible if the employer can prove that one of four “affirmative defences” apply: a seniority system, a merit system, a pay system based on quantity or quality of output or any other factor apart from sex. The burden of proof is on the USSF to prove that the disparity can be legitimately explained by one of these four. The federation has attributed the discrepancy to “differences in the aggregate revenue generated by the different teams and/or any other factor other than sex.” The success of the lawsuit depends on whether this is true.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;em&gt;Wall Street Journal&lt;/em&gt; investigation into audited financial reports from the USSF published suggests that it is not. Between 2016 and 2018 women’s games generated about $50.8m in revenue. The men took in about $49.9m. That alone is not enough to settle the case. This money came mostly from ticket sales, but that is not the only source of revenue attributable to the national teams. Much of it comes from broadcast rights and sponsorship deals. As these are bundled together, it is difficult to assess how much ought to be attributed to each team. It is, however, hard to believe that the men’s team, whose best result has been third place in the 1930 World Cup and who failed to qualify last time round, is such a sought-after commodity as to justify the pay disparity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having qualified for the knockout stages of the World Cup, the 28 female players agreed to pursue mediation once the tournament ends. This is unlikely to resolve the matter. Legal disputes over equal pay have been going on since five players filed a complaint with the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission in March 2016. This has been subsumed by the class-action suit. A previous effort at mediation fell apart in March. The US women’s team is now two matches away from the final at the Parc Olympique Lyonnais. Whether they make it there will be decided on the pitch. How they are compensated for their efforts is likely to be decided in court. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 03:40:21 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A former beauty queen accuses Gambia’s former dictator of rape]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/26/a-former-beauty-queen-accuses-gambias-former-dictator-of-rape]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_map504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-26T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHEN FATOU JALLOW was crowned as Gambia’s beauty queen in 2014, it was one of the happiest days of her life. But it was the prelude to a nightmare. Soon afterwards Yahya Jammeh, then the country’s dictator, asked the 18-year-old to marry him. Ms Jallow refused, but Mr Jammeh’s aides kept calling. After accepting an invitation to his home to attend a religious event, Ms Jallow says she was drugged and raped by Mr Jammeh. “He asked me what made me think that I could deny him,” she recalls. “I kept screaming and he kept telling me no one could hear me.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ms Jallow’s torment was far from an isolated case. Human Rights Watch and trial International, watchdogs based in New York and Geneva respectively, have detailed other allegations of sexual abuse by Mr Jammeh and his aides. Their report, released today, includes accounts from two other women who allege that the former dictator sexually abused them. A spokesman for Mr Jammeh’s party denied the allegations in a written statement to the BBC. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Mr Jammeh, who had seized power in a coup in 1994, was ousted in early 2017. But public anger against him lives on, stoked by a stream of new revelations about the horrors of his rule. Many have emerged in testimony before a Truth, Reparations and Reconciliation Commission established by Gambia’s new president, Adama Barrow, to investigate the old regime’s crimes and recommend prosecutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Jammeh’s henchmen killed and tortured thousands. Journalists and activists disappeared in the night, and families often never saw the victims’ bodies again. Dissidents were thrown into an airless dungeon known as the “crocodile hole” beneath the headquarters of Mr Jammeh’s intelligence agency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The longer he ruled, the more erratic he became. His men once detained and drugged an estimated 1,000 villagers with a powerful hallucinogen because he thought that witchcraft was responsible for the death of a family member. He also claimed to be able to cure hiv with his bare hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a poor country of about 2m people, he allegedly stole energetically. When he fled into exile in Equatorial Guinea he did so in his Rolls-Royce, leaving the state’s coffers empty. Campaigners are pressing Equatorial Guinea’s president, Teodoro Obiang, to hand him over for trial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reed Brody, an American lawyer working with Human Rights Watch, notes that many of Mr Jammeh’s victims came from other west African countries, including Ghana and Ivory Coast. These included 56 migrants who were massacred in 2005 by his men. Mr Brody thinks that the latest rape allegations will add pressure. “It’s going to be harder and harder for Obiang to keep protecting Jammeh,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Jallow managed to escape from Gambia and now lives in Canada, where she is studying social care. Talking about what happened “is my duty to other girls”, she says. “I am willing to open the gate and make sure that this man will one day face justice. I want to send a message to men in our society, that we’re not property, that we’re not goats.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 03:40:20 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Corporate America is growing more dissatisfied with Donald Trump]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/26/corporate-america-is-growing-more-dissatisfied-with-donald-trump]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_woc955.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-26T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;DONALD TRUMP ran as a CEO president, whose shrewd business skills would jump-start the American economy. After his victory, corporate bosses clamoured to donate to his inauguration; others joined his advisory boards. Their enthusiasm has since waned. The 50-odd business leaders recruited to advise the president quit just seven months into his term. Many of the bosses that once filled his cabinet, including Rex Tillerson of ExxonMobil and Gary Cohn of Goldman Sachs, have quit or been fired. The president’s Twitter feed is littered with insults against corporate titans who have crossed him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complaints about the president and his policies from America’s boardrooms are growing ever more frequent. An analysis of earnings-call transcripts by &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; suggests that executives of publicly traded companies are discussing Mr Trump’s tariffs in about 15% of their calls, up from 5% a year ago. Mentions of the president’s trade war, which began to appear early last year, have also risen (see chart). Although some of these mentions come from bosses who are hopeful that the Trump administration’s policies will eventually yield benefits, the vast majority are critical.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Firms are particularly worried about Mr Trump’s protectionist policies. “We’re concerned about tariffs because they lead to higher prices on everyday products for American families,” said Brian Cornell, the boss of Target, a big retail chain, during the company’s latest earnings call. “We pay a lot of tariffs,” said John Olin, Harley-Davidson’s chief financial officer, in a call on April 23rd. The motorcycle-maker reckons it will pay $100m in duties in 2019. “If the tariffs go away, that’s a pretty significant reduction in headwinds,” said James Loree, the boss of Stanley Black &amp;amp; Decker. Tariffs cost the toolmaker $100m last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Executives say they are negotiating lower prices with foreign suppliers and rejigging supply chains to avoid getting hit with tariffs. But so far, according to a study published last month by the IMF, Americans are paying the bulk of the costs. The IMF found that, despite the president’s claims that China is footing the bill, the costs of Mr Trump’s tariffs on Chinese goods are being borne “almost entirely” by American importers. Fresh rounds of tariff increases will be even harder for American buyers to escape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump is scheduled to meet Xi Jinping, China’s president, this weekend at the G20 summit in Japan, where trade negotiators from both sides are hoping to hash out a deal. Early signs are not promising. In an interview with Fox Business Network on Wednesday Mr Trump threatened to slap tariffs on another $325bn-worth of Chinese goods—covering nearly all the country’s remaining exports to the United States—if the two sides did not reach a deal. America’s most powerful business leaders are talking. Their president may not be listening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 03:40:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China hopes to beat America&#x27;s armed forces by copying them]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/china/2019/06/26/china-hopes-to-beat-americas-armed-forces-by-copying-them]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_cnp001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-26T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;OVER THE PAST decade, the People’s Liberation Army (PLA) has been lavished with money and weaponry. Chinese military spending rose by 83% between 2009 and 2018, by far the largest growth spurt of any big country. This splurge has enabled China to deploy precision missiles and anti-satellite weapons that challenge America’s supremacy in the western Pacific. China’s leader, Xi Jinping, says his “Chinese dream” includes a “dream of a strong armed forces”. That, he says, involves “modernising” the PLA by 2035 and making it “world-class”—in other words, America-beating—by mid-century. He has been making considerable progress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organisational reforms may be less eye-catching than missiles that fly at Mach 5, unmanned cargo planes and electromagnetically powered superguns (all of which China has tested in the past year). Yet Mr Xi has realised that there is little point in grafting fancy weapons onto an old-fashioned force. During the cold war the PLA evolved to repel the Soviet Union and America in big land wars on Chinese soil. Massed infantry would grind down the enemy in attritional battles. In the 1990s Chinese leaders, alarmed by American prowess in the Gulf war of 1991, decided to focus on enhancing the PLA’s ability to fight “local wars under high-technology conditions”. They were thinking of short, sharp conflicts on China’s periphery, such as over Taiwan, in which air and naval power would be as important as ground forces. Mr Xi decided that winning such wars required changing the armed forces’ structure. He has done more in the past three years to reform the PLA than any leader since Deng Xiaoping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Xi’s principal aim is to increase “jointness”. This term, borrowed from Western military jargon, refers to the ability of different services—army, navy and air force—to co-operate on the battlefield quickly and seamlessly. Jointness is especially important for fighting wars that break out abroad. It can be difficult for commanders at national headquarters to choreograph soldiers, sailors and pilots from a great distance. The different services must be able to work together without instruction from on high.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China’s model is the United States, which—under the Goldwater-Nichols Act of 1986—drastically reformed its own armed forces in order to achieve this goal. The Pentagon carved up the globe into “combatant commands”. No longer would services squabble among themselves. All soldiers, sailors and pilots in a given area, such as the Persian Gulf or the Pacific, would take orders from a single officer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; Mr Xi has followed suit. Before his reforms, army and navy commanders in the country’s seven military regions would report to their respective service headquarters, with little or no co-ordination. In February 2016 Mr Xi replaced the regions with five “theatres”, each under a single commander (see map). The eastern one based in Nanjing would prepare for war with Taiwan and Japan, for instance. The sprawling western theatre, in Chengdu, would handle India. The southern one in Guangzhou would manage the South China Sea.&lt;p&gt;As well as these geographic commands, two others were formed in 2015, each aimed at an American vulnerability. American forces depend on communications via satellites, computer networks and other high-tech channels. So Mr Xi created a new Strategic Support Force to target these systems. It directs space, cyber, electronic and psychological warfare. In 2018 it conducted exercises against five PLA units in what the Pentagon called a “a complex electronic warfare environment”. American military power in Asia also depends on a network of bases and aircraft carriers. Mr Xi took aim at these by establishing a new service called the PLA Rocket Force—an upgrade of what was previously known less rousingly as the Second Artillery Corps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He has also been trimming the armed forces’ bloated ranks, though they remain over 2m-strong. Since 2015 the PLA has shed 300,000 men, most of them from the land forces, which have lost one-third of their commissioned officers and shrunk from 70% of the PLA’s total strength to less than half (though happily the army has kept its dance troupes, which it had been told it would lose). By contrast, the marines are tripling in size. Navy and air-force officers have gained more powerful posts, including leadership of two theatre commands. This reflects the PLA’s tilt towards the seas—and the skies above them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is hard to tell whether the new PLA is more proficient on the battlefield. China has not fought a war in four decades. The last Chinese soldiers with experience of a large-scale conflict—a war with Vietnam in 1979—will retire shortly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there is evidence that the PLA is getting better at jointness. Some of China’s growing number of forays beyond its borders, notably bomber flights around Taiwan and over the South China Sea, indicate increasing co-ordination between air and naval forces. “We see a lot of joint exercises to work out kinks in the system and get the services used to working with each other,” says Phillip Saunders of the National Defence University in Washington. Chinese war games were once highly scripted affairs. Now officers are assessed on the realism of their training, says Meia Nouwens of the International Institute for Strategic Studies in London. Before Mr Xi’s reforms the “blue team”, which simulates an adversary, would always ritually lose large-scale annual exercises known as “Stride” in Inner Mongolia. Now they usually win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But China’s troops may still be ill-prepared for complex warfare. In America promotions depend on officers’ ability to work with other services. Their Chinese counterparts often spend their entire careers in one service, in one region and even doing the same job. Political culture is another problem. “The structures that China is trying to emulate are based on openness, on delegation of authority and collaboration,” notes Admiral Scott Swift of MIT, who retired last year as commander of America’s Pacific Fleet. He says modern warfare requires decentralised decision-making because cyber and electronic warfare can sever communications between commanders and units. “Militaries that are founded on democratic principles are going to be much more adept at adapting to that environment,” Admiral Swift suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Xi is an authoritarian who strives for centralised control. His predecessor, Hu Jintao, did not have a tight grip on the PLA, says Mr Saunders. That is because Mr Hu’s own predecessor, Jiang Zemin, had appointed the two vice-chairmen of the Central Military Commission, a powerful body that oversees the armed forces. They stayed throughout Mr Hu’s tenure, frustrating any efforts to reform the PLA and curb its endemic corruption and ill-discipline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Xi is determined not to suffer the same fate. His anti-corruption purges have ensnared more than 13,000 officers (three serving generals were demoted in June, according to the South China Morning Post, a newspaper in Hong Kong). Mr Xi slimmed down the military commission from 11 to seven members, kicking off the service chiefs and adding an anti-graft officer. The body was also given control of the paramilitary People’s Armed Police, which in turn absorbed the coast guard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Predictably, the restructuring has generated resentment. Senior officers are irked at losing privileges. Demobilised soldiers sometimes take their grievances to the streets—one reason why Mr Xi founded a ministry of veterans’ affairs in 2016. But, says Ms Nouwens, younger ranks benefit from merit-based promotion, take pride in the growing prominence of the PLA in Chinese film and television, and admire Mr Xi’s “great rejuvenation of the Chinese nation”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They will have an opportunity to show off on October 1st when a huge military parade will be staged in Beijing to mark the 70th anniversary of Communist rule. It will be the first such show in the capital since Mr Xi launched his reforms. Expect a world-class performance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 03:40:18 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can the Labour party solve Brexit?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/26/can-the-labour-party-solve-brexit]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_blp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-26T18:00:32Z&quot;&gt;Jun 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BRITISH HEADLINES are dominated by the contest to become the next Conservative prime minister, and the Tories&amp;#x27; divisions over Brexit. But the opposition Labour Party, too, is split over Britain&amp;#x27;s relationship with the EU. Anne McElvoy interviews John McDonnell, the shadow chancellor, who is one of the strongest voices calling for a second referendum and says Labour should campaign to remain in the EU. She asks him about revoking Article 50, if he would push for a vote of no confidence to force a general election, whether he has ambitions to become Labour leader and what the party is doing to root out anti-Semitism. Runtime: 31 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/35c6b5d2-3ae6-450b-ac14-f67cd25ffefa&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 02:41:22 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Xi Jinping wants China’s armed forces to be “world-class” by 2050]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/china/2019/06/26/xi-jinping-wants-chinas-armed-forces-to-be-world-class-by-2050]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_cnp001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-26T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;OVER THE PAST decade, the People’s Liberation Army (PLA) has been lavished with money and weaponry. Chinese military spending rose by 83% between 2009 and 2018, by far the largest growth spurt of any big country. This splurge has enabled China to deploy precision missiles and anti-satellite weapons that challenge America’s supremacy in the western Pacific. China’s leader, Xi Jinping, says his “Chinese dream” includes a “dream of a strong armed forces”. That, he says, involves “modernising” the PLA by 2035 and making it “world-class”—in other words, America-beating—by mid-century. He has been making considerable progress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Organisational reforms may be less eye-catching than missiles that fly at Mach 5, unmanned cargo planes and electromagnetically powered superguns (all of which China has tested in the past year). Yet Mr Xi has realised that there is little point in grafting fancy weapons onto an old-fashioned force. During the cold war the PLA evolved to repel the Soviet Union and America in big land wars on Chinese soil. Massed infantry would grind down the enemy in attritional battles. In the 1990s Chinese leaders, alarmed by American prowess in the Gulf war of 1991, decided to focus on enhancing the PLA’s ability to fight “local wars under high-technology conditions”. They were thinking of short, sharp conflicts on China’s periphery, such as over Taiwan, in which air and naval power would be as important as ground forces. Mr Xi decided that winning such wars required changing the armed forces’ structure. He has done more in the past three years to reform the PLA than any leader since Deng Xiaoping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Xi’s principal aim is to increase “jointness”. This term, borrowed from Western military jargon, refers to the ability of different services—army, navy and air force—to co-operate on the battlefield quickly and seamlessly. Jointness is especially important for fighting wars that break out abroad. It can be difficult for commanders at national headquarters to choreograph soldiers, sailors and pilots from a great distance. The different services must be able to work together without instruction from on high.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China’s model is the United States, which—under the Goldwater-Nichols Act of 1986—drastically reformed its own armed forces in order to achieve this goal. The Pentagon carved up the globe into “combatant commands”. No longer would services squabble among themselves. All soldiers, sailors and pilots in a given area, such as the Persian Gulf or the Pacific, would take orders from a single officer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_cnm951.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; Mr Xi has followed suit. Before his reforms, army and navy commanders in the country’s seven military regions would report to their respective service headquarters, with little or no co-ordination. In February 2016 Mr Xi replaced the regions with five “theatres”, each under a single commander (see map). The eastern one based in Nanjing would prepare for war with Taiwan and Japan, for instance. The sprawling western theatre, in Chengdu, would handle India. The southern one in Guangzhou would manage the South China Sea.&lt;p&gt;As well as these geographic commands, two others were formed in 2015, each aimed at an American vulnerability. American forces depend on communications via satellites, computer networks and other high-tech channels. So Mr Xi created a new Strategic Support Force to target these systems. It directs space, cyber, electronic and psychological warfare. In 2018 it conducted exercises against five PLA units in what the Pentagon called a “a complex electronic warfare environment”. American military power in Asia also depends on a network of bases and aircraft carriers. Mr Xi took aim at these by establishing a new service called the PLA Rocket Force—an upgrade of what was previously known less rousingly as the Second Artillery Corps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He has also been trimming the armed forces’ bloated ranks, though they remain over 2m-strong. Since 2015 the PLA has shed 300,000 men, most of them from the land forces, which have lost one-third of their commissioned officers and shrunk from 70% of the PLA’s total strength to less than half (though happily the army has kept its dance troupes, which it had been told it would lose). By contrast, the marines are tripling in size. Navy and air-force officers have gained more powerful posts, including leadership of two theatre commands. This reflects the PLA’s tilt towards the seas—and the skies above them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is hard to tell whether the new PLA is more proficient on the battlefield. China has not fought a war in four decades. The last Chinese soldiers with experience of a large-scale conflict—a war with Vietnam in 1979—will retire shortly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there is evidence that the PLA is getting better at jointness. Some of China’s growing number of forays beyond its borders, notably bomber flights around Taiwan and over the South China Sea, indicate increasing co-ordination between air and naval forces. “We see a lot of joint exercises to work out kinks in the system and get the services used to working with each other,” says Phillip Saunders of the National Defence University in Washington. Chinese war games were once highly scripted affairs. Now officers are assessed on the realism of their training, says Meia Nouwens of the International Institute for Strategic Studies in London. Before Mr Xi’s reforms the “blue team”, which simulates an adversary, would always ritually lose large-scale annual exercises known as “Stride” in Inner Mongolia. Now they usually win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But China’s troops may still be ill-prepared for complex warfare. In America promotions depend on officers’ ability to work with other services. Their Chinese counterparts often spend their entire careers in one service, in one region and even doing the same job. Political culture is another problem. “The structures that China is trying to emulate are based on openness, on delegation of authority and collaboration,” notes Admiral Scott Swift of MIT, who retired last year as commander of America’s Pacific Fleet. He says modern warfare requires decentralised decision-making because cyber and electronic warfare can sever communications between commanders and units. “Militaries that are founded on democratic principles are going to be much more adept at adapting to that environment,” Admiral Swift suggests.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Xi is an authoritarian who strives for centralised control. His predecessor, Hu Jintao, did not have a tight grip on the PLA, says Mr Saunders. That is because Mr Hu’s own predecessor, Jiang Zemin, had appointed the two vice-chairmen of the Central Military Commission, a powerful body that oversees the armed forces. They stayed throughout Mr Hu’s tenure, frustrating any efforts to reform the PLA and curb its endemic corruption and ill-discipline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Xi is determined not to suffer the same fate. His anti-corruption purges have ensnared more than 13,000 officers (three serving generals were demoted in June, according to the South China Morning Post, a newspaper in Hong Kong). Mr Xi slimmed down the military commission from 11 to seven members, kicking off the service chiefs and adding an anti-graft officer. The body was also given control of the paramilitary People’s Armed Police, which in turn absorbed the coast guard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Predictably, the restructuring has generated resentment. Senior officers are irked at losing privileges. Demobilised soldiers sometimes take their grievances to the streets—one reason why Mr Xi founded a ministry of veterans’ affairs in 2016. But, says Ms Nouwens, younger ranks benefit from merit-based promotion, take pride in the growing prominence of the PLA in Chinese film and television, and admire Mr Xi’s “great rejuvenation of the Chinese nation”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They will have an opportunity to show off on October 1st when a huge military parade will be staged in Beijing to mark the 70th anniversary of Communist rule. It will be the first such show in the capital since Mr Xi launched his reforms. Expect a world-class performance. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 02:41:21 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Economist asks: Labour’s John McDonnell]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/26/the-economist-asks-labours-john-mcdonnell]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_blp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-26T18:00:32Z&quot;&gt;Jun 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHILE BRITISH headlines are dominated by the race to become the next Conservative prime minister, the opposition Labour party is divided over how to resolve the Brexit stalemate. Anne McElvoy interviews John McDonnell MP, the shadow chancellor, who is one of the strongest voices calling for a second referendum in which he wants Labour to campaign to remain in the EU. Anne asks him about revoking Article 50, if he would push for a vote of no confidence to force a general election, whether he has ambitions to become Labour leader and what the party is doing to root out anti-Semitism. Runtime: 31 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/35c6b5d2-3ae6-450b-ac14-f67cd25ffefa&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 01:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Our essay competition for young people]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/26/our-essay-competition-for-young-people]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190617_OFD100_google_now_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-26T15:11:59Z&quot;&gt;Jun 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;THE ECONOMIST&lt;/em&gt;’s Open Future initiative was begun last year to make the case for political, economic and social freedoms at a time when these values are under assault. We want this exploration of ideas to involve our critics as well as our supporters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of the initiative we are holding an essay contest. It is open to people between 16 and 25 years old. Essays should be no longer than 1,000 words. The deadline for submissions is July 31st 2019. Please read the formal &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/19/terms-and-conditions-for-young-peoples-essay-contests&quot;&gt;terms of the competition&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The winning essay will be published on &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;&amp;#x27;s Open Future website and the winner will be invited to attend one of the three Open Future Festival events, to be held simultaneously in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://events.economist.com/events-conferences/asia/open-future-festival-hong-kong&quot;&gt;Hong Kong&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://events.economist.com/events-conferences/emea/open-future-festival-manchester/&quot;&gt;Manchester&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://events.economist.com/events-conferences/americas/open-future-festival-chicago/&quot;&gt;Chicago&lt;/a&gt; on Saturday October 5th 2019. &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; will pay for travel and accommodation; if the winner is under 18, we will pay for a guardian to accompany the winner as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Essays should answer the question by taking a stance and making a case based on arguments and facts. We will select the best essays based on the quality of their arguments, not the extent to which they align with our views. Though good writing is important, judges will make allowances for those for whom English is not their first language.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Essayists should email their submissions by &lt;strong&gt;July 31st 2019&lt;/strong&gt;, with the subject “Open Future essay contest” to: &lt;strong&gt;OpenFuture@Economist.com&lt;/strong&gt;. Please send only one, final submission, and place the text in the body of the email: we cannot accept attachments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The essay question is:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What fundamental economic and political change, if any, is needed for an effective response to climate change?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Description: For decades the world has been aware that human activity is heating up the planet to dangerous levels, with potentially calamitous consequences. Despite efforts by government, business and individuals to curtail the trend, carbon emissions are still rising. Perhaps new thinking is needed, since previous attempts to deal with the problem have failed. So what might be done?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Again, please do read the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/19/terms-and-conditions-for-young-peoples-essay-contests&quot;&gt;terms&lt;/a&gt; of the competition. We are a global organisation and we operate a strict privacy policy around the world. How we will use your personal data is spelled out in the terms of the competition, and how we handle personal data more generally is in our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economistgroup.com/results_and_governance/governance/privacy/&quot;&gt;privacy policy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By entering the competition, you agree to the terms of the competition, and you agree to us processing and using your personal data for the purposes described in the terms—including to administer the contest, to attribute winning entries and runners-up publicly and for promotional purposes. We will not use your details to market other services to you unless you specifically give us permission to do so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We encourage you to read last year’s winning essays &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2018/09/10/fresh-ideas-on-how-to-fix-the-world&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good luck!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 23:40:24 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>