<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Don&#x27;t read too much into the release of two jailed journalists in Myanmar]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/07/dont-read-too-much-into-the-release-of-two-jailed-journalists-in-myanmar]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_asp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I can&amp;#x27;t wait to go to my newsroom,” Wa Lone told a crowd of reporters as he walked free of Insein prison in Yangon, Myanmar&amp;#x27;s biggest city. Mr Wa Lone and Kyaw Soe Oo, who work for Reuters news agency, were released on May 7th. The pair were convicted in September 2018 of breaking the Official Secrets Act and received a seven-year sentence. They had served 511 days before being released as part of an amnesty of over 6,000 prisoners to mark the country&amp;#x27;s New Year holiday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the beginning, the case against the journalists was absurd. The pair had been working on an investigation into the killing of ten men from the Rohingya Muslim minority in Rakhine state, where soldiers forced more than 700,000 Rohingyas to flee to Bangladesh in 2017, murdering a further 7,000 or so. The government never denied that the killings took place and last year convicted ten soldiers for their role in them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trial of the two journalists was a farce, orchestrated by the military. The pair were alleged to have broken a law dating back to the colonial era. The defence argued that they were entrapped by police who invited them to dinner, handed them state documents, and arrested them shortly afterwards. One officer admitted to burning his notes of the arrest; another policeman said they had been ordered to set up the journalists. A third was caught consulting notes written on his hand when testifying against the pair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, Mr Wa Lone and Mr Kyaw Soe Oo were sentenced, much to the dismay, in particular, of Western governments. They saw it as yet another symptom of Myanmar’s failure to reform itself, even under the de facto leadership of Nobel Peace prize winner Aung San Suu Kyi, head of the ruling National League for Democracy party. Activists held the case up as an example of the continuing oppression of human-rights. Every new legal appeal made front-page news in Myanmar. Diplomats pleaded with government officials for the journalists&amp;#x27; release. But despite all the pressure, Ms Suu Kyi refused to intervene, arguing that she could not interfere with the judicial process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two weeks ago the journalists had their third and final appeal rejected. That meant that all legal avenues to free the journalists had been exhausted. A pardon, which leaves court rulings intact, allows Ms Suu Kyi to make a small but attention-grabbing concession to the West, while not being seen to backtrack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, the journalists&amp;#x27; release certainly does not indicate any change of heart by the government. Under Ms Suu Kyi freedom of expression in Myanmar is being severely curtailed. A report released in January by Human Rights Watch, an NGO, found that a piece of loosely worded legislation which was supposed to regulate the telecoms sector is being used to crackdown on journalists and silence government critics. Since the National League for Democracy took power in 2016, about 140 cases have been brought under this law, many of which are baseless. Scores of reporters still languish in prison. Many of those who remain free now feel compelled to self-censor. The situation, sadly, is all too reminiscent of journalism under the old military regimes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thus freeing Mr Wa Lone and Mr Kyaw Soe Oo is part of a “balancing act”, argues Gerard McCarthy of Australian National University. Ms Suu Kyi must weigh the preferences of Western governments, previously her strongest backers, against many Burmese, who think that the two journalists betrayed their country by appearing to side with the hated Rohingya. Objections from this constituency, and the generals, will be assuaged by the fact that 6,000 other prisoners were freed at the same time. The release of the two journalists is a welcome gesture, but a small one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 04:06:26 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cory Booker unveils an ambitious gun-control plan]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/07/cory-booker-unveils-an-ambitious-gun-control-plan]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_USP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T18:16:01Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON MAY 6th, the day Senator Cory Booker published his presidential plan to cut gun violence, there were two shootings in his state of New Jersey, in which two people were injured. Across America, that day alone, there were 71 shootings, in which 14 died and dozens were wounded, according to the Gun Violence Archive, a nonprofit research organisation. It reckons that so far this year guns have killed 4,764 Americans, including 873 teenagers—and 196 children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Booker is making much on the campaign trail of being the only Democratic presidential candidate to live in a poor inner city area—in Newark, where he was mayor—and he highlighted the relentless, daily nature of gun violence in America when he unveiled his plan. “This is an everyday experience to people like me and folks in my community”, he said. “And I&amp;#x27;m not unique. This is happening all over the country, ripping apart communities.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The senator’s gun-control plan is part of his effort to stand out in a crowded Democratic field. Earlier this month Mr Booker said his campaign was short of the number of donors that would qualify him to appear in the televised primary debates that begin in June. But his plan is notable for two other reasons. First, it is the most ambitious gun control proposal to have been put forward by a presidential candidate. Though it would ban assault weapons, close loopholes that allow domestic abusers to buy guns and prevent the bulk sale of firearms, its central feature is the creation of a national licensing programme. This would require prospective gun-buyers to undergo an extensive background check by the Federal Bureau of Investigation, entailing fingerprinting and an interview, in order to obtain a five-year gun licence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No such national programme currently exists, but research suggests that licensing is the best way to cut America’s gun death rate, which is by far the highest in the rich world. Mr Booker cited a study from 2015 that shows gun deaths in Connecticut dropped by 40% after the state introduced a gun licensing programme. Massachusetts, which requires buyers to obtain a permit—a weeks’ long process involving an interview and a background check—has one of the lowest gun death rates in America. In 2016 it had 3.4 gun deaths per 100,000 people. Nearby New Hampshire, where buying a gun is a much simpler process, had 9.4 deaths per 100,000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Booker’s plan also suggests the Democratic Party has changed its thinking on gun control as a possible election issue. Democrats have not always wanted to campaign on gun control. Many believe a ban on assault weapons passed during Bill Clinton’s presidency cost them control of the House of Representatives in 1994 and that Al Gore’s enthusiasm for gun control cost him the presidency in 2000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their political calculus seems to be changing. Thanks in part to a new student-led movement for gun control that was sparked by a mass school shooting in Parkland, Florida, last February, the issue was prominent in November’s mid-terms. In at least 12 races, Democrats given an “F” rating by the National Rifle Association kicked out “A”-rated Republicans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though there are concerns that support for gun controls could turn off the sort of working class swing voters that in 2016 helped elect President Donald Trump, most 2020 Democratic candidates have said they back tighter gun controls. Senator Kamala Harris said recently she would give Congress 100 days to pass gun control laws before she used presidential executive power to enforce them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The election of a Democratic president may mean not mean much for America’s gun laws, however. Any comprehensive legislation would have to be passed by Congress; while the Republican Party remains in control of the Senate that is unlikely to happen. In March, having taken control of the House, Democrats passed a universal background checks bill, the first major gun control bill since 1994. Though such a step is backed by a majority of Americans it has not gone anywhere in the Senate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One Republican senator was quick to proclaim his opposition to serious gun-control laws after Mr Booker unveiled his plan. “BREAKING: the latest terrible idea to come out of the Democrats’ 2020 primary is a federal gun registry”, tweeted gun-loving Senator Rick Scott of Florida. “...What’s next? Will we have to register sharp knives?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 03:11:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Two jailed Reuters journalists are released by presidential pardon]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/07/do-not-read-too-much-into-the-release-of-two-jailed-journalists]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_asp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I can&amp;#x27;t wait to go to my newsroom,” Wa Lone told a crowd of reporters as he walked free of Insein prison in Yangon, Myanmar&amp;#x27;s biggest city. Mr Wa Lone and Kyaw Soe Oo, who work for Reuters news agency, were released on May 7th. The pair were convicted in September 2018 of breaking the Official Secrets Act and received a seven-year sentence. They had served 511 days before being released as part of an amnesty of over 6,000 prisoners to mark the country&amp;#x27;s New Year holiday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the beginning, the case against the journalists was absurd. The pair had been working on an investigation into the killing of ten men from the Rohingya Muslim minority in Rakhine state, where soldiers forced more than 700,000 Rohingyas to flee to Bangladesh in 2017, murdering a further 7,000 or so. The government never denied that the killings took place and last year convicted ten soldiers for their role in them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trial of the two journalists was a farce, orchestrated by the military. The pair were alleged to have broken a law dating back to the colonial era. The defence argued that they were entrapped by police who invited them to dinner, handed them state documents, and arrested them shortly afterwards. One officer admitted to burning his notes of the arrest; another policeman said they had been ordered to set up the journalists. A third was caught consulting notes written on his hand when testifying against the pair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, Mr Wa Lone and Mr Kyaw Soe Oo were sentenced, much to the dismay, in particular, of Western governments. They saw it as yet another symptom of Myanmar’s failure to reform itself, even under the de facto leadership of Nobel Peace prize winner Aung San Suu Kyi, head of the ruling National League for Democracy party. Activists held the case up as an example of the continuing oppression of human-rights. Every new legal appeal made front-page news in Myanmar. Diplomats pleaded with government officials for the journalists&amp;#x27; release. But despite all the pressure, Ms Suu Kyi refused to intervene, arguing that she could not interfere with the judicial process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two weeks ago the journalists had their third and final appeal rejected. That meant that all legal avenues to free the journalists had been exhausted. A pardon, which leaves court rulings intact, allows Ms Suu Kyi to make a small but attention-grabbing concession to the West, while not being seen to backtrack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, the journalists&amp;#x27; release certainly does not indicate any change of heart by the government. Under Ms Suu Kyi freedom of expression in Myanmar is being severely curtailed. A report released in January by Human Rights Watch, an NGO, found that a piece of loosely worded legislation which was supposed to regulate the telecoms sector is being used to crackdown on journalists and silence government critics. Since the National League for Democracy took power in 2016, about 140 cases have been brought under this law, many of which are baseless. Scores of reporters still languish in prison. Many of those who remain free now feel compelled to self-censor. The situation, sadly, is all too reminiscent of journalism under the old military regimes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thus freeing Mr Wa Lone and Mr Kyaw Soe Oo is part of a “balancing act”, argues Gerard McCarthy of Australian National University. Ms Suu Kyi must weigh the preferences of Western governments, previously her strongest backers, against many Burmese, who think that the two journalists betrayed their country by appearing to side with the hated Rohingya. Objections from this constituency, and the generals, will be assuaged by the fact that 6,000 other prisoners were freed at the same time. The release of the two journalists is a welcome gesture, but a small one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 03:11:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Two jailed Reuters journalists are released by presidential pardon]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/07/two-jailed-reuters-journalists-are-released-by-presidential-pardon]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_asp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I can&amp;#x27;t wait to go to my newsroom,” Wa Lone told a crowd of reporters as he walked free of Insein prison in Yangon, Myanmar&amp;#x27;s biggest city. Mr Wa Lone and Kyaw Soe Oo, who work for Reuters news agency, were released on May 7th. The pair were convicted in September 2018 of breaking the Official Secrets Act and received a seven-year sentence. They had served 511 days before being released as part of an amnesty of over 6,000 prisoners to mark the country&amp;#x27;s New Year holiday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the beginning, the case against the journalists was absurd. The pair had been working on an investigation into the killing of ten men from the Rohingya Muslim minority in Rakhine state, where soldiers forced more than 700,000 Rohingyas to flee to Bangladesh in 2017, murdering a further 7,000 or so. The government never denied that the killings took place and last year convicted ten soldiers for their role in them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trial of the two journalists was a farce, orchestrated by the military. The pair were alleged to have broken a law dating back to the colonial era. The defence argued that they were entrapped by police who invited them to dinner, handed them state documents, and arrested them shortly afterwards. One officer admitted to burning his notes of the arrest; another policeman said they had been ordered to set up the journalists. A third was caught consulting notes written on his hand when testifying against the pair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, Mr Wa Lone and Mr Kyaw Soe Oo were sentenced, much to the dismay, in particular, of Western governments. They saw it as yet another symptom of Myanmar’s failure to reform itself, even under the de facto leadership of Nobel Peace prize winner Aung San Suu Kyi, head of the ruling National League for Democracy party. Activists held the case up as an example of the continuing oppression of human-rights. Every new legal appeal made front-page news in Myanmar. Diplomats pleaded with government officials for the journalists&amp;#x27; release. But despite all the pressure, Ms Suu Kyi refused to intervene, arguing that she could not interfere with the judicial process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two weeks ago the journalists had their third and final appeal rejected. That meant that all legal avenues to free the journalists had been exhausted. A pardon, which leaves court rulings intact, allows Ms Suu Kyi to make a small but attention-grabbing concession to the West, while not being seen to backtrack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, the journalists&amp;#x27; release certainly does not indicate any change of heart by the government. Under Ms Suu Kyi freedom of expression in Myanmar is being severely curtailed. A report released in January by Human Rights Watch, an NGO, found that a piece of loosely worded legislation which was supposed to regulate the telecoms sector is being used to crackdown on journalists and silence government critics. Since the National League for Democracy took power in 2016, about 140 cases have been brought under this law, many of which are baseless. Scores of reporters still languish in prison. Many of those who remain free now feel compelled to self-censor. The situation, sadly, is all too reminiscent of journalism under the old military regimes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thus freeing Mr Wa Lone and Mr Kyaw Soe Oo is part of a “balancing act”, argues Gerard McCarthy of Australian National University. Ms Suu Kyi must weigh the preferences of Western governments, previously her strongest backers, against many Burmese, who think that the two journalists betrayed their country by appearing to side with the hated Rohingya. Objections from this constituency, and the generals, will be assuaged by the fact that 6,000 other prisoners were freed at the same time. The release of the two journalists is a welcome gesture, but a small one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 03:10:10 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tech’s raid on the banks]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/07/techs-raid-on-the-banks]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/mt_twitter_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T14:10:28Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;DIGITAL DISRUPTION is coming to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/special-report/2019/05/02/young-people-and-their-phones-are-shaking-up-banking&quot;&gt;banking&lt;/a&gt; at last. Helen Joyce travels across Asia to see how fintechs like Ant Financial are transforming how people spend, save and invest their money, and asks whether traditional banks can catch up. Who will win the battle to be the bank of the future? And could having a bank in your pocket make your money safer? Runtime: 23 min &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-tech-sraidonthebanks&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 02:07:04 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A plane crash in Moscow raises safety questions about the Sukhoi Superjet]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/gulliver/2019/05/07/a-plane-crash-in-moscow-raises-safety-questions-about-the-sukhoi-superjet]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_BLP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T15:58:00Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;ON MAY 5TH a Sukhoi Superjet operated by Aeroflot, Russia’s flag carrier, erupted in flames while attempting an emergency landing at Sheremetyevo Airport in Moscow. CCTV footage shows the airliner make a hard landing, bounce perhaps 20ft in the air, and plunge back down with sufficient force to break the undercarriage and set the fuel tanks alight. At least 41 of the 78 passengers and crew died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Too little is known at this early stage to make informed assessments of the cause of the crash. Some survivors have claimed that the aircraft was struck by lightning shortly after take-off. That should have been an unremarkable if unnerving event. The average commercial jet will be struck by lightning once a year. Complications almost never arise because modern airframes are designed to conduct electrical currents safely across their exterior surfaces. If, as some have suggested, the lightning caused damage to the Superjet’s internal electrical components, questions will need to be asked about the design of the aircraft. Equally, investigators will need to know why the pilots attempted an emergency landing without first dumping fuel in order to reduce the risk of damage if the kerosene ignited.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;The Soviet Union had a torrid air-safety record, but over the past decade Russia’s airlines, and particularly state-owned Aeroflot, have moved into line with global standards. Aeroflot is included on the Operational Safety Audit registry run by the International Air Transport Association, an international trade body which certifies airlines to the highest measurable standards of any recognised global organisation. Air crashes are still more common in Russia than in many other countries, but its pilots have to contend with one of the most extreme climates on the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;And so attention has focused on Sukhoi, the Russian state-owned planemaker that manufactures the Superjet. The plane does not suffer the problems of many Soviet-era airliners. It has suffered only one other fatal accident, in 2012, when a demonstration flight in Indonesia crashed, killing 45 people, due to pilot error. The jet has lost favour with carriers over the past year, not so much because of any design errors, but because of problems relating, in particular, to engine maintenance. These problems have been costly for certain airlines as Sukhoi’s failure to develop a global maintenance network has resulted in a shortage of spare parts. This factor alone has been off-putting for airlines. Citijet of Ireland, Brussels Airlines and Adria Airways of Slovenia have already dumped the craft. After the latest crash, Yamal Airlines of Russia cancelled its planned purchase of 10 Superjets. Even if investigators exonerate Sukhoi of any blame for the crash, the planemaker is unlikely to convince any new airlines to fly the jet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 00:07:05 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Punters are betting a princely sum on the royal baby’s name]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/07/punters-are-betting-a-princely-sum-on-the-royal-babys-name]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_woc667.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR AN event shrouded in secrecy, yesterday’s royal birth has had gamblers reaching for their pockets. Ever since the Duke and Duchess of Sussex announced in October 2018 that they were expecting a child “in the spring”, they have shared scant information about their due date, let alone the expected sex of their first child. The baby boy’s arrival even caught some news organisations by surprise, with lunchtime “push” notifications that the Duchess had gone into labour being followed swiftly by reports that she had given birth many hours earlier. Despite this uncertainty, or perhaps because of it, a number of bookmakers have allowed punters to bet on the royal baby’s arrival date, sex, weight and name.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far, the public’s predictive powers have been weak. On Saturday two major bookmakers were giving the chances of a baby girl a 75% likelihood, and just 35% for a boy. (A higher percentage in such a binary market reflects more money being staked on it, and the extra 10% is how bookies make money regardless of the outcome). One gambling firm reports a healthy profit on bets that Ms Markle would give birth in April. And a late flurry of wagers over the weekend on the child’s name saw Diana usurped as the leading contender in favour of Ivy, which at one point had a probability of 41%—a huge prediction given that the sex had not yet been revealed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With all gambling activity now focused on the royal moniker, an industry spokesman estimates that the £500,000 wagered on the name so far could double by April 8th, when the announcement is expected. Alexander and Spencer are currently the leading contenders at 19%. If the gambling public’s predictions so far are anything to go by, expect another surprise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;More on the royal family:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.1843magazine.com/features/can-meghan-markle-modernise-the-monarchy&quot;&gt;Can Meghan Markle modernise the monarchy?&lt;/a&gt; [July 2018]&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/03/08/is-girls-education-the-great-leap-forward-for-feminism&quot;&gt;The Economist asks with Meghan Markle, Annie Lennox, Adwoa Aboah, Julia Gillard and other guests&lt;/a&gt; [March 2019]&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/international/2019/04/27/how-monarchies-survive-modernity&quot;&gt;How monarchies survive modernity&lt;/a&gt; [April 2019]&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/WIOfEHlVp_c&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 22:07:28 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[An exhibition of material and visual culture from the Calais “Jungle”]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/07/an-exhibition-of-material-and-visual-culture-from-the-calais-jungle]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_BKP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T13:27:29Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AT THE back of the Pitt Rivers Museum in Oxford, beyond the Mexican caricature masks and Siberian underwear made from reindeer hide, is a small room with a big show. The first thing you see at the entrance is a hand-stencilled sign that says: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Welcome to the Jungle&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pop. 8143&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Children 1496&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Unaccompanied 1291”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The “Jungle” here is the Calais Jungle, an encampment for migrants and refugees who, having crossed from Africa and the Middle East, eked out an existence outside the city in northern France while they waited for passage to Britain. The official version is that the camp was in use between January 2015 and October 2016, after which 6,400 migrants were removed in 170 buses, with the aim, according to &lt;em&gt;Le Monde&lt;/em&gt;, of resettling them in different parts of France. On October 26th 2016 the French interior ministry announced that the Calais “Jungle” had been taken apart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a counterpoint to this narrative, Dan Hicks, a professor of archaeology at Oxford University, and a French colleague, Sarah Mallet, set about telling a different, and ongoing, story. Through drawings, photographs, objects and audio recordings—most of them borrowed from volunteers who worked in the camp—they have turned a political irritation into a powerful human drama about cruelty and kindness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.oapen.org/viewer/web/viewer.html?file=http://www.oapen.org/document/1004862&quot;&gt;The book that accompanies the show&lt;/a&gt; describes in detail how the authorities on both sides of the Channel helped create the beginnings of what Theresa May, when she was home secretary, described as “a really hostile environment for illegal migrants”. Residents of the “Jungle” are treated to “an endless guerrilla siege”, walled in by concrete and barbed wire, their tents cut open with blades and sprayed with teargas and then burned. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What might, in other hands, have been voyeurism or a piece of poverty tourism turns out to be anything but. The Pitt Rivers opened in 1884, the same year as the Berlin Conference that partitioned Africa. Like other anthropology museums of the time, it subscribed to the vogue for placing human beings across the world in various categories of  “us” and “them”, with Europeans sitting at the top of a supposed human hierarchy. Conscious of this history—“our national borders and anthropology museums are both Victorian technologies of classification,” the exhibition notes say; “they were designed to forge differences between people”—the curators have chosen to highlight the drama and boredom of everyday life in a migrant camp. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;A series of delicate pencil-and-wash drawings tell individual stories of young men such as Abdul, a 17-year-old Afghan who was eight years old when his father was killed by the Taliban, forcing him to flee to Pakistan and then Iran. He is in the “Jungle”; his 15-year-old brother is in Turkey. Children’s cut-out figures, crayon drawings and schoolwork show how much effort is made to give young people an education. A blue wooden cross with a slanted crossbeam (pictured), which was given to the Bishop of Bangor after he visited the camp, tells of St Michael’s, the makeshift Orthodox church established there for those who had fled Eritrea.&lt;p&gt;The “Jungle” landscapes of Calais began to emerge not in January 2015 but as far back as the 1990s, the curators say. They are still there. The official government line, in Britain as well as France, may well be that the area has been cleared. But a brief email (printed out and pinned up at the end of the exhibition), which an agency called Help Refugees sends the curators every month, says that on May 2nd this year there were “1,000 displaced people living between Calais and Dunkirk, over 280 of which are unaccompanied children. This number of children has doubled in two months.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Migrants fleeing poverty and war is one of Europe’s biggest political challenges. As this exhibition shows, how Europeans decide to treat them is a profound moral test, too. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Lande: The Calais ‘Jungle’ and Beyond” is at the Pitt Rivers Museum, Oxford, until November 29th. Read more: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/prospero/2018/01/08/a-thoughtful-dramatisation-of-life-in-the-calais-jungle&quot;&gt;A thoughtful dramatisation of life in the Calais “Jungle”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 21:06:44 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“We’ve failed to grasp how deep Erdogan&#x27;s playbook is”—Istanbul’s election rerun]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/07/weve-failed-to-grasp-how-deep-erdogans-playbook-is-istanbuls-election-rerun]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_blp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T10:27:18Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TURKEY&amp;#x27;S RULING AK party never conceded defeat in Istanbul’s mayoral election in March. Now the result has been annulled, and a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/07/turkey-cancels-the-oppositions-victory-in-the-istanbul-election&quot;&gt;rerun&lt;/a&gt; ordered, to the dismay of opposition politicians and Western governments. A trade deal between China and America has been thrown into &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/06/the-us-china-trade-talks-are-at-risk-of-breakdown&quot;&gt;doubt&lt;/a&gt; thanks to a presidential tweet. And why more women are colonising a genre of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/05/04/female-mcs-are-changing-brazilian-funk-music&quot;&gt;Brazilian music&lt;/a&gt; known for its misogyny. Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/mayormaynot-turkey-selectionre-run&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 21:06:43 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Turkey cancels the opposition’s victory in the Istanbul election]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/07/turkey-cancels-the-oppositions-victory-in-the-istanbul-election]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_eup501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEFORE THE evening of May 6th, and despite the miserable state of their country&amp;#x27;s democracy under President Recep Tayyip Erdogan, Turks could console themselves with the thought that, on election day, they could anyway vote freely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That assurance was dashed when the country’s electoral board cancelled the result of the mayoral election in Istanbul conducted on March 31st. It ordered a new one for June 23rd, thereby deposing Ekrem Imamoglu, the first opposition politician to preside over Turkey’s biggest city in a quarter century.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkey’s descent into autocracy appeared to plumb new depths overnight. The markets braced for more turmoil. The lira has slumped by more than 3% since the announcement, reaching its lowest level in seven months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The drama had been in the making since late March, when voters in Istanbul handed Mr Imamoglu a narrow yet shocking victory. That was a bitter setback for Mr Erdogan, his Justice and Development (AK) party and their mayoral candidate, a former prime minister. AK immediately contested the outcome. The morning after the vote, the city woke up to banners and billboards heralding victory—for Mr Erdogan and his party.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Newspapers managed by the president’s cronies accused the opposition of conspiring with terrorists to steal the election. AK complained that tens of thousands of former bureaucrats sacked following an attempted coup in 2016 should not have been allowed to vote. Mr Erdogan claimed to have unearthed evidence of other “organised crimes” at the ballot box. Late last week, prosecutors launched dozens of investigations related to AK’s claims, questioning some 100 people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the end, the election board voted to annul the election, citing improprieties in the appointment of some polling-station officials. AK hardliners applauded. Mr Erdogan’s communications director called the decision a “victory for our democracy”. The opposition called it a disgrace. Appearing before a crowd of supporters in his Istanbul neighbourhood, Mr Imamoglu came out swinging, condemning the board for caving in to pressure from the president and his men. “You elected the president under the same rules last year, and you held a referendum and changed the constitution under the same rules,” he said. If Mr Imamoglu’s election can be undone, then “the constitution is questionable, and so is the presidential election.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analysts see Mr Erdogan’s fingerprints on the decision, and warn that Turkey and free elections no longer belong in the same sentence. “For nearly 70 years, there was a consensus in Turkey that political power changed through the ballot box, and that consensus came to an end today,” says Soner Cagaptay of the Washington Institute for Near East Policy, an American think-tank. “I thought there was one institution in Turkey that could act somewhat independently,” said Kemal Kirisci, a senior fellow at the Brookings Institution, “and I was wrong.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The opposition appears unlikely to boycott the repeat election, however, or to stage mass protests. (Mr Imamoglu’s Republican People’s Party suggested as much on May 7th.) Fear is a big factor. Of the millions of Turks who took part in the last big wave of protests in 2013, hundreds have been hauled through the courts. One, a respected philanthropist, has spent nearly two years in prison on outlandish coup charges. He and 15 others face life sentences. Mr Erdogan already brands the opposition as terrorists and provocateurs. Demonstrations would risk playing right into his hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Imamoglu, whose campaign had succeeded against seemingly insurmountable odds, appears in no mood to surrender. Some observers reckon Mr Erdogan may have miscalculated, and that his actions will give Mr Imamoglu an even larger margin of victory next month. Others warn that Turkey’s strongman may go to extremes to wrest back control of the city that elected him mayor three decades ago, a position he used as a springboard to national power. “Erdogan did not call a new election to roll the dice and see what happens,” says Howard Eissenstat, an expert at the Project on Middle East Democracy, an advocacy group in Washington, DC. “The cost of losing [again] would be an unacceptable demonstration of weakness.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 21:06:42 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>