<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Benedict XVI is a pole of attraction for critics of Pope Francis]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/04/22/benedict-xvi-is-a-pole-of-attraction-for-critics-of-pope-francis]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/000_1ft5f3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-22T10:57:40Z&quot;&gt;Apr 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;AS WAS CLEARLY observed on April 21st by excited pilgrims as well as television-watchers across the world, only one white-robed prelate appeared on a balcony overlooking Saint Peter’s Square to deliver the traditional Easter message. Pope Francis (pictured) duly chided rich countries over the arms race, called for peace in the greater Middle East and Africa, and lamented the victims of terror in Sri Lanka. The power of such occasions depends both on modern technology and on a centuries-old tradition, which holds that the task of representing Jesus Christ as his “vicar” on earth falls to a single, uniquely legitimate office-holder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;But in the grounds of the Vatican, there are two gentlemen who use the title of pope: Francis and his predecessor, Benedict XVI, who lives nearby in a comfortable former convent. Officially, they get along well. On April 15th the current pontiff called on Benedict to offer congratulations on the eve of his 92nd birthday. But in photographs, Francis looked less genial than usual, and some wondered whether the wishes had been delivered through gritted teeth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;For several years, it has been clear that the relatively liberal, relatively inclusive style that Francis brings to the papacy is triggering a wave of theological and political opposition in many Catholic quarters. And some of that opposition is crystallising around Benedict, who styles himself “pope emeritus” and has retained some of the trappings of his old office, including the all-white garb plus a papal ring and dangling cross.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;What is not so clear is how far Benedict himself, and/or people with strong influence over him, are encouraging people to think of him as a counter-weight to Francis. But Massimo Faggioli, an Italian theologian, has likened the present situation to a “post-modern version” of a medieval schism: between 1378 and 1417, two and sometimes three clerics vied for the title of pope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Recent events have brought the contrast between the two clerics to a head. Benedict’s newly-published &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/04/12/a-former-pope-blames-the-swinging-sixties-for-clerical-crimes&quot;&gt;essay&lt;/a&gt;, blaming the surging sex-abuse crisis on the swinging sixties and “homosexual cliques” in seminaries, was his most blatant intervention since stepping down in 2013. Francis showed a very different style when, in a TV show aired on April 19&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;, he assured a gay British comedian that “only people who don’t have a heart” would fail to respect him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;For Vatican-watchers, all this simply marks one more episode in a long-term build-up of tension between the two popes, egged on by conservative critics of Francis. It was three years ago that Matteo Salvini, the anti-immigrant politician who is now Italian interior minister, sported a T-shirt with a pun in capital letters. “IL MIO PAPA E BENEDETTO” could either mean “my pope is Benedict” or “my pope is blessed”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;On the ecclesiastical front, four conservative cardinals (of whom America’s Cardinal Raymond Burke was the best-known) showed their hand in November 2016 with a letter that challenged a Vatican document which had promised more generous treatment to Catholics who divorce and remarry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;A few months later, the Benedict camp seemed to offer moral support to that challenge. At the funeral of one of the four signatories, a German prelate who is one of Benedict’s close&lt;span &gt; &lt;/span&gt;aides, Georg Gänswein, read a letter from the ex-pontiff, saying pointedly that God would not abandon the church “even if the boat [is] on the verge of capsizing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Whereas traditionalist clerics take issue with Francis over reproduction and sexuality, worldly politicians find fault with him (and see merit in his predecessor) over questions like immigration and the protection of traditional Western culture. European conservatives loved Benedict for his perceived attachment to the heritage of their continent; their American counterparts resent Francis for his anti-capitalism and his embrace of the grievances of the global South. All these impulses have come together in the increasing prominence of a right-wing Catholic think-tank located not far from Rome, the Dignitatis Humanae Institute, with which Cardinal Burke and Steve Bannon, a former adviser of President Donald Trump, are deeply involved.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;In the world of Catholic theology, as opposed to its political exploitation, there are those who insist that the Francis-Benedict rift is either exaggerated or being mischievously fanned by people who have little real concern for either cleric. Indeed, even among theologically-minded fans of Francis, some still profess admiration for Benedict “at his best” as a clear thinker and teacher. Michael Sean Winters, a Catholic writer, responded to the 6,000-word essay by calling it a mixture of flawed analysis and trivial anecdote which nonetheless contained glimmers of the “genius and beauty” which characterised the work of Benedict (formerly Cardinal Joseph Ratzinger) at its finest.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;And to right-wing Americans who loathe Francis’s aversion to capitalism and embrace of the environment, it can be pointed out that both Benedict and his predecessor John Paul II had some harsh things to say about the unrestrained market. Nor has any recent pope been a fan of America’s military policy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;On the other hand, Benedict has hardly made life easy for his successor.&lt;span &gt;  &lt;/span&gt;After his surprise retirement in March 2013, he vowed to “remain hidden to the world”. He could have retired to a monastery in his native Bavaria and never said another public word. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Instead, he gave himself scope for future interventions. He not only kept many of the paraphernalia of office but, so critics argue, seemed keen to retain its essence. Many canon lawyers say his chosen title of “pope emeritus” is a dubiously-founded provocation, and that it would have been more correct to call himself bishop emeritus of Rome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Others note that Benedict’s resignation speech, in Latin, was profoundly and perhaps deliberately ambiguous. He said that, because of his age, he no longer had strength to exercise the papal ministry (munus in Latin). But he then went on to say that the munus had aspects: one consisted of acting and speaking and the other of praying and suffering. Father Stefano Violi, a canon-law teacher, reckons that Benedict was merely surrendering the administrative duties of a pope but not the pastoral ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;For conservatives who want to present themselves as anti-Francis but loyal (perhaps more loyal than the pontiff himself) to the Catholic tradition, Benedict’s presence in the Vatican city is, at a minimum, a golden opportunity.&lt;span &gt; And Benedict seems unable to resist the temptation of offering that opportunity.&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 00:06:23 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[American millennials think they will be rich]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/22/american-millennials-think-they-will-be-rich]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/articles/20190427_woc760.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-22T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;MORE THAN half of American millennials, the generation of people born between 1981 and 1996, believe that they will one day be millionaires; one in five think they will get there by the age of 40. These are the findings from a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://s1.q4cdn.com/959385532/files/doc_downloads/research/2018/Millennials-and-Money-survey.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;survey&lt;/a&gt; conducted in 2018 by TD Ameritrade, a financial-services company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.brookings.edu/wp-content/uploads/2019/03/How-Will-Retirement-Saving-Change-by-2050.docx.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;working paper&lt;/a&gt; by the Brookings Institution, a think-tank, offers a sobering antidote to this youthful optimism. It finds that millennials are less wealthy than people of a similar age were in any year from 1989 to 2007. The economic crisis of 2008-09 hit millennials particularly hard. Median household wealth in 2016 for 20- to 35-year-olds was about 25% lower than it was for the similar-aged cohort in 2007.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;American millennials are comparatively poor because many of them came of age during the financial crisis, when demand for labour was low and borrowing money became harder. The recovery has been slow, which has further reduced millennials’ long-term earning potential. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.federalreserve.gov/econres/feds/files/2018080pap.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt; by the Federal Reserve, published last year, found that millennial household incomes were 11% lower than they were for people in Generation X (those born between the mid-1960s and 1981) at a comparable age; they were 14% lower than for baby boomers at the same point in their lives. A growing number of young people have taken on debt to finance their studies. And because real wages have not kept up with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2018/08/07/for-most-us-workers-real-wages-have-barely-budged-for-decades/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;inflation&lt;/a&gt;, the cost of living has risen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_WOC757.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190427_WOC757.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190427_WOC757.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190427_WOC757.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190427_WOC757.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190427_WOC757.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190427_WOC757.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190427_WOC757.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190427_WOC757.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190427_WOC757.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;Worse still, the Brookings paper reports that young people’s prospects for accumulating wealth in old age are grim. Millennials do more freelance and part-time work than other generations did, which makes it more difficult to obtain an employer-provided pension. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.nirsonline.org/wp-content/uploads/2018/02/Millennials-Report-1.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Only 55%&lt;/a&gt; of this generation have access to retirement plans, compared with 77% of Generation X and 80% of baby-boomers. Moreover, those who do have employer pensions are more likely to have defined-contribution pensions than defined-benefit ones, meaning that they bear the risk if investment returns disappoint. And as America seeks to plug its &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2018/02/08/americas-extraordinary-economic-gamble&quot;&gt;long-term fiscal shortfalls&lt;/a&gt;, millennials will have to bear the burden of any future cuts to Social Security and Medicare. All of this helps to explain why the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2017/05/05/its-becoming-more-common-for-young-adults-to-live-at-home-and-for-longer-stretches/&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;share&lt;/a&gt; of people aged 25 to 34 who are living with their parents has increased from 10% in 2000 to about 15% today. That is not quite the high life millennials imagined.&lt;p&gt;But all is not lost. Millennials are living longer and are the best-educated generation in history. Taken together, this could yet mean that the youngest millennials, who have been less scarred by the crisis, could contribute towards their retirement pots for longer. Then there is mum and dad: even if they don’t become millionaires, millennials will one day inherit from their parents, and that may help redress their relative poverty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 22:07:27 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Airlines may be underestimating the cost of the 737 MAX groundings]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/gulliver/2019/04/18/airlines-may-be-underestimating-the-cost-of-the-737-max-groundings]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/000_1f706b.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-18T10:58:39Z&quot;&gt;Apr 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;IN MARCH REGULATORS around the world grounded all Boeing 737 MAX jets after two of the type crashed within five months of each other, killing 346 people. Soon afterwards Ryanair, the carrier in Europe that has placed the most orders for the new jet, insisted that the move would have little impact on its network. That was either wishful thinking or misinformation. Just three weeks later, the number of flights it had scheduled from London to Edinburgh, Britain’s busiest domestic route, fell 85%. Frequencies from London to Belfast plummeted 91%. If flights had to be axed, those ones made the most sense. Margins are tight on these routes due to high domestic aviation taxes in Britain and stiff competition from other airlines and rail firms. But the move highlights the growing toll that the MAX’s grounding is having on airlines around the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Across the Atlantic, 275 flights per day are now being cancelled by American and Southwest, the two airlines that operate the most MAXs in America. Both carriers hope to resume normal service in August, by which time Boeing hopes to have fixed the software bug that is suspected to have caused the two crashes. But the timeline is mere guesswork.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Even if accurate, it could take Boeing much longer to get the fix approved by regulators in other countries. In previous years, the quality of the regulatory processes at the Federal Aviation Administration, America’s aviation regulator, was so respected that other countries deferred to its judgement in reciprocal arrangements. But now officials in Europe and Canada want to conduct their own tests before letting the MAX back in their skies. They were dismayed and alarmed by the reluctance of the FAA to ground the jet after the second crash in Ethiopia. Some suspect that Boeing’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/03/23/regulatory-capture-may-be-responsible-for-boeings-recent-problems&quot;&gt;cosy relationship&lt;/a&gt; with its regulator may have skewed its judgement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Despite these difficulties, Boeing’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/gulliver/2019/04/07/why-boeings-shares-have-not-fallen-further-after-the-737-max-crashes&quot;&gt;share price&lt;/a&gt; is up just under a fifth since the start of the year. Investors think airlines will stand by their MAX orders given that Airbus, Boeing’s European competitor, has no spare capacity to produce more of its rival A320neo jet. But Boeing has already slowed the rate at which it assembles MAXs, down from 52 to 42 aircraft per month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;In any case, its 5,000-strong orderbook for MAX jets looks vulnerable. Garuda, an Indonesian carrier, is cancelling its 49 orders. Lion Air and Ethiopian Airlines—the two carriers that have lost MAX aircraft—are unlikely to honour their 212 orders. Other big operators might use the grounding as an excuse for trimming commitments. Even airlines loyal to the manufacturer will hit Boeing with hefty compensation bills for the extra costs that they have incurred since the planes were grounded. And the relatives of the 346 dead are likely to sue the aircraft manufacturer in great numbers as well. Boeing will not be ruined by this crisis. But nor will it emerge unscathed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 19:07:38 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ukraine elects Volodymyr Zelensky, TV star and political neophyte]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/22/ukraine-elects-volodymyr-zelensky-tv-star-and-political-neophyte]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/articles/000_1ft9pb.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-22T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WITH DANCE music blaring, drinks flowing, and ping-pong balls flying about, Volodymyr Zelensky’s election-day headquarters in Kiev felt like a nightclub. Mr Zelensky (pictured) had reason to party: as expected, the comedian-cum-candidate trounced the incumbent, Petro Poroshenko, in the presidential run-off election on April 21st. He racked up a stunning 73% of the vote against the president’s 24%. Despite having no political experience and only a vague policy platform, voters entrusted him with the helm of a country that needs radical reform and is still enmeshed in a simmering war with Russia. Best known for playing a schoolteacher who becomes president in a popular TV series called “Servant of the People”, Mr Zelensky entered his election-night festivities to the theme song from the show he has made a reality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A native Russian-speaker of Jewish heritage hailing from the south-eastern city of Kryvyi Rih, Mr Zelensky galvanised support from across the country. He carried all but one of the 25 Ukrainian regions where voting was held. (Crimea, which Russia annexed in 2014, did not hold an election.) His slick campaign targeted voters online and through social media, while largely eschewing conventional campaigning in the form of rallies and interviews. He offered broadly popular promises to maintain Ukraine’s Western-leaning course, to end the war, and to fight corruption, while proffering few specifics and promising to crowdsource important appointments and policies. He emerged as the projection of voters’ frustration with Mr Poroshenko’s checkered leadership and of their hopes for a better future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite widespread fears about challenges to the legitimacy of the vote, election day passed off smoothly. An emboldened civil society and free press helped hold politicians to account. “Information has been plentiful and accessible, no one has pressured me, this is my choice,” one Kievan nurse said after casting a vote for Mr Zelensky. Mr Poroshenko conceded promptly, promising to “accept the will of the Ukrainian people”. Five years after its revolution, Ukraine has seen competitive elections unseat a sitting president in a peaceful transition of power—a rarity in the post-Soviet region and a genuinely impressive achievement. In his first remarks after exit polls became public, Mr Zelensky nodded to this reality, and the example it may set: “To all the countries of the former Soviet Union: look at us, everything is possible.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Poroshenko’s campaign was a crude appeal to patriotism. He ran under the slogan of “Army, Language, Faith”, playing up his successes at securing an independent Ukrainian Orthodox Church and visa-free travel to the European Union. He sought to paint Mr Zelensky as dangerously inexperienced and beholden to outside interests. “He is a bright candy wrapper,” Mr Poroshenko said in a debate ahead of the vote. “There are Russians inside and fugitive oligarchs,” he added, referring to Mr Zelensky’s murky ties with Ihor Kolomoisky, a controversial oligarch whose TV channel airs his shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both the successes and the reservations about his opponent were reasonable points to draw attention to. But voters instead focused on Mr Poroshenko’s failure to fulfil the promises of the revolution that swept him to power five years ago. With corruption still rife and GDP per head in Ukraine the lowest in Europe, just 9% of Ukrainians have confidence in their government, the lowest level in the world. “I voted for Poroshenko [in 2014], but things haven’t got better,” said Nadezhda Tsaplyuk, who voted for Mr Zelensky in the district in Kiev where Mr Poroshenko won more support than anywhere else in the city in 2014. “Sure we have visa-free [travel to the EU], but I don’t have the money to go anywhere.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This malaise fuelled Mr Zelensky’s rise. Many Ukrainians expressed their choice in terms of opposition to the current regime, rather than enthusiasm for the candidate himself. “People are voting against the old authorities,” Daniil Bychenok, an 18-year-old student, said. “We don’t know what we’re voting for.” In the run-up to the vote, polls showed that 60% of those who planned to support Mr Zelensky saw it as a protest vote. “Zelensky is winning because we can’t live like this any longer,” says Vladimir Bazhanov, a pensioner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expectations for Mr Zelensky, in turn, are as high as confidence in the current regime is low. “He’ll jail a few of them and everything will get better,” Olga Podolskaya, a retired lawyer, predicted hopefully. Promising vague but radical change proved to be an effective campaign strategy. But Mr Zelensky may struggle to fulfill the hopes voters have for him. “People are waiting for a miracle, but there won’t be any miracles,” Volodymyr Fesenko, a political analyst, said ahead of the vote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite his huge victory, Mr Zelensky will face many challenges once he takes office. Rival parties will still control parliament, the Rada, which holds significant power in Ukraine’s mixed system. He will need to turn his new party, Servant of the People, named after his TV show, into a real political machine if he wants to gain control of the Rada in the autumn. Vladimir Putin still has many tools to put pressure on his new counterpart. Ukraine’s loan agreement with the International Monetary Fund stipulates further increases in household gas prices this year, measures that have already proved deeply unpopular. Disappointment from unmet expectations, in fact, is the subject of the second season of Mr Zelensky’s show, entitled “From Love to Impeachment”. As one Zelensky aide says, “We know what can happen: we wrote this all already.” After the post-election buzz wears off, the thankless reality of governing will begin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 18:06:53 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A massacre on Easter in Sri Lanka kills at least 290 people]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/21/a-massacre-on-easter-in-sri-lanka-kills-at-least-290-people]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-21T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update (22nd April 2019):&lt;/strong&gt; This is a moving news story. The death toll will be updated as it rises. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT HAS BEEN nearly ten years since the guns fell silent in Sri Lanka’s civil war. But bloodshed returned with a vengeance on Easter Sunday when a succession of explosions ripped through three churches packed with worshippers, and three five-star hotels. At least 290 people were killed and hundreds more were injured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The coincidence of the attacks with the upcoming anniversary of the Sri Lankan army’s defeat of the Tamil Tiger rebels on May 19th—ending a war that pitted the ethnic Tamil and a largely Hindu minority, against the Sinhalese Buddhist majority—may be just that. The authorities are being cautious about apportioning blame, particularly because of the recent history of communal violence on the island, both during and after the war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A senior police official said there were signs the six blasts were all suicide bombings. This was a favourite tactic of the Liberation Tigers of Tamil Eelam, but no fingers are being pointed at any Tamil groups. And suicide tactics, especially aimed at religious targets and foreign tourists, are also a hallmark of international jihadist groups. Yet the country has little history of jihadist activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The explosions were the deadliest attacks in the country since the end of the war. They took place in close succession beginning at around 8.30am. The first was at the St Sebastian Church in Negombo, a Catholic-majority area. Photographs showed tiles blown off a blackened roof and bloodied bodies on the ground. Two other explosions occurred at St Anthony’s Church in Colombo (another Catholic church), and at the Zion Church (Evangelical) in Batticaloa, around 220km east of the capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 30 minutes later, there were explosions at the Shangri-La, the Kingsbury and the Cinnamon Grand hotels in Colombo. All are five-star venues and many of the victims were enjoying Easter breakfast special offers. At least 11 foreigners were confirmed killed. Among the nationalities were Indian, Turkish, Portuguese, British and joint US-UK nationals. The authorities counted the bodies of 25 more people presumed to be foreign. The US State Department said “several” Americans had been killed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two more explosions took place later in the day, in which eight people were killed, but they appear to be related to security forces’ raids on terrorists’ suspected hideouts. Seven people were arrested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main hospital in Colombo was a scene of chaos, with hysterical relatives swarming the narrow road leading to the emergency unit amid a steady flow of ambulances. As news of the attacks spread via social media, police rushed to churches around the country and sent worshippers home. Cardinal Malcolm Ranjith, the head of the Catholic church, cancelled all other services. Security forces were later deployed to guard churches, hotels and the international airport. The government cancelled school for children whose new terms were starting Monday. Universities were declared indefinitely closed. A countrywide police curfew came into effect in the afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whoever the perpetrators may be, there are worries that the blasts will stir renewed inter-communal strife. Of Sri Lanka’s population of more than 20m people, about 75% are Sinhalese (who are mostly Buddhists). Tamils, living mostly in the north and east, make up about 11% and are predominantly Hindu. The rebellion by the Tamil Tigers lasted for 27 years. Muslims make up about 9% of the population and speak Tamil. Although they did not join the Tamil Tigers’s rebellion—and indeed some were evicted from the north by them—after the war Muslims have become the target of Buddhist-nationalist attacks. Christians, mostly Roman Catholics, make up about 7% of the population and straddle the Sinhalese-Tamil divide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The puzzle was why the Catholic church was targeted,” said Jayadeva Uyangoda, a political scientist. The spread of Catholicism dates to 1505 with Portuguese colonisation and subsequent proselytisation. Catholics permeate all levels of governance, the private sector and even the army, but they were not a particular focus of Tamil Tiger attacks during the civil war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;St Anthony’s church is patronised by both Tamils and Sinhalese, including non-Christians. Any assaults in recent times against Christians—also by Buddhist extremist groups—have been aimed against new Evangelical churches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hence the speculation about “foreign actors”, as Cardinal Ranjith put it—in particular Muslim extremists. Only a few dozen Sri Lankan Muslims are thought to have joined the tens of thousands of foreigners who volunteered to fight with the Islamic State group in Iraq and Syria. Some have worried about more radical forms of Islam being introduced to the island by contact with foreign preachers. Most alarming, in January Sri Lankan police said they uncovered a large cache of explosives at an IS training camp in the north of the country; it was apparently intended for use against several Buddhist monuments in the ancient city of Anuradhapura.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One reason to worry about the possible radicalisation of Muslims is that Sinhalese Buddhist extremists have sought to instigate and co-ordinate mob violence against them. A traffic incident in 2018 in which a Sinhalese truck driver was assaulted by four Muslim men (and subsequently died) resulted in days of attacks on Muslim homes and businesses and a large number of injuries. In 2014, there was Buddhist-Muslim sectarian violence in several towns in the south fired by the racist speech by a Buddhist monk, Galagodatte Gnarasara, who is now in prison for contempt of court (on a separate matter).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the Easter bombings, as rumours and incendiary anti-Muslim comments spread like wildfire, the government swiftly shut down all social-media platforms, including WhatsApp, Viber, Facebook and YouTube.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the hunt for the perpetrators begins, Sri Lanka will be counting the cost of a day of carnage it had not expected. The Catholic church is preparing for mass funerals, which the government has said it will pay for. The country as a whole has suffered a blow to its lucrative tourism sector. Until Easter day it had enjoyed a reputation as one of the safest countries for holidaymakers. That has changed utterly, along with much else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 18:06:52 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A massacre on Easter Sunday in Sri Lanka kills 290 people]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/21/a-massacre-on-easter-sunday-in-sri-lanka-kills-290-people]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-21T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update (22nd April 2019):&lt;/strong&gt; This is a moving news story. The death toll will be updated as it rises. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT HAS BEEN nearly ten years since the guns fell silent in Sri Lanka’s civil war. But bloodshed returned with a vengeance on Easter Sunday when a succession of explosions ripped through three churches packed with worshippers, and three five-star hotels. At least 290 people were killed and hundreds more were injured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The coincidence of the attacks with the upcoming anniversary of the Sri Lankan army’s defeat of the Tamil Tiger rebels on May 19th—ending a war that pitted the ethnic Tamil and a largely Hindu minority, against the Sinhalese Buddhist majority—may be just that. The authorities are being cautious about apportioning blame, particularly because of the recent history of communal violence on the island, both during and after the war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A senior police official said there were signs the six blasts were all suicide bombings. This was a favourite tactic of the Liberation Tigers of Tamil Eelam, but no fingers are being pointed at any Tamil groups. And suicide tactics, especially aimed at religious targets and foreign tourists, are also a hallmark of international jihadist groups. Yet the country has little history of jihadist activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The explosions were the deadliest attacks in the country since the end of the war. They took place in close succession beginning at around 8.30am. The first was at the St Sebastian Church in Negombo, a Catholic-majority area. Photographs showed tiles blown off a blackened roof and bloodied bodies on the ground. Two other explosions occurred at St Anthony’s Church in Colombo (another Catholic church), and at the Zion Church (Evangelical) in Batticaloa, around 220km east of the capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 30 minutes later, there were explosions at the Shangri-La, the Kingsbury and the Cinnamon Grand hotels in Colombo. All are five-star venues and many of the victims were enjoying Easter breakfast special offers. At least 11 foreigners were confirmed killed. Among the nationalities were Indian, Turkish, Portuguese, British and joint US-UK nationals. The authorities counted the bodies of 25 more people presumed to be foreign. The US State Department said “several” Americans had been killed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two more explosions took place later in the day, in which eight people were killed, but they appear to be related to security forces’ raids on terrorists’ suspected hideouts. Seven people were arrested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main hospital in Colombo was a scene of chaos, with hysterical relatives swarming the narrow road leading to the emergency unit amid a steady flow of ambulances. As news of the attacks spread via social media, police rushed to churches around the country and sent worshippers home. Cardinal Malcolm Ranjith, the head of the Catholic church, cancelled all other services. Security forces were later deployed to guard churches, hotels and the international airport. The government cancelled school for children whose new terms were starting Monday. Universities were declared indefinitely closed. A countrywide police curfew came into effect in the afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whoever the perpetrators may be, there are worries that the blasts will stir renewed inter-communal strife. Of Sri Lanka’s population of more than 20m people, about 75% are Sinhalese (who are mostly Buddhists). Tamils, living mostly in the north and east, make up about 11% and are predominantly Hindu. The rebellion by the Tamil Tigers lasted for 27 years. Muslims make up about 9% of the population and speak Tamil. Although they did not join the Tamil Tigers’s rebellion—and indeed some were evicted from the north by them—after the war Muslims have become the target of Budhist-nationalist attacks. Christians, mostly Roman Catholics, make up about 7% of the population and straddle the Sinhalese-Tamil divide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The puzzle was why the Catholic church was targeted,” said Jayadeva Uyangoda, a political scientist. The spread of Catholicism dates to 1505 with Portuguese colonisation and subsequent proselytisation. Catholics permeate all levels of governance, the private sector and even the army, but they were not a particular focus of Tamil Tiger attacks during the civil war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;St Anthony’s church is patronised by both Tamils and Sinhalese, including non-Christians. Any assaults in recent times against Christians—also by Buddhist extremist groups—have been aimed against new Evangelical churches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hence the speculation about “foreign actors”, as Cardinal Ranjith put it—in particular Muslim extremists. Only a few dozen Sri Lankan Muslims are thought to have joined the tens of thousands of foreigners who volunteered to fight with the Islamic State group in Iraq and Syria. Some have worried about more radical forms of Islam being introduced to the island by contact with foreign preachers. Most alarming, in January Sri Lankan police said they uncovered a large cache of explosives at an IS training camp in the north of the country; it was apparently intended for use against several Buddhist monuments in the ancient city of Anuradhapura.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One reason to worry about the possible radicalisation of Muslims is that Sinhalese Buddhist extremists have sought to instigate and co-ordinate mob violence against them. A traffic incident in 2018 in which a Sinhalese truck driver was assaulted by four Muslim men (and subsequently died) resulted in days of attacks on Muslim homes and businesses and a large number of injuries. In 2014, there was Buddhist-Muslim sectarian violence in several towns in the south fired by the racist speech by a Buddhist monk, Galagodatte Gnarasara, who is now in prison for contempt of court (on a separate matter).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the Easter bombings, as rumours and incendiary anti-Muslim comments spread like wildfire, the government swiftly shut down all social-media platforms, including WhatsApp, Viber, Facebook and YouTube.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the hunt for the perpetrators begins, Sri Lanka will be counting the cost of a day of carnage it had not expected. The Catholic church is preparing for mass funerals, which the government has said it will pay for. The country as a whole has suffered a blow to its lucrative tourism sector. Until Easter day it had enjoyed a reputation as one of the safest countries for holidaymakers. That has changed utterly, along with much else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 16:54:24 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Easter massacre in Sri Lanka kills more than 200 people]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/21/easter-massacre-in-sri-lanka-kills-more-than-200-people]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-21T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IT HAS BEEN nearly ten years since the guns fell silent in Sri Lanka’s civil war. But bloodshed returned with a vengeance on Easter Sunday when a succession of explosions ripped through three churches packed with worshippers, and three five-star hotels. At least 207 people were killed and hundreds more were injured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The coincidence of the attacks with the upcoming anniversary of the Sri Lankan army’s defeat of the Tamil Tiger rebels on May 19th—ending a war that pitted the ethnic Tamil and a largely Hindu minority, against the Sinhalese Buddhist majority—may be just that. The authorities are being cautious about apportioning blame, particularly because of the recent history of communal violence on the island, both during and after the war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A senior police official said there were signs the six blasts were all suicide bombings. This was a favourite tactic of the Liberation Tigers of Tamil Eelam, but no fingers are being pointed at any Tamil groups. And suicide tactics, especially aimed at religious targets and foreign tourists, are also a hallmark of international jihadist groups. Yet the country has little history of jihadist activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The explosions were the deadliest attacks in the country since the end of the war. They took place in close succession beginning around 8.30 am. The first was at the St Sebastian Church in Negombo, a Catholic-majority area. Photographs showed tiles blown off a blackened roof and bloodied bodies on the ground. Two other explosions occurred at St Anthony’s Church in Colombo (another Catholic church), and at the Zion Church (Evangelical) in Batticaloa, around 220km east of the capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 30 minutes later, there were explosions at the Shangri-La, the Kingsbury and the Cinnamon Grand hotels in Colombo. All are five-star venues and many of the victims were enjoying Easter breakfast special offers. At least 11 foreigners were confirmed killed. Among the nationalities were Indian, Turkish, Portuguese, British and joint US-UK nationals. The authorities counted the bodies of 25 more people presumed to be foreign. The US State Department said “several” Americans had been killed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two more explosions took place later in the day, in which eight people were killed, but they appear to be related to security forces’ raids on terrorists’ suspected hideouts. Seven people were arrested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main hospital in Colombo was a scene of chaos, with hysterical relatives swarming the narrow road leading to the emergency unit amid a steady flow of ambulances. As news of the attacks spread via social media, police rushed to churches around the country and sent worshippers home. Cardinal Malcolm Ranjith, the head of the Catholic church, cancelled all other services. Security forces were later deployed to guard churches, hotels and the international airport. The government cancelled school for children whose new terms were starting Monday. Universities were declared indefinitely closed. A countrywide police curfew came into effect in the afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whoever the perpetrators may be, there are worries that the blasts will stir renewed inter-communal strife. Of Sri Lanka’s population of more than 20m people, about 75% are Sinhalese (who are mostly Buddhists). Tamils, living mostly in the north and east, make up about 11% and are predominantly Hindu. The rebellion by the Tamil Tigers lasted for 27 years. Muslims make up about 9% and speak Tamil. Although they did not join the Tamil Tigers’s rebellion—and indeed some were evicted from the north by them—after the war Muslims have become the target of Budhist nationalist attacks. Christians, mostly Roman Catholics, make up about 7% of the population and straddle the Sinhalese-Tamil divide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The puzzle was why the Catholic church was targeted,” said Jayadeva Uyangoda, a political scientist. The spread of Catholicism dates to 1505 with Portuguese colonisation and subsequent proselytization. Catholics permeate all levels of governance, the private sector and even the army, but they were not a particular focus of Tamil Tiger attacks during the civil war.&lt;br/&gt;St Anthony’s church is patronised by both Tamils and Sinhalese, including non-Christians. Any assaults in recent times against Christians—also by Buddhist extremist groups—have been aimed against new Evangelical churches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hence the speculation about “foreign actors”, as Cardinal Ranjith put it—in particular Muslim extremists. Only a few dozen Sri Lankan Muslims are thought to have joined the tens of thousands of foreigners who volunteered to fight with the Islamic State group in Iraq and Syria. Some have worried about more radical forms of Islam being introduced to the island by contact with foreign preachers. Most alarming, in January Sri Lankan police said they uncovered a large cache of explosives at an IS training camp in the north of the country; it was apparently intended for use against several Buddhist monuments in the ancient city of Anuradhapura.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One reason to worry about the possible radicalisation of Muslims is that Sinhalese Buddhist extremists have sought to instigate and coordinate mob violence against them. A traffic incident in 2018 in which a Sinhalese truck driver was assaulted by four Muslim men (and subsequently died) resulted in days of attacks on Muslim homes and businesses and a large number of injuries. Earlier, in 2014, there was Buddhist-Muslim sectarian violence in several towns in the south fired by the racist speech by a Buddhist monk, Galagodatte Gnarasara, who is now in prison for contempt of court (on a separate matter).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the Easter bombings, as rumours and incendiary anti-Muslim comments spread like wildfire, the government swiftly shut down all social-media platforms, including WhatsApp, Viber, Facebook and YouTube.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the hunt for the perpetrators begins, Sri Lanka will be counting the cost of a day of carnage it had not expected. The Catholic church is preparing for mass funerals, which the government has said it will pay for. The country as a whole has suffered a blow to its lucrative tourism sector. Until Easter day it had enjoyed a reputation as one of the safest countries for holidaymakers. That has changed utterly, along with much else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 03:14:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Easter day massacre in Sri Lanka kills more than 200 people]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/21/easter-day-massacre-in-sri-lanka-kills-more-than-200-people]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-21T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IT HAS BEEN nearly ten years since the guns fell silent in Sri Lanka’s civil war. But bloodshed returned with a vengeance on Easter day when a succession of explosions ripped through three churches packed with worshippers, and three five-star hotels. At least 207 people were killed and hundreds more were injured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The coincidence of the attacks with the upcoming anniversary of the Sri Lankan army’s defeat of the Tamil Tiger rebels on May 19th—ending a war that pitted the ethnic Tamil and a largely Hindu minority, against the Sinhalese Buddhist majority—may be just that. The authorities are being cautious about apportioning blame, particularly because of the recent history of communal violence on the island, both during and after the war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A senior police official said there were signs the six blasts were all suicide bombings. This was a favourite tactic of the Liberation Tigers of Tamil Eelam, but no fingers are being pointed at any Tamil groups. And suicide tactics, especially aimed at religious targets and foreign tourists, are also a hallmark of international jihadist groups. Yet the country has little history of jihadist activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The explosions were the deadliest attacks in the country since the end of the war. They took place in close succession beginning around 8.30 am. The first was at the St Sebastian Church in Negombo, a Catholic-majority area. Photographs showed tiles blown off a blackened roof and bloodied bodies on the ground. Two other explosions occurred at St Anthony’s Church in Colombo (another Catholic church), and at the Zion Church (Evangelical) in Batticaloa, around 220km east of the capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 30 minutes later, there were explosions at the Shangri-La, the Kingsbury and the Cinnamon Grand hotels in Colombo. All are five-star venues and many of the victims were enjoying Easter breakfast special offers. At least 11 foreigners were confirmed killed. Among the nationalities were Indian, Turkish, Portuguese, British and joint US-UK nationals. The authorities counted the bodies of 25 more people presumed to be foreign. The US State Department said “several” Americans had been killed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two more explosions took place later in the day, in which eight people were killed, but they appear to be related to security forces’ raids on terrorists’ suspected hideouts. Seven people were arrested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main hospital in Colombo was a scene of chaos, with hysterical relatives swarming the narrow road leading to the emergency unit amid a steady flow of ambulances. As news of the attacks spread via social media, police rushed to churches around the country and sent worshippers home. Cardinal Malcolm Ranjith, the head of the Catholic church, cancelled all other services. Security forces were later deployed to guard churches, hotels and the international airport. The government cancelled school for children whose new terms were starting Monday. Universities were declared indefinitely closed. A countrywide police curfew came into effect in the afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whoever the perpetrators may be, there are worries that the blasts will stir renewed inter-communal strife. Of Sri Lanka’s population of more than 20m people, about 75% are Sinhalese (who are mostly Buddhists). Tamils, living mostly in the north and east, make up about 11% and are predominantly Hindu. The rebellion by the Tamil Tigers lasted for 27 years. Muslims make up about 9% and speak Tamil. Although they did not join the Tamil Tigers’s rebellion—and indeed some were evicted from the north by them—after the war Muslims have become the target of Budhist nationalist attacks. Christians, mostly Roman Catholics, make up about 7% of the population and straddle the Sinhalese-Tamil divide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The puzzle was why the Catholic church was targeted,” said Jayadeva Uyangoda, a political scientist. The spread of Catholicism dates to 1505 with Portuguese colonisation and subsequent proselytization. Catholics permeate all levels of governance, the private sector and even the army, but they were not a particular focus of Tamil Tiger attacks during the civil war.&lt;br/&gt;St Anthony’s church is patronised by both Tamils and Sinhalese, including non-Christians. Any assaults in recent times against Christians—also by Buddhist extremist groups—have been aimed against new Evangelical churches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hence the speculation about “foreign actors”, as Cardinal Ranjith put it—in particular Muslim extremists. Only a few dozen Sri Lankan Muslims are thought to have joined the tens of thousands of foreigners who volunteered to fight with the Islamic State group in Iraq and Syria. Some have worried about more radical forms of Islam being introduced to the island by contact with foreign preachers. Most alarming, in January Sri Lankan police said they uncovered a large cache of explosives at an IS training camp in the north of the country; it was apparently intended for use against several Buddhist monuments in the ancient city of Anuradhapura.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One reason to worry about the possible radicalisation of Muslims is that Sinhalese Buddhist extremists have sought to instigate and coordinate mob violence against them. A traffic incident in 2018 in which a Sinhalese truck driver was assaulted by four Muslim men (and subsequently died) resulted in days of attacks on Muslim homes and businesses and a large number of injuries. Earlier, in 2014, there was Buddhist-Muslim sectarian violence in several towns in the south fired by the racist speech by a Buddhist monk, Galagodatte Gnarasara, who is now in prison for contempt of court (on a separate matter).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the Easter bombings, as rumours and incendiary anti-Muslim comments spread like wildfire, the government swiftly shut down all social-media platforms, including WhatsApp, Viber, Facebook and YouTube.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the hunt for the perpetrators begins, Sri Lanka will be counting the cost of a day of carnage it had not expected. The Catholic church is preparing for mass funerals, which the government has said it will pay for. The country as a whole has suffered a blow to its lucrative tourism sector. Until Easter day it had enjoyed a reputation as one of the safest countries for holidaymakers. That has changed utterly, along with much else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 02:06:34 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can opera seduce a new generation?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/19/can-opera-seduce-a-new-generation]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_blp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-19T16:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ANNE MCELVOY goes backstage at New York’s newest arts centre, the Shed, to talk to Renée Fleming, a Grammy-winning soprano. They discuss bending the rules of genre and gender opposite Ben Whishaw in “Norma Jeane Baker of Troy”, why opera isn’t in trouble, and how to reclaim the title of “diva” for the 21st century. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-reneefleming&quot; width=&quot;500&amp;amp;quot;&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com&amp;amp;gt;Apple Podcasts | &amp;amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com https:=&quot;&quot; spotify=&quot;&quot; com=&quot;&quot; show=&quot;&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWVjb25vbWlzdGFza3M&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=142125&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/Business--Economics-Podcasts/The-Economist-Asks-p999213/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 00:06:40 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[On “Game of Thrones”, Conservatism, Israel and Lidl]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/bagehots-notebook/2019/04/19/on-game-of-thrones-conservatism-israel-and-lidl]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_blp909.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-19T10:08:16Z&quot;&gt;Apr 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“GAME of Thrones”, which, in case you hadn’t noticed, returned for its eighth and final season this week, has already had a profound impact on the television industry (if you’re a TV producer with an idea for a multi-series drama your chances of getting a green light have skyrocketed). Let’s hope it has an equally profound impact on the history industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past few decades academics have focused on history from below—hence all those university seminars on bastardy in 15th-century Nottingham and hand-loom weavers in 18th-century Lincoln. They have done this for obvious intellectual reasons: Karl Marx’s contention that “the history of all hitherto existing societies is the history of class struggle” is undoubtedly a powerful insight. Added to this is a sociological reason: the vast expansion of the universities (and the arrival of a more socially and ethnically diverse student population) means that historians are reluctant to teach the same thing as they did when they were training a future ruling class. A changing student body requires a changing curriculum. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Game of Thrones” suggests they were doubly wrong. They are wrong about demand: even in a democratic age people are fixated on the old-fashioned history of kings and queens: that is the history of people who combine something that is quite unusual (lots of power) with other things that are quite usual (personal quirks and family quarrels). History may be in decline as an option in universities precisely because it focuses so much on history from below rather than on history from above. In some ways “Game of Thrones” is a dramatic presentation of Walter Bagehot’s great insight about the British monarchy, that it thrived in a democratic age precisely because it humanised power by putting a family and its foibles on the throne.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They are also wrong about something more fundamental. “Game of Thrones” is compelling precisely because it recognises that dynastic struggles have often taken precedence over class struggles. Up until the first world war, the world was run by a collection of dynasties that possessed every human foible imaginable (from insanity to dwarfism to incestuous longings) and who spent their lives playing the game of thrones: forming dynastic alliances, sometimes even marrying their relatives, going to war over rival family claims to the throne and, above all, scheming to maximise their power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Game of Thrones” gets a remarkable number of big things right about the nature of dynastic societies. One is that the dynastic principle eliminates the difference between the public and private realms, a difference that is fundamental to democratic and meritocratic societies. Public life in a dynasty is shaped by the personal foibles of the monarch. Power is wielded by people who can get physically close to the king. The world’s oldest political offices are all related to the monarch’s physical needs—looking after his horse or falcons, or guarding his bedchamber—and were usually reserved for members of his own family or the most blue-blooded aristocrats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A second is that dynasties put biology at the heart of society. The fate of kingdoms depends on the physical fitness of kings and their ability to produce male heirs (Britain arguably had its first Brexit, the Reformation, because of Henry VIII’s difficulties in producing a male heir). Political dynasties can become global powers if they can marry the right people and produce enough children (the Saxe-Coburgs were the greatest dynasty builders of the 18th and 19th centuries, succeeding first in capturing the British throne and then, because of Queen Victoria’s clever marriage scheming, putting their progeny on the thrones of most of Europe). Royal daughters had to expect to be pawns in the game of alliance building.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of which leads me to unveil my idea for an HBO production of my own: a history of the Habsburg dynasty. This would be relatively cheap by the standards of recent productions: most of the great Habsburg palaces are still intact and Vienna’s museums are stuffed full of suits of armour, portraits, furniture, table settings etc. And the story is every bit as weird as the story of the “Game of Thrones”. The Habsburgs were so prone to in-breeding that people joked that they married their cousins and slept with their siblings. Charles II of Spain was a mass of genetic problems: his head was too big for his body and his tongue was too big for his mouth, so that he had difficulty speaking, and constantly drooled; his first wife complained that he suffered from premature ejaculation and his second wife that he was impotent; as if that wasn’t enough, he also suffered from convulsions. He died at 39, mercifully without an heir. These personal peccadilloes didn’t prevent the Hapsburgs from becoming champion players of the game of thrones, producing one of the most far-flung and enduring empires the world has seen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;**** &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“CONSERVATIVE” is one of those words that comes with an implied question: what is it that you want to conserve? Britain’s Conservative Party is in such turmoil at the moment because it is at sixes and sevens over its answer to this question. In the Cameron-Osborne years it wanted to conserve the Clinton-Blair consensus: that is a combination of free-market economics (symbolised by support for globalisation), social liberalism (symbolised by support for gay marriage) and government activism, particularly in the creation of human capital. That was always an elite project that failed to stir the emotions of most conservative voters and, when it came to gay marriage and hyper-globalisation, may well have repelled them. But it was an elite project that was destroyed in the flames of the Iraq war, arguably the first and last war of neo-conservative globalisation, and the 2008 financial crisis. Now the battle is on between three different answers to the question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most powerful is the nation-state. The heart of Brexit is not racism (as some Remainers annoyingly claim) or a desire to be truly global as opposed to narrowly European-focused (as Boris Johnson pretends). It is the desire to restore the sovereignty of the nation-state. Brexiteers don’t just dislike the demands that the European Union poses in terms of agreeing to its rules and regulations. They dislike the idea, beloved of some if not all in Brussels, that the nation-state is an anachronism that we need to get beyond. The fury of the Brexiteers’ resistance to Theresa May’s half-way house approach to Brexit, combined with the flight of many Conservative voters to the Brexit Party, suggests that, to survive, the Conservative Party may have no choice but to become the party of the nation-state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This defence of the nation-state is linked to a broader defence of the traditional British way of life: that is, Britain’s green and pleasant land (Michael Gove’s agenda at the department of the environment); its provincial cities (the devolution initiative and the creation of new mayors); its built environment (the department of housing’s “building beautiful” initiative which has been sadly overshadowed by the row about Sir Roger Scruton).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A second answer is the traditional values of family and faith. This is the answer that the Cameroons most disliked. Proclaiming a faith in God or a belief in the traditional family was a sure way of getting yourself kicked off the Notting Hill dinner-party invitation list. But they were not alone: Theresa May, the daughter of a vicar and a regular churchgoer, initially embraced transgender rights on the grounds that it was the new gay marriage. The Conservative grassroots are rather more tradition-minded than this, particularly when it comes to transgender activists. Jacob Rees-Mogg has demonstrated that you can win a large grassroots following by speaking out unashamedly for “faith and family”, particularly if you link defence of faith and family to defence of the nation-state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A third answer is the capitalist system. The Conservative Party has traditionally been the party of business and the City—indeed there was a time, between the wars, when the party was actually dominated by businessmen such as Stanley Baldwin, whose family owned an ironworks, and Neville Chamberlain, whose family once produced a third of the world’s nails. I suspect that Hammond, the chancellor of the exchequer, believes that his party’s main job is to create a favourable environment for business, though he doesn’t exactly wear his political philosophy on his sleeve. The same may be true of Jeremy Hunt, the foreign secretary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A closely connected answer is “freedom”. Many Tories regard the defence of capitalism as part of a broader defence of freedom. (They also argue, from a public-relations point of view, that “freedom” is a much easier sell than “capitalism”.) Liz Truss, Mr Hammond’s underling as chief secretary of the Treasury and a woman who exudes leadership ambition from every paw, is a leading proponent of this school. Her shtick is to update Mrs Thatcher’s freedom agenda for a populist age: continue with the Thatcherite policies of deregulating markets and encouraging competition but also put a heavy emphasis on the gig economy and social liberalism. Her aim is to reinforce the Thatcherite revolution by showing young people that their personal interests, both as consumers and as young professionals, lies in embracing the start-up economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some Conservatives would no doubt argue that the proper answer to the question is “all of the above”: you need a fusion of all these things for each one of them to make sense—for example, you can’t defend Britain’s built environment without having the wherewithal provided by a successful economy. They would also argue that defending Britain’s nation-state—particularly the nation-state’s ability to generate wealth—sometimes entails sacrificing sovereignty to the European Union.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This “fusionist” position is the default position of the party’s pragmatic establishment. But the logic of current politics—not just because of the Brexit debate but also because of the surge of populism—is to force people to make choices that they’ve previously been able to avoid. Conservatives increasingly feel that they have to make a choice between the nation-state and business—and indeed between traditional values and business. Businesses have made it abundantly clear that they have little time for small-minded nationalism. The global market is their God. They have also made it pretty clear that they don’t have that much time for other important conservative virtues such as defending the family or community: Hollywood pumps out material that undermines the traditional families. Big companies such as HSBC (which has plastered London with annoying ads) is determined to prove how woke it is. Big data companies yoke the values of the millennium left with the business practices of the robber barons. I’m sure that Boris Johnson expressed the views of a growing number of Conservatives when he splutterd “fuck business”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;**** &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PROGNOSTICATORS are always thinking that they have discovered “the future” in some bit of the world or other. Hegel thought that he had discovered it in Prussia and John Reed in Soviet Russia (“I have seen the future and it works”). In the 1960s there was almost a consensus that the future lay in California. At the risk of sounding as idiotic as John Reed I would like to nominate Israel. I recently spent a week in that extraordinary country in order to get a break from writing about Brexit. I was repeatedly struck by the extent to which Israel prefigures trends that are spreading around much of the world: the rise of religion and nationalism; the coexistence of a high-tech sector with orthodox communities; the division of society into rival communities that are so hostile to each other that they need to be kept apart by a wall; and the rise of strongmen leaders who argue, in effect, that the imperatives of national security override namby-pamby worries about civil rights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the wake of the second world war the survivors of the Holocaust drew a sharply different conclusion from Nazism than the victorious Allies. The Allies concluded that nationalism needed to be constrained or even, in the case of the architects of the European Union, transcended. By contrast Zionists concluded that the Jewish people needed a nation-state of their own where they could be made safe from any potential enemies—and where they could allow their culture to flourish as never before. Today dreams of a post-nationalist future are dying and the idea that peoples need a place that they can call home for reasons of both self-fulfilment and self-protection is once more on the rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;****&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DURING my Israel adventure I stopped off at a motor stop between Jerusalem and Nazareth. I was struck by the way that Arabs in traditional dress mixed easily with Israeli soldiers (though who knows what was going on in their heads). I was also impressed by the way that a familiar modern economy and a traditional barter economy seemed to co-exist—having handed over my money for a cappuccino in exactly the same way as I would in London, I was approached by Bedouin hawkers trying to sell cordless drills and rides on a camel. How exotic! I thought until I recalled my own experiences back in England. I frequently visit Liddle to buy necessities (bread, grapes, chocolate) only to emerge with a cordless drill or a “smart bicycle helmet” that signals which way you’re turning. The prices are so low that it seems foolish to pass by the jumble of weird goods placed in the centre of the store. All Liddle needs now is a camel or two&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;****&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BACK from the Holy Land I went to the dentist with a toothache. The dentist poked around for a bit, ummed and erred, and referred me to a root-canal specialist. I showed up to the specialist full of dread about the pain, not to mention the cost, of another root canal. A bit more poking and prodding and the specialist pronounced that she couldn’t find anything wrong with my root canals. So why the persistent toothache? She asked me if I had been under any unusual pressure that might have resulted in me clenching my teeth together more than usual. When I replied that I was a political journalist writing about Brexit she immediately pronounced that “that would explain it…it’s bad enough for the rest of us without having to write about it”. Brexit is a toothache as well as a headache. I’m sending my dental bill to Boris Johnson. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 00:06:39 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>