<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[The threat of war between America and Iran, the shrinking Mexican-American population and hot French baby names]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/09/the-threat-of-war-between-america-and-iran-the-shrinking-mexican-american-population-and-hot-french-baby-names]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-09T16:30:55Z&quot;&gt;May 9th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THIS WEEK, our cover story reports on the brewing conflict between &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/11/the-brewing-conflict-between-america-and-iran&quot;&gt;America and Iran&lt;/a&gt;. Also, why the Mexican-American population is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/11/the-mexican-american-population-is-shrinking&quot;&gt;shrinking&lt;/a&gt; (10:05). And, what the latest trends in baby names say about how France is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/11/what-french-baby-names-say-about-the-country&quot;&gt;changing&lt;/a&gt; (17:34)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-may9th2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:07:55 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A court says Ohio’s congressional map is unconstitutional]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/09/a-court-says-ohios-congressional-map-is-unconstitutional]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_USP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-09T15:06:12Z&quot;&gt;May 9th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A BOOK-LENGTH &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.brennancenter.org/sites/default/files/legal-work/2019-05-03-262-Opinion%20and%20Order.pdf&quot;&gt;opinion&lt;/a&gt; striking down Ohio’s congressional map by a panel of three federal judges on May 3rd was written with one particular readership in mind—the justices of the Supreme Court. They have the last word on whether the constitution imposes limits on partisan line-drawing. The federal judges, appointees of George W. Bush, Bill Clinton and Barack Obama, explained how Ohio’s map was rigged to ensure that 12 of the state’s 16 seats in the House of Representatives would go to Republicans despite voters’ fairly even red-blue divide. The ruling concludes that “a predominant partisan intent infected the whole map” in violation of the federal constitution, and orders the state to introduce a remedial map by June 14th. (If the deadline passes without an acceptable map, the court will have one drawn up.) But with an appeal on its way to the Supreme Court—and similar cases pending there involving gerrymanders in Maryland and North Carolina—the staying power of the ruling against Ohio’s map is in the hands of the nine justices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 301-page ruling opens with a detailed account of how Ohio’s “remarkably pro-Republican redistricting bill” was crafted and adopted without Democratic input after the 2010 census. Republican legislators gathered in a DoubleTree hotel room stripped of its usual furnishings and, using three computers, ran “Maptitude”, software that allows cartographers to draw lines “down to the census block unit” and see “corresponding demographic and historical election data for the newly drawn districts in real time”. By the time the draughtsmen unveiled the maps to the legislature, the district lines had been tweaked and polished with the help of Republican consultants masterminding similar efforts in other states. Governor John Kasich signed House Bill 369 into law on September 26th 2011. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Relying on testimony from lawmakers, legislative staffers and political scientists, and based on their own examination of the district lines, the judges analysed Ohio’s congressional map by asking three questions. Did Republicans intend to stymie Democrats in the House elections? Did they succeed? And are there reasons other than pursuing a partisan advantage that could explain the contours of the districts? The answers were yes, yes and no. Republicans gerrymandered on purpose, with stunning success, and no evidence suggests the maps served any function other than to guarantee a 3-to-1 advantage for the Republican Party. “[I]nvidious partisan intent”, and nothing else, marked the map-drawing process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ruling in &lt;em&gt;Ohio A. Philip Randolph Institute v Householder&lt;/em&gt; explains why the plaintiffs have the legal right to sue in court, the issue on which a challenge to a Wisconsin gerrymander &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2018/06/19/the-supreme-court-dodges-big-decisions-on-partisan-redistricting&quot;&gt;foundered&lt;/a&gt; at the Supreme Court last year. It walks through each relevant district, pointing out oddities and laying out how the Democratic plaintiffs were harmed by being “packed” together or by having their influence “cracked” into multiple Republican strongholds. It discusses several metrics political scientists use to measure the extent of cartographical partisanship. And it argues that Ohio’s map dilutes Democrats’ votes in violation of the First and Fourteenth Amendments as well as the Election Clause of Article I. But the heart of the opinion—the passage where the three judges are all but beseeching the nine justices to jump on the anti-gerrymandering bandwagon—is a 10-page section entitled “Pragmatic and Historical Considerations”. Here, the three judges speak clearly and directly to the men and women who will be reviewing their ruling and the companion gerrymandering cases from Maryland and North Carolina.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each of the four points in this section seeks to allay justices’ worries about “justiciability”—the ability of courts to subdue partisan map-makers. First the judges sought to address Chief Justice John Roberts’s concern in the 2017 &lt;em&gt;Gill v Whitford&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/oral_arguments/argument_transcripts/2017/16-1161_bpm1.pdf&quot;&gt;argument&lt;/a&gt; that the court will look like it is siding with one party or another each time it blesses or rejects an electoral map. The impression that the justices are playing favourites will cause, he said, “very serious harm to the status and integrity of the decisions of this court in the eyes of the country”. Not so, the Ohio panel said. Courts are “only fixing &lt;em&gt;the process&lt;/em&gt; by which voters enact political change” when they keep an eye on gerrymandered maps. Scrutinising district lines, Justice Felix Frankfurter wrote in 1946, could be a fraught exercise that brings judges into &amp;quot;the political thicket&amp;quot;; Paul Clement, the lawyer defending the North Carolina gerrymander, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/oral_arguments/argument_transcripts/2018/18-422_5hd5.pdf&quot;&gt;cited that warning&lt;/a&gt; on March 26th. But it is the Supreme Court’s &amp;quot;obligation”, even if &amp;quot;unwelcome&amp;quot;, the Ohio panel wrote, to crack down on politicians seeking to hamstring voters. The justices should not shrink from their duty to “level the playing field” when nefarious actors meddle with the right to vote. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The three-judge panel also refuted Mr Clement’s contention, quoting Justice Sandra Day O’Connor in 1986, that gerrymandering is a “self-limiting enterprise”. That ship has sailed, the court argued. Advances in technology and data-collection (as Justice Elena Kagan wrote last year) “insulat[e] officeholders against all but the most titanic shifts in the political tides”. As for the oft-heard argument that gerrymandering is as old as the republic, the panel noted that the Federalists saw the practice as “a blow at the constitution and a travesty upon the Bill of Rights when it allowed the minority to govern.” That blow is only amplified two centuries later. And the judges threw cold water on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/02/are-states-equipped-to-tackle-partisan-gerrymandering-on-their-own&quot;&gt;suggestions&lt;/a&gt; from several justices that gerrymandering can be fixed via state efforts. It would be “absurd”, the judges wrote, to stay out of the thicket and ask plaintiffs to seek redress from “the entity that committed the alleged violation in the first place”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will the judges who tossed out the Ohio map—together with similar panels striking down gerrymanders in Wisconsin, Maryland, North Carolina and, most recently, Michigan—persuade the Supreme Court to finally take a stand against partisan redistricting? None of the justices seems to enjoy handling a raft of gerrymandering complaints. Justice Breyer lamented in 2016 that racial gerrymandering cases—requiring the justices to wade through “5,000-page records”—just keep coming, year after year. He and other justices are not keen to play map overseer for a new category of skewed-line complaints. But it would seem almost contemptuous for the justices to reject the growing consensus among their lower-court colleagues that gerrymandering claims belong in court and that workable standards exist to adjudicate them. If the Supreme Court gives the green light to contorted line-drawing, attorney Paul Smith said in a 2017 hearing, the coming decade will bring &amp;quot;a festival of gerrymandering the likes of which this country has never seen&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:07:54 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The threat of war between America and Iran, why the Mexican-American population is shrinking and trending French baby names]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/09/the-threat-of-war-between-america-and-iran-why-the-mexican-american-population-is-shrinking-and-trending-french-baby-names]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-09T16:30:55Z&quot;&gt;May 9th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A selection of three essential articles read aloud from the latest issue of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;. This week, our cover story reports on the brewing conflict between &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/11/the-brewing-conflict-between-america-and-iran&quot;&gt;America and Iran&lt;/a&gt;. Both sides need to step back. Also, why the Mexican-American population is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/11/the-mexican-american-population-is-shrinking&quot;&gt;shrinking&lt;/a&gt;, despite headlines from the southern border (10:05). And, what the latest trends in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/11/what-french-baby-names-say-about-the-country&quot;&gt;baby names&lt;/a&gt; say about how France is changing (17:34)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-may9th2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:06:50 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lyft’s revenues double, losses quintuple—and prospects darken]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/11/lyfts-revenues-double-losses-quintuple-and-prospects-darken]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_wbp501_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-11T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;O&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;N MARCH&lt;/small&gt; 29th Lyft became the first ride-hailing company traded on a stockmarket. The company’s share price jumped by 9% on its debut, valuing it at $22.4bn. By May 7th, the day it reported results for the first quarter as a public company, it was worth $17bn. Some investors thought even that was too generous. Lyft’s share price fell by another 11% the next day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although it posted quarterly revenues of $776m, nearly double the level a year ago, the company also recorded a loss of $1.14bn, more than it lost in all of 2018. Most of that was down to booking stock-based compensation plans for employees, who earned $894m from Lyft’s initial public offering. Lyft’s chief financial officer, Brian Roberts, conceded that 2019 would be its “peak loss year”. It will “move steadily towards profitability” thereafter, he promised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How that might happen is unclear. Lyft is still bleeding cash, even excluding employees’ compensation, as sales and marketing and insurance costs rise. The firm’s adjusted operating loss of $230m showed little improvement on the prior year despite fast top-line growth. And Lyft forecast that sales growth in the second quarter of 2019 would slow down sharply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everything that is true of Lyft also holds for Uber—only more so. The ride-hailing goliath was due to list its shares on the New York Stock Exchange on May 10th with a market capitalisation several times Lyft’s. Its losses, too, are larger. According to Uber’s own unaudited first-quarter results, it lost another $1bn or so in the first three months of the year. That brings the total since it was founded in 2009 to $9bn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_WBC887.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190511_WBC887.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190511_WBC887.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190511_WBC887.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190511_WBC887.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190511_WBC887.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190511_WBC887.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190511_WBC887.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190511_WBC887.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190511_WBC887.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both firms have enough cash to continue to burn money for years, but public investors expect a rapid path to profitability. Making it into the black will require either raising prices or reducing the cut of bookings passed on to drivers. The former will be hard; in many markets ride-hailing competes with other cheap modes of transport, such as buses, bicycles and riders’ own cars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latter looks harder still. Drivers on both platforms complain of earnings that barely cover the cost of living. They staged a global strike to coincide with Uber’s &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt;. That is why Lyft and Uber are keen to get rid of drivers altogether. During its earnings call Lyft announced that riders in Phoenix will soon be able to book one of ten robotaxis (all with human safety drivers to begin with). These will be provided by Waymo, the autonomous-car arm of Google’s parent company, Alphabet. In March Uber raised $1bn for its own self-driving venture from investors including Toyota, a Japanese car giant. Both firms’ initiatives have doubtless been designed to signal to Wall Street that there is a way to make red ink turn into gold. Perhaps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Business&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Public distress&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 21:06:50 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America ratchets up the pressure in its trade war with China]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/09/america-ratchets-up-the-pressure-in-its-trade-war-with-china]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_fnp001_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-09T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 9th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;C&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HINA’S PROPAGANDA&lt;/small&gt; machine grinds slowly. But its output is nothing if not consistent. It took more than 24 hours for state media to report President Donald Trump’s threats, tweeted on May 5th, to ratchet up tariffs on China. By that time Chinese stocks had already plunged, a foretaste of global market ructions. When the response finally came in official editorials, it was a familiar refrain from China’s canon of trade-war statements: “We do not want to fight, but we are not afraid to fight and, given no choice, we will fight.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That sounds bellicose. Yet one lesson from the past year’s dispute with America is that China places more weight on the sentence’s first part, its desire to avoid a full-on fight. At multiple points when the Chinese government could have retaliated against America by targeting its businesses, it has instead tried to win them over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dodging a fight, though, does not mean giving in. As &lt;em &gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; went to press, officials from both countries were preparing for talks in Washington to see if they could revive a deal which, until Mr Trump’s tweets, had seemed nearly done. The previous evening, America announced its intention to raise tariffs on $200bn of Chinese goods from 10% to 25% from midnight on May 9th. According to Reuters, citing American government sources, China had backtracked on pledges to rewrite laws on everything from competition policy to intellectual property. Chinese advisers counter that it is American negotiators who have become inflexible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This creates two huge uncertainties for the global economy. One dominates discussion. Will there be a deal or will America raise tariffs? The other receives less attention. Is there a point at which China might lash out against America, even at a cost to itself?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is easy to imagine how China could punch back. Given its $380bn trade surplus with America, China is more vulnerable to tariffs. But American businesses, from Apple to General Motors, have big footprints in China. American firms made roughly $200bn more in sales in China in 2015 than Chinese firms did in America, according to Deutsche Bank. The Chinese government could whip up consumer boycotts. It could hold up supplies at customs. It could smother factories with safety inspections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_FNC873.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190511_FNC873.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190511_FNC873.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190511_FNC873.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190511_FNC873.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190511_FNC873.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190511_FNC873.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190511_FNC873.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190511_FNC873.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190511_FNC873.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In its retaliation, China has already used tariffs to hit sensitive targets. It has pushed soyabean farmers in Iowa and Wisconsin, states that will influence whether Mr Trump can win a second term, to the brink of bankruptcy. But it has largely refrained from deploying the dirtier weapons in its arsenal. After briefly delaying American whiskey shipments at the border last year, Jack Daniel’s is flowing again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even more striking are China’s attempts to be emollient. Having long hesitated, it opened the door last year for a range of foreign firms, from carmakers to insurers, to take majority stakes in their Chinese operations. In March it passed a foreign-investment law that, in theory, addresses some big American grievances. It has even undone some tariffs: in December it lifted extra duties that it had imposed on American cars and car parts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China’s decision to opt for a relatively conciliatory strategy can be explained in three ways. Most obvious is its desire to minimise the trade war. If America were to slap 25% tariffs on all imports from China, that could knock two percentage points off Chinese growth over the next 12 months, according to &lt;small&gt;UBS&lt;/small&gt;, a Swiss bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A second factor is China’s play to win back some support in America. Foreign businesses have grown frustrated with China. A more level playing field could change that, especially if China offers evidence of benefits. News on May 8th that JPMorgan Chase, an American bank, might become the first foreign company to own a majority stake in its Chinese mutual-fund business is just the kind of thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The final point is China’s management of domestic opinion. Xi Jinping, the president, is powerful, but he does not want to arm his critics. One government adviser says that left-wing scholars are planning to greet the announcement of any trade deal as a “day of national humiliation”, a reference to the 19th century when foreign powers dominated China. Front-loading reforms offers some insulation: the government can portray the deal as a ratification of what it was already doing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But domestic politicking also sheds light on why the trade talks have hit a rocky patch. China has more incentive to take a harder line at this moment—just when a deal seems to be within reach. Sending Mr Trump into a frenzy on Twitter may worry investors. But to Chinese officials it looks like Mr Xi is driving a tougher bargain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complicating matters, negotiations have been conducted in English, with the draft agreement (reportedly seven chapters and 150 pages) also in English. As it is translated into Chinese and circulated among more officials, changes are inevitable. “You can’t really renege on something that is a non-binding work in progress,” says James Zimmerman, a partner in the Beijing office of Perkins Coie, a law firm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China still wants to avoid a full-fledged trade war. Should America raise tariffs, China’s initial preference will be to continue with limited retaliation, says Wang Yong, director of the Centre for International Political Economy at Peking University. The American economy would, he thinks, suffer enough damage for Mr Trump to change course. If not, China’s fight-back could get much nastier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Finance and economics&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Speaking softly&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 21:06:49 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thailand’s junta marks the king’s coronation with more election-rigging]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/09/thailands-junta-marks-the-kings-coronation-with-more-election-rigging]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_asp004_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-09T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 9th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HAIS DO NOT&lt;/small&gt; see that much of their king, who spends most of his time in Germany. But for three days starting on May 4th he was on near-constant display for a long and lavish series of ceremonies surrounding his coronation. It all began with a ritual purification at the royal residence in Bangkok. Holy water was poured over the head of Maha Vajiralongkorn, the tenth monarch of the Chakri dynasty. It had been collected from all 76 of the country’s provinces, as well as from around Bangkok. Courtiers and officials wore spotless white uniforms and prostrated themselves before their monarch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The king changed into an embroidered golden suit for an anointing ceremony. Then he lowered onto his own head a pointed helmet of a crown weighing more than 7kg thanks to its crust of gold and diamonds. A royal procession the next day saw the stony-faced monarch paraded through Bangkok on a gilded palanquin. Accompanying troops roasted in the heat. In a separate procession (pictured), respectful elephants dropped awkwardly to their knees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first substantial moments of the new reign came just days later, when the Election Commission released the final results of an election that took place in March. Palang Pracharat, a party created to support the military junta that came to power in a coup in 2014, battled Pheu Thai, which is loyal to Thaskin Shinawatra, a former prime minister who has feuded with the generals since an earlier coup, in 2006. The junta rigged the system in its favour, banning all political activity until a few months before the election, disbanding a second party linked to Mr Thaksin and awarding itself the power to appoint all 250 members of the upper house. Nonetheless, shortly after the vote, a coalition of seven opposition parties, including Pheu Thai and Future Forward, which is popular with young voters, announced they had won a slim majority in the 500-seat lower house.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is not what the results unveiled this week show. The Election Commission concedes that Pheu Thai won the most seats, 136, followed by Palang Pracharat, with 115, and Future Forward, with 80. It annulled the result in one district won by a Pheu Thai candidate, ordering a fresh election. But the biggest blow to the opposition came in the form of tweaks to the formula whereby the commission allocates the 150 seats awarded on a proportional basis. The result was to reduce the tally of the big parties and hand seats to a plethora of tiny ones. This change appeared to breach the commission’s own rules and the election law, but a court found the new maths constitutionally permissible just hours before the party-list results appeared. Entirely coincidentally, the changes reduced the opposition alliance to a minority of 245 seats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chaos awaits, as 27 different parties now hold seats in the lower house. A weak, pro-military coalition looks the most likely outcome. The junta will soon present a list of senators to the king for approval. The two houses will then vote in a joint sitting to select a prime minister. The incumbent, Prayuth Chan-ocha, who led the coup in 2014, had seemed determined to stay on. Bangkok is rife with rumours, however, that the king might promote the selection of a less divisive figure, perhaps from the Privy Council, which is packed with soldiers and technocrats. Either way, the notion that the government ushered into power by the election will have any democratic legitimacy—always a doubtful proposition—now looks entirely forlorn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As if to underline the point, the authorities have set about persecuting Future Forward and its leader, Thanathorn Juangroongruangkit, with a gusto typically reserved for supporters of Mr Thaksin. The party and its leadership face 16 accusations of wrongdoing. The Election Commission intends to press a charge against Mr Thanathorn for holding shares in a media company, which candidates are not allowed to do. He has also been charged with sedition and computer crimes. He denies all the charges, which could lead to a ban from politics, a prison sentence or the complete dissolution of Future Forward. “I’m prepared. I knew this would happen sooner or later,” he says at his party’s buzzing office in Bangkok. “In order to retain power they are willing to do whatever it takes.” He believes the 16 cases are intended to pressure him to negotiate with the junta’s political allies. At least five of Future Forward’s &lt;small&gt;MP&lt;/small&gt;s have been offered $1m apiece to change party, he claims.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Thanathorn is a threat because he is both popular and unblemished by scandal, two characteristics which neither the king nor the generals (nor Mr Thaksin) enjoy. The king has alienated his subjects not only by his absence, but also by his personal cruelty and insistence on sycophantic protocol. It was not just the elephants and courtiers who were forced to prostrate themselves: days before the coronation the palace released images of the king getting married for the fourth time, in which his new wife, a former stewardess, grovelled before the unsmiling groom. He has disowned children and locked up relatives of one of her predecessors. Only a small share of Thais bothered to wear yellow, the royal colour, as requested during the coronation ceremonies. Thousands of civil servants had to be bussed in to swell the attendant crowds, which were much sparser than at the cremation of his father, who was far more popular.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet King Vajiralongkorn apparently feels secure enough to meddle in political matters. Before the election he intervened, quite hypocritically, to prevent his older sister from getting involved in politics. The courts and the Election Commission followed his instructions slavishly, even though they lacked any clear legal underpinning. Just before polling day he told Thais to vote for “good people”; just after it he stripped Mr Thaksin of several military awards. The risk of royal displeasure seems to have deterred neutral parties from joining the opposition coalition in the lower house. That is no coincidence: a weak coalition would be in no position to stand up to the king. That an election that was supposed to restore Thailand to democracy will instead bolster its preening monarch is a crowning irony.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Asia&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Crown and spectre&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 21:06:47 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Iran’s president does not want to walk away from the nuclear deal]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/11/irans-president-does-not-want-to-walk-away-from-the-nuclear-deal]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_map006.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-11T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;WO YEARS&lt;/small&gt; ago the chairman of Iran’s national airline was eager to travel the world and spend a few billion dollars. In December 2016 Farhad Parvaresh shook hands with a Boeing executive to buy 80 passenger jets. A month later he was in Toulouse, France, to take delivery of a new jet, one of 100 ordered from Airbus. Both contracts were vivid symbols of how the world’s economy was opening up to Iran after the conclusion of a deal in 2015 that eased sanctions in exchange for limits on its nuclear programme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Times have changed since America’s president, Donald Trump, withdrew from the nuclear agreement a year ago. The reimposition of American sanctions halted both aeroplane contracts and scared away other potential trading partners. The Iranian economy is now isolated. President Hassan Rouhani, in turn, says Iran will stop abiding by parts of the pact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was not what Mr Rouhani wanted. When America withdrew he said that Iran would still fulfil its commitments under the nuclear deal. The International Atomic Energy Agency confirms that it has. But domestic politics has made his position untenable. As Mr Trump has increased pressure on Iran, he has unwittingly emboldened its hardliners to squeeze Mr Rouhani, one of the architects of the deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Rouhani had hoped that the European Union would blunt the pain of American sanctions by compelling companies and banks to keep doing business with Iran. But European efforts to work around the sanctions and facilitate trade have not been effective. European countries have not taken action against big firms such as Total and Airbus that have backed out of their Iranian contracts. “They don’t want a full-fledged trade war with the &lt;small&gt;US&lt;/small&gt; over Iran because the benefits are too marginal,” says Suzanne Maloney of the Brookings Institution, a think-tank in Washington.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cut off from the global economy, Iran’s economy is plunging. Before Mr Trump was elected one dollar bought 35,000 rial. Today’s black-market rates are upwards of 150,000. Oil sales are hard to track because Iran hides shipments through middlemen and “ghost tankers” with transponders switched off. But analysts think they have fallen to about 1m barrels a day, less than half of their level before sanctions. They will drop more in coming months with the expiry of temporary waivers from sanctions that America granted to the biggest buyers of Iranian oil. New sanctions announced on May 8th target iron, steel, aluminium and copper production, which America says is Iran’s “largest non-petroleum-related source of export revenue”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Suffering Iranians have understandably soured on the nuclear deal and the president who promoted it. A poll in December found that support for the agreement had fallen to 52% from 76% in 2015. Mr Rouhani’s conservative rivals, long suspicious of his attempts to repair relations with America, feel vindicated. Mr Trump’s recent decision to brand the Revolutionary Guard Corps a terrorist organisation gave them another boost; even reformists rallied around them. The ayatollahs who wield power in Tehran have fallen out with those who study in Qom. But Iran is still a clerical regime and the mullahs are in ever-tighter lockstep with the Guards, who also control a big chunk of the economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iran’s parliament has spent months debating legislation meant to remove Iran from a blacklist maintained by the Financial Action Task Force, a global body that sets anti-money-laundering standards. Mr Rouhani risked much political capital to advance these bills, one of which was even opposed by the supreme leader. That effort now looks dead. Hossein Shariatmadari, the curmudgeonly editor of &lt;em &gt;Kayhan&lt;/em&gt;, a state-run daily, calls the bills a sign of “weakness” in the face of American sanctions on the Guards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Rouhani has tried to buy himself time—and to press Europe into offering economic relief—by setting a deadline of 60 days before breaching the nuclear deal further. Hardliners are praising his “first decisive step”. But his ultimatum does not change the underlying political and economic realities. America wants to batter Iran. Europe cannot stop it. Nor does his move change the calendar: even if a future American president were willing to lift sanctions, Mr Trump still has 20 months left in his first term. That is a long time for a weakened Mr Rouhani to endure. In order to fend off hardline critics he is, by undermining the deal, adopting their policies. Even a tactical win for the president is ultimately a victory for his rivals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Middle East and Africa&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Rouhani’s remorse&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 20:07:37 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[As America and Iran act tough, the risk of conflict is growing]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/11/as-america-and-iran-act-tough-the-risk-of-conflict-is-growing]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190511_MAP005_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-11T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;“T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE WORST&lt;/small&gt; deal ever negotiated,” was President Donald Trump’s view of Barack Obama’s signature diplomatic achievement: a deal that placed strict limits on Iran’s nuclear programme in return for sanctions relief. The agreement, signed in 2015 by Iran and six world powers, clumsily named the Joint Comprehensive Plan of Action (&lt;small&gt;JCPOA&lt;/small&gt;), made it much harder for Iran to build an atom bomb, at least for a while. But it has been on life support ever since Mr Trump declared a year ago that he was withdrawing from it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On May 8th Hassan Rouhani, Iran’s president, pushed it closer to death. Mr Rouhani said that Iran would stop complying with parts of the deal and warned that more breaches might follow. His announcement had an ominous backdrop. On May 5th America sent an aircraft-carrier strike group and bombers to the Middle East in response to “troubling and escalatory indications and warnings” of Iranian aggression. Two days later Mike Pompeo, the secretary of state, unexpectedly turned up in Iraq, where America has long accused Iran of sponsoring attacks on American forces. The combination of a dissolving nuclear agreement and more sabre-rattling increases the risk that America and Iran will stumble into a war—whether by accident or design.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now the nuclear deal is hanging on. Iran, said Mr Rouhani, would stop exporting enriched uranium once its stockpile reached 300kg and heavy water over 130 tonnes, thus breaching caps set by the agreement. That is worrying. Enriched uranium, if spun in centrifuges to higher levels of purity, can be used to power nuclear bombs. Heavy water is used in nuclear reactors that can produce plutonium, an alternative bomb fuel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Rouhani also gave the deal’s other signatories—Britain, China, France, Germany, Russia and the European Union—60 days to work out how to relieve the pressure brought on by American sanctions, imposed by Mr Trump, which have crippled the Iranian economy (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/node/21763857&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;). If they do not, Mr Rouhani is threatening to increase not just the volume of its enriched uranium, but also the purity, which is capped at 3.67%, far below the level of around 90% required to make a bomb. Were Iran to enrich some or all of its stockpile to 20%, that would halve the time needed to make the final leap to weapons-grade levels. He also said Iran might resume work on the heavy-water reactor at Arak that had been halted under the nuclear agreement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Rouhani’s calculation, and hope, is that these steps are strong enough to placate hardliners at home and to signal Iran’s resolve to America, but calibrated enough to avoid provoking Europe into reimposing sanctions. Mark Fitzpatrick, a former State Department official (currently at the International Institute for Strategic Studies in London), thinks this might work. The heavy-water limit is vaguely written and is “too minor an issue” to blow up the deal. It will also take some time for Iran to breach the 300kg-limit on enriched uranium. “When it is exceeded, the amount will probably be judged as not so great as to spark a crisis,” says Mr Fitzpatrick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet it is unlikely that the other signatories will be able to meet Iran’s demands. On January 31st Britain, France and Germany announced the creation of Instex, a barter-based channel to isolate Europe-Iran trade from American sanctions. But it has proved a disappointment, covering only food and medicine. Aniseh Bassiri Tabrizi of the Royal United Services Institute, a think-tank, says Iranian officials were especially incensed by America’s decision on April 22nd to end exemptions from its sanctions that had allowed some countries to buy Iranian oil. Europe’s best efforts are unlikely to compensate for that blow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Eventually, we’ll reach another point where Iranians feel they have to go another step further,” says Ilan Goldenberg, a former State Department official. How much further is the question. If Iran were to shrug off the nuclear deal entirely, it could take thousands of old centrifuges out of storage, install them underground and build up a huge stock of uranium enriched to higher levels. All that might bring its breakout timeline—the time it would take to produce enough material for a single nuclear weapon—to two to three months, where it stood in 2015, or even less.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190511_MAM984.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190511_MAM984.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190511_MAM984.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190511_MAM984.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190511_MAM984.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190511_MAM984.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190511_MAM984.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190511_MAM984.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190511_MAM984.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190511_MAM984.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But such dramatic moves would result in the evaporation of European support, diplomatic isolation and possibly even military action. More likely is that Iran continues to slice away at the &lt;small&gt;JCPOA&lt;/small&gt; over time. “What we will have is not an immediate crisis, but a slow-motion crisis that will play out over years—just the way it did before,” says Mr Goldenberg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A race between American sanctions on the one hand, and a gradual Iranian nuclear build-up on the other, would take the world back to the febrile years before the nuclear deal, when American or Israeli air strikes sometimes appeared imminent. But the situation may be more dangerous today. Iranian-backed forces have grown stronger in Lebanon, Syria, Iraq and Yemen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More importantly, American hostility to Iran has grown. Last year Mr Pompeo issued a dozen sweeping “demands” of Iran that resembled terms of surrender. These include halting uranium enrichment (permitted under the deal) and pulling out of Syria. John Bolton, America’s national security adviser, has long advocated regime change. It was he who announced the deployment of warships on May 5th. “I don’t believe that President Trump wants to go to war,” says Wendy Sherman, a former American diplomat who negotiated the nuclear deal. “But I don’t think he fully understands the escalatory cycle Bolton has put him on, and the risks of war, which are growing every single day.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Middle East and Africa&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;A dangerous direction&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 20:07:36 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The brewing conflict between America and Iran]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/11/the-brewing-conflict-between-america-and-iran]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190511_LDD001_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-11T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE DRUMS&lt;/small&gt; of war are beating once again. An American aircraft-carrier strike group is steaming towards the Persian Gulf, joined by &lt;small&gt;B&lt;/small&gt;-52 bombers, after unspecified threats from Iran. John Bolton, the national security adviser, says any attack on America or its allies “will be met with unrelenting force”. In Tehran, meanwhile, President Hassan Rouhani says Iran will no longer abide by the terms of the deal signed with America and other world powers, whereby it agreed to strict limits on its nuclear programme in return for economic relief. Iran now looks poised to resume its slow but steady march towards the bomb—giving American hawks like Mr Bolton further grievances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just four years ago America and Iran were on a different path. After Barack Obama offered to extend a hand if Iran’s leaders “unclenched their fist”, the two sides came together, leading to the nuclear deal. That promised to set back the Iranian nuclear programme by more than a decade, a prize in itself, and just possibly to break the cycle of threat and counter-threat that have dogged relations since the Iranian revolution 40 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today hardliners are ascendant on both sides (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/11/as-america-and-iran-act-tough-the-risk-of-conflict-is-growing&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;). Bellicose rhetoric has returned. Mr Bolton and Mike Pompeo, the secretary of state, believe in using economic pressure to topple the Iranian regime and bombs to stop its nuclear programme. In Tehran the mullahs and their Revolutionary Guards do not trust America. They are tightening their grip at home and lashing out abroad. In both countries policy is being dictated by intransigents, who risk stumbling into war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is probably too late to save the nuclear deal, known as the Joint Comprehensive Plan of Action (&lt;small&gt;JCPOA&lt;/small&gt;). Iran has been complying, but critics in America complain that its temporary restrictions will ultimately legitimise the nuclear programme and that the deal will not stop Iran from producing missiles or sowing murder and mayhem abroad. President Donald Trump pulled America out of the agreement last year, calling it a “disaster”. It is not, but that damage is done. Renewed sanctions on Iran and the threat to punish anyone who trades with it have wrecked what is left of the agreement. Last week America cancelled waivers that let some countries continue to buy Iranian oil. It is extending sanctions to Iran’s metals exports. Instead of reaping the benefits of co-operation, Iran has been cut off from the global economy. The rial has plummeted, inflation is rising and wages are falling. The economy is in crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Predictably, rather than bringing Iran’s leaders to their knees, America’s belligerence has caused them to stiffen their spines. Even Mr Rouhani, who championed the nuclear deal, has begun to sound like a hawk. Having long hoped that Europe, at least, would honour the promise of the deal, he is exasperated. On the anniversary of America’s exit from the agreement, on May 8th, he said that Iran would begin stockpiling low-enriched uranium and heavy water, which would in sufficient quantities breach its terms. Without economic progress in 60 days, he said, Iran “will not consider any limit” on enrichment. All this suggests that Iran will start moving closer to being able to build a nuclear bomb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As he walks his country towards the brink, Mr Rouhani has three audiences in mind. The first is his own hardliners, who detest the nuclear deal and have been pressing him to act. He appears to have appeased them, for now. On May 7th the front page of an ultraconservative newspaper declared: “Iran lighting match to set fire to the &lt;small&gt;JCPOA&lt;/small&gt;.” He is also trying to get European companies to break with America. He will not succeed. Despite European Union attempts to design mechanisms that allow European businesses to skirt American sanctions, most of them have decided that the American market is too valuable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iran’s most important audience is America, with which it seems to be playing an old game. Iranian leaders have long seen the nuclear programme as their best bargaining chip with the West. Though they have claimed that it is peaceful, &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt; inspectors have found enough evidence to suggest otherwise. The technology is the same whether power or a weapon is the ultimate goal. Iran’s centrifuges can produce a bomb faster than sanctions can topple the regime, goes the logic of hardliners. But they are wielding a double-edged sword. The threat of obtaining a nuclear weapon is useless if it does not seem credible. And if it is credible, it risks provoking military action by America or Israel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The potential for miscalculation is large and growing. American troops are within miles of Iranian-backed forces in Iraq and Syria. Its warships are nose to nose with Iranian patrols in the Gulf. America recently declared the Guards a terrorist group; then Iran did the same to American forces in the Middle East. Officials on both sides say their intent is peaceful, but who can believe them? America’s accusations that Iran has been planning to attack American forces or its allies in the Middle East are suspiciously unspecific. Violence by Iran’s proxies may be just the sort of provocation that leads America to launch a military strike. Mr Pompeo once suggested that he preferred American sorties to nuclear talks with Iran. Mr Bolton penned an article in 2015 in the &lt;em &gt;New York Times &lt;/em&gt;entitled “To Stop Iran’s Bomb, Bomb Iran”. Now even Mr Rouhani appears to agree that the way forward lies with provocation and escalation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A nuclear Iran would spur proliferation across the Middle East. Bombing would not destroy Iranian nuclear know-how, but it would drive the programme underground, making it impossible to monitor and thus all the more dangerous. The only permanent solution is renewed negotiation. Mr Trump, a harsh critic of America’s foreign wars, therefore needs to keep the likes of Mr Bolton in check. He will face pressure from hardline politicians at home and opposition in the region, not least from Israel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doing deals, though, is a Trump trademark. The president has shown an ability to change direction abruptly, as with North Korea. A new war is not in his interest, even if being hard on Iran is part of his brand. The Europeans can help him by urging Iran to keep within the deal—and condemning it if it leaves. Mr Rouhani, who spurned Mr Trump in the past, now says he is willing to talk with the deal’s other signatories if today’s agreement is the basis. That has so far been a non-starter for the Trump administration. It should not be. As the threat of a conflict grows, all sides need to head back to the negotiating table.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Leaders&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Collision course&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 20:07:35 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lyft’s revenue double, losses quintuple—and prospects darken]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/11/lyfts-revenue-double-losses-quintuple-and-prospects-darken]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190511_WBP001_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-11T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;O&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;N MARCH&lt;/small&gt; 29th Lyft became the first ride-hailing company traded on a stockmarket. The company’s share price jumped by 9% on its debut, valuing it at $22.4bn. By May 7th, the day it reported results for the first quarter as a public company, it was worth $17bn. Some investors thought even that was too generous. Lyft’s share price fell by another 11% the next day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although it posted quarterly revenues of $776m, nearly double the level a year ago, the company also recorded a loss of $1.14bn, more than it lost in all of 2018. Most of that was down to booking stock-based compensation plans for employees, who earned $894m from Lyft’s initial public offering. Lyft’s chief financial officer, Brian Roberts, conceded that 2019 would be its “peak loss year”. It will “move steadily towards profitability” thereafter, he promised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How that might happen is unclear. Lyft is still bleeding cash, even excluding employees’ compensation, as sales and marketing and insurance costs rise. The firm’s adjusted operating loss of $230m showed little improvement on the prior year despite fast top-line growth. And Lyft forecast that sales growth in the second quarter of 2019 would slow down sharply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everything that is true of Lyft also holds for Uber—only more so. The ride-hailing goliath was due to list its shares on the New York Stock Exchange on May 10th with a market capitalisation several times Lyft’s. Its losses, too, are larger. According to Uber’s own unaudited first-quarter results, it lost another $1bn or so in the first three months of the year. That brings the total since it was founded in 2009 to $9bn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both firms have enough cash to continue to burn money for years, but public investors expect a rapid path to profitability. Making it into the black will require either raising prices or reducing the cut of bookings passed on to drivers. The former will be hard; in many markets ride-hailing competes with other cheap modes of transport, such as buses, bicycles and riders’ own cars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latter looks harder still. Drivers on both platforms complain of earnings that barely cover the cost of living. They staged a global strike to coincide with Uber’s &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt;. That is why Lyft and Uber are keen to get rid of drivers altogether. During its earnings call Lyft announced that riders in Phoenix will soon be able to book one of ten robotaxis (all with human safety drivers to begin with). These will be provided by Waymo, the autonomous-car arm of Google’s parent company, Alphabet. In March Uber raised $1bn for its own self-driving venture from investors including Toyota, a Japanese car giant. Both firms’ initiatives have doubtless been designed to signal to Wall Street that there is a way to make red ink turn into gold. Perhaps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Business&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Public distress&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 20:07:34 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>