<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[A conservative government is returned to power in Australia]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/18/a-conservative-government-is-returned-to-power-in-australia]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_blp903.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-18T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A CHANGE OF government had seemed almost guaranteed. The right-leaning Liberal Party, and their smaller coalition partners, the Nationals, had been in power for six tumultuous years. Ever since the previous election, three years ago, they had trailed the Labor Party in the opinion polls. The opposition’s private tallies had left it almost certain of victory. But the results of the election on May 18th have surprised everyone: the conservatives have been returned for a third term in office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Votes are still being counted, and some constituencies remain too close to call, but the national broadcaster estimates that the coalition has picked up 74 of 151 seats in the House of Representatives, compared with Labor’s 66. It would need two more seats to form a majority, and will otherwise govern in a hung parliament (as it did before this election). “I have always believed in miracles,” sang the prime minister, Scott Morrison (pictured), who is an evangelical Christian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A miracle it may be. Liberal MPs had ejected two sitting prime ministers during their six years in power. The removal nine months ago of Malcolm Turnbull, a relative moderate, had seemed to jeopardise the Liberals’ already wobbly standing with voters, who punished the party for its continual in-fighting in a recent state election and in several by-elections. But Australians’ anger has apparently abated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government has veered hard to the right under Mr Morrison. He promised little beyond more jobs, lower income taxes and a continuation of Australia’s 28 years of economic growth. Perhaps more importantly, he whipped up fear about the economic consequences of Labor’s plans to cut greenhouse-gas emissions and to close tax loopholes for the rich.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This seems to have won the coalition favour in Queensland, a state with a population scarcely bigger than that of Sydney or Melbourne, but with disproportionate influence on politics as Australia’s main swing state. It is home to most of Australia’s coal mines, which leaves many locals wary of environmental regulation. Labor had hoped to win some marginal seats in the state. Instead, voters turned out in even greater force for the Liberals than they had at the previous federal election.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Liberals won several marginal seats in Queensland from Labor, helped by votes funnelled from smaller nativist parties under Australia’s system of preferential voting. The hardline immigration minister, Peter Dutton, who initiated the coup against Mr Turnbull last year, had feared being ejected from parliament. In the end he retained his seat with a bigger margin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may have helped that the conservatives supported a controversial plans for a big new coal mine owned by an Indian conglomerate, Adani. Labor had hummed and hawed about its future, and pledged to generate more of Australia’s electricity from renewable sources. The party had hoped such green stances would help it win seats in Victoria, a far more progressive state. It had won a state election there last year in a landslide. But in this election, Victorians only swung two percentage points in Labor’s direction. In the end, no seats in that state seem to have changed hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It did not help that Labor’s leader, Bill Shorten, was unpopular. He immediately stood down, tearfully conceding that he was “hurting”. Mr Morrison polls better. He had portrayed himself as a bumbling soccer dad, throwing out Australianisms at every turn. That made some urbanites cringe. But his studied everyman persona may have helped clinch blue-collar votes in Queensland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Liberals suffered only one major upset: in Sydney’s wealthy northern beaches, Tony Abbott, a former Liberal prime minister and the leader of the party’s right wing, was ejected from parliament after 25 years. He once called climate change “crap” and pushed for Australia to quit the Paris Agreement, which aims to reduce global emissions. That left him out of step with his more environmentally minded constituents, who voted in an independent candidate, Zali Steggall, with a monumental swing of more than 12%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A change is taking place in Australian politics, Mr Abbott surmised, that will seem familiar to Americans. The Liberals increasingly represent the working classes, while wealthier, city-dwelling conservatives are turning to more progressive politicians. Politics also seem to hinge more on atavistic distinctions than on policies. There has also been one other change that works in Mr Morrison’s favour. The Liberal party has modified its rules to make it harder to turf out sitting prime ministers. So unlike his predecessors, he should have three uninterrupted years to convince voters that they made the right decision when picking him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 04:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Scandal fells the vice-chancellor of Austria]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/18/scandal-fells-the-vice-chancellor-of-austria]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_blp905.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-18T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;MANY VISITORS to Ibiza do things they regret. But rarely do they involve dodgy discussions with wealthy Russians over procurement contracts and sales of stakes in newspapers. On May 18th Heinz-Christian Strache (pictured), the leader of Austria’s hard-right Freedom Party (FPÖ), resigned as the country’s vice-chancellor after a stunning exposé published overnight by German media suggested that he had been prepared to manipulate the Austrian state to help his party’s fortunes. “Enough is enough,” declared Sebastian Kurz, the chancellor, a few hours later, calling time on the government and announcing an early general election.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During a boozy evening at a rented villa on the Spanish island in July 2017, three months before an Austrian general election, Mr Strache and Johann Gudenus, an ally, met “Alyona Makarova”, a young woman who claimed to be the niece of a Russian oligarch, and a companion. Over champagne, sushi and copious amounts of Red Bull, Mr Strache appears to have offered to help his interlocutor gain access to juicy state highway contracts once he joined the government. In exchange, Ms Makarova would take a 50% stake in the Kronen Zeitung, a popular Austrian tabloid, and help reinvent it as an FPÖ mouthpiece. Such a turn, enthused Mr Strache, could lift his party’s support from 27% to 34%. On several occasions during the conversation Mr Strache vowed not to do anything illegal. But seven hours of footage, some of which has been made public, finds the FPÖ pair musing on the possibility of building a media landscape modelled on Hungary’s, thinking about ways to circumvent party-donation rules, and lamenting the West’s “decadence”—before decamping to a nightclub.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact the whole operation was an elaborate sting. At an emotional appearance before the press Mr Strache apologised for his “extremely embarrassing statements”, blaming “typical alcohol-fuelled macho posturing” and a desire to impress his “attractive hostess”. Yet he said he was resigning only to save the reputation of the government (in which the FPÖ had served as junior coalition partner to Mr Kurz’s People’s Party, or ÖVP), defiantly asserting that the only illegal action in Ibiza was the filming of his meeting. He hinted at dark conspiracies behind the operation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The source of the set-up remains unclear. Whoever was behind it mounted a sophisticated operation, including the courting of Mr Gudenus before the meeting, the installation of cameras and microphones throughout the Ibiza apartment, and, after sitting on the footage for nearly two years, a leak to the German press that was presumably designed to harm Mr Strache in the run-up to next week’s European election. Der Spiegel and Süddeutsche Zeitung, the German publications that ran the story, say their source insists on anonymity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Strache’s political career is surely over. But Mr Kurz finds himself in a tricky spot. After inviting the FPÖ, a party with a long history of flirtation with neo-Nazism, to join the ÖVP in government in 2017, Mr Kurz promised anxious European allies that he could tame his coalition partner’s more extreme instincts. That proposition has lately been tested; some governments have halted intelligence co-operation with Austria amid concerns over the FPÖ-led interior ministry’s links with Russia, and a stream of mini-scandals has highlighted the extremism that the party still harbours in its ranks. Now Mr Strache’s antics have punched a giant hole in Mr Kurz’s argument that the best way to manage the far-right is to co-opt them. In the short term the ÖVP is well placed to fight an election. Mr Kurz remains personally popular, and the third force in Austria, the Social Democrats, have struggled in opposition. But forming a coalition without either may prove hard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scandal has also troubled Mr Strache’s friends outside Austria. Today Matteo Salvini, Italy’s deputy prime minister and the leader of its populist Lega party, held a large rally in Milan, flanked by Marine Le Pen and other avatars of Europe’s nationalist right, as part of a joint campaign for the European elections. A senior politician from the FPÖ had been due to join them, but had to cancel at the last minute. The usually loquacious Mr Salvini had nothing to say about his erstwhile ally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;See also:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/briefing/2019/05/18/the-european-parliament-elections-are-responding-to-a-changed-world&quot;&gt;The European Parliament elections are responding to a changed world (May 16th 2019)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 04:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A conservative government is returned to power]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/18/a-conservative-government-is-returned-to-power]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_blp903.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-18T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A CHANGE OF government had seemed almost guaranteed. The right-leaning Liberal Party, and their smaller coalition partners, the Nationals, had been in power for six tumultuous years. Ever since the previous election, three years ago, they had trailed the Labor Party in the opinion polls. The opposition’s private tallies had left it almost certain of victory. But the results of the election on May 18th have surprised everyone: the conservatives have been returned for a third term in office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Votes are still being counted, and some constituencies remain too close to call, but the national broadcaster estimates that the coalition has picked up 74 of 151 seats in the House of Representatives, compared with Labor’s 66. It would need two more seats to form a majority, and will otherwise govern in a hung parliament (as it did before this election). “I have always believed in miracles,” sang the prime minister, Scott Morrison (pictured), who is an evangelical Christian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A miracle it may be. Liberal MPs had ejected two sitting prime ministers during their six years in power. The removal nine months ago of Malcolm Turnbull, a relative moderate, had seemed to jeopardise the Liberals’ already wobbly standing with voters, who punished the party for its continual in-fighting in a recent state election and in several by-elections. But Australians’ anger has apparently abated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government has veered hard to the right under Mr Morrison. He promised little beyond more jobs, lower income taxes and a continuation of Australia’s 28 years of economic growth. Perhaps more importantly, he whipped up fear about the economic consequences of Labor’s plans to cut greenhouse-gas emissions and to close tax loopholes for the rich.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This seems to have won the coalition favour in Queensland, a state with a population scarcely bigger than that of Sydney or Melbourne, but with disproportionate influence on politics as Australia’s main swing state. It is home to most of Australia’s coal mines, which leaves many locals wary of environmental regulation. Labor had hoped to win some marginal seats in the state. Instead, voters turned out in even greater force for the Liberals than they had at the previous federal election.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Liberals won several marginal seats in Queensland from Labor, helped by votes funnelled from smaller nativist parties under Australia’s system of preferential voting. The hardline immigration minister, Peter Dutton, who initiated the coup against Mr Turnbull last year, had feared being ejected from parliament. In the end he retained his seat with a bigger margin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may have helped that the conservatives supported a controversial plans for a big new coal mine owned by an Indian conglomerate, Adani. Labor had hummed and hawed about its future, and pledged to generate more of Australia’s electricity from renewable sources. The party had hoped such green stances would help it win seats in Victoria, a far more progressive state. It had won a state election there last year in a landslide. But in this election, Victorians only swung two percentage points in Labor’s direction. In the end, no seats in that state seem to have changed hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It did not help that Labor’s leader, Bill Shorten, was unpopular. He immediately stood down, tearfully conceding that he was “hurting”. Mr Morrison polls better. He had portrayed himself as a bumbling soccer dad, throwing out Australianisms at every turn. That made some urbanites cringe. But his studied everyman persona may have helped clinch blue-collar votes in Queensland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Liberals suffered only one major upset: in Sydney’s wealthy northern beaches, Tony Abbott, a former Liberal prime minister and the leader of the party’s right wing, was ejected from parliament after 25 years. He once called climate change “crap” and pushed for Australia to quit the Paris Agreement, which aims to reduce global emissions. That left him out of step with his more environmentally minded constituents, who voted in an independent candidate, Zali Steggall, with a monumental swing of more than 12%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A change is taking place in Australian politics, Mr Abbott surmised, that will seem familiar to Americans. The Liberals increasingly represent the working classes, while wealthier, city-dwelling conservatives are turning to more progressive politicians. Politics also seem to hinge more on atavistic distinctions than on policies. There has also been one other change that works in Mr Morrison’s favour. The Liberal party has modified its rules to make it harder to turf out sitting prime ministers. So unlike his predecessors, he should have three uninterrupted years to convince voters that they made the right decision when picking him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 02:40:45 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[In a first for Asia, Taiwan legalises gay marriage]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/18/in-a-first-for-asia-taiwan-legalises-gay-marriage]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_blp901_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-18T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUBILANT CHEERS erupted from tens of thousands of demonstrators packed in rainy streets surrounding Taiwan’s parliament, the Legislative Yuan, followed by more than a few tearful hugs. The news had just arrived that the lawmakers inside had voted to legalise gay marriage. Taiwan is the first country in Asia to do so, unless you count Australia and New Zealand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lawmakers had been rushing to finalise the bill ahead of a deadline imposed by the constitutional court, the Council of Grand Justices. In 2017, the council ruled that barring same-sex couples from marrying violated their constitutional right to be treated equally and ordered the government to adopt legislation permitting same-sex marriage within two years. The deadline was May 24th; the new law was approved on May 17th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not all were convinced that the Legislative Yuan would meet the deadline. To put pressure on lawmakers, crowds of gay-rights activists and their supporters converged on the legislature as three bills on the subject were being debated. They waved rainbow placards that read, “The vote must pass. No concessions in negotiations” and “Not one country, two marriage systems”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Asia, Taiwan has long stood out as a bastion of gay rights. The annual gay pride parade in Taipei, the capital, draws tens of thousands, many from overseas. In contrast, sex between men is punishable by death in Afghanistan. Brunei this year also put into effect a criminal code that prescribes execution by stoning for gay sex (although the country’s sultan says it will not be implemented). Gay sex only became legal in India in September, thanks to a court ruling. In mainland China, same-sex marriage is illegal and gay people are often regarded as deviants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite having dragged her feet about implementing the court ruling, Tsai Ing-wen, the president, pointed to the new law as proof of the strength of Taiwan’s democracy. “Today is a proud day for Taiwan,” she declared. “We have let the world see our values of goodness and tolerance in our land.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before she took office in 2016, Ms Tsai had declared herself a supporter of same-sex marriage. “In the face of love, everyone is equal,” she simpered. But in the face of a backlash from opponents of gay marriage, including Christian groups, she crumbled. On the defensive after adopting a controversial pension reform, and fearful of a pummelling in municipal elections in 2018, she dropped gay marriage. Her Democratic Progressive Party (DPP) was pummelled anyway. In the end, the courts took the decision out of Ms Tsai’s hands. But she still hesitated to fulfil the supreme court’s ruling, in part because the results of referendums held at the same time as the municipal elections implied that voters were not enthusiastic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Opponents of gay marriage came up with two of the three bills that lawmakers debated this week. They would have accorded second-class status to gay marriage—in fact, they did not even use the word “marriage”, speaking instead about “same-sex unions” and “same-sex family relationships”. But Ms Tsai used the DPP’s majority to push through the most progressive bill.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even this bill does not give gay couples exactly the same rights as heterosexual ones. It does not allow gay couples to adopt children to whom they are not related. Nor does it permit marriages with foreigners, unless they come from countries that have also legalised gay marriage. And it contains a woolly clause that implies that gay marriages will not create legal ties with in-laws. That may create problems for same-sex spouses who want to adopt their partner’s surname, for example, or argue that they should not be obliged to testify against their partner’s relatives in court.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these sops, conservatives are still angry. Sammy Yu, an opponent of gay marriage, points out that voters approved a referendum demanding that the civil code restrict the definition of marriage to a union involving a man and a woman. He says the new law is “really damaging to democracy”. But ignoring the supreme court would have been damaging too, and would not have achieved anything. It had ruled that, if parliament did not act, gay couples should be allowed to register their marriages with local authorities from May 24th anyway. By May 7th more than 250 gay couples had applied, according to the Ministry of Interior. Ms Tsai, meanwhile, has fallen back on platitudes. “We need to learn about understanding and coexistence,” she avers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 01:40:01 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Afghanistan beyond the blast walls]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/17/afghanistan-beyond-the-blast-walls]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/kabul_taxi_final_ii.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WAR-ZONES ARE often more ordinary than you expect. So it was recently when I made my first trip to Afghanistan. As we pulled out of Hamid Karzai airport in Kabul and onto the highway my taxi driver turned to me and said that “the worst thing” about life in Afghanistan is the traffic. What about the war, I asked? Oh, yes, sure, sometimes bombs go off, he replied. And the security everywhere is a pain (we had just driven through about half a mile of checkpoints and blast walls). But bombs rarely inconvenience, whereas traffic, that happens every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From abroad, it is easy to imagine Afghanistan to be everywhere as we see it on the evening news: soldiers clambering aboard helicopters; men in turbans clutching rifles; women in baby-blue burqas sheltering behind bombed out walls. You can find all of those things, certainly. But they are not what you are most likely to see. Kabul most of the time feels like what it is: another poor, traffic-choked South Asian city. Traffic is not Kabul’s only problem. The city, with a population that could be as high as 5m people now, is fringed by the mountains of the Hindu Kush, which trap the smoke from the fires people burn to keep warm in the winter, not to mention pollution from traffic and brick kilns near the city. When I arrived, it was still cold, the very tail end of winter, and the soot gets stuck in your lungs and your clothes, giving you the smell of someone who has been at a bonfire.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although Afghanistan is home to one of the deadliest wars in the world, more people die from air pollution each year than do from the fighting—around 17,000 in 2016, according to the World Health Organisation, compared with around 3,500 civilian deaths from the war that year. Thankfully it is seasonal. As the weather changes, suddenly the air becomes clear again and Kabul becomes rather pleasant. Men on side streets grind sugar cane into juice. The city is given some glamour by wedding halls, lit up like casinos, where wealthier Kabulis get married. On Fridays, the day of rest, boys take over roads to play cricket in their kurtas and salwar kameez. Daily life in Afghanistan continues away from the buzzing helicopters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sadly, most of the foreigners who work in Afghanistan don’t get to see much of that side of the country, because they are not often allowed out of their diplomatic compounds except under heavy protection. The part of Afghanistan known to most visitors as the “green zone” is nothing like the rest of the city. Concrete blast walls four metres high, topped with barbed wire and surrounded with HESCO blocks—giant wire-framed sandbags—surround everything. There is very little traffic, and at every junction, soldiers man roadblocks and check cars for explosives. The American embassy compound is Ozymandian in its size; it occupies the entirety of what must have once been a city neighbourhood. Soon, it will have to find some tenants, as the American government is pulling out half of its staff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The security is necessary, because both the Taliban and Islamic State like to drop rockets and send suicide bombers to this part of the city. Most of the staff of embassies can travel around the city only in armoured cars with armed guards. So I had the funny experience of interviewing people who, even though they knew far more than me about the details of Afghan politics, had seen less of the country. It cannot be good that decisions about policy are made by people who are scarcely allowed outside the blast walls. So much of the West’s failure to build a stable Afghanistan comes down to the reliance on a distorted vision of the country that exists only in compounds like this: a world in which the Taliban are a clearly defined group, for example, rather than a messy, ever-changing alliance. But what is the alternative? Earlier this month Taliban fighters bombed the offices of Counterpart International, an American NGO that works outside the green zone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Foreigners hiding away hurts the economy, too. Not far from the diplomatic quarter in Kabul is Chicken Street, a delightful, pedestrianised corner of the city lined with shops selling carpets, antiques and leather goods. For a while its vendors made a good living from the crowds of foreigners based in Kabul. In one emporium, the owner had a complete selection of Victorian flintlock cavalry pistols for sale, the steel embossed with Queen Victoria’s crest. “All fake”, the seller informed me, enthusiastically, “but very good fake”, demonstrating the smooth action of the trigger. Nowadays there are very few customers for such trinkets. As the NATO military presence has wound down in Afghanistan, so too has the spending—and the opportunities for Afghans to get rich working as translators, drivers and suppliers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, for all of the catastrophe of the war there are still some positive legacies. For the capital of such a poor country, Kabul has good roads and a surprisingly reliable electricity supply. There is a small but real middle class, and freedoms unimaginable in the 1990s when the Taliban were in charge. In cafes in western Kabul, you can find women in jeans flirting with their boyfriends over sickly-sweet desserts. Everyone has a mobile phone, from which to happily blast Hindi pop music. Even if the Taliban come back, which sadly now is an all too likely outcome, not all of this will be undone. The country has changed too much. Almost half of the population now were born after the American invasion. Four times more people live in Kabul than in the 1990s. Far more Afghans know of life beyond the traditional confines of the Pashtun village, the inspiration of the Taliban, to go back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is the optimistic thought, anyway. In the countryside around Kandahar I also visited schools where boys—and only boys—recite Quranic verses in classrooms where the walls were riddled with bullet holes. In the past, both the Taliban and Nato-backed forces had taken over the buildings to use as military outposts. Since then, no repairs had been done. Some girls do go to school, but not many. Parents ask why they should risk the shame of sending a girl to school when the education available is so pathetic anyway? Not all change is easy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 05:40:25 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The curse of genius]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/news/2019/05/17/the-curse-of-genius]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_blp902.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190406_OPP601_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190406_OPP601_1.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190406_OPP601_1.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190406_OPP601_1.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190406_OPP601_1.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190406_OPP601_1.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190406_OPP601_1.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190406_OPP601_1.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190406_OPP601_1.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190406_OPP601_1.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This piece is from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.1843magazine.com/&quot;&gt;1843&lt;/a&gt;, our sister magazine of ideas, lifestyle and culture. It was published in the June/July 2019 issue.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TOM REMEMBERS the day he decided he wanted to be a theoretical astrophysicist. He was deep into research about black holes, and had amassed a box of papers on his theories. In one he speculated about the relationship between black holes and white holes, hypothetical celestial objects that emit colossal amounts of energy. Black holes, he thought, must be linked across space-time with white holes. “I put them together and I thought, oh wow, that works! That’s when I knew I wanted to do this as a job.” Tom didn’t know enough maths to prove his theory, but he had time to learn. He was only five.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tom is now 11. At home, his favourite way to relax is to devise maths exam papers complete with marking sheets. Last year for Christmas he asked his parents for the £125 registration fee to sit maths GCSE, an exam most children in Britain take at 16. He is currently working towards his maths A-level. Tom is an only child, and at first Chrissie, his mother, thought his love of numbers was normal. Gradually she realised it wasn’t. She would take him to lectures about dark matter at the Royal Observatory in London and notice that there were no other children there. His teacher reported that instead of playing outside with other kids at breaks, he wanted to stay indoors and do sums.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One day his parents took him to Milton Keynes to have his intelligence assessed by an organisation called Potential Plus, formerly the National Association for Gifted Children. “We told him it was a day of puzzles,” Chrissie says. “It was my dream world,” Tom says. “Half a day of tests!” His mother waited while he applied his mind to solving problems. When they were shown the results, Tom’s intelligence put him in the top 0.1% in Britain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Precocious children are often dismissed as the product of pushy, middle-class parents. Nurture and environment clearly do play an important role in any child’s intellectual development. Talk to your child about politics over the dinner table and he is likely to develop confident opinions about the way the world should be run. Suggest that your toddler think of slices of cake in terms of angles and she may well display an early aptitude for mathematics. Practice can make perfect. The child with a gift for playing the piano who practises five hours a day is more likely to end up performing at Carnegie Hall than the equally gifted one who plays for just 20 minutes a week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But children like Tom are different. He was brought up in an underprivileged part of south London: 97% of pupils at his first school didn’t speak English as a first language. When it comes to numbers – or his other passions such as Latin and astrophysics – Tom’s parents have little idea what he’s talking about. His genius is not of their engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Intelligence tests are marked “on a curve”, meaning that the results are transformed into a bell curve: what matters is how you do compared with others who take them. By definition, most scores bunch in the middle: the average result in a cohort becomes an intelligence quotient (IQ) of 100; the middle two-thirds of scores become IQs of 85 to 115. The outliers are few. About two people in 100 have IQs below 70, and another two have IQs above 130. By the time you get 45 points away from the average of 100 in either direction, you’re down to about one person in 1,000. But since only a small percentage of any population takes IQ tests, identifying very exceptional children is hard. Most schools have none.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Society prizes intelligence. Geniuses are viewed with awe and assumed to be guaranteed prosperity and success. Yet there is a dark side to intelligence. Like many gifted children, Tom’s childhood has often been unhappy. Aged five, he talked about wanting to end his life: he said he planned to do this by banging his head repeatedly against a wall. “Life’s like a maze, only bigger,” Tom told his mum. “I feel I’m getting lost.” His GP said he was suffering from severe depression, and reckoned its roots lay in Tom’s “genius”, and the frustration and isolation this was causing him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tom finds it hard to relate to other children and has few friends. At school he has been shunted out on his own into corridors and offices. “They didn’t want him in the class because he’s doing different stuff,” Chrissie says. To distract his mind from “dark thoughts”, Tom turns to puzzles and calculations, often late at night. He has long suffered from insomnia. The strain affects the whole family: “I don’t understand parents who seek this,” says Chrissie. “I can’t cope with it. I just want to take it away.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many others echo the pain of Tom and his family. Mensa, an international organisation founded in Britain in 1946 to nurture the country’s most intelligent people, has 20,000 members (you must apply to join). When I put out a request via Mensa to hear from gifted children and their parents, my inbox fills with emails, many of them anguished. Those that I speak to say that, for fear of inspiring jealousy, they don’t dare talk to others about their children’s abilities. Given a sympathetic ear, they pour out their woes at such length that I nearly despair of getting them off the phone. Almost all are afraid of being identified, and insist on fake names.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some countries value extremely high intelligence more than others and offer specific educational provision for such children. Yet even if your genius is prized, admired and cultivated, social and psychological issues that often accompany great ability may make it an unwelcome gift. From the inside – and for many families that I spoke to – genius can feel more like a curse than a blessing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most experts reserve the term “gifted” for children who demonstrate three characteristics. First, gifted children begin to master a particular discipline – a language, maths or chess – much younger than most. They do so easily, so they also progress much faster than their peers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Secondly, this mastery is achieved largely on their own, rather than as a result of parental prodding. A child’s surroundings and socio-economic background certainly affect their speed of development: there is a close correlation between the number of words a child’s parents have spoken to them by the time they’re three and the child’s academic success aged nine. Studies suggest that children born into professional families may have heard some 4m more words by then than the offspring of parents with lower educational backgrounds. Such families often have higher incomes to provide more educational opportunities too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Lyn Kendall, a consultant on gifted children at Mensa – who was herself a gifted child in a working-class family – insists that reading Nietzsche to your five-year-old, or forcing them to do three hours of extra homework, cannot “make” a genius.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_blp904.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190518_blp904.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190518_blp904.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190518_blp904.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190518_blp904.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190518_blp904.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190518_blp904.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190518_blp904.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190518_blp904.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190518_blp904.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many children who have extremely high IQs show signs of extraordinary ability even as tiny babies, before pushy parenting is able to have much impact. “From a very early age – pre-language – these children understand what is going on around them, understand what people say but cannot respond,” says Kendall. Most toddlers appear to explore the world as they encounter it, distracted by passing cars or the arrival of a new toy. By contrast, Kendall describes gifted children of that age as “driven”: “They never stop and they set themselves incredibly high standards.” We often associate the early years of childhood with taking joy in simple things, living in the present and an inability to think through the consequences of actions. Instead, says Kendall, watching gifted toddlers, “it’s almost as if someone has taken an 18-year-old and put them in a newborn body.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A third characteristic of gifted children is that their interests often seem near-obsessive. They have what is sometimes called “a rage to master”. Jesse is five. When he was one and crawling, his father Richard tells me, he would do anything to avoid having his nappy changed. “We found that the only way we could keep him still was to give him things to take apart and put back together again. We had a yellow torch with a built-in bulb, and he would take the battery out, put it back in, and test whether it worked. If he’d put the battery in the wrong way round, he’d persevere until he got it right.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first IQ tests to measure intelligence were developed by Alfred Binet and Theodore Simon in the early 20th century. They evaluated short-term memory, analytical thinking and mathematical ability. Though the tests have changed since then, the basic skills they attempt to measure have remained the same. Within a few points either way, IQ is fixed throughout your life: the only way you’ll lose it is because of a brain injury.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So-called “intelligence” tests abound online. Many children take aptitude tests at school. Most of these can be gamed or, at least, children can be trained to excel at them. Mensa does its best to make its tests “culture fair” – in other words it aims to identify intelligence that is intrinsic rather than taught. “The original gifted children will have invented the wheel and discovered fire,” says Kendall. But even Kendall, who is in the business of evaluating children, admits that “testing IQ is not like measuring height”. No assessment is completely objective.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most tests look only at particular types of intelligence, such as mathematical and verbal reasoning. That reflects how narrow society’s notions of giftedness are. Many other types of skill and characteristics are missed, such as voracious curiosity or the ability to make intellectual connections. The tests are unlikely to identify future novelists or poets, or children who may be exceptionally good at sports or music. We don’t yet have a way to measure creative, artistic or emotional intelligence. The sorts of children we rate as “geniuses” tend to be only those who fall into the standard categories.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some people question the very notion of giftedness. The definition of a gifted child has fragmented over time, says Deborah Eyre, founder of High Performance Learning, an organisation that works with schools and teachers in Britain to try to help large numbers of children become “high performers”. She does not see aptitude as innate. Eyre says that no matter where you look in the world, the children of wealthy parents are over-represented in cohorts of gifted children. Those who come from minority backgrounds are under-represented: “Latinos don’t get selected [for programmes] in the US, Maoris don’t in New Zealand.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She also says that what marks out brilliant and high-achieving children – and adults – is often determination. The difference between two equally talented physicists, one who goes on to win a Nobel prize and one who does not, is their will to succeed. Apparent genius, she argues, is a combination of some kind of potential, along with the right support and personal drive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eyre claims that a certain type of parent, usually a highly educated one, takes pride in having a “gifted child” to show off. But this view wasn’t borne out by the parents I spoke to, most of whom found their children’s gifts to be a source of anxiety, even distress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of these parents face two main difficulties. One is how to cater to the advanced intellectual development of their child. The second dimension is more rarely voiced but may cause just as many problems: exceptionally intelligent children are often socially isolated, even disruptive. Gifts that are admired in the abstract often seem less welcome in person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you were to meet Ophelia Gregory, you’d think that the good fairies must have clustered around her cradle. Now 17, she is willowy and beautiful, with deep-green eyes. Her family – mother Kerry, father Tom and three younger brothers – is close and loving. At the age of 12, Ophelia clocked 162 in Mensa’s IQ test. It is the highest possible score for someone under 18, and on a level with Stephen Hawking, the ground-breaking cosmologist who died last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet so far, extraordinary intelligence has brought Ophelia little happiness. For her, being categorised as “gifted” is simply “more trouble than it’s worth”. She has been bullied and changed schools several times. I wonder what Kerry would say to a parent longing for a gifted child? “I’d say, ‘It should be a great thing, but it’s not. It never will be.’”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_blp905.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190518_blp905.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190518_blp905.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190518_blp905.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190518_blp905.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190518_blp905.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190518_blp905.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190518_blp905.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190518_blp905.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190518_blp905.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;We have long known that some individuals have extraordinarily high intelligence. Only more recently have psychologists started to look at whether and how this affects other areas of these individuals’ lives. Gifted children often experience what psychologists call “asynchronous development”: exceptional abilities in some areas may be associated with, or come at the cost of other aspects of maturity. “The parts of the brain that control the learning of words, patterns and numbers develop extremely quickly in these children,” says Andrea Anguera of Potential Plus. “But the frontal lobe, which controls the regulation of emotions, doesn’t develop as fast.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A gifted child may have an advanced ability to master something like maths, but more limited capacity to deal with their social environment which is another important part of growing up and fitting in over the course of their lives. “A gifted child might be prone to complete social meltdowns,” says Anguera. “They can’t understand how other children work, and they can’t control their emotions.” Being exceptionally able in some areas means they need “the right support” in others, she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the early 20th century American psychologist Leta Hollingworth talked about “socially optimal intelligence”, which she associated with an IQ of between 125 and 155. Ratchet the score beyond that, and what Norman Geschwind, an American behavioural neurologist, termed a “pathology of superiority” can creep in: the dominance of one bit of the brain can affect the development of other parts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We don’t yet know why this is, or whether it’s down to nature, nurture or both. One study shows that among members of Mensa in America, the rate of ADHD (attention deficit hyperactivity disorder) is almost twice that diagnosed in the general population. Others argue that because some gifted children are so different from their peers at school, and may interact little with them in the classroom, they may do so less in the playground too. Though in some ways their aptitudes are very adult, many find themselves unable to play games that we often refer to as “childish”: their social development is more restricted. If an exceptionally able five-year-old spends her free time doing algebra, says Anguera, she often doesn’t want to spend time with a peer who prefers to play with cars. Yet once a child is left out of some social situations, her opportunity to catch up or learn these skills diminishes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kendall identifies several characteristics common among gifted children who have no identified behavioural disorders. One trait is that many of them are deeply anxious, usually as a result of over-thinking everything. “Your brain has the capacity to work out all the variables,” she explains, “so it inevitably does.” Hilary emailed me about her son, Lorenzo: “I am finding it increasingly difficult to cope with his heightened emotion and anxiety.” Lorenzo, now 12, became a member of Mensa two years ago and so has opportunities to mix with other very bright kids both in person and online. Lorenzo scored 162 in his IQ test (“Same as Einstein,” Hilary tells me. I don’t have the heart to tell her that Einstein never had his IQ measured). He worries incessantly: “Waiting for a flight to Hong Kong recently, he asked so many questions about what might go wrong with the plane that the waiting hall cleared around us.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sleeping pattern of such children often differs from the norm: switching off their brains can be very difficult. The mother of one gifted child told me that he didn’t sleep for more than 90 minutes at a stretch until he was nearly five.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The emotional and physical health associations with genius don’t stop there. The American branch of Mensa, which has more than 50,000 members, refers to its affiliates as having “hyper brains”. A recent survey of its members suggested that people with exceptionally high intelligence very often have what Kazimierz Dabrowski, a Polish psychologist, dubs “over-excitabilities” or “super-sensibilities”, such as a heightened awareness of one of the five senses, experiencing extremely intense emotions or having very high levels of energy. Among these individuals, the incidence of depression, anxiety and ADHD is higher than in the average population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Giftedness may even be linked with physiological conditions such as food allergies, asthma and autoimmune diseases, which sometimes go hand-in-hand with “sensory processing disorder”. For many exceptionally intelligent individuals, everyday stimuli such as a radio playing in the background, the colour or texture of food, a vibrant display on a classroom wall or a scratchy label in a piece of clothing can become almost unbearable. Because his brain function is so acute, Lorenzo’s senses are more than usually finely tuned, believes Hilary. “He can hear things that we can’t. He can find it impossible to do his homework in a room that would seem to most people completely silent.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Neurologically, high IQ goes with increased efficiency in neural functioning,” says Sonja Falck, a psychotherapist in Britain who works almost exclusively with clients of “extreme intelligence”. “That’s measurable,” continues Falck. “If a person is getting a lot of stimulation and processing it very quickly, they are susceptible to being over-stimulated.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many gifted children struggle with failure. The trouble, Kendall explains, is that if you’re known for being a brainbox you don’t have to try, and so don’t build up resilience. She works with many bright children who “won’t put pen to paper”. At workshops she runs for gifted children, the kids sometimes play Twister, a game where players contort themselves over a mat covered with coloured dots. “They’re in hysterics,” Kendall says. “You can’t get it right so you’re teaching them to do something just for the joy of it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rebecca’s daughter Lizzie is five. She was conceived with donor sperm and her biological father had three degrees. Ahead of her first birthday she was using whole sentences. She completed a puzzle with 48 pieces in which she had to match pictures to the corresponding words at 16 months. By her second birthday she could recite “The Gruffalo”, a 24-page children’s story written in rhyme; when Rebecca forgot her face-cloth at bath time, Lizzie chided, “Mummy, you are an abomination!” Aged three, she announced, “Mummy, I’m not pretty. It’s my chromosomes’ fault.” But like many gifted children, she can become distraught if she gets things wrong. “Some days I feel sorry for her,” says Rebecca. “I just want her to be as normal as possible.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is difficult. Ahead of play dates, Rebecca clears away Lizzie’s toys so that the other mothers can’t see how advanced she is. People look for gifted children to fail, says Rebecca, “I’ve learned to cover for Lizzie.” Rebecca teaches children with special needs, but says that for her daughter’s particular needs “there’s nothing”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sonja Falck is wary of the word “gifted” because “it connotes privilege”, in that the gifted person is seen as having an advantage over everyone else. But it’s not necessarily an advantage. “Someone who is gifted, but who grows up in an environment that is not supportive, can really suffer. This suffering is hugely under-acknowledged.” Falck tells me about a client of hers who had an abortion: she couldn’t bear the idea of giving birth to a child who might suffer for her “gifts” as she had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Emily’s son Peter is nine. Since he was tiny he has preferred adult company to that of his peers: “At nursery, he used to sob all morning,” says Emily. Physically fragile and a loner, he has ended up in hospital three times after being beaten up at school. In common with many gifted children he has difficulty eating because he is hyper-sensitive to food textures. But for Peter, as for many other children, the greatest problem is that humdrum, day-to-day life is so hard to deal with. He finds school crushingly dull. His head teacher doesn’t see that this is a problem. “A bit of boredom is quite good for you,” he told Emily.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But boredom can be torture. A gifted student needs a fraction of the hours to master a GCSE subject that the school curriculum typically devotes to that subject, suggests Falck. She compares it to a seasoned runner being forced every day to trudge in step with people who walk extremely slowly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How best to educate a gifted child? The challenges are complex and often competing. On the one hand they are able to master material sooner and more rapidly than their peers. On the other, because the social skills of many such children are poorly developed, it can be extremely difficult for them to be a child in the traditional sense, to fit in and to learn many of the non-verbal, non-testable skills that social activity teaches you in preparation for being an adult. And without meaning to, such children may come across as smart-arses who, even with the best of intentions, other kids and adults may simply not wish to be around. Adults, especially teachers, may find extremely clever children threatening: a small child talking to you as an equal can put you on the back foot. They literally know more than the adults around them and can’t help but tell them so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After Tom’s assessment at Potential Plus, Chrissie sought advice on how best to educate him. It was obvious to her that his south-London primary school couldn’t cope. Apart from his first teacher at the school, whom Tom describes as “incredible” and who encouraged his interest in maths by sitting with him during break times to work through problems, his other teachers seemed to hate him. One appeared to enjoy belittling him, announcing to the class that “Tom found maths hard today,” while neglecting to mention that he was doing work meant for children ten years older than him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_blp906.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190518_blp906.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190518_blp906.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190518_blp906.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190518_blp906.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190518_blp906.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190518_blp906.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190518_blp906.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190518_blp906.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190518_blp906.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chrissie was told she had two options: she could either home-school Tom or send him to a private school that could give him more individual attention. Both ideas horrified her. She disagreed with home-schooling on principle – surely it would exacerbate his feeling of isolation. Private school was beyond the family’s financial means, but Tom received a bursary and now attends a respected, selective school in London, where the annual fees are £20,000. He still struggles to relate to other kids, and finds the economic disparity between him and his fellow pupils shocking. But he finds the teaching more stimulating. “I do like her, and she has given me harder work,” he says of his maths teacher.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Debate rages about the wisdom of accelerating children out of their age group. If they are moved up, they may struggle socially. If they stay down, they may switch off intellectually. Students need social and psychological support, says Leonie Kronborg of the University of Monash in Australia. She points to programmes for gifted adolescents like the Early Entrance Programme at the University of Washington in America: young teenagers can begin studying at university as part of a group of similarly advanced people their own age, so they are intellectually stimulated but keep socialising with their peers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Faced with sons and daughters who are bored and miserable at school, many parents of gifted children opt to take things into their own hands. Chrissie’s fears aside, home-schooling is surprisingly common for gifted children of highly educated parents. In the mid-1980s a father and daughter, Harry and Ruth Lawrence, made a striking pair, travelling around Oxford on a tandem bicycle. Harry had given up his career in computing and home-educated Ruth since she was five; at 12 she won a place to study maths at Oxford University. Harry accompanied Ruth to all her lectures, making sure that she never “wasted” time by socialising with other young people. She now works as a respected – but not outstanding – mathematician. When she had her first child, she vowed not to push him to move any faster academically than he wanted to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some countries have cultivated an educational environment that is welcoming to gifted children. Singapore runs a highly selective programme designed to identify the most exceptionally intelligent students each year. At the age of eight or nine all children are assessed in maths, English and reasoning. The top 1% are transferred from “normal” classes to the Gifted Education Programme which is run in nine primary schools up to the age of 12. They can then choose whether to attend certain secondary schools that offer such classes. Selected children get “personalised education plans” that include teaching on particular topics in greater depth and breadth, access to additional self-taught online courses, placement in higher classes for specific subjects, and early admission to primary school for very young children. But emphasising educational attainment has proved controversial. Since 2007, there have been efforts to increase socialisation between children of different abilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such an approach reflects a very traditional idea of intelligence – using certain types of tests to identify children with apparently innate intellectual abilities. Elsewhere educationalists are using a broader range of methods to spot highly intelligent children and increasing their focus on attitudes and personality traits often found in the most successful people – the drive, for instance, that Deborah Eyre talks about. In Project Bright Idea, a programme at Duke University in North Carolina, 10,000 ordinary nursery and primary-school children were taught using methods usually applied to the cleverest kids – fostering high expectations, encouraging complex problem-solving and developing meta-cognition (“thinking about thinking”). Nearly all of them went on to do much better in tests than their comparable peers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What will become of Tom and Ophelia, Lizzie, Lorenzo and Peter? Raj Chetty, an American economist at Harvard University has calculated that those who score in the top 5% of standard tests at primary school are many times more likely than the other 95% to file patents as adults – and that probability is far higher among bright kids from rich families. Whatever their natural talents, children whose aptitudes are nurtured and given opportunities have a far better chance in life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But gifted children do not necessarily shine later on. Some are what Chetty refers to as “lost Einsteins”: children who weren’t given an outlet for their intelligence or the encouragement to stretch their intellect, or who needed help to deal with the isolation of their experience. There are those whose abilities are missed by the limitations of IQ tests. And there are the many exceptional children who face barriers in later years because they never developed the interpersonal skills needed to succeed in the workplace or the wider world of social activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the 1920s Lewis Terman, an American psychologist, studied 1,500 children with very high intelligence. Others followed up that group 70 years later. They found that they had accomplished no more than their socio-economic status would have predicted. One child Terman excluded as not bright enough, William Shockley, had co-invented the transistor and won the Nobel prize in physics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And an unhappy childhood stays with you. Kim Ung-yong was a child prodigy in South Korea. Now a civil engineer in his 50s, he feels he was cheated of a childhood. He began speaking at six months and had mastered four languages by the age of two. He gained his first PhD aged eight, and was then headhunted to work for NASA. “I led my life like a machine,” he has said. “I woke up, solved the daily assigned equation, ate, slept…I was lonely and had no friends.” Even Albert Einstein, one of the most emblematic examples of genius, wrote in 1952: “It is strange to be known so universally and yet be so lonely.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s a bleak message for the child geniuses of today. Looking to the future, Tom’s mum Chrissie doesn’t seem hopeful. “Show me a story of a child like this which ends well,” she says. “They don’t exist.” Then she turns to Tom reassuringly. “Maybe you will be the first.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The author, Maggie Fergusson, is literary editor of the &lt;/em&gt;Tablet&lt;em&gt; and a freelance writer&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 04:40:28 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How unprecedented is the decline of Game of Thrones?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/17/how-unprecedented-is-the-decline-of-game-of-thrones]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_woc068_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p id=&quot;docs-internal-guid-ace91606-7fff-0cca-75c0-c922d6990ca2&quot; dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;FEW TELEVISION shows have managed to captivate audiences in quite the way Game of Thrones has. The first episode of the current season reportedly drew 17.4m viewers—impressive, given it is hosted by HBO, a premium subscription service. In contrast, the first episode of the final season of Breaking Bad attracted just 2.9m viewers.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Yet, although Breaking Bad&amp;#x27;s last season received almost universal praise from critics, fans are unlikely to hold the final season of Game of Thrones in the same regard. Reviews on IMDb, a repository of television and film reviews, show that the most recent two episodes of the show received average ratings of just 6.1 and 6.7 out of 10. Those numbers are far below the average for the show&amp;#x27;s previous seasons. The lowest rating any episode received prior to the current season was 8.1.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;What went wrong? Fans have offered a number of theories. One is that, though the show&amp;#x27;s authors are brilliant at adapting other peoples&amp;#x27; work, they may be less adept at writing original screenplays. The first six seasons of Game of Thrones were based on George R.R. Martin&amp;#x27;s “A Song of Ice and Fire” series of books, but the last two seasons have been based on their own writing. Another possible reason is that the authors simply did not give themselves enough time to work on the project. The final season of Game of Thrones is just six episodes long but needed to resolve a lot of plot points. Some fans wonder about the writers&amp;#x27; commitment to the show, noting that they have recently received a lucrative contract to work on a new Star Wars film.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Few have high hopes for Game of Thrones&amp;#x27; final episode, which airs this Sunday. Punters on betting markets reckon the episode&amp;#x27;s rating on Rotten Tomatoes, another television-and-film review site, will probably fall below 64.5%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;The show&amp;#x27;s decline is not without precedent. Data from IMDb show that at least one prominent show has had a harder fall: Netflix&amp;#x27;s House of Cards. The series, originally based on a British drama from 1990, suffered immensely after the unexpected departure of Kevin Spacey, the lead actor who had to be removed after being publicly accused of sexual harassment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;The final episode of Game of Thrones seems likely to leave millions of fans feeling unsatisfied and angry. But they should take solace that it could have been a lot worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 02:40:22 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Does freedom need guidance?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/17/does-freedom-need-guidance]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/ea_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-17T16:45:06Z&quot;&gt;May 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anne McElvoy asks Cass Sunstein, a former advisor to Barack Obama and co-author of Nudge, to what extent the state has the right to interfere in our personal freedom. They discuss how GPS can be a metaphor for decision making, the limits of nudging and why left-wing Democrats might be their own worst enemy. Runtime: 23 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-casssunstein&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 01:40:35 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The race to become Britain’s next PM]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/17/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_WOP008.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- data-infographic-js=&quot;/2019/tory-leadership/js/bundle.js&quot; data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/tory-leadership/css/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/tory-leadership/css/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE UNOFFICIAL &lt;/small&gt; race to succeed Theresa May as leader of the Conservative Party, and thus prime minister, has been going on ever since her disastrous election performance two years ago. On May 16th it moved up a gear when senior Tory backbenchers met Mrs May and extracted a promise that if, as expected, she fails in her fourth attempt to pass her Brexit bill in the House of Commons early next month, she will outline a timetable for her departure. The upshot is that 10 Downing Street is likely to have a new occupant this summer.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The man most fancied to succeed her, Boris Johnson, a former foreign secretary and prominent Brexiteer, had earlier that day thrown his hat in the ring. “Of course I’m going for it,” he told an audience of insurance brokers in Manchester. Expect more candidates to break cover over the course of the next few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Betfair Exchange, a gambling website, has been tracking punters’ predictions on the next Tory leader. According to the wisdom of the crowd, a handful of candidates stand out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p &gt;Source: Betfair Exchange&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Adrian Wooldridge, our political editor, assesses the chances of the leading Conservative politicians hoping to take the top job in this short film
&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ychDrZ2QzlE&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 18 May 2019 01:40:34 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Bacurau”, a violent new film, takes aim at Brazil’s leadership]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/17/bacurau-a-violent-new-film-takes-aim-at-brazils-leadership]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BKP511.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-17T16:12:10Z&quot;&gt;May 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 2018, when Jair Bolsonaro won Brazil’s presidential election, outside observers feared that his proposed public-spending cuts would hurt the country’s creative sector—particularly the film industry, which relies on state funding and tax incentives. Mr Bolsonaro has already subsumed the ministry of culture into a more general “ministry of citizenship”, but the full effects of his policies are yet to be felt. The country is currently enjoying a robust presence at the Cannes film festival, with five movies chosen for the “official selection”. The most interesting and prominent is “Bacurau”, a Western which had its premiere on May 15th. It deploys the conventions of survivalist and militaristic action films to criticise not just Brazil’s current leadership, but all those in power with authoritarian tendencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Set in the near future, “Bacurau” opens in a fictional separatist and self-sufficient town of that name in Brazil’s mountainous interior. The inhabitants live mostly in harmony, sharing resources, paying their respects when a beloved elderly matriarch dies and taking it in turns to keep watch over the only road to the outside world. The early scenes are realistic and richly drawn, with petty squabbles and rekindled love affairs; more unusual is that the local folk routinely take psychotropic drugs, which do not produce any obvious hallucinations but do seem to heighten the senses and bind the community together. “Make the most of life,” one elder proclaims, “for as long as we have life.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For how long will that be? The mayor of the surrounding region, a flashy strongman type named Tony Jr. (Thardelly Lima), has cut off Bacurau’s water supply in a bid to assert control. He rolls through the small town as part of his election campaign, bearing “gifts” like a truck full of second-hand books which are dumped into the dirt. Then comes a larger conspiracy to literally erase Bacurau from the map—as its inhabitants discover when they try to find their home on Google and GPS systems—and soon mobile phones lose signal, too. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most ominous is the arrival in Bacurau of a paramilitary group. Tellingly, they hail not from Brazil but from America. They could be hired mercenary forces or, as their amateurish behaviour indicates, tourists who want to hunt humans for sport. But the distinction hardly matters: they behave as racist psychopaths, lusting for blood and taking pleasure in their kill counts. When they can’t find anyone else to shoot, they shoot each other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although “Bacurau” was in the works for a decade before Mr Bolsonaro’s election, the film’s content &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.apnews.com/30ffa13a136049de87e56a8e7e2e5a77&quot;&gt;became more extreme&lt;/a&gt; as Brazil’s political climate darkened, to match an atmosphere that Kleber Mendonça Filho and Juliano Dornelles, the film-makers, have described as “like a dystopia”. The president has said that left-wing “outlaws” should “be banished from our homeland”, but “Bacurau” makes heroes of outlaws, redefining the relationship between individuals, their homeland and the nation that claims them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such themes are familiar from Mr Filho’s two previous narrative features, “Neighboring Sounds” (2012) and “Aquarius” (2016), which told stories of opposition to the encroachment of modernity in the Brazilian coastal community of Recife. “Bacurau” is less driven by human drama, preferring as it does the surreal violence of a genre movie. Once the villagers take up arms—energised by their pharmaceuticals—the film has the feel of “Red Dawn” if it were set in the fictional town of Macondo from Gabriel García Márquez’s “One Hundred Years of Solitude”. In order to respond to the existential threats, the community mines its own history for battle tactics and weaponry (a key scene features the local museum). “Bacurau” tells a globalised audience as much as a Brazilian one that victory over tyranny must come from within.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 23:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>