<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Why Pope Francis may open the door to married priests]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/06/18/why-pope-francis-may-open-the-door-to-married-priests]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_BLP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T18:12:32Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NOT FOR the first time, Pope Francis—or, to be more precise, his aides in the Vatican—have raised eyebrows. On June 17th, in a document that sets the agenda for a meeting in October to discuss the problems of the Amazon basin, they declared that the Catholic church should consider ordaining married men. The problems of Amazon communities range from the destruction of the natural environment to the persecution of its indigenous peoples. For the Catholic church, however, there is another pressing issue—it does not have anywhere near enough priests to minister to the existing Catholic population, let alone proselytise or fend off a growing challenge from Evangelical Christianity. Some Catholic figures talk of confronting a “Eucharist famine”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The document asks the bishops who will attend the gathering, or synod, to discuss making priests of “elders, preferably indigenous, respected and accepted by their community, even if they have a constituted and stable family”. It also moots the idea of women taking part in what it calls “official ministry,” but quite what that could mean is unclear. The bishops would not be able to authorise the change, but they could recommend it to Francis who does have the power to enact it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those versed in the law and lore of Catholicism might be tempted to ask what all the fuss is about. Priestly celibacy is not required by doctrine. It is a tradition, or discipline. There were plenty of married priests in early Christianity. Even today Eastern-rite churches—those in Eastern Europe and the Middle East that have practices similar to those of the Orthodox but regard the pope as their leader—have priests with wives and children. And since 1994, when the Church of England began ordaining women, almost 400 Anglican priests have been accepted into the Catholic church, including many with families. Roughly one in 10 of the Catholic priests in England and Wales was formerly an Anglican.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, what is being proposed now is qualitatively different. The Eastern rite churches are exceptional in many ways and account for less than 2% of the world’s baptised Catholics. The decision by Francis’s predecessor, Pope Benedict, to open the doors to traditionalist Anglican vicars, is in effect a temporary concession. When the last of the Anglican ecclesiastical refugees dies, if no change has been made in the meantime, the Catholic priesthood of the Western or Latin rite will go back to being entirely celibate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, a decision to ordain married men in the Amazon, however exceptional it might appear, would set a precedent for the entire church. That is in part because the problems of the Amazon reflect a broader challenge that faces the Catholic church in much of the rest of the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In parts of the Amazon basin, the ratio of baptised Catholics to priests exceeds 8,000 to one. But then it is more than 5,000 to one in Africa. Globally, it has risen from about 1,900 to one in 1980 to about 3,100 to one in 2016. Until now, the lowest ratios have been in Europe and North America. But in Europe the average age of priests is high and, as death takes its toll, the figure will rise steeply. In America, the situation is not much better: already, one in five US parishes has no resident priest. The problem facing the Catholic church in the Amazon basin, then, is simply a worldwide problem writ large. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Africa, priestly vocations are rising. In Asia, they are more or less holding steady. But, unless there is a wholly unexpected reversal in the steeply falling trend in other parts of the world, the remedy proposed for the Amazon basin will be just as valid elsewhere. The snappiest phrase from the document is one that refers to facilitating the transition from a “Church that visits” to a “Church that remains”. It is probably not the last time you will hear it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 05:40:18 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump takes aim at Mario Draghi over interest rates]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/18/donald-trump-takes-aim-at-mario-draghi-over-interest-rates]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_fnp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARIO DRAGHI was certainly hoping for a reaction when he stood up to speak at the annual conference of the European Central Bank (ECB) in Portugal on June 18th—but perhaps not from the world’s most powerful man. Mr Draghi announced that the ECB stood ready to ease monetary policy if the euro area’s economy did not improve. Hours after he returned to his seat, President Donald Trump denounced him on Twitter for “making it unfairly easier for them to compete against the USA”. The Europeans, he claims “have been getting away with this for years, along with China and others.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The outburst shows again that Mr Trump views interest rates and exchange rates, and not just the trade tariffs he likes to brandish, as weapons of economic warfare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By declaring that the ECB had “considerable headroom” to ease monetary policy, Mr Draghi was trying to convince sceptical investors that the central bank would be able to boost the euro area’s flagging economy. He seemed to succeed for a while; the euro fell by 0.5% against the dollar on his comments as investors anticipated further stimulus in the coming months. (It made up much of the fall later in the day, though.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market reaction riled Mr Trump: unusually, he singled out “Mario D” for attack. But he has complained about a weak euro before. In July last year he blamed both the EU and China for manipulating their interest rates and exchange rates. Accusations that central banks engage in competitive devaluation are not new, and have even been lobbed at America in the past. When the Fed expanded its quantitative-easing programme in 2010, a number of countries intervened to devalue their currencies, prompting Guido Mantega, then Brazil’s finance minister, to coin the term “currency war”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump&amp;#x27;s criticism of the weak euro—and therefore of the strong dollar—may have been strategically timed. Over the next two days the Federal Reserve meets to discuss monetary policy, and Mr Trump has called frequently for interest rates to be cut. But since the Fed is independent in its rate-setting, he has no direct influence over its decision, let alone the ECB’s. Asked whether he was starting a currency war, Mr Draghi responded that his only objective was to achieve the bank’s inflation target. “We don’t target the exchange rate,” he said. His audience burst into applause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump can, though, decide to initiate new trade hostilities with Europe. A decision on whether to increase levies on America’s imports of cars is expected by November. If Mr Trump thinks America has been treated unfairly by the ECB, that might make him more disposed to do so. But the ECB’s monetary easing is not a zero-sum game. Although looser policy does work partly through a weaker exchange rate, its effect on boosting the euro area should also create more appetite to buy American motorbikes and bourbon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Mr Trump were to use exchange rates as a reason to whack tariffs on imports from Europe, that could prove self-defeating. The euro zone’s economy would take another knock and Mr Draghi would be forced to inject even more stimulus, pushing the euro down further. Indeed the ECB thinks businesses’ fear of American protectionism, as well as a slow-down in global trade, is already taking a toll on the euro zone. Ironically, Mr Trump might be part of the reason Mr Draghi had to stand up today in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 05:40:17 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Are women less interested in politics than men?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/18/are-women-less-interested-in-politics-than-men]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_woc922.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WESTERN SOCIETY has no shortage of stereotypes about the activities and interests of men and women. Have they shaped how they think about politics? When asked the question “How interested would you say you are in politics?”, the share of men who answer “very” or “fairly” interested is significantly larger than that of women. This phenomenon has been observed across more than a dozen rich countries. It may have harmful consequences. If women are less interested in politics, they may be less likely to take part in it, including voting or running for office. And their views—particularly on social issues like workplace equality, parental leave and child care, which they care about on average more than men do—may not be adequately represented in government.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/pops.12600&quot;&gt;new study&lt;/a&gt; by Marta Fraile of Central European University and Irene Sánchez-Vítores of the European University Institute finds that the gap in political interest appears early in life. Using data from the British Household Panel Survey, which polled 10,300 people between 1991 and 2009, the authors find that the gender gap among 15-year-old Britons is already about 20 percentage points. For 25-year-olds, it grows to roughly 30 points. For better-educated people, who tend to be more engaged in politics, the divide is even greater. Among British adults with a university degree, the gender gap in interest in politics is a whopping 37 percentage points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors suggest several possible explanations for the gap, ranging from social norms to the under-representation of women in public life. They note one intriguing correlation. In countries with more gender equality—as measured by an index developed by the European Institute for Gender Equality, a think-tank—the gap in interest in politics tends to be smaller. In Portugal, it is about 30 percentage points; but in Denmark and Finland, where women enjoy a comparatively high degree of equality, it is just 10 points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 05:40:16 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The rising cost of education and health care is less troubling than believed]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/18/the-rising-cost-of-education-and-health-care-is-less-troubling-than-believed]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_fnd000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMONG THE compensations of ageing is the right to bore youngsters with stories of the prices of yesteryear. Once upon a time a ticket to the cinema cost just five quid, and a hogshead of mead but a farthing. Of course, savvier youths know how to debunk such tales. Adjust for inflation and many things are cheaper than ever. Since 1950 the real cost of new vehicles has fallen by half, that of new clothing by 75% and that of household appliances by 90%, even as quality has improved. Tumbling prices reflect decades of improvements in technology and productivity. But the effect is not economy-wide. Cars are cheaper, but car maintenance is more expensive, and costs in education and health care have risen roughly fivefold since 1950. Though no mystery, this rise is often misunderstood, with serious economic consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are as many explanations for the ballooning cost of such services as there are politicians. But as a newly published analysis argues, many common scapegoats simply cannot explain the steady, long-run rise in such prices relative to those elsewhere in the economy. In “Why are the prices so damn high?” Eric Helland of Claremont McKenna College and Alex Tabarrok of George Mason University write that quality has improved far too little to account for it. Administrative bloat is not the answer either. In America the share of all education spending that goes on administration has been roughly steady for decades. Health-care spending has risen faster than GDP in rich countries, despite vast differences in the structure of their health-care systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The real culprit, the authors write, is a steady increase in the cost of labour—of teachers and doctors. That in turn reflects the relentless logic of Baumol’s cost disease, named after the late William Baumol, who first described the phenomenon. Productivity grows at different rates in different sectors. It takes far fewer people to make a car than it used to—where thousands of workers once filled plants, highly paid engineers now oversee factories full of robots—but roughly the same number of teachers to instruct a schoolful of children. Economists reckon that workers’ wages should vary with their productivity. But real pay has grown in high- and low-productivity industries alike. That, Baumol pointed out, is because teachers and engineers compete in the same labour market. As salaries for automotive engineers rise, more students study engineering and fewer to become teachers, unless teachers’ pay also goes up. The cost of education has thus risen because of the rising pay needed to fill teaching posts. Other factors matter too, and can explain, for instance, why Americans pay more than Europeans for health care and higher education. But across countries, none is as important as the toll exacted by cost disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baumol’s earliest work on the subject, written with William Bowen, was published in 1965. Analyses like that of Messrs Helland and Tabarrok nonetheless feel novel, because the implications of cost disease remain so underappreciated in policy circles. For instance, the steadily rising expense of education and health care is almost universally deplored as an economic scourge, despite being caused by something indubitably good: rapid, if unevenly spread, productivity growth. Higher prices, if driven by cost disease, need not mean reduced affordability, since they reflect greater productive capacity elsewhere in the economy. The authors use an analogy: as a person’s salary increases, the cost of doing things other than work—like gardening, for example—rises, since each hour off the job means more foregone income. But that does not mean that time spent gardening has become less affordable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither do high prices necessarily need fixing. Many proposed solutions would be good for growth but would not lessen the disparity in costs between the output of high-productivity sectors and low-productivity ones. Boosting the supply of labour by increasing immigration could depress costs in both, for instance, but the price of a college education in terms of sedans would remain eye-watering. Innovation in stagnant sectors, while welcome, would shift the problem of cost disease elsewhere. A burst of productivity growth in education—because of improved online instruction, say—should contribute to a decline in the price of education per student. But because a given instructor could serve many more students than before, teachers’ potential income would rise, luring some would-be doctors away from the study of medicine and exacerbating the problem of cost disease in health care. A productivity boom in health care might shunt the cost disease to dentistry, or child care, or veterinary medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only true solution to cost disease is an economy-wide productivity slowdown—and one may be in the offing. Technological progress pushes employment into the sectors most resistant to productivity growth. Eventually, nearly everyone may have jobs that are valued for their inefficiency: as concert musicians, or artisanal cheesemakers, or members of the household staff of the very rich. If there is no high-productivity sector to lure such workers away, then the problem does not arise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A cure worse than the disease&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;These possibilities reveal the real threat from Baumol’s disease: not that work will flow toward less-productive industries, which is inevitable, but that gains from rising productivity are unevenly shared. When firms in highly productive industries crave highly credentialed workers, it is the pay of similar workers elsewhere in the economy—of doctors, say—that rises in response. That worsens inequality, as low-income workers must still pay higher prices for essential services like health care. Even so, the productivity growth that drives cost disease could make everyone better off. But governments often do too little to tax the winners and compensate the losers. And politicians who do not understand the Baumol effect sometimes cap spending on education and health. Unsurprisingly, since they misunderstand the diagnosis, the treatment they prescribe makes the ailment worse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 01:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Banking bad—Deutsche’s new division]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/18/banking-bad-deutsches-new-division]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_blm503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T16:32:22Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DEUTSCHE BANK&lt;/strong&gt; plans to create a new division, a “bad bank”, which will hold tens of billions of euros of assets as part of an overhaul of it is operations. Will the remaining firm become profitable enough to satisfy regulators and investors? And, the growing concern in &lt;strong&gt;China&lt;/strong&gt; over balancing the books at a local level. Also, our correspondent takes a trip to &lt;strong&gt;Citeco—France’s museum of economics.&lt;/strong&gt; Patrick Foulis hosts. Runtime: 16 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/f70d13b5-afcd-429e-a072-05b734f2c009&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 00:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why “The Wild Bunch” ranks among the most influential Westerns]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/18/why-the-wild-bunch-ranks-among-the-most-influential-westerns]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_BKP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T15:14:49Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 1969 three Westerns vied for supremacy. “True Grit”, the first to be released, was a nostalgic throwback. It featured a veteran star of the saddle, John Wayne, as Rooster Cogburn, a one-eyed lawman who comes out of retirement to help a precocious little girl (it won Wayne his only Oscar). “Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid”, which arrived a few months later, had a more modern sensibility. Its pair of outlaws—Paul Newman and Robert Redford, the two most watchable heartthrobs of the era—were transformed into fun-loving folk heroes; it went on to become the highest-grossing film at the American box office that year. But it was “The Wild Bunch”, released 50 years ago on June 18th 1969, which blew fist-sized holes in the genre. It was the least commercially successful film of the lot, but it did the most to change the trajectory of the Western.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the time, cowboys and gunfighters were dominating the small screen on popular shows such as “Gunsmoke”, “Bonanza”, “Rawhide” and “The Westerner” (and providing Clint Eastwood and Steve McQueen with their first glimpse of fame). But on film, the Western had begun its long &lt;em&gt;adios&lt;/em&gt; in the 1950s. “High Noon” (1950), “Shane” (1953) and “The Searchers” (1956) all charted the end of the Wild West, the arrival of civilisation and the hero’s final walk into the sunset. The Spaghetti Western briefly reinvigorated the genre with cheap, nihilistic and stylistically ambitious films, but even Sergio Leone, the maestro of the subgenre, had released the elegiac “Once Upon a Time in the West” in 1968. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ageing outlaws of “The Wild Bunch” are likewise coming to the end of the road. “We’ve got to start thinking beyond our guns,” says Pike Bishop (William Holden), as “those days are closing fast.” Pike leads his gang into one last hold-up, which turns into a massacre when they are ambushed by bounty hunters. The shootout is bloody, bizarre and indiscriminate. Along with the outlaws and lawmen, women, civilians and a tuba player are blown away or trampled by horses. There are no goodies and baddies, just violent, greedy, immoral men and innocents caught in the crossfire. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sam Peckinpah, the director, spoke of violence as “ugly, brutalising and bloody fucking awful”, but he found an aesthetic appeal in it, too. He showed blood spurting from bullet wounds in slow motion. He made use of quick cuts and cacophonous sound design to put the viewer in the middle of the horror and the excitement. The final shootout, between the four remaining members of the Bunch and a Mexican army, surpasses the first in bloody carnage, portraying an ultraviolence unseen in war films—let alone Westerns—at that time. While the movie was being shot in Mexico, Martin Luther King Jr and Bobby Kennedy were assassinated, and riots had broken out from Detroit to New Jersey. The Vietnam war had entered its deadliest period for American troops. The film’s violence reflected that of its time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peckinpah’s outlaws are neither countercultural folk heroes like Butch and Sundance nor noble old-timers like Cogburn. Early in the film Pike utters a starkly murderous command: “If they move, kill ‘em!” He pays lip service to the code of the outlaw—“when you side with a man, you stay with him. And if you can’t do that, you’re like some animal, you’re finished”—but he uses one of his group as a decoy to save his own skin, killing another when the man can’t ride a horse. Pike has alienated and betrayed other friends. In other words, he fails even by his own lax standards, let alone the moral sureties that had once underpinned the genre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The three Hollywood Westerns released the following year, in 1970—“A Man Called Horse”, “Little Big Man” and “Soldier Blue”—were similarly brutal, and they also began to unpick the racist myths that underpinned the genre. Peckinpah’s movie had set a new standard for action cinema. Drink and self-destruction would take their own toll on Peckinpah’s talent, but with “The Wild Bunch” he left an indelible bloody thumbprint on the history of cinema.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 23:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Supreme Court sinks a Republican gerrymander in Virginia]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/18/the-supreme-court-sinks-a-republican-gerrymander-in-virginia]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_USP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T17:55:24Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;CURIOUS VOTING lineups marked three of the four rulings the Supreme Court handed down on June 17th. The arrangement of justices in &lt;em&gt;Virginia House of Delegates v Bethune-Hill,&lt;/em&gt; a 5-4 decision dealing a death-blow to a racially biased gerrymander of Virginia’s state legislative map, was particularly notable. The majority opinion was written by Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg and signed by two fellow liberals, Elena Kagan and Sonia Sotomayor. But the two most conservative jurists on the court, Justices Neil Gorsuch and Clarence Thomas, rounded out the majority. The dissenting quartet comprised three conservatives and Justice Stephen Breyer, who usually votes with the liberals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The matter in &lt;em&gt;Bethune-Hill&lt;/em&gt; differs from that of two partisan gerrymandering cases set to be decided before the end of June. Those challenges,&lt;em&gt; Lamone v Benisek &lt;/em&gt;and&lt;em&gt; Rucho v Common Cause, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/03/28/the-supreme-court-does-not-like-gerrymandering&quot;&gt;ask&lt;/a&gt; the justices to do something they have never done: impose a limit on political parties’ efforts to entrench power by drawing district lines that guarantee them a lopsided proportion of seats in Congress or in state legislatures. The Virginia case concerns racial gerrymandering, the practice of unconstitutionally moving voters in and out of districts based on their race, which the Supreme Court has policed for decades. By scuttling a racially gerrymandered map that Republicans adopted in 2011, the Supreme Court sets the stage for a possible Democratic takeover of Virginia’s Senate and House of Delegates when Virginians vote on November 5th 2019. For Republicans, such a loss could come with interest. If the Democrats prevail, they will control the next round of redistricting in 2021 after population data from the 2020 census are reported. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The substantive legal question in &lt;em&gt;Bethune-Hill&lt;/em&gt; was whether Virginia Republicans violated the Equal Protection Clause of the Fourteenth Amendment when they packed black voters into a number of majority-minority districts. The House of Delegates claims it was only trying to comply with the Voting Rights Act of 1965 in sketching a map that allowed minorities to elect their choice of candidates. But the challengers saw the House’s target of 55% black voters in these districts as excessive and designed to dilute black voting influence in surrounding areas. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In their &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/18pdf/18-281_6j37.pdf&quot;&gt;ruling&lt;/a&gt; on June 17th, the Supreme Court did not breathe a word on the heart of the matter. Instead, the five justices in the majority dismissed the House of Delegates’ appeal on the grounds the body does not have “standing” to sue. Justice Ginsburg began by citing a clear provision of Virginia law: “[a]uthority and responsibility for representing the state’s interests in civil litigation...rest exclusively with the state’s attorney-general”. Since Mark Herring, Virginia&amp;#x27;s attorney-general, declined to appeal a lower-court ruling striking down the gerrymandered map and appointing a special master to draw up a fair replacement, the case is closed. Virginia’s House of Delegates may not open it. And as Justice Sotomayor &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/03/19/the-supreme-court-considers-a-racial-gerrymandering-challenge-in-virginia&quot;&gt;observed&lt;/a&gt; during the oral argument, the gerrymandered map, “at best”, is a product of “the legislature as a whole” or “the people of Virginia”—not of the House of Delegates alone. Justice Ginsburg used this idea to respond to the House’s second argument for standing: that the House is independently harmed by the revised electoral maps and should have the right to sue, whatever the attorney-general’s plans may be. Not so, the majority responded. Redistricting is not the sole province of the House—it is entrusted to the General Assembly as a whole, and the House is only half of that institution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his dissent, Justice Samuel Alito explained why the House of Delegates has the right to sue. It should “really go without saying”, he wrote, that changes to an electoral map “have an important impact on the overall work of the body”. If it were not for the significant effects redrawn districts have on “the composition of a legislature” and “the things that a legislature does”, legislators would not take such pains in “drawing, contesting and defending districting plans”. It is “really quite astounding”, he wrote, to “suggest otherwise”. And the question of who serves in an institution matters greatly to it: “Does a string quartet have an interest in the identity of its cellist? Does a basketball team have an interest in the identity of its point guard? Does a board of directors have an interest in the identity of its chairperson?” Clearly, the dissent concludes, “the invalidation of the House’s redistricting plan and its replacement with a court-ordered map would cause the House to suffer a ‘concrete’ injury”, the basic requirement for standing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aside from the political repercussions from the ruling in &lt;em&gt;Bethune-Hill&lt;/em&gt;—enhanced prospects for a Democratic sweep of Virginia’s General Assembly in the autumn—there are two more subtle implications. The first concerns the Supreme Court’s legitimacy. The institution has never been divorced from politics, but nomination battles over President Donald Trump’s two Supreme Court picks have cast the institution in an increasingly ideological—and partisan—light. &lt;em&gt;Bethune-Hill&lt;/em&gt; shows that justices are capable of voting against the interest of the party of the president who nominated them—at least occasionally. The ruling will give Chief Justice John Roberts something to point to when he insists (as he often does) that the justices “serve one nation”, not “one party or interest”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But by signing onto Justice Alito’s dissent, the chief will have a hard time writing or joining an opinion in &lt;em&gt;Rucho&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Lamone&lt;/em&gt; that dismisses the impact of partisanship in redistricting. In the &lt;em&gt;Rucho&lt;/em&gt; oral argument in April, Chief Justice Roberts &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/oral_arguments/argument_transcripts/2018/18-422_5hd5.pdf&quot;&gt;expressed&lt;/a&gt; scepticism that “partisan identification” is the “only basis on which people vote”. Electoral results “can change dramatically” depending on other factors, such as “the particular appeal of individual candidates” or who is at the top of the ticket. This sentiment clashes with the view in Justice Alito’s dissent that an electoral map’s lines—who votes in which district—obviously have “institutional and legislative consequences”. It isn’t clear whether the chief’s decision to sign Justice Alito’s dissent in &lt;em&gt;Bethune-Hill&lt;/em&gt; translates into a willingness to tame the gerrymander—but that mystery should be resolved in a matter of days. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 23:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[On Britain beyond Brexit and the future of Conservatism]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/bagehots-notebook/2019/06/18/on-britain-beyond-brexit-and-the-future-of-conservatism]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_BLP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T12:00:15Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE END-OF-AUSTERITY message has certainly got through to the Centre for Policy Studies (CPS). On June 10th the CPS launched “Britain Beyond Brexit”, a new collection of essays edited by George Freeman and written for the most part by fellow products of the 2010 intake of MPs. The CPS hired the biggest room in 1 George Street—a vast hall decked out with gilt paint and portraits of bearded Victorians—and provided the guests not just with decent sandwiches but also with champagne and cream-and-strawberry scones. Several leadership candidates, such as Sajid Javid and Dominic Raab, made speeches. Penny Mordaunt clucked around like a mother hen (I wonder if her decision to sit out this leadership election might prove that she’s the most sensible member of the class of 2010). Mr Freeman made great claims that his book provides the party with “a new Conservatism for a new generation” and the intellectual tools that it needs to fight the resurgent hard left.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His enthusiasm is infectious. But he claims too much. His book is more of a curate’s egg than a Viagra pill capable of reviving a flagging conservative philosophy, let alone a hand grenade aimed at the headquarters of Corbynism. In his introduction Mr Freeman rightly argues that the Conservative Party is facing a crisis of the same sort of magnitude that it faced in 1848, 1901 and 1945. The political era that was created by Thatcherism is collapsing thanks most obviously to the financial order but also to the fact that Thatcherism doesn’t offer any obvious solution to pressing problems such as over-crowded commuter trains. The various contributors also tackle issues that Conservatives have shied away from, such as the importance of devolution. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet much of the book demonstrates just how difficult it is for a party to refuel intellectually while still in government. The chapter by Matt Hancock, the health secretary, is shockingly bad: a predictable paean of praise to technological innovation bereft of interesting examples and written in a succession of clichés. (One well-read Tory commented acidly that the fact that the chapter was so bad proved that it was written by its purported author rather than by an aide.) The book as a whole is notably free of detailed discussion of subjects such as social care (the issue that killed the party in the last election) or corporate reform. The Conservative Party as a whole will have to do a lot better than this if it is to make a compelling case against a resurgent far-left Labour Party. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;****&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An excellent cover package in this week’s &lt;em&gt;New Statesman&lt;/em&gt; on “The closing of the conservative mind” (with a promise of more to come!). Robert Saunders argues that the Conservative Party has always been much more of a party of ideas than it likes to pretend: its regeneration in the 1940s and particularly in the 1980s came because of its willingness to embrace radical new thinking about the basic building blocks of society. But now in place of ideas the party has nothing but a kamikaze ideology (“Brexit or bust”) and an empty faith in markets and technology (see above). Theresa May was an idea-free zone (compare her to Lord Salisbury or Arthur Balfour). Boris Johnson, her all-but-certain successor, is no more of an intellectual despite his ability to quote Latin tags. There are a few interesting thinkers in the party such as Jesse Norman and Rory Stewart (both, worryingly, Old Etonians) but this is much more the party of Gavin Williamson, the former fireplace salesman who boasts about his lack of interest in political theory, than it is the party of these eccentric “reading men”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The point is well made. But couldn’t it equally well be applied to the Liberal mind or the Labour mind—or perhaps the Western mind in general? The Blair-Cameron-Clinton liberalism that dominated politics in the 1990s and early 2000s is exhausted. This liberalism rested on a simple formula: simply add social liberalism to economic liberalism and you have the ingredients of a good society. The more acute observers of politics always knew that this was too good to be true: Daniel Bell’s “The Cultural Contradictions of Capitalism” demonstrated that social liberalism had the potential to destroy the moral capital that forms the basis of economic liberalism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But over the past few years we have learned that if anything Mr Bell underestimated the contradictions of the position. The biggest problems facing most capitalist societies at the moment stem from the excesses of both forms of liberalism. The excesses of economic liberalism have given us giant corporations that are crushing competition and, in the case of internet companies, developing a sinister form of surveillance capitalism. The excesses of social liberalism have given us various forms of social breakdown that can be seen at their most extreme in America: record levels of broken families; an epidemic of drugs, particularly opioids; millions of men who have dropped out of the labour force and taken to a life of petty crime and binge-watching TV. It’s unfair to blame these problems on social liberalism alone. They have a lot to do with the destruction of manufacturing jobs and the legacy of slavery. But social liberalism clearly has something to do with it: the lightening of prohibitions on self-destructive behaviour leads people to make decisions which, in the long-term, can leave them either addicted to drugs or lacking the skills or self-discipline to become productive members of society. The ultimate example of the failure of the double liberalism is San Francisco, where hundreds of homeless drug addicts live on the streets—and where tech billionaires and would-be-billionaires have to dodge piles of human faeces as they walk to the latest trendy sushi joint. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then there is the Labour mind. The Labour Party has responded to the collapse of neoliberalism not by trying to produce a new progressive synthesis but by re-embracing one of the 20th century’s most blood-stained ideologies. Jeremy Corbyn—a man who makes Theresa May look like an intellectual—has surrounded himself by hard-line Marxists such as Andrew Murray and Seumas Milne who, with their public-school educations, secular fanaticism and appetite for party infighting, come straight out of the pages of David Caute’s “The Fellow-Travellers”. John McDonnell, the shadow chancellor, is clearly one of the cleverest people in parliament, with an appetite for buttressing his Trotskyism with ideas borrowed from other traditions, particularly the co-operative tradition, and an ability to use new ideas (such as taking 10% of shares into public ownership) to serve old purposes. But the fact that he’s such a vigorous walker should not blind us to the fact that he’s walking in the wrong direction and trying to lead his country over a cliff. While this band is in charge the Labour mind is not so much closed as dead. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;****&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;New Statesman&lt;/em&gt; cover package coincides, more or less, with the publication of George Will’s new magnum opus, a 640-page study of conservatism called “The Conservative Sensibility” (Mr Will says that he chose “sensibility” rather than “mind” because “mind” was already taken, by Russell Kirk). “The Conservative Sensibility”—a torrent of philosophical musings on the great American and European conservative traditions—is proof that at least one conservative mind is still open. Mr Will still beats all his rivals in his ability to combine high thinking with a shrewd capacity to understand day-to-day American politics. The book’s reception is also proof that it’s not just conservative minds that have closed: when, as a Princeton alumnus, he addressed a group of Princeton students recently, these children of privilege decided to turn their backs on him for various unknown intellectual sins. But Mr Will’s book does also indirectly support the thesis of the closing of the conservative mind: it is hard to think of any of today’s angry young “movement” conservatives surviving in journalism for fifty years, as Mr Will has, and still having enough to say to produce a big book at 78. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 21:40:36 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“He’s never really stopped campaigning”—Trump makes it official]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/18/hes-never-really-stopped-campaigning-trump-makes-it-official]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_blm502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T11:22:14Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AMERICA&amp;#x27;S PRESIDENT&lt;/strong&gt; heads back to the Sunshine State today to announce his candidacy. What to expect this time around? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/17/muhammad-morsi-egypts-only-democratic-ruler-dies-in-court&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Muhammad Morsi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Egypt’s first democratically elected president, has died in court. We look back on his troubled leadership and ignominious end. And, this year’s &lt;strong&gt;Women’s World Cup&lt;/strong&gt; is drawing much more attention than past tournaments, in part because of a long-overdue reckoning about money in the sport. Runtime: 20 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/a7a69868-ebe9-4950-8d13-8bac9642d622&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 19:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Facebook wants to create a digital currency]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/18/facebook-wants-to-create-a-worldwide-digital-currency]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_wbp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A GLOBAL DIGITAL currency would make sending money across the world as easy as texting. It would do away with fees, delays and other barriers to the flow of cash. It would give those in less developed countries access to the financial system and a way to protect hard-earned wages against runaway inflation. It could trigger a wave of innovation in finance, much like the internet did in online services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That, in a nutshell, is what on June 18th Facebook promised to launch within a year. Libra, as the social network’s new currency is to be known in honour of an ancient Roman unit of mass (and the word for “pound” in many romance languages), professes to be all about “empower[ing] billions of people”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The potential is indeed enormous. If each of Facebook’s 2.4bn users converted a slice of their savings into libras, it could immediately become one of the world’s most circulated currencies. It could also, if widely adopted, vest unprecedented power in the hands of its issuer. In a tacit acknowledgment that its mishandling of user data, condoning the spread of misinformation and other sins have devalued its stock with policymakers, users and potential partners—though not investors—Facebook wants to outsource the running of Libra to a consortium of trustworthies recruited from the world of finance, technology and NGOs. The consequences for the global financial system could be far-reaching. So could the impact on Facebook’s business.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the project lives up to the mock-ups, buying, selling, holding, sending and receiving libras will be a doddle. It can be done in Facebook’s Messenger app or WhatsApp, another messaging-service-cum-social-network it owns—and, later next year, in a standalone app. All at a tap of a smartphone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far, so familiar. Messenger already offers payments to Americans. WhatsApp is testing a similar function in India. But these services do not cross borders, and require users to have a bank account. Fintech firms like TransferWise, which offer international transfers to the banked, take a 4-5% cut to wire $200—a third less than Western Union but not nothing. Libra will be global and cheap, and require no bank accounts: more bitcoin than Venmo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Except that, unlike bitcoins and other cryptocurrencies, libras will change hands in seconds, not minutes, for next to nothing, not a few dollars. The system should handle 1,000 transactions a second at its launch, and more later, compared with no more than seven a second for bitcoin. The virtual coins will be bought with real money, which will top up the reserve backing the currency. This should prevent wild price swings from bitcoin-like speculation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If it works, Libra could be a money-spinner for Facebook, albeit not directly. Notional transaction fees would not generate much revenue. But libras should allow Facebook to charge more for online ads, by making purchases of advertised products quicker and simpler. It could furnish a new source of data to target adverts, making up for user information Facebook will forgo with the “pivot to privacy”, which Mark Zuckerberg, its boss, proclaimed in March with respect to messaging. Libra would let his company catch up with WeChat, a Chinese super-app which offers payments and other financial services, and whose foreign ambitions are on hold as the Sino-American trade war rages on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technically and financially, Facebook could probably pull off such an ambitious undertaking on its own. Not politically. Its culture is more measured than it was in its early years, when it aspired to “move fast and break things”—but only a bit. Chary consumers may choose not to entrust their money to a social network which has, until recently, leaked their personal data left and right. Unless users appear on board, merchants may be reluctant to embrace the currency, however hassle-free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enter the Libra consortium. The association, to be based in reassuringly staid Geneva, will take over from Facebook before the first libra has been spent and manage the hard-currency reserves. Facebook has enlisted 28 prospective founding members out of an envisaged 100, each with equal voting rights and operating a node in a decentralised system which issues coins. They include financial firms (Visa and Stripe, among others), online services (Spotify, Uber), cryptocurrency wallets (Anchorage, Coinbase), venture capitalists (Andreessen Horowitz, Union Square Ventures) and charities (Kiva, Mercy Corps)—though, for the time being, no banks. Not a libertarian alternative to the existing financial system, in other words, but a complement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To add credibility to its promise, broken in the past, to keep social and financial data strictly separate, Facebook has created a subsidiary, Calibra, to run Libra services within its apps. It is unlikely to face hurdles to uptake from Apple or Google. It is impossible to imagine them expelling Messenger and WhatsApp—and later other providers Facebook is inviting to the open-source project—from their app stores, as they have done with other cryptocurrency offerings, many of which have turned out to be scams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To get Libra going, the consortium will pay merchants to offer discounts to customers who pay in the new currency, financed by a $10m one-off fee each member pays for a seat at the table. Eventually, Facebook would like anybody, not just the consortium, to be able to generate the currency, move it and offer services on top of its “blockchain” (crypto-speak for the database that keeps track of who owns what). At that point, Libra would truly turn into Bitcoin, minus the kinks and the libertarianism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hard currency&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;With a project with so many moving parts, much can go wrong. Although Facebook says it has a working prototype, the technology is untested; sceptics doubt that a 100-node system, let alone a bigger one, could process thousands of transactions per second. Hackers are doubtless champing at the bit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then there are consortium dynamics. Facebook will have to prove to the other 99 Libra members that it is truly prepared to give up control. At the same time, because important decisions need a two-thirds majority, someone has to knock heads together. The history of information technology is littered with initiatives which collapsed under the weight of internal conflict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The biggest barrier may be political. Facebook has apparently consulted many regulators. Initially they should be able to keep tabs on Libra. The providers of digital wallets will have to comply with national rules, like those against money-laundering. Calibra, whose integration into Messenger and WhatsApp will initially make it the dominant wallet, is bound to stoke competition concerns. These may recede as the currency grows bigger and more decentralised, only to be replaced by worries about financial stability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Libra’s success, then, is far from assured. But it could prove useful even if it flops, for it offers a blueprint for how Facebook itself could one day be governed. The Libra Association’s main task is to oversee the blockchain, ensuring, for instance, that Calibra does not enjoy privileged access to it. An equivalent Facebook Association, some observers have ventured, could be composed of representatives of users, advertisers, data-protection authorities and so on. Their job could be to oversee the “social graph”, another database, which lists all of Facebook’s users and the links between them—and to guarantee that Facebook users can post to another social network and vice versa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Calls for a Facebook constitution along these lines have grown louder as the social network’s influence on world affairs, from election-meddling in America to genocide in Myanmar, has become apparent. Mr Zuckerberg is no stranger to such thinking. In 2009 Facebook let users vote on big changes in its privacy policies but abandoned the experiment with global democracy a few years later. Last year Mr Zuckerberg announced that Facebook wanted to set up a “content review board” of independent experts—a kind of “Supreme Court”, in his words, which would make “the final judgment call on what should be acceptable speech”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asked whether Libra could serve as a model for Facebook, David Marcus, who is in charge of the project, replies that it marks “a coming of age, the moment we recognise that there are some things that we shouldn’t control—and a radical departure from the traditional way of operating things”. Perhaps. But checks and balances would almost certainly make Facebook less profitable. It would be ironic if a new digital currency marked the beginning of the end of Facebook’s money-minting days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 19:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>