<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Online identification is getting more and more intrusive]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/05/22/online-identification-is-getting-more-and-more-intrusive]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_std004.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-22T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;MOST ONLINE fraud involves identity theft, which is why businesses that operate on the web have a keen interest in distinguishing impersonators from genuine customers. Passwords help. But many can be guessed or are jotted down imprudently. Newer phones, tablets, and laptop and desktop computers often have beefed-up security with fingerprint and facial recognition. But these can be spoofed. To overcome these shortcomings the next level of security is likely to identify people using things which are harder to copy, such as the way they walk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many online security services already use a system called device fingerprinting. This employs software to note things like the model type of a gadget employed by a particular user; its hardware configuration; its operating system; the apps which have been downloaded onto it; and other features, including sometimes the Wi-Fi networks it regularly connects through and devices like headsets it plugs into.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results are sufficient to build a profile of both the device and its user’s habits. If something unusual is then spotted—say, access to a bank account being sought from a phone with a different profile from that which a customer usually uses—appropriate measures can be taken. For example, additional security questions can be posed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LexisNexis Risk Solutions, an American analytics firm, has catalogued more than 4bn phones, tablets and other computers in this way for banks and other clients. Roughly 7% of them have been used for shenanigans of some sort. But device fingerprinting is becoming less useful. Apple, Google and other makers of equipment and operating systems have been steadily restricting the range of attributes that can be observed remotely. The reason for doing this is to limit the amount of personal information that could fall into unauthorised hands. But such restrictions also make it harder to distinguish illegitimate from legitimate users.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is why a new approach, behavioural biometrics, is gaining ground. It relies on the wealth of measurements made by today’s devices. These include data from accelerometers and gyroscopic sensors, that reveal how people hold their phones when using them, how they carry them and even the way they walk. Touchscreens, keyboards and mice can be monitored to show the distinctive ways in which someone’s fingers and hands move. Sensors can detect whether a phone has been set down on a hard surface such as a table or dropped lightly on a soft one such as a bed. If the hour is appropriate, this action could be used to assume when a user has retired for the night. These traits can then be used to determine whether someone attempting to make a transaction is likely to be the device’s habitual user.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Behavioural biometrics make it possible to identify an individual’s “unique motion fingerprint”, says John Whaley, head of UnifyID, a firm in Silicon Valley that is involved in the field. With the right software, data from a phone’s sensors can reveal details as personal as which part of someone’s foot strikes the pavement first, and how hard; the length of a walker’s stride; the number of strides per minute; and the swing and spring in the walker’s hips and step. It can also work out whether the phone in question is in a handbag, a pocket or held in a hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using these variables UnifyID sorts gaits into about 50,000 distinct types. When coupled with information about a user’s finger pressure and speed on the touchscreen, as well as a device’s regular places of use—as revealed by its GPS unit—that user’s identity can be pretty-well determined, Mr Whaley claims. UnifyID began offering behavioural biometrics to its clients (which include retail banks, online retailers, delivery companies and ride-sharing firms) in 2017. In time, advertisers will pay for the scoop on individuals’ lifestyle-revealing movements, reckons Mr Whaley, though his firm has no plans yet to expand in that direction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The lidless eye&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Behavioural biometrics can, moreover, go beyond verifying a user’s identity. It can also detect circumstances when it is likely that a fraud is being committed. On a device with a keyboard, for instance, a warning sign is when the typing takes on a staccato style, with a longer-than-usual finger “flight time” between keystrokes. This, according to Aleksander Kijek, head of product at Nethone, a firm in Warsaw that works out behavioural biometrics for companies that sell things online, is an indication that the device has been hijacked, and is under the remote control of a computer program rather than a human typist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On a device with a touchscreen rather than a keyboard, however, the reverse is true. Most people type with their thumbs on touchscreens, so flight times between keystrokes are longer. In this case, therefore, it is short flight times which are a signal of something suspicious going on—for example, that a touchscreen device is actually being operated remotely, using the keyboard of a laptop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Used wisely, behavioural biometrics could be a boon. As Neil Costigan, the boss of BehavioSec, a behavioural-biometrics firm in San Francisco, observes, the software can toil quietly in the background, continuously authenticating account-holders without badgering them for additional passwords, their mother’s maiden name “and all that nonsense”. UnifyID and an unnamed car company are even developing a system that unlocks the doors of a vehicle once the gait of the driver, as measured by his phone, is recognised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Used unwisely, however, the system could become yet another electronic spy, permitting complete strangers to monitor your actions, from the moment you reach for your phone in the morning, to when you fling it on the floor at night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 23:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“He really has had his fingers burned”—Austrian scandal and Europe’s fringe parties]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/22/he-really-has-had-his-fingers-burned-austrian-scandal-and-europes-fringe-parties]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/austria.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-22T11:50:03Z&quot;&gt;May 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS A SCANDAL involving &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/18/scandal-fells-the-vice-chancellor-of-austria&quot;&gt;Austria&lt;/a&gt;’s hard-right Freedom party&lt;/strong&gt; causes the government to unravel, we examine the fringe parties of Europe and assess their chances in this week’s &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/briefing/2019/05/18/the-european-parliament-elections-are-responding-to-a-changed-world&quot;&gt;European elections&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. And as tech billionaires continue to indulge their obsessions with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/05/18/jeff-bezoss-ambition-to-colonise-space-is-straight-from-the-1970s&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;space travel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, we look at the sketchy economics of moving off-world. Also, a stark warning for lovers of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/15/americas-avocado-supply-is-set-to-tighten&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;avocados&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: supply concerns make them a volatile brunch choice. Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/ibizaremix-austriaandtheeuropeanfringe&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 20:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“FOOD: Bigger than the Plate” leaves you wanting more]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/22/food-bigger-than-the-plate-leaves-you-wanting-more]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_BKP508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-22T12:10:29Z&quot;&gt;May 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOOD IS more than a question of taste. The UN’s Food and Agriculture Organisation &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/briefing/2018/10/13/why-people-in-rich-countries-are-eating-more-vegan-food&quot;&gt;estimates that around 80% of agricultural land is devoted to rearing livestock&lt;/a&gt;, yet it yields only 18% of the world’s calories. Cattle are the fifth-largest producers of methane, a greenhouse gas which affects the climate. Were the world’s eaters to switch to vegetarianism, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2016/04/19/why-eating-more-vegetables-is-good-for-the-environment&quot;&gt;in 2050 agricultural emissions would be 29% lower&lt;/a&gt;—or 70% lower were people to opt for veganism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new exhibition at the Victoria and Albert Museum (V&amp;amp;A) in London seeks to “pose questions about how the collective choices we make can lead to a more sustainable, just and delicious food future”. Entitled “FOOD: Bigger than the Plate”, it features more than 70 installations by artists, designers, scientists and chefs, divided into four sections: “Compost”, “Farming”, “Trading” and “Eating”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first part, “Compost”, examines how the invention of landfill rubbish-disposal and mains-drainage systems during the Industrial Revolution disrupted the food cycle. Where before people had been aware of the waste they and their food produced, returning its nutrients (and less beneficial byproducts) to the soil, a culture of “flush and forget” permanently changed attitudes towards waste. The projects featured in this section offer ways to restore the cycle—used coffee grounds from the V&amp;amp;A’s café make for nutritious soil beds, which grow mushrooms then used in café meals; an Italian dairy farmer turns the 150,000kg of manure produced every day by his 3,500 cows into a terracotta-like material for bricks, tiles and tableware. Though this is all interesting and innovative, the section rather resembles a sustainable design fair. One problem is being ignored: that of persuading people to consume less in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best parts of the show try to take on these questions of scale. In “Trading”—which focuses on the buying, selling and transporting of food—“Banana Story”, a design project by Johanna Seelemann, points out the vast amounts of international travel hidden in “made in” labels. Her “banana passport” tracks a single banana’s 14-day journey from a tree in Ecuador to a supermarket in Iceland, covering 8,800km and passing through 33 pairs of hands. It succeeds because it attaches bigger questions to a small item: if you had to give that passport a stamp of approval every time you bought a banana in the supermarket, would you still buy it? Would you feel comfortable eating a banana every day once you had seen the energy and human labour required to deliver it to you? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On to “Farming”, and “Our Daily Bread”, a 13-minute film by Nikolaus Geyrhalter and Wolfgang Widerhofer, looks at industrial food production and high-tech farming. Bulls bred to provide sperm for artificial insemination file past the camera, pumped with so much testosterone that their muscles unnaturally bulge like bodybuilders’. In a lettuce field at night, kneeling workers inch forward in silence, following the picking-machine’s basket like dogs behind a bone. The slick processes show how detached and clinical food production has become, which is almost as troubling as scenes of animal slaughter. “Our Daily Bread” is partly screened off—presumably because some viewers or young children might find certain scenes upsetting—but it is one of the few things in the exhibition that fulfils its claim to “question values” or “make us reconsider”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“FOOD: Bigger than the Plate” also features tasty morsels exploring more positive attitudes towards food. In the final section, “Eating”, the visitor is introduced to the Korean idea of &lt;em&gt;son-mat&lt;/em&gt; (literally, “the taste of one’s hands”), an expression which refers to the ineffable brilliance of your grandmother&amp;#x27;s cooking. A table is laid with examples of innovative tableware. There are coloured plates to make eating easier for those with dementia—food is more easily distinguishable on bright blue plates, and the colour apparently stimulates the appetite—and funny-shaped spoons which are said to heighten the sensitivity of the user&amp;#x27;s palate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these highlights, the exhibition lacks a clear thesis and invites only superficial engagement. Perhaps the curators are right to avoid an overwhelming sense of doom and gloom, but the show does not prompt the viewer to consider how attitudes towards eating—whether gluttonous and globalised or ascetic and local—affect the environment. The final exhibit is a “food lab”, where staff make a miniature canapé for each visitor based on a quiz about the future of food. Gimmicks such as this are skirting far more interesting questions: a tiny canapé is not going to encourage people to think big, or make big changes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“FOOD: Bigger than the Plate” continues at the V&amp;amp;A in London until October 20th&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 19:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“He really has had his fingers burned”—Austrian scandal and Europe’s fringe parties]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/22/he-really-has-had-his-fingers-burned-austria-and-europes-fringe-parties]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/austria.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-22T11:50:03Z&quot;&gt;May 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS A SCANDAL involving &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/18/scandal-fells-the-vice-chancellor-of-austria&quot;&gt;Austria&lt;/a&gt;’s hard-right Freedom party&lt;/strong&gt; causes the government to unravel, we examine the fringe parties of Europe and assess their chances in this week’s &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/briefing/2019/05/18/the-european-parliament-elections-are-responding-to-a-changed-world&quot;&gt;European elections&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. And as tech billionaires continue to indulge their obsessions with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/05/18/jeff-bezoss-ambition-to-colonise-space-is-straight-from-the-1970s&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;space travel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, we look at the sketchy economics of moving off-world. Also, a stark warning for lovers of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/15/americas-avocado-supply-is-set-to-tighten&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;avocados&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: supply concerns make them a volatile brunch choice. Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/ibizaremix-austriaandtheeuropeanfringe&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 19:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Donald Trump preparing pardons for troops accused of war crimes?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/21/is-donald-trump-preparing-pardons-for-troops-accused-of-war-crimes]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_USP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-21T19:38:45Z&quot;&gt;May 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PRESIDENT DONALD TRUMP is reported to be considering a Memorial Day pardon for a number of American troops accused of killing civilians in Iraq and Afghanistan. As so often happens with Mr Trump, the cases appear to have come to his attention via Fox News. The accused troops have been championed by hosts including Pete Hegseth, himself an Afghan and Iraq war vet, as “men who went into the most dangerous places on earth with a job to defend us and made tough calls on a moment&amp;#x27;s notice.” This is familiar framing for Fox: lawyer versus warrior, activist versus cop, political correctness over the hard facts of a kill-or-be-killed world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iraq and Afghanistan were indeed environments in which combatants were hard-pressed to distinguish snipers from a bystanders, or commuters from car bombers, and had to make decisions fast. But most of the cases that may be under review by Mr Trump are not based on prosecutors second-guessing warriors from a place of safety. Rather, they are based on the testimonies of their comrades-in-arms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most prominent alleged defendant is Edward Gallagher, a decorated Navy SEAL platoon leader accused of killing an Islamic State prisoner during the siege of Mosul of 2017. He faces a court-martial later this month. The case against him is built on testimony from fellow SEALS, who say he also randomly gunned down civilians and threatened them. Clint Lorance, an Army lieutenant in Afghanistan who is serving a 19-year sentence for his role in the killing of two unarmed Afghans in 2012, was also denounced by men under his command, who said he gave them orders to shoot civilians they didn&amp;#x27;t think were a threat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The defenders of these men and the other accused offer justifications for why their men testified against them. Mr Gallagher&amp;#x27;s lawyer, for example, says that the men were malcontents who had been chewed out as &amp;quot;pussies&amp;quot; by their tough leader. Scapegoating, questionable informants, and stitch-ups cannot be ruled out in the military justice system any more than they can be in the civilian one. But most veterans find these scenarios far-fetched. Units are tight-knit. Grumbling against a leader may be common, but it is almost unheard of for a leader to be so unpopular his men would concoct a story against him—especially when he erred on the side of being too aggressive. &amp;quot;A platoon leader who is willing to loosen the reins a little and allow his subordinates to aggressively pursue the enemy will generally be a pretty popular guy,&amp;quot; commented one Afghan vet about Mr Lorance on Task and Purpose, a popular military blog.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To pardon men accused by their fellow soldiers and then convicted could cause grave damage to the military justice system and America’s standing. It is already extremely difficult for a prosecutor to reconstruct a shooting incident in a war zone and prove beyond a reasonable doubt that the shooter acted maliciously and not in reasonable fear of his or her life. Only the most egregious offenders, those whose actions were dreadful enough to have shocked their own comrades, come to trial. If even the baddest of bad apples get a pardon, why would anyone come forward? What hope does the US military justice system have of deterring war crimes in the first place?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many prominent former officers are horrified. General Barry McCaffrey, a long-time Trump critic, says circumventing military justice gives a &amp;quot;terrible signal”. Even some Trump allies, like Dan Crenshaw, a Republican Congressman and former SEAL, says a pardon should only be considered after evidence is produced in court.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;American commanders have long grappled with the damage civilian casualties did to missions that depended on winning the trust and cooperation of Iraqis and Afghans. In Iraq, for example, American and other foreign forces were responsible for perhaps 10-15% of the approximately 180-200,000 civilian deaths logged by the Iraq Body Count, an NGO. The vast majority of those were probably misjudgements or accidental killings, not deliberate murders of non-combatants. But your correspondent, who lived in Baghdad from 2003 to 2007, found that while Iraqis were statistically in greater danger from militias and insurgents, they often had a particular horror of the Americans, an alien force that could swat out their family&amp;#x27;s lives for a moment&amp;#x27;s inattention or impatience in traffic. Generals like David Petraeus, former head of the Central Intelligence Agency and America’s former commander in Afghanistan, regularly implored the troops to err on the side of caution when it came to opening fire. Critics of Mr Trump’s mooted pardon say it sends a signal to both American troops and the countries that might host them that America is not so worried about civilian deaths after all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But with Iraq and increasingly Afghanistan widely seen as failures, Americans are less concerned about the military&amp;#x27;s readiness to fight counterinsurgency wars. Some on the right treat the mere suggestion of war crimes as an insult to the American warrior. The left tends to see the crime in the war itself, not the fine details of the waging. Americans who care about a more restrained military, even if that also means a more effective military, may be thin on the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 05:40:36 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A political dynast is favoured to be Japan’s next prime minister]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/21/a-political-dynast-is-favoured-to-be-japans-next-prime-minister]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_asp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-21T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;GLANCE AT THE members of the Diet and this much is clear: Japanese politics is a business for old men. The average age of a member of parliament hovers at around 55, and prime ministers tend to be even older than that. So it is striking that people are talking about a 38-year-old, Shinjiro Koizumi (still a man, of course), as a potential successor to Shinzo Abe, the incumbent prime minister, who must step down by 2021 according to the rules of the ruling Liberal Democratic Party (LDP).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Koizumi is the son of a prominent former LDP prime minister, and, like many MPs, won the seat his father vacated when he retired from politics. In the decade since he was elected, however, he has made a name for himself in his own right. He has charisma, is a good orator and is unusually candid; he cites JFK, whose portrait adorns his walls, as an inspiration because he was an idealist who “talked to people not the media”. It doesn’t hurt that Mr Koizumi is fodder for glossy magazines thanks to his film-star looks (his brother is an actor).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Koizumi has been trying to show he has substance, not just star appeal, even though he has never had a job in the cabinet. His most important role in the government to date has been monitoring the reconstruction effort after the Tohoku earthquake in 2011—a task he is said to have done well. He is also an enthusiastic advocate of reforming health care and pensions, a step he says might help Japan get over its gloom about its ageing and shrinking population. He speaks of transferring resources from the old to the young, by making people work longer, for example, and by making child-rearing easier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He earned a master’s degree at Columbia University and speaks fluent English—a rarity in the Diet. He is hardly an iconoclast, rejecting immigration as a balm for the country’s demographic ailments, as most politicians do. He is woolly on other social issues. But he says he wants to push diversity. “If I hadn’t gone to the US, I wouldn’t really understand what diversity is,” he says; “It is hard to feel in Japan.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many Japanese take it for granted that Mr Koizumi will eventually become leader of the LDP and prime minister (the two jobs tend to go together); the question is when. The LDP’s leadership race involves votes among both its MPs and its broader membership. Polling suggests he is the most popular choice among the public; the media refer to him as Japan’s Macron. It helps that there are few strong alternatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Koizumi has to tread a delicate line by being enough of an insider to gain support within the party, but enough of a critic to earn the respect of the public at large. He praises Mr Abe’s reforms, but did not vote for him in LDP leadership elections in 2012 and 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Koizumi is coy about whether he will stand in 2021: “Let’s see.” But he points out that on the one hand, young people are becoming estranged from politics, and on the other that the LDP attracts more young voters than any other party. “Japan is getting ready to see more young leaders in politics,” he says, with a generous seasoning of self-interest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 05:40:35 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Did pollsters misread Australia’s election, or did pundits?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/21/did-pollsters-misread-australias-election-or-did-pundits]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_woc967.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-21T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUSTRALIAN ELECTION-WATCHERS appear to have given more credence to the opinion of a psychic crocodile named &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.ntnews.com.au/news/the-race-is-over-burt-the-psychic-croc-has-picked-saturdays-election-winner/news-story/f38616bb23fca38fedaf8a6e8d32b6cb&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Burt&lt;/a&gt;, who predicted a win for the Labor Leader, Bill Shorten, than they did to the true state of the public opinion polls. On May 20th the &lt;em&gt;Sydney Morning Herald&lt;/em&gt; wrote that pollsters had “spectacularly missed” the results of last week’s election, which ended in a “miracle” victory for Scott Morrison, the Liberal prime minister. The polls did indeed misfire—but only by a paltry two percentage points, slightly less than the historical average error in surveys taken during the final month of a campaign in Australia. Arguably it is pundits who have even more to answer for, having argued that the gap between the Liberals and Labor was much greater than the polls suggested. “Labor will win in this election,” Andy Marks, a political scientist, declared three weeks ago. “I think that’s virtually unquestionable.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Critics in Australia have compared the upset to big electoral surprises in other English-speaking democracies, such as America’s last presidential contest and Britain’s referendum on leaving the EU. However, polling before the vote gave Labor an even more tenuous lead than the modest advantages thought to be held by Hillary Clinton and the Remain campaign. Where America’s leading election forecasters gave Mrs Clinton anywhere from a 70% to 85% chance of winning the presidency, the odds of Mr Shorten becoming PM were much closer to 50%. According to a forecasting model developed by Peter Ellis, an Australian statistician for the Nous Group, a consultancy, the opposition party had merely a 54% chance of either winning an outright majority or capturing enough seats alongside minor-party allies to form a governing coalition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The count on a few closely contested seats has not yet been concluded. But forecasters currently predict that the coalition of the Liberal and National parties will win 78 of the 151 seats in the House of Representatives. Labor is projected to get just 67. Similar to the polls themselves, these outcomes are also narrowly within the realm of what analysts should have considered plausible based on a fair reading of the polls. Mr Ellis pegged the chance of an outright Coalition victory at 17%, though the magnitude of Labor’s disappointment was more surprising: he reckoned the probability that they would win 67 or fewer seats at just 4%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of this means that pollsters should be crowing about their performance. Their surveys showed a narrow Labor lead with metronomic regularity—so consistently, in fact, that it is likely at least some of them weighted their raw results to ensure their published figures resembled those of their competitors. Given the number of polls taken and their sample sizes, there was just a 3% chance that such a series of surveys would show so little variation if they had been truly random and independent. Although the polls indeed showed a close race, a lack of methodological transparency means the pollsters must share some blame for the public’s confusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 05:40:35 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[When the chips are down—America and Huawei]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/21/when-the-chips-are-down-america-and-huawei]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/huawei.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-21T16:53:43Z&quot;&gt;May 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;HOW WILL the Trump administration’s &lt;strong&gt;restrictions on American companies selling products to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/20/holding-out-on-huawei&quot;&gt;Huawei&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; affect the Chinese telecoms giant? Can the world’s second biggest smartphone maker adapt to not doing business with America? Also, &lt;strong&gt;Michael Froman&lt;/strong&gt;, a former US trade representative and the vice-chairman of MasterCard, discusses &lt;strong&gt;how private companies can promote freer trade&lt;/strong&gt;. And &lt;strong&gt;Jennifer Eberhardt&lt;/strong&gt;, a professor of psychology at Stanford University, explains &lt;strong&gt;the science of racial bias&lt;/strong&gt;. Simon Long hosts. Runtime: 22mins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/39fc4a99-8861-437d-81e2-684d13e48f92/moneytalks-whenthechipsaredown&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 03:40:30 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The footballer caught up in Armenia’s conflict with Azerbaijan]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/21/the-footballer-caught-up-in-armenias-conflict-with-azerbaijan]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_blp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-21T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;HENRIKH MKHITARYAN is no ordinary Armenian. At 30 years of age, he has won the “Armenian Footballer of the Year” award a record eight times. He captains his country’s national team, and has played for some of Europe’s biggest clubs.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Yet, despite such credentials, “Micki” (pictured above) finds himself caught up in Armenia’s ongoing conflict with Azerbaijan, its neighbour. He will not play in the Europa League final on May 29th, when his current team, Arsenal, play another London side, Chelsea, in Baku, Azerbaijan’s capital. Both club and player made the decision, seemingly due to fears over his safety. Arsenal said the club had not received “acceptable guarantees” from UEFA, the governing body of European football, that it would be safe for Mr Mkhitaryan to travel, and they have now taken matters into their own hands.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;That Arsenal seems to have felt it has no option but to pull its player out of the final has angered the club and its fans, who were already incensed with UEFA’s decision, after a bidding process by member states, to host the event in Azerbaijan. Baku is further east than Baghdad, and the club, like Chelsea, is being allocated just 6,000 tickets for a stadium that holds more than 68,000 people. But Mr Mkhitaryan’s situation is also a reminder that a little-known political rivalry is still tense. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The conflict centres on control of the Nagorno-Karabakh region, which declared independence from Azerbaijan in 1988 as the Soviet Union started to break apart. After the Armenians sided with Nagorno-Karabakh, a full-scale war broke out—in which some 30,000 people had died by 1994. The region has been under Armenian control ever since, but this has failed to bring a lasting peace. There have been frequent skirmishes along the Azeri-Armenian border. Some 200 people were killed in a “four-day war” in April 2016. What started as a dispute over territory has become “an interstate rivalry”, says Thomas De Waal, a senior fellow with Carnegie Europe, a think tank. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Recently there have been a few encouraging signs. The so-called velvet revolution in Armenia last year saw Nikol Pashinyan become prime minister and set up a democratic government. Mr Pashinyan has since met Ilham Aliyev, the president of Azerbaijan, several times and made positive public statements, breathing some life into the peace process. However, Mr De Waal notes there has not been much indication of compromise on either side yet.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Elkhan Mammadov, the general secretary of Azerbaijan’s football association, points out that Armenians have competed in sporting events in Baku before. Four years ago 25 Armenian athletes competed in the European Games there, though they were booed by local fans. Mr Mammadov also says that the country’s government had issued guarantees for Mr Mkhitaryan’s “protection and safety”. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;But this public reminder of the conflict with Armenia could overshadow the final. On such a huge occasion, Azerbaijan would have hoped to present itself as a “welcoming” and “accommodating” country, says Simon Rofe of London University&amp;#x27;s School of Oriental and African Studies. Its hosting of other sporting events, such as an annual Formula 1 Grand Prix, has also been criticised as an attempt to deflect criticism from its poor human-rights record.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;That an Armenian sportsman did not feel safe travelling to Azerbaijan reflects poorly on the two countries’ relations, but also on UEFA. The organisation said it had developed a “comprehensive security plan” in conjunction with authorities in Azerbaijan, and showed it to Arsenal. UEFA describes Mr Mkhitaryan’s absence as a “personal decision”. “Micki” has missed less important matches in Azerbaijan in the past, but this is different, he says. He wrote on Twitter: “It&amp;#x27;s the kind of game that doesn&amp;#x27;t come along very often for us players and I must admit, it hurts me a lot to miss it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 03:40:28 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Arab states waste heaps of food during Ramadan]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/21/arab-states-waste-heaps-of-food-during-ramadan]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_map501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-21T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS MUSLIMS HAVE for centuries, Ahmed Toufiq broke his Ramadan fast by nibbling a date while the call to prayer echoed across the Nile. Then he turned to the heaping plates in front of him. He made short work of a fragrant lentil soup, but his pace slowed as he picked through salads and scooped dips with steaming pita bread. When he walked outside for a cigarette 20 minutes after sunset, a server collected half a plate of untouched kebab and rice. “Before &lt;em&gt;iftar&lt;/em&gt;, you feel like you want to eat for two,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arab states waste a lot of food. A study in 2016 by the Economist Intelligence Unit, our sister company, found that Saudi Arabia bins 427kg per person annually, triple the average in Europe and North America. Some may chalk this up to traditions of hospitality: even a “light lunch” in Cairo or Beirut leaves guests in a torpor. The reasons are more varied, though. Half of the fruits and vegetables grown in Egypt are never eaten because they are often moved to market in open-air trucks and wilt quickly in the heat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The problem gets worse during Ramadan. Residents of the United Arab Emirates each produce an extra 1.8kg of waste per day in the holy month, a 67% increase. Food accounts for 55% of Dubai’s trash, up from 22% in other months. Bahrain’s food waste increases by half to 600 tonnes daily. Buffets are a major culprit, especially in the Gulf, where hotels and restaurants often serve through the night. A study by researchers at Masdar, a state-owned renewable-energy firm in Abu Dhabi, found that just 53% of food at &lt;em&gt;iftar&lt;/em&gt; buffets is eaten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is an expensive waste. Some governments see it as a security risk, too. The region is a net food importer. In the weeks before Ramadan, state-run media admonish their citizens to be less wasteful. On social media diners now swap recommendations not on lavish buffets but on a la carte options. Autocratic regimes that frown on civil society are happy for their citizens to take up the cause of food waste. Wahab, a Qatari start-up, sends volunteers to collect leftovers from hotels and restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few hotels in Dubai have installed cameras and scales to track what winds up in the bin. Chefs use the data to cook less of unpopular dishes. One Hilton property says the system cut buffet waste by 70%. Others are doing away with the buffet altogether—if not for &lt;em&gt;iftar&lt;/em&gt; then for &lt;em&gt;suhour&lt;/em&gt;, the pre-dawn “dinner”. A growing number of restaurants advertise &lt;em&gt;prix fixe&lt;/em&gt; menus as a waste-free way to break fasts. As an added perk, in an emirate struggling with an economic slump, these meals are cheaper. A lavish hotel buffet might set customers back 200 dirhams ($54). Set menus cost about half that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Egypt’s national food bank feeds about 1.8m families during Ramadan. Some of the food is sourced from hotels that package leftovers from their buffet trays. For health reasons, though, uneaten food from a customer’s plate must be thrown away. After 15 hours of fasting eyes are bigger than stomachs. High-tech cameras will not help. So one Cairo hotel found a low-tech solution for its buffet: it made the plates smaller.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 02:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>