<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[How to read the Supreme Court’s latest ruling on abortion rights]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/29/how-to-read-the-supreme-courts-latest-ruling-on-abortion-rights]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_USP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-29T14:30:20Z&quot;&gt;May 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 2016, Donald Trump said &lt;em&gt;Roe v Wade,&lt;/em&gt; the 1973 abortion-rights ruling, would “automatically” be overruled by justices he would appoint to the Supreme Court. Three years later, with two of his picks in robes and a surge of challenges to &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt; flying to the court, abortion-rights supporters fear Mr Trump’s prediction may be close to coming true. But, so far, every time a reckoning on &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt; seems imminent, the Supreme Court has taken a step back. Abortion rights are in trouble, but it seems that the conservative justices on the nation’s highest court (with the notable exception of Clarence Thomas) are content to plod along rather than rush headlong into a decision that could spark a dangerous new flashpoint in the culture wars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While states like Georgia and Alabama have been passing alarmingly extreme abortion bans that are flatly out-of-line with &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt;, the Supreme Court has been considering whether to take &lt;em&gt;Box v Planned Parenthood of Indiana and Kentucky,&lt;/em&gt; a case involving a more insidious type of anti-abortion law. &lt;em&gt;Box&lt;/em&gt; concerns HEA 1337, which Mike Pence, now the vice-president, signed into law in 2016 when he was governor of Indiana. In a Seventh Circuit Court of Appeals &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://casetext.com/case/planned-parenthood-ind-ky-inc-v-commr-of-the-ind-state-dept-of-health&quot;&gt;ruling&lt;/a&gt; last year, two of the law’s provisions were deemed unconstitutional: a requirement that fetal remains from abortions be buried or cremated; and a bar on abortions motivated solely by the fetus’s race, sex or diagnosed disability such as Down syndrome. The fetal-remains provision lacks a rational basis, the Seventh Circuit held, while the “non-discrimination” rule undermines &lt;em&gt;Roe’s&lt;/em&gt; promise, reaffirmed in 1992 in &lt;em&gt;Planned Parenthood v Casey,&lt;/em&gt; that states may place no “undue burden” on a woman’s right to end a pregnancy prior to viability, or about 24 weeks’ gestation. To prohibit women with particular motivations from aborting their fetuses is to impose “far greater than a substantial obstacle” on the constitutional right, the Seventh Circuit ruled. These limits are “absolute prohibitions on abortions prior to viability which the Supreme Court has clearly held cannot be imposed by the state”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The justices decide which cases they will decide, and they can take as long as they like to “grant” or “deny” a so-called “petition for certiorari”. &lt;em&gt;Box&lt;/em&gt; had been on the justices’ conference table since early January, and they have mulled over how to handle it at 14 private conferences. Finally, on May 28th, the court issued a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://casetext.com/case/box-v-planned-parenthood-of-indiana-and-kentucky-inc&quot;&gt;curious ruling&lt;/a&gt; on &lt;em&gt;Box&lt;/em&gt;. First, by a vote of 7-2, the justices reversed the Seventh Circuit on the fetal-remains question. Under the deferential standard employed at the appeals court, the justices noted in an unsigned opinion, states may regulate how aborted fetal tissue is disposed of. (The ruling left open whether the provision might fail the “undue burden” test from &lt;em&gt;Casey&lt;/em&gt;, since it wasn’t litigated that way.) Second, by a 9-0 vote, the court declined to weigh in on the discrimination claim. Without saying a word on the controversy over aborting fetuses diagnosed with Down syndrome, the court simply observed that “[o]nly the Seventh Circuit has thus far addressed this kind of law” and pointed to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://supreme.findlaw.com/supreme_court/rules/part3.html&quot;&gt;Rule 10&lt;/a&gt;, according to which the justices generally stay on the sidelines when a legal issue has not “been considered by additional courts of appeals”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brief 650-word opinion contrasts sharply with the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.scotusblog.com/case-files/cases/box-v-planned-parenthood-of-indiana-and-kentucky-inc/&quot;&gt;hundreds of pages of briefs&lt;/a&gt; from pro-life organisations and religious groups urging the Supreme Court to save both parts of Indiana’s law. The surgical side-step, coming after months of deliberation, bears the fingerprints of Chief Justice John Roberts, the new median justice on a right-tilting court. Though Chief Justice Roberts worked against &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt; as a lawyer in George W. Bush’s Justice Department and has voted to chip away at abortion rights, he has become keener to steer the court away from treacherous waters. With a baldly political light cast on the court in the Trump era—especially during last autumn’s explosive confirmation hearing for Brett Kavanaugh—the chief seems increasingly circumspect. He is loth to take on a controversy that would spring a 5-4 abortion decision on America just weeks before the parties’ national conventions in the summer of 2020.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Chief Justice Roberts did not construct this compromise by himself. On the left, he persuaded Justices Elena Kagan and Stephen Breyer to uphold the fetal-remains law—apparently by demurring on whether it might fail under a different litigation strategy. (Justices Sonia Sotomayor and Ruth Bader Ginsburg would have left in place the lower-court ruling against fetal-tissue rule.) On the right, the chief convinced his fellow conservatives to hold their fire on the Down syndrome provision. Justice Samuel Alito and Mr Trump’s two picks (Justices Kavanaugh and Neil Gorsuch) joined the per-curiam silently. Only Justice Clarence Thomas would not be restrained, penning a 20-page tirade associating women who choose to end their pregnancies with the eugenics movement of the 20th-century. Abortion is “rife with the potential for eugenic manipulation”, he wrote, and prenatal tests giving women information about fetal abnormalities add fuel to a moral travesty. The only reason Justice Thomas cited for not voting to take up Indiana’s appeal—and allowing the Down-syndrome provision to take effect—was the matter of Supreme Court procedure. “[F]urther percolation” in the lower courts, he wrote, “may assist our review of this issue”. That review, he hastened to note, should take place “soon”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Viewed alongside the court’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/02/08/the-supreme-court-blocks-abortion-clinic-regulations-in-louisiana&quot;&gt;refusal&lt;/a&gt; in February to let anti-abortion clinic regulations go into effect in Louisiana—a move that surprised many observers—this court’s Solomonic ruling in &lt;em&gt;Box&lt;/em&gt; signals a Supreme Court that is in no hurry to entertain serious challenges to &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt; while a presidential campaign is underway. But abortion rights face a highly uncertain future in the hands of the justices in the medium term, and with prospects of another Supreme Court appointment for Mr Trump in the coming years, the pace toward a post-&lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt; reality could pick up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 22:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can think-tanks survive a post-fact world?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/05/29/can-think-tanks-survive-a-post-fact-world]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_OPP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-29T14:30:00Z&quot;&gt;May 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A HUNDRED years ago this week, diplomats and academics from the British and American delegations at the Versailles peace conference at the end of the first world war met for a dinner at the Hotel Majestic in Paris, a short stroll from the Arc de Triomphe. Their aim was to work out how to continue their fruitful co-operation beyond the peace talks and promote internationalist values in their countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their initial idea for a single Anglo-American institute to fuse a weakened Britain and an ascendant America was not realised. But the dinner on May 30th 1919 gave rise to two institutions that have shaped public outlook and public policy on foreign affairs ever since: the Royal Institute for International Affairs (known as Chatham House, after the building in which it resides), set up in London in 1920, and the Council on Foreign Relations, founded the following year in New York. They have served as templates for numerous other think-tanks around the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet as the two organisations prepare to celebrate their centenaries, the festivities are tinged with anxiety. For how can institutions founded to pursue non-partisan, evidence-based research, carried out by experts, survive in an era when facts do not seem to matter quite so much?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After all, people have had “enough of experts”, in the words of Michael Gove, a senior Tory politician in Britain. President Donald Trump positively boasts of trusting his gut “more than anybody else’s brain”. Many of the West’s elected leaders have explicitly rejected the entire rationale for the sort of serious-mined wonkery that used to earn think-tanks influence, status and, most importantly, donors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With their main customers—politicians and legislators—more eager to probe their digestive tracts rather than scour policy pamphlets for ideas, one might wonder whether think-tanks have had their day. Could they too go the way of five-year plans, Britain’s National Coal Board and Betamax?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though the quest for fresh political ideas predate modern think-tanks—be it colonial America&amp;#x27;s pamphleteers or Britain&amp;#x27;s Fabian Society, founded in 1884—they served a vital function in the 20th century by presenting government officials with thoughtful analysis and policy options that were more immediate and relevant than from academia (but ideally held to the same standard and often by practitioners holding the same qualifications). This was the era of think-tanks, from private meetings at Chatham House to plan for reconstruction following the second world war, to Paul Baran at RAND conjuring up the idea for a data-network that became the internet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The think-tank industry expanded rapidly, responding to an almost insatiable demand for bright ideas and practical policy proposals. Most of these were devoted to domestic and economic policy rather than foreign affairs. American and British think-tanks were often in lockstep at the forefront of ideological churn, from Keynesianism to Thatcherism/Reaganism in the 1980s, through to Blairism, the “third way” and Bill Clinton’s “New Democrat” era in the 1990s and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think of the influence of the Institute of Economic Affairs on Mrs Thatcher, or the links between the Heritage Foundation, the American Enterprise Institute and the Reagan administrations. A political generation later, Demos and the Institute for Public Policy Research (IPPR) contributed to the creation of Tony Blair’s New Labour. The Progressive Policy Institute provided the intellectual blueprints for Bill Clinton’s centrist agenda. The Brookings Institution, the Carnegie Endowment, the Aspen Institute and others were never too far away. Think-tanks not only contributed ideas, but also people; presidential and prime ministerial staffs were stuffed with their bright young wonks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But as a class, the thinkocracy was caught out badly by the phenomena of Trump and Brexit. In neither case did it contribute much to these movements, nor did it see them coming. Robin Niblett, the director of Chatham House, has donned the hair-shirt. In an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://academic.oup.com/ia/article-abstract/94/6/1409/5162428?redirectedFrom=fulltext&quot;&gt;essay&lt;/a&gt; last November, he noted that “Western think-tanks evolved principally into supporters and managers of globalisation […] focusing excessively, or indeed exclusively, on the net gains […] and insufficiently, or indeed not at all, on the local dislocation and widening economic and social inequality.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Britain, the insurgency against the European Union, against immigration, against London and the south-east, against globalisation—all exposed by the Leave campaign’s victory in the Brexit referendum in 2016—largely by-passed London’s thinkocrats. In America, the policy jocks missed similar signs of anger on both the right and the left, whether the issue was the culture wars or the economy. The think-tanks thus failed in one of their primary functions: to analyse and clarify the main trends of the day, and consequently to advocate relevant policies. Accustomed to making the weather, think-tanks were victims of an intellectual storm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, much of the new thinking (or gut-gazing) of men like Steve Bannon and Nigel Farage evolved specifically in opposition to what they perceived to be an out-of-touch elite of pointyheads and political careerists—exemplified (for them) by bodies such as Chatham House and the Council on Foreign Relations. In as far as Mr Trump has any use for advisers dealing in evidence-based arguments, it is, as one of those advisers, Cliff Sims, recalls of his time in the White House, to “provide the underlying analytics that confirm his intuition”. The concept of “objective truth” has broken down, especially in America—and this is exactly what think-tanks have traditionally aspired to enunciate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Furthermore, this is symptomatic of a rising distrust of experts and professionals more generally. The loss of confidence in professions such as politics and journalism is well advertised. But in America, for instance, this has extended to all institutions associated with learning and knowledge. In 1974 the average confidence level for these institutions peaked at about 50%, yet by 2012 it had declined to just 31%. In Britain, according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://yougov.co.uk/topics/politics/articles-reports/2017/02/17/leave-voters-are-less-likely-trust-any-experts-eve&quot;&gt;YouGov&lt;/a&gt;, a polling organisation, in 2017 just 25% of respondents trusted economists—the backbone of many think-tanks—while 44% distrusted them. Only politicians were more distrusted. Think-tanks are equally on the receiving end of the new scepticism in Britain. In a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://weareflint.co.uk/forging-the-think-tank-narrative-uk&quot;&gt;poll&lt;/a&gt; last year only 17% of respondents trusted what think-tanks had to say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The stakes are rising. The anti-fact populists are muscling up for a fight. Mr Bannon and others have leased a 13th-century monastery outside Rome to serve, in his words, as a right-wing “gladiator school for cultural warriors”. Mr Bannon wants it to be a counterweight to the Open Society Foundation backed by George Soros, a liberal-minded investor and philanthropist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How can think-tanks survive in this setting? They could wait it out, of course. All the polling suggests that deepening political partisanship in both American and Britain accounts for some of this distrust in expertise. That is, Republicans are far more likely to be sceptical of evidence-based research and scientific methods than Democrats, just as Brexiteers are more sceptical of authority than Remainers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As one academic &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://osf.io/preprints/socarxiv/tkpn5/&quot;&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; of contemporary American politics concludes: “For the lying demagogue to have authentic appeal, it is sufficient that one side of a social divide regards the political system as flawed or illegitimate”. The centre may yet regroup, provoking a renewed faith in objective facts. But that is to bet on the Trump era not being part of a long-term secular trend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More to the point, think-tanks should help themselves. The first place to start is with trust. To an extent, people are right to be sceptical of the institutions’ claims to objectivity. Many of them have a long way to go in terms of openness and transparency. And far from being engrossed in the noble pursuit of truth and reason, some of the beltway think-tanks have begun to look more like brainy guns for hire, prepared to shoot off whatever argument a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.nytimes.com/2014/09/07/us/politics/foreign-powers-buy-influence-at-think-tanks.html&quot;&gt;country&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.nytimes.com/2016/08/08/us/politics/think-tanks-research-and-corporate-lobbying.html&quot;&gt;corporation&lt;/a&gt; gives them—a situation exposed by the New York Times. Brookings and the Center for Strategic and International Studies have come under particular scrutiny. The think-tanks need to be vigilant that they’re not simply selling their brands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next, think-tanks must get outside the bubbles of London, Washington, DC or New York and have a broader reach, both in terms of input and output. IPPR, for one, set up a well-respected branch in the north of England with offices in Manchester and Newcastle. Meanwhile, Chatham House has been expanding its London headquarters. As for CFR, it holds an annual “national” meeting in New York: its membership might learn more about the forces shaping American politics if the location were changed to Youngstown, Ohio—emblematic of a small city’s factory closures, crime and disgruntlement. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last, think-tanks must not abandon their strengths, of reason and empirical analysis, but they need to draw from wider sources of knowledge and experience and then communicate their research to a wider audience. They means doing more to involve ethnic minorities, young people, people of different political persuasions and, most of all, fully-blown mavericks. Some of the thinkers who Mrs Thatcher deployed so successfully in her think-tanks were barely house-trained, but they certainly had plenty of attitude and iconoclasm, precisely what is needed to think the unthinkable. Sir Alfred Sherman, for one, had fought for the communists in the Spanish civil war; a journalist, he enjoyed nothing better than riling the bien pensants. Think-tanks can survive in a post-fact universe not by marshalling more facts but by showing more verve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three years after the meeting that gave birth to Chatham House and the CFR, the Hotel Majestic was the setting for another get-together: the so-called “dinner party of the century”. Five of the most acclaimed artists of the 20th century dined and debated there: the novelists James Joyce and Marcel Proust, the young painter Pablo Picasso, the composer Igor Stravinsky and the choreographer Sergei Diaghilev. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each represented a new and vibrant strand of the Modernism in the air. Today their achievements are considered classics, but relegated to libraries and museums, respected more for their historical importance than their contemporary relevance. Think-tanks, an idea born of that era, must reform themselves to avoid a similar fate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 22:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Gentleman Jack” and the problem of the unlikeable female protagonist]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/29/gentleman-jack-and-the-problem-of-the-unlikeable-female-protagonist]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_BKP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-29T11:31:59Z&quot;&gt;May 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ANNE LISTER turns up in Halifax in 1832 with all the swaggering elan of a cowboy riding into town. Dressed in black—including a great-coat and a top hat—she bosses around her father and sister, faces off with the neighbours, reminisces about her female lovers, extracts rent from tenants, commandeers a stagecoach and shoots a horse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is clear from the first episode of “Gentleman Jack” that Lister (Suranne Jones) is a singular individual. The series—a joint venture by HBO and the BBC—tells an unlikely true story. Lister defied the customs of her time as a landowner (she inherited Shibden Hall, in West Yorkshire, from her uncle in 1836, but ran the estate long before that), mountaineer and traveller. Something of a polymath, she studied surgery in Paris under George Cuvier and helped build coal pits. Lister is also considered by some to be the “first modern lesbian”, taking a local heiress named Ann Walker as her common-law wife. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a further gift to dramatists, Lister was also an obsessive diarist, recording the minutiae of her life in more than 4m words. Large sections, mostly concerning her love affairs with women, were written in a “crypt” of her own devising, which combined mathematical symbols, punctuation and the Greek alphabet. The code was not fully cracked until more than a century after her death, and the diaries have been a source of fascination ever since. Sally Wainwright, who wrote and directed “Gentleman Jack”, worked with Anne Choma, a historian, to transcribe new passages to better inform the show’s plot. The series spans the 18-month period in which Lister seduces Walker, whose fortune she believes will help prop up her ailing estate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Gentleman Jack” is brighter and more engaging than most period dramas. Filmed in and around the real Shibden Hall, the show gives a true sense of time and place, from the glamour of country estates to the grim reality of local mines. Ms Jones brings a steely determination to her character that is compelling to watch. Sophie Rundle offers a suitable contrast as Walker, at turns spoilt, frustratingly fragile and desperate for affection. The actresses’ shared scenes are dynamic, showing how the balance of power between two people can shift from moment to moment, and how inequality, be it in desire, wealth, status or self-confidence, allows for manipulation. Their interactions are intelligent and frequently funny.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scenes depicting physical intimacy between the two women—too often an opportunity for gratuitous nudity or pornified raunchiness—are handled deftly here. In a first for a BBC production, Ms Wainwright hired an “intimacy coordinator” to choreograph them, and it shows. The sex scenes seem realistic, providing depth and feeling to the storyline rather than mere shock value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet “Gentleman Jack” strives too hard to make its central character likeable. Lister’s diaries reveal her to be a complicated, often unpleasant, woman, yet in the show these traits are toned down. Many of her worst qualities are mitigated: her snobbery and cruelty towards the working class is reduced to a brief argument about the 1832 Reform Act that expanded male suffrage; her disdainful manipulation of Walker for financial gain is sanitised with romantic feelings it is unclear the real Lister ever felt; her selfishness is portrayed as an admirable attempt to live entirely on her own terms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Gentleman Jack” also skirts around the nuances of gender and sexuality in the period, one caught between the leniency of the Georgian period and the relative prudishness of the Victorians. Unlike male homosexuality, lesbianism was not criminalised but rather ignored. Intense “romantic friendships” among women were relatively common, and there are several examples of longstanding, public lesbian partnerships before Lister’s and Walker’s. Indeed, Lister was perceived as unusual mostly because she conducted business like a man (“Gentleman Jack” was considered an insulting nickname). Opposition to her union with Walker was chiefly driven by fears of money-grabbing rather than sexual bigotry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The series, with eight hour-long episodes, would have had ample room to examine such details—particularly if it had lost the somewhat tiresome subplots involving peripheral characters, unlikely murders and coach accidents. “Gentleman Jack” is advertised as a show about the first “modern lesbian”, yet it does not trust its audience to be modern enough to grasp historical nuances or accept a challenging female lead. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 20:40:27 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“There are no signs he is learning from the failures”—Nigeria’s President Buhari gets another term]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/29/there-are-no-signs-he-is-learning-from-the-failures-nigerias-president-buhari-gets-another-term]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/buhari.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-29T10:30:48Z&quot;&gt;May 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/02/28/nigerias-president-muhammadu-buhari-wins-a-second-term&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;MUHAMMADU BUHARI&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; earned the nickname “Baba Go Slow” for a lackadaisical approach to reform as Nigeria’s president. He mismanaged the economy, failed to tackle corruption and has been unable to restrain the terrorist group Boko Haram. Will he be more effective in his &lt;strong&gt;second term&lt;/strong&gt;? Also, &lt;strong&gt;why so many climbers are perishing on the slopes of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/11/how-mount-everest-went-mainstream&quot;&gt;Mount Everest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/11/how-mount-everest-went-mainstream&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. And for the first time in football history, clubs from just one nation compete in Europe’s top tournaments. We examine how England’s &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/05/12/how-manchester-city-came-to-rule-english-football&quot;&gt;Premier League&lt;/a&gt; teams outperformed expectations.&lt;/strong&gt; Runtime: 18 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/babagoslow-nigeria-spresidentgetsanotherterm&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 20:40:26 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Religious zeal is surging in Russia’s military forces]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/05/29/religious-zeal-is-surging-in-russias-military-forces]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_BLP503_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-29T10:26:09Z&quot;&gt;May 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;ON MAY 3RD an unusual ceremony took place at Westminster Abbey, one of the Church of England’s grandest temples. To mark 50 years of Britain’s sea-based nuclear arsenal, the Dean of Westminster offered thanks to all those who had served with the country’s nuclear-deterrent forces. The Duke of Cambridge and other pillars of the establishment were among a packed congregation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;However, they were roundly booed by protesters who had gathered outside. The Campaign for Nuclear Disarmament denounced the church service as “morally repugnant” and staged a “die-in”. About 200 priests and two bishops had also said that it was wrong to offer thanks for such lethal weapons. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;Across America’s armed forces the dissemination of the Christian faith, and its association with military prowess, is also controversial, and is widely challenged on constitutional grounds (see previous &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/05/25/onward-christian-soldiers&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;). Yet there is one historically Christian land where, albeit after a 70-year communist interlude, the national church enjoys huge, growing and largely uncontested influence over the armed forces. That country is Russia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;Having built up close relationships with all parts of the defence establishment, especially the triad of forces which stand ready to deliver land-, sea- and air-launched nukes, the Russian Orthodox church is now reinforcing its role at the apex of the country’s military machine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;In a weird historical turnaround, uniformed clerics may increasingly be reproducing the function exercised in the Soviet era by a caste of officers known as zampoliti. Their job was to maintain morale, check for any signs of dissident thinking and keep fanning the flames of Marxist zeal.    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;Bits of the story on the church’s military role can be pieced together from news bulletins. For example, it was announced in February that priests embedded with the airborne troops would learn to drive armoured cars. But the entire tale has now been presented in methodical detail by an Israeli scholar, Dmitry Dima Adamsky. In his new book, “Russian Nuclear Orthodoxy”, he shows how church-military relations have evolved in the three decades since atheistic communism fell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;Mr Adamsky portrays what he calls a decade of “genesis” when various ad-hoc forms of synergy emerged; a decade of “conversion” when the different parts of the armed forces, including the navy and air force, regained strength with much moral support from the church; and a decade of “operationalisation” when church-military relations became more entrenched.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;These relations have taken many spectacular forms. They include the building of prayer spaces large and small in defence installations of all kinds, not least on nuclear submarines; the blessing of missiles in their silos, and of fighter-aircraft as they are about to go on combat missions; and aerial manoeuvres corresponding to a “procession with the cross”, an Orthodox ritual in which the faithful sanctify a piece of territory by marching round it with crosses and banners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;When service personnel receive pep talks on the sweep of Russian history, there is much emphasis on the deep links between religion and the army, starting with the military saints of medieval times and the icons they carried into battle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;As Mr Adamsky shows, some of the church’s earliest, and most improbable, relationships were developed with scientists, both military and civilian, who were involved in different stages of the nuclear cycle, from handling nuclear fuel to designing new weapons. In the early 1990s Russians in this sector were deeply demoralised, badly paid, and uncertain whether the country’s arsenal had any future at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;In many ways, the church came to the rescue. Take the town of Sarov. To any devout Russian, it is the home of Saint Seraphim, an ascetic monk who was one of the most revered holy men of the tsarist era. In communist times, the place was turned into a super-secret nuclear research centre known as Arzamas-16. After the Soviet Union collapsed, it regained its old religiously resonant name but kept its nuclear prowess. It became a popular venue for conferences co-organised by the church and the nuclear personnel, at which the need to preserve Russia’s nuclear capacity, even in the hardest times, was proclaimed in a feel-good way by everybody present. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;Patriarch Kirill, the head of the Russian Orthodox church since 2009, has said the church can take credit for maintaining the country’s nuclear capacity in an era when finances and confidence were rock-bottom.  As a matter of historical fact, Orthodox churches, including the Russian one, have generally sought accommodation with earthly powers; but the clerical-nuclear partnership was still an unusual one, perhaps reflecting the fact that both parties were struggling hard to adapt to a new era and felt they needed friends.      &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;According to Mr Adamsky, a professor at IDC Herzliya university, the latest big development is a seemingly arcane but important addition to the structure of Russia’s defence establishment. As of last August, a new body was established. Dubbed the “Main Political Directorate of the General Staff”, it is headed by a general with the rank of deputy defence minister. To anyone with an ear for Soviet terminology, this sounded like the institution which fostered communist zeal across the Red Army. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;The new unit will also have an ideological role. It has been told to “develop structures at all levels for armed forces, right down to the [individual] military unit.” And one of the main purposes of these structures will be to inculcate the Orthodox tradition. To that end, it will train military priests and raise funds for a vast church of the armed forces, to be erected by next year in a place outside Moscow called Patriot Park. It will have space for 6,000 people, and the colour-scheme will reflect the hues of missiles and armoured cars. Decorations will include battle scenes from the Bible. Elsewhere in the park there will be monuments dedicated to the patron saints of each branch of the forces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;The directorate’s first head, General Andrei Kartapolov, was reported to believe that “the modern Russian serviceman cannot be formed without cultivating a lofty [sense of] spirituality inside him...” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;In short, the present order makes it very hard to belong to a minority faith, such as the Jehovah’s Witnesses, who reject military service, and have suffered a wave of persecution this year.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;As with almost every centuries-old religion tradition, Russian Orthodoxy’s spiritual tool-box includes more than one way of approaching peace and war. It venerates the peace-minded medieval brothers Boris and Gleb, martyred princes who accepted death meekly; and Saint Philip, martyred in 1569 because he challenged Ivan the Terrible’s killing sprees. Right now, the church leaders and the Kremlin are ensuring that it is the martial spirit that prevails. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 20:40:25 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Facebook’s planned new currency may be based on a blockchain]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/29/facebooks-planned-new-currency-may-be-based-on-a-blockchain]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_fnp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE EXCITEMENT among crypto-buffs is palpable. Facebook, the world’s largest social network, appears to be planning to launch a digital coin early next year. But they should not get their hopes up too high. If the firm does indeed launch what is being dubbed FB Coin, GlobalCoin or Libra, it will be a tame sort of cryptocurrency—more Bitcoin 0.5 than 2.0.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook has declined to comment, but is clearly up to something. Last year it put a highly regarded senior executive, David Marcus, in charge of a new team exploring “ways to leverage the power of blockchain technology”, which underlies cryptocurrencies. In April Mark Zuckerberg, Facebook’s boss, said at its annual shindig for developers that it “should be as easy to send money to someone as it is to send a photo”. It seems to be talking to potential partners, such as credit-card issuers and merchants, and financial regulators, such as Mark Carney, the governor of the Bank of England.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In America Facebook’s Messenger app already allows peer-to-peer transfers, but only in existing currencies and between accounts linked to bank-issued debit cards. But the new blockchain-based money would be a currency on its own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reasons abound why Facebook might want to take this step. It has to pull even with other big global apps that already offer easy payment features, such as WeChat in China. A digital coin would work in developing countries, where many people are unbanked and remittances from abroad are large (India is rumoured to be among the first countries where it will be available). If it is used for commerce, not just peer-to-peer payments, Facebook could take part of the fee that now goes to card-issuers, and charge more for ads, since buying the products touted would be quicker and simpler. It could move into services such as tipping, for which other payment systems are too pricey (at the Facebook do Mr Zuckerberg demonstrated how users could send content-creators some digital change). Data on payments would help make up for what the firm will lose in its planned “pivot to privacy”, which includes steps such as allowing users to communicate on encrypted channels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But despite the crypto-buzz, the new currency is unlikely to be a close relative of Bitcoin, says Lex Sokolin, a fintech analyst—that is, a decentralised system with no one in charge. Facebook will want to be in control to gather data, simplify administration and avoid the currency being targeted by speculators such as hedge funds. It will be a “stablecoin”, backed by established currencies such as the dollar to avoid the volatility that has bedeviled Bitcoin (which is heading back towards $9,000 after falling to little more than $3,000 last year). Regulators, fearing money-laundering or other criminal activity—as happens with Bitcoin—will surely set strict rules, perhaps capping transfers and stopping the new currency from crossing borders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook is well-placed to make a go of the venture, according to Ben Thompson of Stratechery, a widely read newsletter on the tech industry. Its services now boast a total of 2.4bn monthly users. It could entice merchants with discounts if they use the new coin to buy ads, and users by paying them in it for viewing those ads—or perhaps, which would be a giant step for Facebook, even for providing data about themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet it will not have the field to itself. Similar coins already exist. Signal and Telegram, two messaging apps, are also planning digital cash. Moreover payment cards are ubiquitous in the rich world, and easy to use online. And then there is the question of whether, for all its reach, a FaceCoin would really be welcome. Should a firm that has shown a cavalier attitude towards users’ data be trusted to deal with their money?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 20:40:24 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Greater access to abortion may have reduced America’s crime rate]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/27/greater-access-to-abortion-may-have-reduced-americas-crime-rate]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_woc138.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-27T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 27th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ANTI-ABORTION POLICIES are on the rise in America. Influenced mainly by objections from religious conservatives, legislators in states such as Georgia, Ohio and Alabama have passed new laws limiting the practice. In some instances, the new regulations go so far as to ban abortions even in cases of rape or incest—a measure supported by just 11% of voters, according to Morning Consult, a pollster. Restricting access to abortions means that more parents who don’t want to raise children would be forced to do so. Recent research suggests this could reverse decades of progress made on curbing crime in America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a paper published in 2001, the economists John Donahue and Steven Levitt credited the legalisation of abortion across America with much of the subsequent reduction in crime in the country. They argued that violent crime in states where abortion had been banned before 1973 was 15-25% rarer in 1997 than it would have been had abortion remained illegal. The study was politically explosive, and widely criticised. Many sceptical scholars sought to poke holes in its methods, including one group who discovered an “inadvertent but serious computer programming error” (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2005/12/01/oops-onomics&quot;&gt;see article&lt;/a&gt;) underlying its findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly two decades later, Messrs Donahue and Levitt have returned to the subject, and present new evidence that bolsters their original claim. In a new working paper circulated by the National Bureau of Economic Research, they attribute a whopping 45 percentage points of the total 50% decline in crime since 1990 to legal abortion. Their primary evidence is that crime fell much faster in states where more abortions were performed than it did in those where the procedure was rarer. In the early 1990s violent crime was about 50% more common in states with relatively high abortion levels than it was in those where abortion was infrequent. By 2014, crime rates in the two groups of states had converged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors argue that this statistical association reflects an underlying causal relationship. Armed with a cache of annual state-level data on abortions, crime rates and other factors—including economic conditions, welfare payments, access to firearms and alcohol consumption—they seek to isolate the impact of abortion on violent crime, after controlling for other variables that also affect crime rates. With all other factors held constant, they find that an increase in the abortion rate of 100 per 100,000 births leads to a 10-20% reduction in crime. Past studies have also shown that children born to women who wanted an abortion but did not receive one were much more likely to become criminals and had poorer life prospects than those who were born to parents ready and willing to raise them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 05:41:09 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The great jobs boom]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/28/the-great-jobs-boom]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/jobsboom.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-28T19:00:21Z&quot;&gt;May 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The received wisdom is that work is becoming low-paid and precarious, with jobs lost to automation and the gig economy. The data say otherwise. What does the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/23/the-rich-world-is-enjoying-an-unprecedented-jobs-boom&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;jobs boom in the rich world&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; mean for the global economy? Also, will &lt;strong&gt;Alibaba’s plans to list in Hong Kong&lt;/strong&gt; start a corporate shift away from Wall Street? And, &lt;strong&gt;the role of clearing houses&lt;/strong&gt; in averting financial crises. Philip Coggan hosts. Runtime: 20 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-justthejob&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 02:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why seaplanes are so dangerous]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/gulliver/2019/05/28/why-seaplanes-are-so-dangerous]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_BLP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-28T15:51:59Z&quot;&gt;May 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;ON MAY 13TH the pilot of a seaplane flying over Alaska steered to give a better view of a waterfall, just as he had done on many flights before. This time, he saw a flash on his left—and crashed into another plane. Both aircraft plunged into the sea, killing six people. The following week another seaplane crashed in Alaska with two more fatalities. America’s National Transportation Safety Board (NTSB), the government agency that is investigating the accidents, has warned that seaplanes, which are able to take off and land on water, may no longer be a safe form of transport. It has asked the Federal Aviation Administration, a regulator, to upgrade its rules about seaplanes, which currently fall far short of safety regulations for other commercial aircraft.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Seaplanes used to be the main form of air transport before the second world war, during which America and Europe were carpeted with concrete runways suitable for large passenger jets for military reasons. But it is not just weaker regulation that makes these sorts of planes dangerous today. The lack of a runway on solid ground is also a problem—one of the reasons they fell out of favour seven decades ago. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;The most exhaustive study of seaplane accidents on water, published by the Canadian government in 1994, found that over two-thirds of fatalities were caused by drowning, rather than the crash impact itself. As the report noted, “had these accidents occurred on land, a large percentage of them might have been non-fatal.” This is because it is difficult to safety evacuate a seaplane on water. The report found that only 8% percent of occupants of these planes were able to escape easily, compared to 26% that escaped with difficulty. Nearly half did not escape at all. Comparisons with accidents involving land-based aircraft are particularly stark. The same report found that for this type of plane, only 0.2% of nose-over or nose-down accidents on take-off or landing were fatal, compared to 10% for seaplanes.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;There are several reasons for this. Seaplanes often flip upside during a crash landing, something which is relatively rare on land. Passengers who are scared of jumping in the water can block escape routes. For those that do escape, help takes longer to organise and arrive than on land. And icy water, which can cause hypothermia, can kill otherwise unharmed passengers. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Pressure to fly these aircraft in less than ideal weather is also a problem. Float planes, as they are also called, are often chartered by cruise lines, particularly in Alaska, as a quick way to give passengers a tour of the landscape. But cruise lines want to ensure these flights start and end on time so their passengers do not delay the ship setting sail. As a result, the NTSB has found that some seaplane pilots feel pressured by tight cruise-ship schedules to carry out excursions even when conditions are dangerous. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;But a regulatory crackdown on seaplanes looks likely to run into political resistance in America. Alaska is particularly reliant on seaplanes. Most of the American state is inaccessible by road and the tourism industry there is heavily reliant on seaplanes to get visitors around. Alaskans are also six times more likely than the average American to own a plane. Seaplanes are likely to be around for some time yet. &lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 02:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Airlines would like to see Boeing’s 737 MAX back in the air]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/28/airlines-would-like-to-see-boeings-737-max-back-in-the-air]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_woc124.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-28T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A YEAR AGO at Farnborough Air Show, Dennis Muilenburg, boss of Boeing, beamed as orders for its new 737 MAX jetliner rolled in. At next month’s Paris Air Show he will be less upbeat. In March regulators around the world grounded the plane, after two of them crashed within five months, killing 346 people. On May 23rd aviation regulators were due to convene in Dallas to review Boeing’s application to unground the MAX, now that it says it has fixed the software thought to have contributed to the accidents. Mr Muilenburg says he is “confident” that the updated plane will be “one of the safest aeroplanes ever to fly”. On May 22nd America’s Federal Aviation Administration suggested it could be a while before it is back in the air. All told, airlines have ordered around 5,000 maxes. This week Ryanair, which awaits 135 of them, said it will have to cut 1m seats from this year’s schedules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2019 02:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>