<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[America defends freedom of conscience abroad]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/04/30/america-defends-freedom-of-conscience-abroad]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_BLP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-30T09:31:47Z&quot;&gt;Apr 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR SOME Americans, such as Vice-President Mike Pence, promoting religious liberty at home and opposing religious persecution round the world are parts of a single, inter-connected struggle. About a month ago, Mr Pence told cheering fellow conservatives that “freedom of religion is under attack in our country” and cited the criticism endured by his wife Karen for teaching at a Christian school where openly gay people are unwelcome. In other contexts, he has insisted that opposing religious oppression everywhere must be central to American diplomacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Others would say that the contentious issues bunched under “religious freedom” in domestic American debates (the role of contraception in employer-funded health plans, religiously inspired teaching in schools, and so on) are of a different order to the dreadful persecution that takes place in many parts of the world. On the first cluster of issues, reasonable folk might disagree; over the second, no decent person could fail to be horrified, and opposing such horrors (from blasphemy trials to re-education camps) must surely be a common American concern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In practice, though, even the global defence of freedom of conscience has become increasingly politicised. That shows up in the make-up of the United States Commission on International Religious Freedom (USCIRF), a bipartisan agency constituted by Congress and the White House that is tasked to provide advice on persecution and how best to oppose it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Commissioners have tended to be distinguished academics or religious figures whose personal authority somewhat transcended politics. But things are more contentious now. The panel includes the former and current presidents of the Family Research Council, a conservative lobby group which declares that homosexuality is “harmful to those who engage in it” and denounces same-sex nuptials as a “radical redefinition and falsification of marriage”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to those Republican stalwarts (respectively Gary Bauer and Tony Perkins), there are Democratic nominees. The USCIRF’s rotating chairmanship is now held by Tenzin Dorjee, a scholar of Tibet and Tibetan Buddhism who was appointed to the panel by Nancy Pelosi, the Democratic Speaker of the House. Another Democratic choice is Gayle Manchin, an educator and former First Lady of West Virginia, who is vice-chair of the panel. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diverse as they are, these people hold some things in common, and these include a healthy disrespect for the persecution of believers in communist and former communist lands. The USCIRF’s annual report, published this week, was harsher than ever in its denunciation of China, for its persecution of Muslims, Buddhists, Christians and other believers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the north-west of China, the report noted, Muslims were under constant surveillance, and subject for example to intrusive blood sampling, the confiscation of phones and a ban on sending children to the mosque. “Even worse, the Chinese government has ripped entire families apart, detaining between 800,000 and 2m adults in concentration camps and relegated some of their children to orphanages.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Mr Bauer put it, in any rating of severe religious oppressors, “China would be in a category all by itself...they are an equal opportunity persecutor. They go after anybody, any sect that might compete with the communist, atheistic government of China.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The USCIRF commended the State Department for keeping China, along with nine other countries, on its list of “countries of particular concern” or egregious persecutors and it urged that six other countries, including Russia, be added to the list. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russia has come under fire recently for its harsh persecution of Jehovah’s Witnesses, scores of whom have been arrested, charged with “extremism” and in some cases tortured. Some pietistic forms of Islam, not known to advocate or practise violence, have also been proscribed in Russia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The USCIRF urged the administration to consider the possibility of sanctions against Saudi Arabia after 37 people, mostly from the Shia Muslim minority, were executed. Saudi Arabia features on every list of egregious persecutors but successive American administrations granted waivers that preclude punitive measures against the kingdom. On April 26th Mr Dorjee said the State Department must stop “giving a free pass” to the Saudis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However a Republican nominee to the commission, Johnnie Moore, insisted on April 29th that all was not ill in Saudi Arabia. “It’s a kingdom where there are lots of different things happening, some things that are the worst in the world, and [by] the same token there is a glimmer of light,” said Mr Moore, a member of group of evangelicals who support President Donald Trump. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a gesture that some might see as mildly pro-Saudi, the Commission’s report proposed that the Houthis (enemies of the Saudi-led coalition fighting a cruel war in Yemen) be added to a list of “entities of particular concern”, in other words, non-state actors which practise religious persecution. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a world where authoritarian regimes (and other cruel zealots such as lynch mobs and terrorists) seem ever more confident, many might wonder how much difference to anything can be made by manoeuvres on the inside track of American politics and diplomacy. For example, whatever anyone proposes, it seems very unlikely that America will ever impose sanctions against its Saudi allies because of religious persecution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the fact that America has elaborate machinery for the monitoring and advocacy of religious freedom, both by the USCIRF and the State Department, does serve a purpose. Whatever their ideological antecedents, and however little sympathy they might have for Islam, the staunch Republican conservatives who sit on the USCIRF are obliged ex officio to stand up for oppressed Muslims in China and, say, Myanmar; that is more than many Muslim governments do. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As regards Russia, many American conservatives and evangelicals might be somewhat tempted by hints coming from high places in Moscow, including the state-guided media, that there should be a common Russian-American front, grouping traditionalists in both countries, against sexual and reproductive freedom, and in support of oppressed Christians in the Middle East. But through the USCIRF and its research, American non-conformists are brought face to face with the fact that Russia’s present rulers are no friends of dissident Christian sects or idiosyncratic religious groups. That sets sensible limits to any love affair between American and Russian religious conservatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:06:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Advice from a dismal scientist to new parents]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/04/30/advice-from-a-dismal-scientist-to-new-parents]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_FND000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-30T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR NEW parents, it is a terrifying moment. The hospital doors close behind them, leaving them with a new and helpless human being. The baby’s survival into adulthood seems impossible. What if it will not eat? What if it is allergic to water? What if an owl carries it off? Probably, few parents wish at that moment for the help of an economist. But “Cribsheet”, a new book by Emily Oster of Brown University, shows that in the hectic haze of parenthood an economist’s perspective can prove surprisingly clarifying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Oster’s academic work relates to health and health policy. A recent paper, for example, studied how food-purchasing decisions change in response to being diagnosed with diabetes. Five years ago she published a book on pregnancy, drawing on her training as an economist and her own experience (her husband, Jesse Shapiro, with whom she has two children, is also an economist at Brown). “Cribsheet” tackles the next step in the journey from childfree person to parent. Deciding whether to have a child in the first place fairly obviously involves economic calculations, from the impact on the parents’ earning potential to the resources that must be set aside to pay for nappies, child care and university. The decisions that come in a torrent after the birth, in contrast, such as whether to breastfeed or how to manage sleeping arrangements, might not seem so amenable to such thinking. But Ms Oster’s new book shows that they are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parents generally try to maximise the welfare, present and future, of their children (and, secondarily, themselves) subject to constraints of money and time. That requires choices. Economics can help a parent judge these trade-offs. Good choices begin with good information. Before deciding whether breastfeeding is worth the time, trouble and physical toll, it helps to know the benefits compared with feeding with formula. Parents do as most people do when making a hard call: turn to experts, friends, family and the internet. But different sources provide wildly different answers—and often with an extraordinary intensity of belief. As Ms Oster notes, internet mums frequently write as though ignoring their advice is tantamount to abandoning a child to wolves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The help she provides begins with sorting through published research and determining what is worth heeding. This involves more than identifying outright disinformation, of the sort published by anti-vaccination groups. The conclusions of serious research also need to be treated with care. Unless studies are well-designed, the results can be influenced by confounding factors. The purported benefits of breastfeeding, such as conferring a higher IQ on the child, can reflect the fact that women who are richer and better educated, and have higher IQs, are more likely to breastfeed. More reliable research attempts to take account of these factors. Whenever possible—and breastfeeding is a case where participants would almost certainly refuse to co-operate—researchers arrange randomised controlled trials, randomly dividing participants into “control” and “treatment” groups, only one of which engages in the behaviour under study, the better to isolate its effects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even when a study is well designed, it can require statistical sophistication to understand the size of any effect and the significance of the result. Non-economists may find “Cribsheet” interesting as a guide to understanding research findings, though harried parents may focus more on its concrete guidance. There is plenty of this. Breastfeeding, it turns out, provides short-term health benefits to babies (notably by making diarrhoea less common) and reduces the mother’s risk of developing breast cancer. But there is no hard evidence that breastfed babies enjoy long-term health or cognitive benefits compared with bottlefed ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, given the potential benefits, why not do it? Economic analyses include not only what is gained by a choice, but what is foregone. For example, putting an infant to sleep beside a parent in bed rather than alone in a cot is associated with a higher risk of sudden infant death. If there are no exacerbating factors (such as a mother who smokes or drinks), that increased risk is tiny: 22 deaths in 100,000, rather than eight. But why risk it? The answer may be that it is worth it. Sleeping side by side can make breastfeeding easier. More importantly, for some parents it is the only way to settle the baby (and hence to get some sleep themselves).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prolonged sleep deprivation is horrible and makes it harder to be a good parent—or to function. Some mummy bloggers may find it unconscionable that a mother would expose her child to extra risks in order to treat herself to a few hours of sleep. Ms Oster suggests that, if well-informed parents make that choice, then it is reasonable: a welfare-enhancing balancing of benefits and costs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A mother’s place is in the wrong&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Economic reasoning can feel bloodless. But the calculations in Ms Oster’s book seem more human than “Mummy War” moralising, in their recognition that parental time and energy are finite. She reckons it is helpful to think about work-life balance in bluntly economic terms: “What is the optimal configuration of adult work hours for your household?” In the past, male economists like Gary Becker used such logic to argue that women should “specialise” in home-making. But Ms Oster points out that the benefits to a household of more income (often a necessity) should not be ignored—and neither should a mother’s preferences. Although research suggests that policies allowing a parent to stay home in an infant’s first months do benefit children, staying home for two years rather than one does not meaningfully alter a child’s prospects. Women who need or want to return to work should not be kept from doing so by guilt or others’ expectations, she writes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parenting can be fraught. “Cribsheet” aims to help parents do better. And in capturing how they struggle when beset by dubious information and emotional pressure from peers, it also holds lessons for economists. Welfare-maximising decisions are hard to make, and sometimes people need a little help. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 00:06:55 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bret Easton Ellis is wrong about millennial reading habits]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/04/30/bret-easton-ellis-is-wrong-about-millennial-reading-habits]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_BKP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-30T15:41:35Z&quot;&gt;Apr 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“WHAT IS millennial culture?” Bret Easton Ellis asked in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.thetimes.co.uk/article/the-interview-american-psycho-author-bret-easton-ellis-on-why-he-hates-millennials-0zngpx6pq&quot;&gt;a recent interview with the &lt;em&gt;Sunday Times&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt; of London. “There’s no writing. They don’t care about literature. None of them read books.” He went on: “Where is the great millennial novel? There isn’t one.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Ellis, the so-called “bad boy of American literature”, was at his zenith in the 1980s and ‘90s when he published novels such as “Less Than Zero” and “American Psycho”. “White”, a work of nonfiction, is his first book in nearly a decade. It is advertised as an “admonishment of received truths”; mostly it is a screed on what he calls “Generation Wuss”. His main source on the subject appears to be his younger boyfriend, Todd, and Todd’s friends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The millennial Mr Ellis conjures is already familiar from newspaper thinkpieces. She eats $8 avocado toast and drinks $5 lattes, while her parents pay her rent and her therapy bills. She scrolls listlessly through social media, occasionally allowing herself to be outraged by opinions she does not agree with. She measures her worth in likes, and has not picked up a book since college. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facts rather complicate this picture, not least when it comes to who millennials actually are. The youngest, born in the early 2000s, are just entering college and cannot legally drink beer in America. Others are pushing 40, and likely have families of their own and no interest in social media whatsoever. While the term is handy for curmudgeons, “millennial” encompasses a wide range of ages and experiences, as the &lt;em&gt;Wall Street Journal&lt;/em&gt; style guide &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://blogs.wsj.com/styleandsubstance/2017/12/04/vol-30-no-11-millennials/&quot;&gt;pointed out&lt;/a&gt; when cautioning against the overuse of the term in the paper’s pages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_WOC111.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190504_WOC111.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190504_WOC111.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190504_WOC111.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190504_WOC111.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190504_WOC111.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190504_WOC111.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190504_WOC111.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190504_WOC111.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190504_WOC111.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another inconvenient truth is that millennials are reading, and more than other generations. Pew Research Centre, a think-tank, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.pewresearch.org/fact-tank/2018/03/08/nearly-one-in-five-americans-now-listen-to-audiobooks/&quot;&gt;conducted a study&lt;/a&gt; in 2018 that found that 84% of 18- to 29-year-olds in America had read or listened to a book in some format in the past year (see chart). Of 30- to 49-year-olds, 74% had done so; for  50- to 64-year-olds the figure was 71%. Adults aged 65 and older were the least interested in the written word. Such details are inconvenient for the standard caricature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The myth of millennials’ neglect of culture persists not because it is true or useful, but because it serves the interests of someone like Mr Ellis, who has built his career on provocation. In the past he has acknowledged that he has young readers: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.amazon.com/gp/feature.html?docId=571852&quot;&gt;in an interview from 2005&lt;/a&gt;, Mr Ellis said that he gets fan mail about “Less Than Zero” (1985) “from people who weren’t really born yet when the book came out”. Yet perhaps the most telling moment in the &lt;em&gt;Sunday Times&lt;/em&gt; piece is when Decca Aitkenhead, the interviewer, asks him if he’s read Sally Rooney, the author of the novels “Conversations with Friends” and “Normal People”, which was nominated for the Man Booker prize. Ms Rooney, who was born in 1991, is often hailed—and assailed—as “first great millennial novelist”. Mr Ellis says: “Er, remind me who Sally Rooney is?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While deriding millennials for not reading, Mr Ellis reveals that he hasn’t read much of their writing, either. Ms Aitkenhead points out that he also hasn’t bothered with “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2018/09/27/the-real-victims-of-campus-activism-are-the-students&quot;&gt;The Coddling of the American Mind&lt;/a&gt;”, Greg Lukianoff’s and Jonathan Haidt’s popular treatise, and “to have written a book about the mindset of millennials without bothering to consult this...seems a remarkable omission”. Ross Douthat, a columnist for the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt;, recently made a similar comment about the absence of generational novel. What they both actually seem to be saying is that they haven’t read a great millennial novel, and because they are tastemakers, it follows that there isn’t one. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If there is no “Great Novel” for this generation it may well be because the generational novel was always a myth. There is something to be gained by eschewing the idea of the “Great Millennial Novel” altogether: it encourages reading variously and widely, rather than seeking a particular voice to fit a stereotype. That, incidentally, is what millennials are already doing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:06:42 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Indonesia wants to move the capital from sinking Jakarta]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/30/indonesia-wants-to-move-the-capital-from-sinking-jakarta]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_ASP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-30T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAKARTA IS bursting at the seams. Around 10m people squeeze into Indonesia&amp;#x27;s chaotic capital, with another 20m in the surrounding metropolitan area. Rapid urbanisation and a woeful lack of buses and trains have left the roads heavily jammed. In 2016, a survey found that the city had the worst traffic in the world. Businesspeople, fed up with spending an hour in a taxi getting to a meeting just a few blocks away, speak over Skype instead. Some policemen have started a side line in selling motorcade escorts to them. A new underground service, decades in the making, already feels jam-packed.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The city&amp;#x27;s growth has hurt the environment, too. Developers have concreted over the city ‘s green bits and floodplains in their haste to erect ever-taller, and heavier, office blocks; discarded plastic clogs up the rivers. As a result, floods have become more frequent and deadly. Jakarta is the world&amp;#x27;s fastest-sinking urban area. Some neighbourhoods are dropping at a rate of 25cm per year, and researchers think that almost all of north Jakarta could be submerged in 30 years. Rising sea levels is one contributory factor. Another is that only one third of residents have access to piped water, so the rest bore holes in the ground to tap the natural reservoir beneath the city. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;It is partly for these reasons that Joko Widodo, Indonesia&amp;#x27;s president, known as Jokowi, wants to move the capital. On April 29th, after a cabinet meeting on the topic, Bambang Brodjonegoro, the head of the National Development Planning Agency, announced the government&amp;#x27;s plans. A precise site for the new capital has not been chosen, but it will not be on Java, the island where Jakarta is located. The most likely destination is Palangkaraya, the capital of the province of Central Kalimantan, part of the Indonesian portion of Borneo (an orangutan sanctuary on the outskirts of the city is pictured above right). Not all branches of government will up sticks. Those most-closely tied to Indonesia&amp;#x27;s economy, like the central bank, will stay put.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The choice of destination highlights Jokowi&amp;#x27;s other reason for the move: he wants to reduce regional income inequalities. Indonesia is an archipelago of 13,000 or so islands, but it is dominated by Java, which accounts for about 58% of GDP and about the same share of the population. Moving the capital to Borneo would not only ease Jakarta&amp;#x27;s overcrowding, but also help reduce regional income gaps. Average wages are about 40% lower in Central Kalimantan than in the capital.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Borneo could benefit in other ways. Its dense and luscious rainforests have long suffered at the hands of natural-resource firms, like those involved in palm oil and coal mining, whose razing of trees and polluting of rivers goes largely unpunished. Getting away with these environmental sins is made easier by the island’s sparse population and remoteness from policymakers. If it becomes home to legions of government officials, politicians and journalists, the argument goes, the industry&amp;#x27;s most nefarious deeds will become harder to ignore. Then again, locals have already expressed fears that building the new capital, however modest in size, will itself devour more of that luscious rainforest. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The idea of shifting the capital is not new. It was originally proposed by Sukarno, Indonesia&amp;#x27;s founding father and first president, in the 1950s. Many of his predecessors toyed with similar plans. The idea is not unique to Indonesia either. Countries around the world, from Nigeria to Myanmar, have relocated their capitals. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;If the plan is implemented, there is no reason why it would not work. Fewer Jakartans would reduce the strain on the city&amp;#x27;s roads and rivers. And the experience of other countries suggests that when civil servants move, private-sector jobs follow, often in services like law and consulting.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Yet getting it done will be tricky. Bureaucrats are likely to resist a move away from the schools and hospitals, let alone the glitzy bars and malls, of Jakarta. Moreover, Indonesian politics is beset by self-interested oligarchs, many of whom own real estate in Jakarta and would not like to see the value of their property portfolios fall. They have halted less-ambitious reforms, which were not in their interests, with relative ease.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Even without this resistance, presidential term limits mean Jokowi&amp;#x27;s reign will last only five more years. The government concedes that moving the capital will probably take twice as long. His successor could easily reverse his changes, perhaps citing the rampant corruption and overrun costs that afflict most large government projects in Indonesia. Leaving Jakarta will be a slow and laborious process—rather like getting anywhere in Jakarta itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Related story:&lt;br/&gt;Capital flight: Why governments want to move civil servants out of national capitals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;https://www.economist.com/international/2019/04/04/why-governments-move-civil-servants-out-of-national-capitals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 23:06:41 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Who are the biggest bullshitters?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/30/who-are-the-biggest-bullshitters]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_WOC813_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-30T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EVERYBODY tells the occasional fib. But whereas liars consciously conceal the truth, reckons Harry Frankfurt, a philosopher, bullshitters are shameless: they say what they want to, without even considering the truth. Bluffers seem to be everywhere: the share of Americans who believe that most people can be trusted has fallen from 48% in 1984 to just 31% today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://ftp.iza.org/dp12282.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_new&quot;&gt;new study&lt;/a&gt; of the phenomenon has found that North America is especially prone to speaking bull. John Jerrim, Phil Parker and Nikki Shure, three academics, have used an educational survey of 40,000 teenage students in nine English-speaking countries to find out who is most likely to spout nonsense. They inserted a section into the questionnaire which asked students how well they understood a collection of 16 mathematical concepts. Some were familiar, such as “polygon” and “probability”, but three were fake: “proper number”, “subjunctive scaling” and “declarative fraction”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results show substantial differences between countries. Canadian and American teenagers were especially likely to profess knowledge of these bogus topics, whereas the Scots and Irish were perfectly happy to admit their ignorance. In news that will shock nobody, in every country men claimed to be experts more often than women. The rich were more boastful than the poor. More surprising was the finding that immigrants were generally more likely to bluff about maths than native students were.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What explains these differences? The academics doubt that the bullshitters were simply trying to impress the questionnaire’s markers. The students who bluffed about maths were just as likely as the non-bluffers to admit that they had skipped school recently, for example. A more likely answer is that the blaggers over-estimated their own knowledge. They also tended to rate themselves highly when it came to gauging their own popularity, perseverance on academic tasks and problem-solving ability. The data suggest that they might not be consciously lying, but instead be weaving their own fantasies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/JePq8Zz28HE&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 21:06:35 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Joe Biden launches himself as a fighter for the working class]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/04/29/joe-biden-launches-himself-as-a-fighter-for-the-working-class]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/000_1g151r.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-29T21:31:56Z&quot;&gt;Apr 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT IS NOT always a mistake to refight the last battle. Joe Biden, addressing the first crowd of his official campaign on April 29th, in Pittsburgh, promised to overcome the mistakes made by the Democrats in 2016. Three years ago his party failed to fire up blue-collar workers, especially in the Midwest. Mr Biden said he would focus on the power of organised labour and ordinary, middle-class folk—the backbone of America, he said, from teachers to health-workers to plumbers—who do extraordinary things. “I am a union man, period”, he vowed, earning cheers of “We want Joe!” He stood in a union hall, before a “Biden Workers for America” poster, amid members of a firefighters’ union that had just endorsed him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also said his campaign would focus on the small towns and struggling parts of Pennsylvania that Democrats neglected so badly in 2016. Democrats tend to do well in cities and suburbs, but Mr Trump fired up large numbers of rural voters, turning Pennsylvania Republican in the first presidential race since 1988. Mr Biden had chosen Pittsburgh to launch his campaign, he said, because: “If I’m gonna beat Donald Trump in 2020, it’s going to happen here”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His map-reading is spot on. No Democratic presidential candidate since Harry Truman in 1948 has reached the White House without taking Pennsylvania. Mr Trump’s path to a second term almost certainly depends on his holding on to the state’s 20 electoral college votes. Along with Michigan and Wisconsin, which Mr Trump also narrowly won, the state will serve as the centre of the 2020 campaign. Mr Biden’s big advantage is that he can cast himself as a local boy. He was born in the state, was a senator next door in Delaware and has long been claimed by Pennsylvania Democrats as their own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nothing in Mr Biden’s cautious speech in Pittsburgh was surprising, including his failure to mention immigration (he knows that more than a few blue-collar voters in the Midwest agree with Mr Trump’s position on that). He has borrowed a slogan—“the dignity of work”—that was previously deployed this year to good effect by another Midwestern presidential-aspirant, Sherrod Brown. In early March Mr Brown, a 66-year-old senator from Ohio, said he would not enter the race. That disappointed many who saw him as an affable younger version of 76-year-old Mr Biden. But it cleared Mr Biden’s path to stand as the representative for America&amp;#x27;s ordinary, hard-working folk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The approach is calculated to undermine a president during a time of prolonged economic growth. By saying “the dignity of work is my measure”, Mr Biden brushes aside statistics about low unemployment and high GDP, pointing instead to how ordinary workers feel. His talk of higher wages and more respect could resonate well with some of the president’s wavering supporters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What does the start of Mr Biden’s campaign mean for his Democratic rivals? Polls suggest he is the solid frontrunner, with 25% or more support in a crowded field. After eight years as vice-president to Barack Obama, who remains enormously popular, Mr Biden starts with a big advantage. Most people already know who he is. Last week he raised more money—$6.3m—in the first 24 hours of his campaign than any other candidate had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also instantly attracted Mr Trump’s attention. Ahead of his first rally the president posted a tweet about “sleepy Joe Biden” and the leaders of the fire fighters’ union who endorsed him. At times during his rally Mr Biden sounded like a less angry, more upbeat version of Mr Trump—at one point he chastised the bosses of GM, a carmaker, for closing factories in America and opening a new plant in Mexico.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Biden’s greatest strength is his ability to be a voice for the sort of angry, blue-collar worker who drifted away from the Democrats in 2016, while also promising to be a more civil, hopeful and upbeat sort of leader. More than once during his speech he emphasised his optimism, telling voters to choose “hope over fear” and “truth over lies”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Biden will be vulnerable, however, if primary voters reject the idea of refighting the battle of 2016. He might make amends for Hillary Clinton’s failure to excite blue-collar supporters. He might, by virtue of his association with Mr Obama, win the backing of many African-Americans. But other parts of the Democrats’ broad coalition—including urban, youthful voters, or people who want make history by electing a female president or a gay one—do not want to vote for an elderly white man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On policy, meanwhile, Mr Biden can appear cautious—he is anxious not to scare away swing voters, even if that means failing to inspire those to his left. Though he criticised Mr Trump’s tax cut, for example, he did not propose reinstating higher taxes on the rich. Instead he promised to close “tax loopholes” that supposedly let the rich evade $1.6 trillion in taxes. That is a big number, but it is a long way from the grand promises made by some of his rivals. Mr Biden is a cautious man. But for now he appears to be the Democrat most likely to take on Mr Trump next year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 20:05:47 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Strikes in Argentina, and more from our daily podcast]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/30/strikes-in-argentina-and-more-from-our-daily-podcast]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/theintelligence_twitter_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-30T11:30:22Z&quot;&gt;Apr 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WITH PATIENCE running thin amid rampant inflation and a devaluing currency, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/04/30/planned-strikes-are-the-latest-challenge-to-mauricio-macri&quot;&gt;trade unions in Argentina&lt;/a&gt; have organised two days of strikes against the government of Mauricio Macri. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/27/taiwans-richest-man-says-his-run-for-president-is-divinely-inspired&quot;&gt;Taiwan’s richest man&lt;/a&gt; has announced his bid to become the country&amp;#x27;s president. But with much of his business based in China, he will struggle to convince voters that he has no conflicts of interest. And &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/04/16/the-supreme-court-scrutinises-a-bar-on-scandalous-trademarks&quot;&gt;America’s Supreme Court&lt;/a&gt; is deciding whether to ensure trademark protection for businesses with vulgar names. Runtime: 20 min.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/inflationarypressure-argentina-sstrikes&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 19:06:20 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Planned strikes are the latest challenge to Mauricio Macri]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/04/30/planned-strikes-are-the-latest-challenge-to-mauricio-macri]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_AMP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-30T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THIS WEEK Argentine trade unions opposed to the government of Mauricio Macri will try to bring the country to a halt. On April 30th they plan to shut down flights, the metro in Buenos Aires, banks and schools. Even hospitals will run reduced “Sunday services”. On the following day, a holiday, unions will lead a rally at the presidential palace, joined by politicians from the Peronist opposition party.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“This strike is a demonstration of repudiation by our society of a government which has produced hunger, misery, unemployment and indebtedness,” declared Hugo Moyano, the boss of the truckers’ union, in a radio interview over the weekend. Union leaders called for a “complete rejection of the government’s economic policy”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The strike will sharpen a confrontation that will last through national elections scheduled for October. Mr Macri is trying desperately to create economic conditions favourable to his re-election. The economy is not co-operating. Inflation in the year to March was 54.7%. GDP shrank last year and is expected to do so again in 2019. About one in three Argentinians is now living in poverty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These numbers reflect the Macri government’s tactical mistakes in correcting the populist policies of its predecessors, led by Cristina Fernández de Kirchner and her husband, Néstor Kirchner. A rise in American interest rates, plus a lack of confidence in Mr Macri’s reforms, led to a run on Argentina’s peso last year, which led in turn to a record $57bn loan from the IMF. It has so far failed to steady the economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fear is mounting that failure will bring Ms Fernández back to power. Last week the peso lost 8% of its value against the dollar. The gap between yields on American Treasury bonds and those on Argentina’s dollar-denominated bonds, which reflects the market’s perception of Argentina’s creditworthiness, widened to more than ten percentage points for the first time since Mr Macri took office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market’s doubt “has no foundation”, Mr Macri insists. “We Argentines are not going back.” To ensure the truth of this claim, his government has adopted unorthodox economic policies that could test the terms of its deal with the IMF. On April 17th it announced an anti-inflation package, which includes controls on the prices of 60-odd staple foods plus delays in planned price increases for public services, such as transport.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far the new measures have had little effect. Some items with frozen prices, such as milk, have disappeared from many supermarket shelves, and the government says that supplies of other items (including the national drink of &lt;em&gt;mate&lt;/em&gt;) will not be available until the second week of May.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Till now the IMF has tolerated Mr Macri’s unorthodoxy, perhaps fearing that policy would become even less orthodox were he to lose the election. On April 29th the IMF agreed to allow the central bank to intervene earlier and harder to support the peso. It can step in even before the currency weakens beyond 51.5 to the dollar (the previous trigger point). And if the currency nonetheless reaches that limit, it can now spend more to push it up ($250m a day, rather than $150m). The falling peso has raised import prices and undermined the public’s faith in price stability. Propping it up, therefore, should help to pull inflation down. But it will also harm the competitiveness of Argentina’s exporters. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A bumper harvest this year may have reassured the IMF. Government revenues from a tax on exports of such commodities as soya and biodiesel will be 230bn pesos ($5bn) this year, about 1% of GDP, according to a new report by the board of trade in Rosario, an export hub. That is a near doubling in nominal terms from the level of 2018. That revenue increase will help reduce the government’s primary deficit (ie, before interest payments). Under the agreement with the IMF, this year the government is supposed to eliminate the primary deficit, which was 2.6% of GDP in 2018 (including infrastructure investment).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The extra money will ease pressure on the government as it waits for inflation to come down. The strikers and the Peronist opposition will seek to keep the pressure on. Ms Fernández is taking full advantage of Mr Macri’s plight. Although she has been indicted on several charges of corruption she leads the president in the polls. Her newly published book, a memoir-cum-campaign manifesto called “Sincerely”, is a best-seller.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her political comeback is fuelling speculation that Mr Macri’s Cambiemos (“Let’s Change”) coalition will find someone more popular than he is to be its presidential nominee. The likeliest replacement may be María Eugenia Vidal, the governor of the province of Buenos Aires, which has 40% of the country’s population. The chaos planned by Argentina’s trade unions this week may boost her political career, as well as that of Ms Fernández.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 14:05:43 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Joe Biden launches himself as a fighter for the working class]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/04/30/joe-biden-launches-himself-as-a-fighter-for-the-working-class]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_USP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-30T01:31:56Z&quot;&gt;Apr 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT IS NOT always a mistake to refight the last battle. Joe Biden, addressing the first crowd of his official campaign on April 29th, in Pittsburgh, promised to overcome the mistakes made by the Democrats in 2016. Three years ago his party failed to fire up blue-collar workers, especially in the Midwest. Mr Biden said he would focus on the power of organised labour and ordinary, middle-class folk—the backbone of America, he said, from teachers to health-workers to plumbers—who do extraordinary things. “I am a union man, period”, he vowed, earning cheers of “We want Joe!” He stood in a union hall, before a “Biden Workers for America” poster, amid members of a firefighters’ union that had just endorsed him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also said his campaign would focus on the small towns and struggling parts of Pennsylvania that Democrats neglected so badly in 2016. Democrats tend to do well in cities and suburbs, but Mr Trump fired up large numbers of rural voters, turning Pennsylvania Republican in the first presidential race since 1988. Mr Biden had chosen Pittsburgh to launch his campaign, he said, because: “If I’m gonna beat Donald Trump in 2020, it’s going to happen here”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His map-reading is spot on. No Democratic presidential candidate since Harry Truman in 1948 has reached the White House without taking Pennsylvania. Mr Trump’s path to a second term almost certainly depends on his holding on to the state’s 20 electoral college votes. Along with Michigan and Wisconsin, which Mr Trump also narrowly won, the state will serve as the centre of the 2020 campaign. Mr Biden’s big advantage is that he can cast himself as a local boy. He was born in the state, was a senator next door in Delaware and has long been claimed by Pennsylvania Democrats as their own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nothing in Mr Biden’s cautious speech in Pittsburgh was surprising, including his failure to mention immigration (he knows that more than a few blue-collar voters in the Midwest agree with Mr Trump’s position on that). He has borrowed a slogan—“the dignity of work”—that was previously deployed this year to good effect by another Midwestern presidential-aspirant, Sherrod Brown. In early March Mr Brown, a 66-year-old senator from Ohio, said he would not enter the race. That disappointed many who saw him as an affable younger version of 76-year-old Mr Biden. But it cleared Mr Biden’s path to stand as the representative for America&amp;#x27;s ordinary, hard-working folk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The approach is calculated to undermine a president during a time of prolonged economic growth. By saying “the dignity of work is my measure”, Mr Biden brushes aside statistics about low unemployment and high GDP, pointing instead to how ordinary workers feel. His talk of higher wages and more respect could resonate well with some of the president’s wavering supporters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What does the start of Mr Biden’s campaign mean for his Democratic rivals? Polls suggest he is the solid frontrunner, with 25% or more support in a crowded field. After eight years as vice-president to Barack Obama, who remains enormously popular, Mr Biden starts with a big advantage. Most people already know who he is. Last week he raised more money—$6.3m—in the first 24 hours of his campaign than any other candidate had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also instantly attracted Mr Trump’s attention. Ahead of his first rally the president posted a tweet about “sleepy Joe Biden” and the leaders of the fire fighters’ union who endorsed him. At times during his rally Mr Biden sounded like a less angry, more upbeat version of Mr Trump—at one point he chastised the bosses of GM, a carmaker, for closing factories in America and opening a new plant in Mexico.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Biden’s greatest strength is his ability to be a voice for the sort of angry, blue-collar worker who drifted away from the Democrats in 2016, while also promising to be a more civil, hopeful and upbeat sort of leader. More than once during his speech he emphasised his optimism, telling voters to choose “hope over fear” and “truth over lies”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Biden will be vulnerable, however, is if primary voters reject the idea of refighting the battle of 2016. He might make amends for Hillary Clinton’s failure to excite blue-collar supporters. He might, by virtue of his association with Mr Obama, win the backing of many African-Americans. But other parts of the Democrats’ broad coalition—including urban, youthful voters, or people who want make history by electing a female president or a gay one—do not want to vote for an elderly white man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On policy, meanwhile, Mr Biden can appear cautious—he is anxious not to scare away swing voters, even if that means failing to inspire those to his left. Though he criticised Mr Trump’s tax cut, for example, he did not propose reinstating higher taxes on the rich. Instead he promised to close “tax loopholes” that supposedly let the rich evade $1.6 trillion in taxes. That is a big number, but it is a long way from the grand promises made by some of his rivals. Mr Biden is a cautious man. But for now he appears to be the Democrat most likely to take on Mr Trump next year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 10:07:29 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The past decade has brought a compliance boom in banking]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/04/29/the-past-decade-has-brought-a-compliance-boom-in-banking]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_FNP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;COMPLIANCE OFFICERS are the killjoys of finance. To bankers and traders keen to let rip, they are the po-faced types who, while generating no revenue themselves, frown at any transaction that might breach this rule or contravene that regulation. A recent episode of “Billions”, a television drama about Wall Street, captured the rainmakers’ frustration: so fed up is “Dollar” Bill Stern with having his wings clipped by Ari Spyros that the veteran trader rams the side of the compliance chief’s Porsche (pictured above) when he pulls out of the car park of their hedge fund, Axe Capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But pity not finance’s in-house policemen, for they have had a golden decade since the crisis. While swathes of banking has laboured under cutbacks and stiff capital requirements, compliance departments’ headcount and clout have grown. Banks clobbered by fines for aiding corruption, money-laundering and sanctions-busting have beefed up their compliance, risk, legal and internal-audit teams. Compliance officers will never be the rock stars of finance, but they have moved from drums to rhythm guitar. And though some banks hint at having reached “Peak Compliance”, staffing and investment are likely to remain well above pre-crisis levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Combating financial crime is central to the compliance effort. Enforcement has been ratcheted up since America passed the Patriot Act, which targeted money flowing to terrorists and other bad actors, after the September 11th attacks. Regulators have fined financial firms at least $28.4bn for money-laundering and sanctions violations since 2008; BNP Paribas alone coughed up $8.9bn for sanctions shenanigans. Aiding tax evaders has cost banks at least another $9.5bn. There is more to come: Scandinavian banks embroiled in scandals involving laundered Russian money, including Danske Bank and Swedbank, are bracing for penalties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Corrupt money is only part of the picture. Compliance is about keeping on top of a plethora of regulations, covering everything from capital and corporate governance to disclosure and diversity. Compliance teams even have to fret about diversions like “office pools”—sweepstakes on sports events—in case they fall foul of gambling laws. Thomson Reuters, which tracks regulatory alerts, reckons that 56,321 were issued by 900 bodies in 2017. “You have to build an industrial-scale operation just to digest all the regulatory changes,” says Colin Bell, HSBC’s chief compliance officer (CCO).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keen to show that compliance is a priority, banks highlight it much more in filings than they used to (see chart 1). They seem to have backed up talk with action—though its extent is hard to gauge because disclosure is patchy and banks define compliance and related functions in varying ways. Disclosures, such as they are, suggest that it accounts for 10% or more of the workforce at large banks these days, up from perhaps half that in the mid-2000s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the end of 2018, some 30,000 (or 15%) of the 204,000 employees of Citi, an American bank, worked in compliance, risk and other control functions—enough to fill more than two-thirds of the seats at Citi Field, the New York Mets’ baseball stadium. At the end of 2008 it was just over 4% of employees. JPMorgan Chase could just about fill it with the 43,000 it claims to employ in “fortress controls” (a category that is probably broader).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HSBC, which was fined $1.9bn in 2012 for banking Mexican drug money and other lapses, has around 5,000 employees in anti-money-laundering (AML) compliance. Standard Chartered, which has coughed up $1.8bn for breaches of sanctions, has 3,500. Both banks spend $500m a year on AML alone—for Standard Chartered, the equivalent of a fifth of its pre-tax profit for 2018. British banks’ annual AML spend is £5bn ($6.5bn), according to the Financial Conduct Authority.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since BNP Paribas was hit with its mega-fine in 2014, it has nearly doubled headcount in compliance and other control functions, to almost 13,000. Growing demand for AML sleuths has been a boon for those who certify them, too. The Association of Certified Anti-Money-Laundering Specialists, based in Miami, has seen worldwide membership grow from 5,600 to 70,000 since 2007.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Banks caught up in dirty-money scandals are not only rushing to hire, but keen to advertise the fact in order to calm market nerves. Danske Bank has said it will hire 600 new compliance staff this year; it has already quadrupled the number since 2015, to 1,200. ABN Amro, which is under scrutiny because an operation that it used to own may have been connected with the Troika Laundromat, a Russian money-washing scheme, has disclosed details of its investment in AML (including a tripling of staff engaged in “client due diligence”). Banks are also throwing money at staff training—and policing it more assiduously. Gone are the days when traders could get interns to take their computer-based compliance tests for them while they popped out for a pint. Such ruses are now a sacking offence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compliance is gaining not just investment, but clout. In the past it was often buried in the legal or risk department, and compliance chiefs reported to chief risk officers or general counsels. Now they are more likely to have a direct line to the top: for instance, HSBC’s Mr Bell reports directly to the chief executive and attends meetings of the board’s risk committee. The CCO’s role now involves much more than ensuring the firm is within the law: liaising with the boss and the board, ensuring investors and regulators have the information they need, and helping shape the bank’s risk culture. “It has become a much more influential position,” says Mark Jackson of Heidrick &amp;amp; Struggles, a recruitment firm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the financial crisis, the market for compliance jobs became one of the hottest in finance. CCOs earn nothing like banks’ rainmakers, but the best-paid can expect basic annual salaries of over $1m. (Compliance also weighs heavily in pay for top dogs: at HSBC, “risk and compliance” is the biggest component the board considers when assessing the CEO, weighted at 25%. Profit counts for 20% and revenue growth 10%.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consequently, compliance is attracting more big names than it used to. Jennifer Calvery, HSBC’s head of financial-crime threat mitigation, was previously head of FinCEN, America’s AML regulator, a role that strikes fear into bankers’ hearts the world over. Recruiters say talented lawyers who would previously have shunned compliance roles are now more interested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So too are banks’ profit generators. In recent years BNP Paribas has encouraged employees to move between the business side and compliance to “disseminate the compliance and conduct culture”, says Nathalie Hartmann, its compliance chief—and previously head of portfolio management. Under BNP’s post-fine compliance framework, “conduct and control officers” wander trading floors and sales desks, spotting wayward behaviour earlier than would previously have been possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Banks such as BNP and HSBC, which are now several years into compliance-boosting efforts, have entered a “stabilisation” phase, says a consultant. Having started by throwing people at the problem, they are now seeking to increase efficiency and lower costs. Some, including UBS, have even suggested it may be time to pare back after the boom. Spending on compliance at HSBC peaked in 2017, says Mr Bell. “As in any cycle of transformation, there is a settling-in phase, when you can, for instance, do without some of those who did the initial training or initiated technology projects that are now up and running.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some financial firms, particularly small ones, are outsourcing compliance functions or specific projects. Compliance Risk Concepts, an American firm that takes on such work, has seen demand for its services grow by over 30% a year, says Mitch Avnet, its managing partner. And in America, which strengthened controls earlier than Europe did, the market for jobs in compliance has eased a bit. Jack Kelly of Compliance Search Group, a recruiter, attributes this partly to regulatory forbearance: not so much actual deregulation (the Trump administration has cut less red tape than promised) as “winks and nods” from regulators to signal they will enforce rules less stringently. John Gilmore of BarkerGilmore, another recruiter, says that while the market remains strong, “we’re no longer seeing amazing bidding wars for well-qualified compliance officers where there would be two other offers on the table and you couldn’t be sure the guy would start until he actually walked through the door.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, the biggest question for bank controllers is how many humans they can replace with bots without compromising compliance. HSBC is looking at the possibility of using big data to assign a financial-crime-risk score to each customer. Banks are partnering with some of the hundreds of “regtechs” that have sprouted in recent years: startups with names like Regbot and Arachnys that tout cutting-edge compliance solutions. According to HTF, a market-research firm, global regtech market revenue was $1.4bn in 2018 and is forecast to reach $6.4bn by 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most mature part is AML screening, which is dominated by bigger firms such as Refinitiv and Dow Jones that help banks and companies vet clients and potential trading partners for money-laundering, sanctions and terrorist-finance risks. It continues to grow at quite a clip: sales increased 18% in 2018, reckons Burton-Taylor, another research firm. Some big hitters are backing the robot revolution. “Over time, AI willdramatically improve [AML processes] as well as other complex compliance requirements,” wrote Jamie Dimon, the chief executive of JPMorgan Chase, in his latest letter to shareholders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now, though, many banks struggle to choose between the myriad products hustling for attention, says Stacey English of Thomson Reuters. “AI carries risks we don’t understand,” says a large bank’s compliance chief. Regulators will need convincing, too. In December a group of American regulators issued a statement urging banks to use “innovative approaches”, including AI, to enhance money-laundering compliance. But banks remain nervous that regulators will penalise banks if techno-experiments fail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea of compliance algorithms replacing warm-blooded sleuths is fanciful, say experts. Sujata Dasgupta, the head of financial-crimes compliance at Tata Consultancy Services, sees compliance staff moving into “higher-quality investigations”, with bots used for “more rule-based, repetitive screening tasks”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, bankers expect no let-up in either financial-crime enforcement or new regulation. America’s increased use of sanctions as a foreign-policy tool under Donald Trump means banks must be more vigilant than ever (see chart 2). Demand is growing for people who can help banks negotiate new data-protection and privacy rules, such as the EU’s GDPR. Tougher enforcement is increasing compliance risks, too. Britain, for instance, has increased personal liability for senior executives at financial firms caught behaving badly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also rewarding more vigorous compliance efforts is the growing tendency of regulators, including America’s Department of Justice, to offer big reductions in penalties to firms that self-report violations in financial-crime and corruption cases. Hardly surprising, then, that a global study of risk and compliance officers at 800 financial firms in 2018 found that 43% expected their team to grow over the next 12 months, with only 5% expecting a reduction. If the Russian laundromat scandal claims more victims, another hiring spree may be around the corner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A picture of Eliot Spitzer hangs on a wall at Mr Kelly’s compliance-recruitment firm. As New York’s attorney-general from 1999 to 2006, Mr Spitzer was a scourge of Wall Street, tilting at banks for various alleged transgressions and sparking an earlier compliance hiring spree. “He’s one of my heroes,” chuckles Mr Kelly, “and scandals are my friend.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 05:06:31 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>