<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[France agonises over the flames that devastated Notre Dame]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/16/france-agonises-over-the-flames-that-devastated-notre-dame]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_EUP001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-16T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE CATHEDRAL of Notre Dame is a “majestic and sublime edifice”, a “vast symphony in stone”, wrote Victor Hugo. “Every surface, every stone of this venerable pile, is a page of the history not only of the country, but of science and of art.” The devastating fire that broke out on April 15th, and destroyed much of the gothic cathedral’s wood-timbered roof and spire, stunned and distressed the French with a force that far exceeded the building’s religious significance. As the flames engulfed the roof, President Emmanuel Macron spoke for many across France when he tweeted that he was witnessing “part of us burn”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why has the fire at Notre Dame stirred such emotion in France? In a city of broad vistas and stolen glimpses, it serves as a fixed point for Parisians; a stable presence that emerges reliably into view, like a much-loved aunt, from bridges across the river Seine. Visited by 13m tourists a year, the cathedral has been the backdrop to countless expressions of awe and romance, as well as been-there selfies. Locals may be riled by the narcissistic crowds, but are proud of what draws them. The 850-year-old cathedral is a national landmark that offers something particular: a form of timelessness, drama and spirituality, to set against the modernity and engineering prowess of the Eiffel Tower.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the night, as firefighters struggled to control the blaze, it looked for a stretch as if the centuries were dissolving in flames. For Parisians, watching in eerie silence on the bridges, the wait was agonising. In his preface to “The Hunchback of Notre Dame”, the novel that reawakened the French to the cathedral’s splendour, Hugo had warned darkly that “soon, perhaps, the Cathedral itself will have vanished from the face of the earth.” As the fire blazed, the visceral fear that Hugo might have been right seemed to touch a profound yearning for Our Lady to survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cathedral had withstood ransacking during the wars of religion, looting during the revolution, two world wars and Nazi occupation, becoming an emblem of resistance in the face of a constantly disrupted history. More than this, Notre Dame is a product of the paradoxes of that history. It is where an emperor, Napoleon, was crowned in 1804, and where the founder of modern republican France, Charles de Gaulle, was remembered upon his death. It was at once a living place of worship for the French Catholic church, and the property of the French secular state: a symbol in itself of the country’s history and its present, in all its glorious contradictions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As he visited the site shortly before midnight, Mr Macron, so often perceived as out of touch, for once found the right words to express this. “Notre Dame de Paris is our history, our literature,” he declared. “The place where we have lived all our great moments, epidemics, wars and liberation. It is the epicentre of our lives and the point from which we measure distance from Paris...This history, it is ours and it is burning.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that those flames have been extinguished, questions will turn to why Notre Dame burned, and how it can be rebuilt. The Paris public prosecutor has opened an investigation, declaring that “nothing suggests it was a deliberate act.” If this was indeed an accident, the focus will be the works to renovate the 19th-century spire, which began last summer. It was the oak-beamed roof above the vaults that proved to be both so flammable, and so difficult for the fire brigade to get to. Thanks to the efforts of 400 firefighters—as well as to the craftsmanship of the 12th and 13th-century stonemasons who built the stone vaults beneath the roof—the cathedral’s main medieval structure was largely saved. Firefighters also managed to save many religious artefacts and relics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How stable the remaining structure is, and whether the stone has been permanently weakened by the intense heat, say engineers, will have to be assessed once the masonry has cooled. Mr Macron vowed that, no matter what, the cathedral will be rebuilt, and launched a fund-raising initiative to that end. In a country that lacks a tradition of private philanthropy, it was notable that France’s richest businessmen vowed to contribute. Two luxury titans, Bernard Arnault and François Pinault, between them pledged €300m ($340m).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The search for somebody to blame will absorb France for some time. Many will want to know exactly what precautions were taken by those working on the renovation, and what exactly was the nature of the disaster-planning for a monument of this scale and national importance, situated amid narrow streets on an inaccessible island in the centre of the city. A broader question is whose responsibility it should be to maintain secular France’s great religious buildings. The government had contributed to the renovation of Notre Dame’s spire. But the cathedral had to raise funds to renew its bells in 2012, and the agreement between the archdiocese and the government over upkeep is unclear. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the morning after the fire, tourists gathered along the cobbled quays to get their shot of the old survivor, damaged but unfallen. For locals, sadness at the damage was mixed with deep relief that it had not been far worse. At one point, and after five months of unrest by gilets jaunes (yellow jackets), the fire seemed to be a ghastly symbol for the torment of France. It broke out just before Mr Macron was due to unveil his response to those protests, and to his “great national debate”, in a speech he promptly had to postpone. The moment was supposed to mark the end of a disaster. Instead, it brought another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Macron now faces a different challenge. The country was already divided, and the president unloved. Today Notre Dame is charred, and Paris, and all of France, is in pain. Just occasionally, such a national drama can help to pull a divided country together. On the night, Mr Macron made a good start. But he has yet to bring closure to his great debate. It will take particular skill to do this while offering solace to a nation still in shock after the drama of Notre Dame. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 05:18:40 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rebuilding Notre Dame after the blaze]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/16/rebuilding-notre-dame-after-the-blaze]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BLP509.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-16T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EMMANUEL MACRON was unequivocal. Speaking after a fire destroyed the roof and spire of the cathedral of Notre Dame in Paris, the French president vowed: “I solemnly say tonight: we will rebuild it together”. An international fund-raising drive has already received its first big pledges. François-Henri Pinault, boss of the Kering luxury-goods company, said he will donate €100m; the family of Bernard Arnault and his LVMH group, another luxury-goods firm, promised a further €200m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exactly how much money will be needed will depend on exactly what the police and fire service find as they rummage through the wreckage. But early signs are encouraging. The efforts of the firemen prevented the blaze from reaching the cathedral’s two belfries. And while pictures of the blaze looked catastrophic, says Lisa Reilly, an architectural historian at the University of Virginia, Notre Dame’s Gothic architecture was designed partly to resist such accidents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The heart of the cathedral is an enclosed stone vault, supported at the sides by buttresses and with a timber-framed roof built atop the ceiling. The idea, says Ms Reilly, is that if the roof catches fire—which was a serious risk in an age when lighting came from candles or oil lamps—it can burn away without compromising the structural integrity of the vault itself. That theory seems to have (mostly) held up. The main body of the cathedral is still standing. But early pictures show that at least one section of the vault has fallen in, scattering charred debris across the cathedral floor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stone may be more resistant to fire than wood, but it is not immune to its effects. One critical question is just how hot the vault became. There was plenty of fuel at Notre Dame. The cathedral’s roof was held up by oak beams so densely packed that they were known as “the forest”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under the right conditions wood fires can reach temperatures of 1,000C or more. Temperatures much lower than that can be enough to cause damage. After a fire at Windsor Castle outside London in 1992, the Building Research Establishment, then a part of the British government, commissioned studies into the effects of fires on stone buildings. Notre Dame is built from limestone, which the BRE found became discoloured at the relatively low temperature of 250C, thanks to chemical reactions in iron compounds within the stone. Higher temperatures caused more serious problems. In laboratory tests, limestone began to weaken at around 600C. At 700C its compressive strength had fallen by about 40%. Rapid cooling—thanks to being deluged with water from firehoses, for instance—weakened the stone still further.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stone is a poor conductor of heat, which means that the temperature on the side of a masonry block facing a fire can be far higher than on the side facing away. Such thermal stresses can cause big cracks. After a fire at York Minster cathedral in 1984 around 100 tons of cracked stonework needed replacing. Even the cooling process can cause problems. “The vault will have had burning timbers sitting on it for some hours,” says Robert Bowles, a British structural engineer who specialises in conserving old buildings. “As the masonry cools down and shrinks it may deform.” One of the priorities will be trying to determine just how sound the damaged portions of the vault’s ceiling remain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;History, though, offers reasons to be cheerful. Notre Dame has been restored before, after vandalism during the French revolution and neglect until the 19th century, when the spire was rebuilt. Dr Reilly points to the cathedral at Reims, whose roof was similarly burnt away after it was hit by shelling in the first world war. Later attacks caused even more damage, leaving the building in a much worse state than Notre Dame. A restoration project, partly funded by the Rockefeller Foundation, saw Reims reopened in 1938. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today&amp;#x27;s restorers should have an easier time of it. Researchers led by the late Andrew Tallon, of Vassar College, in New York, conducted a detailed laser scan of the entire building. Their billion-plus data points constitute a virtual copy of the building, accurate to within 5 millimetres, that could prove vital in the reconstruction effort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A resurrection of Notre Dame, in other words, seems eminently possible. Another priority task, says Mr Bowles, will be to erect a temporary roof so the drying-out process can begin, and to protect the remaining masonry from the elements. Here, at least, the gods seem to be smiling: the weather forecast in Paris is for a week of bright sunshine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 04:08:28 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Could Extinction Rebellion be the next Occupy movement?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/04/16/could-extinction-rebellion-be-the-next-occupy-movement]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BRP004.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-16T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN FRONT OF a bright pink sailing boat emblazoned with the words “tell the truth”, an elderly man in red trousers is telling his. He urges the crowd assembled in the centre of Oxford Circus to use their anger about climate change, but not to allow it to put off others. “If we’re abusive to people that’s not helpful,” he warns, before proceeding to invoke Martin Luther King and Gandhi. He then loses his train of thought. “I’ve forgotten where I was, I’ll pause and invite you to do the same and breathe.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The climate protests, which began on April 15th in 80 cities across 33 countries, may look familiar, but they have a steely core. Extinction Rebellion, the group organising them, was set up in October last year after 94 academics wrote to the Guardian newspaper, calling for action. Founded by British activists, it has three goals: get governments to declare a “climate emergency”; reduce net greenhouse gas emissions to zero by 2025; and make the government create citizens’ assemblies to set climate priorities, bypassing the short-termism of parliamentary democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although plenty of protest movements have lofty aims, Extinction Rebellion has an unusual knack for organisation. In its first six months it has secured high-profile support, including from a former archbishop of Canterbury, and lots of attention. Swarming protests have closed roads, a “die-in” was staged in a shopping centre and naked protesters interrupted a debate in the House of Commons. Demonstrators eschew violence, but are willing—indeed, eager—to be arrested for civil disobedience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The attention this generates can be converted into more activists. Loz, a teacher taking advantage of the Easter holiday to hand out leaflets, says this is her first environmental protest. She was inspired by an Extinction Rebellion event in Bristol, where she now attends weekly meetings. In a tent next to the pink boat, earnest young men explain to passers-by how rigorous academic study of protests has shown that, to bring about change, at least 3.5% of the population must be mobilised. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Extinction Rebellion presents climate change as a moral, not political, cause but tries to avoid being too preachy. As one flag states, “We live in a toxic system but no one individual is to blame.” There are now around 150 chapters in Britain, from Penwith in Cornwall to Inverness in Scotland. Peaches, an artist and psychotherapy assistant, says the protests “are the first thing that spoke to me that it could make the impact we need.” Other green movements have failed, she adds. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some on the left are turned off by the tactic of using arrests to generate publicity, believing it will alienate those who can’t afford to be jailed. Others point out that lots of anti-fracking protesters were locked up without drawing much public sympathy. Still, there are plenty of volunteers in London. By noon on the second day, 209 people had been arrested in the capital. Organisers will be hoping that translates to lots more activists for the next round of protests. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 03:12:42 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Does economic growth depend on population size?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/04/16/does-economic-growth-depend-on-population-size]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_FND000_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-16T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR CENTURIES prior to the Industrial Revolution, Asia’s massively populous societies made the continent the world’s centre of economic gravity. Industrialisation in Europe and North America in the 19th century briefly knocked it from its perch. But now Asian countries’ collective economic might, measured in real output on a purchasing-power-parity basis, is forecast to account for more than half of global production by 2020. Was the West’s period of dominance an anomaly, which could only ever have been short-lived? Is population destiny?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It stands to reason that countries with larger populations might enjoy long-run economic advantages. People are the raw material of economic growth, after all. The more there are, the greater the likelihood that one becomes a Gutenberg or a Watt. In a world without much international trade, populous countries offer the largest markets, and comparatively more opportunity to boost economic output through specialisation and trade. Projecting economic growth rates is fantastically hard even over very short time horizons; over centuries, it is as good as impossible. But there are worse strategies than betting on the places with the most people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Klaus Desmet of Southern Methodist University, Dávid Krisztián Nagy of CREI, a research institute, and Esteban Rossi-Hansberg of Princeton University do just that. In a paper that last month won them the Robert Lucas prize, which recognises excellent research in political economy, they build a model that yokes economic performance to population size, within which they can run time forward by hundreds of years to watch the balance of economic power change. Long-run growth, they suggest, is driven by improvements in technology. And more populous countries should accumulate more innovation than smaller ones do because the return on developing a new technology is higher—there are more people to buy Edison’s light bulb and to enrich Edison, and therefore more incentive to invent the light bulb in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leaning against this force, however, is migration. Right now, the richest places are not the most populous. Should it become relatively easy to migrate, people will move from countries that are populous but poor to others that are rich. As migration swells the population of rich places, their long-run dominance is assured because of the link between population size and innovation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if there is very little migration, then the populous but poor countries will out-innovate the small but rich ones, and make their way up the income league table. The process is not quick; the authors reckon that convergence takes about 400 years. In practice, rich places tend not to allow much migration from poor ones. That could change, but assuming that it does not, the model delivers a striking forecast: half a millennium from now, Asia and sub-Saharan Africa will have become great engines of productivity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stranger things have happened. A millennium ago real output per person was significantly higher in China than in Britain. To predict that a European backwater would lead the world into the most transformative economic epoch in history would have seemed like madness. Over very long time horizons the world’s poorest places can indeed become the world’s richest, even if it does not happen often.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_FNC746_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190420_FNC746_0.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190420_FNC746_0.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190420_FNC746_0.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190420_FNC746_0.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190420_FNC746_0.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190420_FNC746_0.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190420_FNC746_0.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190420_FNC746_0.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190420_FNC746_0.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, if Britain did not have the upper hand over China 1,000 years ago, it did soon after, at least in terms of real output per person. By 1400 incomes in Britain were meaningfully larger than in China (and higher still in the Netherlands and Italy), according to work by Stephen Broadberry of Oxford University, Hanhui Guan of Peking University and David Daokui Li of Tsinghua University. By 1700 the diverging trajectories of China and north-west Europe were clear (though it was anything but obvious just how much further apart they would become). In other words, population over the past millennium has not been destiny. If China’s and India’s masses did not raise them to prosperity during the past 600 years, what reason is there to believe the future will be different?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More’s the pity&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;It is possible that population is destiny, other things equal, but other things are never equal. And so a plague here, or a fateful decision by a Chinese emperor there, can set a region down a path that wipes out the advantages of population. Perhaps those advantages must be harnessed by the right sorts of institutions, or an accommodating culture—which take far longer to develop or adopt than technologies do to emerge. There is no academic consensus regarding what determines economic fortunes over long time horizons, important though the question is. Alternatively, one might argue that conditions have changed in ways that amplify the power of population. A billion brains seem a more economically potent force in an era of mass education, in contrast to the mass illiteracy that prevailed in the past.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But crucially, Asia’s recent rise has not been the result of a spurt of indigenous innovation given its impetus by the size of its population. Rather, it has happened as part of a wave of globalisation, which aided the transfer of technological know-how. Openness to exchanges of goods and ideas, or indeed to immigration, is not an immutable parameter, but subject to change based on human preferences. Mr Desmet and his co-authors reckon that eliminating all barriers to migration would raise global welfare threefold—an extraordinary figure that reflects yawning differences in output per person between countries, and the unrealised human potential they represent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As intriguing as it is to consider the directions in which macro variables such as population or GDP are likely to nudge the world in coming centuries, it is human decisions that will determine which places and people are given the opportunity to become rich. National populations matter to the extent that borders do. It is a depressing notion, but a plausible one, that in half a millennium’s time they will matter still. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 03:10:35 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why the middle-aged are replacing teenagers in maternity wards]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/04/16/why-the-middle-aged-are-replacing-teenagers-in-maternity-wards]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BRP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-16T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN HER 20S, Claire Fenelon was much too busy to have children. After going to university as a mature student, she spent a year in Australia then a few months in France, picking up the language. “I didn’t want to feel I was missing out,” she says. But by the time she was ready to settle down, she struggled to find the right man. At 39, she froze her eggs. Eight years later and still lacking a partner, she decided to “go solo”, giving birth to a son with the help of a sperm donor. “I was desperate to have kids,” she says. “But I didn’t want to have them with the wrong person.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Fenelon belongs to a small but growing cohort of middle-aged women on maternity wards. As in other rich countries, the overall fertility rate in England and Wales is dwindling. But among women aged 40 and over the conception rate is rising. It jumped by 2.6% in 2017 and has more than doubled since 1990, according to statistics published on April 15th. Meanwhile, at the other end of the age spectrum, an even starker change is afoot. The official figures chart the tenth consecutive annual fall in the rate of teenage pregnancies. Since 2007 the conception rate for 15- to 17-year-old girls has dived by 57%. The conception rates of the youngest and oldest mothers are now close to converging (see chart). Middle-aged maternity may soon be more common than teenage pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BRC726.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190420_BRC726.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190420_BRC726.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190420_BRC726.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190420_BRC726.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190420_BRC726.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190420_BRC726.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190420_BRC726.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190420_BRC726.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190420_BRC726.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Advances in health care help to explain the convergence. Although assisted conception accounts for only a small proportion of pregnancies, it is growing more popular and more successful. Between 1991 and 2016, birth rates from in vitro fertilisation (IVF) treatment increased by more than 85%. In 2016 more than 20,000 babies were born following IVF, a small fraction of the 696,000 births that year. About three-fifths of women who use it are 35 or over. Demand is likely to increase as women learn of others whose treatment has been successful. Ms Fenelon was inspired by a magazine article about egg-freezing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Labour governments of 1997-2010 pioneered a public-health strategy to curb rates of teen pregnancy. Nurses manned separate sexual-health clinics for young people, so teenagers did not run the risk of bumping into their parents at family planning centres. Careers advisers were trained to offer health advice as well as tips about jobs, and social workers and foster carers were encouraged to identify those most at risk of an early pregnancy and talk to them about relationships. Doctors were taught how to insert long-acting reversible contraception, such as implants, which are less prone to human error than condoms or the Pill. A study published in the &lt;em&gt;Lancet&lt;/em&gt;, a medical journal, in 2016 concluded that the strategy had “probably contributed” to the falling under-18 conception rate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But government intervention in England cannot explain why the teenage-pregnancy rate began to fall at roughly the same time in Scotland, which was not covered by the strategy, and also dipped elsewhere in Europe, points out Peter Craig of Glasgow University. And since many women who give birth in their 40s do not rely on assisted conception, social factors must also have played a part. “The best form of contraception is aspiration,” says Penelope Law, a gynaecologist. Women in their teens and 20s are much more likely than in previous generations to prioritise education and work over starting a family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Studies have found that female educational enrolment is strongly associated with delaying cohabitation, marriage and childbirth. In the ten years from 2006, the female higher-education participation rate rose by ten percentage points in England, to 56%. In a survey of women at a family planning clinic in Scotland, a third of those who wanted children cited not being at the right stage in their career or concerns that having children would affect success at work as a reason why they had not yet had a child. Many more said they were “enjoying life as it is” or attributed the delay to issues with their current relationship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the national convergence masks persistent regional divides. The over-40s’ conception rate in London is more than double that in the North East, which has a far higher rate of teenage pregnancy than the capital. In Middlesbrough, a northern town, the rate of teenage conception is 145% above the national average, and ticking up. If opportunities are not spread more evenly across the country, northerners may be left holding the baby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 03:10:34 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spanish general election poll tracker]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/16/spanish-general-election-poll-tracker]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-16T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;

&lt;figure data-infographic- data-infographic-js=&quot;/2019/eu-elections-spain/js/bundle.js&quot; data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/eu-elections-spain/css/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/eu-elections-spain/css/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;O&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;N APRIL&lt;/small&gt; 28th Spain will hold its third general election in almost as many years. Pedro Sánchez, the Socialist prime minister, who presided over a minority government, called the snap election in February after his national budget was rejected in parliament. All 350 seats in Congress and 208 of the 266 seats in the Senate are being contested.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The election has been shaped by the Catalan crisis. The region’s leaders held an unconstitutional referendum on secession in 2017; after they declared “independence”, the national government imposed direct rule and dissolved the Catalan parliament. Though Catalonia’s self-government has since been restored, a dozen separatist leaders are being tried in the Supreme Court on charges punishable by long prison terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The referendum alarmed many Spaniards and contributed to a rightward shift in national politics. It led to a surge in support for Vox, a previously insignificant ultra-conservative party, which is now polling at 11% and could gain as many as 30 seats in Congress. The conservative People’s Party (&lt;small&gt;PP&lt;/small&gt;) joined it in coalition in the southern region of Andalucía, and has sounded more hardline on immigration. Both Pablo Casado, the &lt;small&gt;PP&lt;/small&gt;’s new leader, and Albert Rivera of Ciudadanos, a liberal party, have threatened to impose direct rule on Catalonia, which is likely to increase support for independence. Ciudadanos also responded to Mr Sánchez’s attempts to strike a conciliatory tone with Catalan parliamentarians by ruling out a coalition with the Socialists.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Although Spain’s political right has gained popularity, it has become fractured. That could benefit the Socialists, allowing them to capture some of the &lt;small&gt;PP&lt;/small&gt;’s seats in rural areas. Spain’s system of proportional representation rewards the biggest parties in small provinces.&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;p&gt;If the Socialists can gain more ground, they would hope to form a majority coalition with either Podemos, a leftist populist outfit, or (if it drops its objections) Ciudadanos. But if no government can be formed, Spain will have to hold another election in the autumn. Meanwhile the Catalan crisis, the cause of the political shake-up, rumbles on in the courts.&lt;/p&gt; 

&lt;figure data-infographic- &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p &gt;Source: pollofpolls.eu&lt;br/&gt;
Photo credits: PA; AFP; Rex/Shutterstock; Getty Images &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 03:10:33 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A big week for American banks]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/16/a-big-week-for-american-banks]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/money_talks_11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-16T18:07:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMERICA’S LARGEST banks reported earnings this week. Bank of America’s chief executive, Brian Moynihan, tells Anne McElvoy why he is bullish about the American economy and justifies his pay package. Also, can &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/04/15/a-new-era-at-goldman-sachs-starts-in-the-shadow-of-a-scandal&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs&lt;/a&gt; reinvent itself in the shadow of a scandal? And &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/04/16/tiger-woods-made-our-golf-model-look-silly-have-we-learned-a-lesson&quot;&gt;Tiger Woods’s stroke of genius&lt;/a&gt;—for the business of golf. Simon Long hosts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-bigbanktheory&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id420929545?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/2Yvo8QxZf7WlSEsIwKjtX4&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWVjb25vbWlzdG1vbmV5dGFsa3M&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=18377&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/Business--Economics-Podcasts/The-Economist-Money-Talks-p603831/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 02:06:18 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Supreme Court scrutinises a bar on “scandalous” trademarks]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/04/16/the-supreme-court-scrutinises-a-bar-on-scandalous-trademarks]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_USP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-16T14:53:45Z&quot;&gt;Apr 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 1990, Erik Brunetti (pictured) launched FUCT, an edgy casual-clothing line aimed at twenty-somethings. In 2011, to ward off counterfeiters selling shorts and hats emblazoned with the same four capital letters, Mr Brunetti applied for a trademark from the United States Patent and Trademark Office (PTO). His application was initially approved, but an official then deemed the mark unacceptable because “FUCT is the phonetic equivalent of the word ‘fucked’, the past-tense form of the verb ‘fuck’”. An appeal proved fruitless: the PTO’s appeals-board agreed that FUCT should be denied a trademark due to its “anti-social imagery,” lack of “taste” and themes “of extreme nihilism.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Brunetti’s fight to protect his brand with a trademark reached America’s highest court on April 15th. In grappling with the legal question—does a law permitting the PTO to deny protection to marks that are “immoral, deceptive or scandalous” violate the First Amendment?—the justices and lawyers &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/oral_arguments/argument_transcripts/2018/18-302_7k47.pdf&quot;&gt;studiously avoided&lt;/a&gt; pronouncing the word at issue. Malcolm Stewart, the government lawyer defending the law, offered a clinical description of FUCT as “the equivalent of the profane past-participle form of a well-known word of profanity and perhaps the paradigmatic word of profanity in our language”. Mr Stewart presented the ban on scandalous trademarks as “a valid condition on participation in a federal programme”, not a restriction that violates the freedom of speech guarantee in the First Amendment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast to a prohibition on speech, Mr Stewart said, the Lanham Act (the law at issue) represents “a good accommodation”. Referring to &lt;em&gt;Federal Communications Commission v Pacifica Foundation,&lt;/em&gt; a ruling from 1978 involving broadcast of comedian George Carlin’s “Filthy Words”, he said “people who find the Carlin monologue funny or thought-provoking” can go to his show or buy the DVD, while the profanity will not be forced “upon anybody who finds it offensive”, Likewise, Mr Brunetti can sell his clothing bearing the FUCT logo without enlisting the imprint of the federal government. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several justices seemed uncomfortable with this accommodation. Justice Neil Gorsuch noted “shocking numbers” of trademarks that, it seems, the PTO arbitrarily refused to honour that “look remarkably similar” to marks it granted. When Mr. Stewart began his reply, explaining why a mark spelled P-H-U-C may get the PTO’s blessing, Justice Gorsuch interrupted. “I don&amp;#x27;t want to go through the examples&amp;quot;, he said. &amp;quot;I really don&amp;#x27;t want to do that.” His reponse was understandable. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/DocketPDF/18/18-302/71462/20181108141004942_36908%20pdf%20Sommer.pdf&quot;&gt;briefs&lt;/a&gt; mention that FCUK and FWORD were granted, along with PINK TACO FAN CLUB and I BRAKE FOR COCK!, while the likes of HANDJOB (a nail salon) and FAT COCK BEER (a light lager) were not. Justice Gorsuch, Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg and others seemed worried about the arbitrariness of government officials’ judgments of what counts as “scandalous”. It seems applicants have little idea whether their envelope-pushing marks will run afoul of the Lanham Act; it’s a “flip of the coin”, Justice Gorsuch complained. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet several justices were just as concerned about the implications of a potential win for Mr Brunetti. Justice Stephen Breyer suggested that because a few vulgar and racist words have a “different physiological effect on the brain”, requiring the PTO to trademark them all might inflict harm. Would a Supreme Court decision striking the “scandalous” line from the Lanham Act mean that FUCT and “the racial slur we all know about” would suddenly appear “on every bus where it’s advertised” and on “newsstands in Times Square” where “children and others see it”? No, said John Sommer, Mr Brunetti’s lawyer. Just because a brand has a trademark does not require companies to accept ads featuring the mark. Anyway, Mr Sommer added, “my client&amp;#x27;s goods are not going to be a target at Wal-Mart”. And a case from 2017, &lt;em&gt;Matal v Tam,&lt;/em&gt; had already ruled another section of the Lanham Act unconstitutional: the bar on trademarks that are “disparaging”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chief Justice John Roberts and Justice Samuel Alito pressed the point. Even if FUCT doesn’t suddenly hang on racks at WalMart, the chief noted, it is “going to be on people walking down through the mall”. For parents who hope to “teach their children not to use those kinds of words”, the government’s imprimatur via the trademark is counterproductive. The registration of the mark “will facilitate its use in commerce” even if it is only sold, as FUCT is, on the internet. Justice Alito fretted that “really dirty words” would be quickly snatched up by potty-mouthed retailers seeking trademark registrations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Judging from the oral argument,&lt;em&gt; Iancu v Brunetti&lt;/em&gt; may be a close call. The justices tend to be protective of free speech, but the prospect of patent-office officials forced to approve vulgar or racist trademarks makes them queasy—perhaps for good reason. In his final minutes at the podium, Mr Stewart noted that in the wake of &lt;em&gt;Matal&lt;/em&gt;, the patent office no longer rejects trademarks just because they include perceived racial slurs. But applications that include a reference to “the single-most offensive racial slur”—the n-word, presumably—have been put on hold pending the court’s ruling in &lt;em&gt;Iancu&lt;/em&gt;.  The decision should arrive by the end of June, whether to cheers or curses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(此域名已被污染，谢谢大家一直以来的支持)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 01:06:18 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The right-wing Finns Party does well in Finland’s election]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/16/the-right-wing-finns-party-does-well-in-finlands-election]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_EUP002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-16T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE FINNS are the happiest nation in the world, according to the United Nations, and tied with Sweden and Norway for the freest, according to Freedom House. They are also at or near the top in education, not to mention consumption of coffee. But after the national election on April 14th, they have given up their claim to have solved the problem of far-right populism. The Finns Party (PS), an anti-immigrant, Eurosceptic party previously known in English as the True Finns, surged in the final weeks and took 17.5% of the vote, just a whisker behind the winning Social Democrats (SDP) at 17.7%. The SDP will probably now form a centre-left government, but as in so much of Europe, the far right’s strength will make things complicated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The PS’s result was almost exactly the same as in 2015. But after that election, the country’s centre-right National Coalition and Centre parties thought they had tamed the populists by bringing them into the ruling coalition, forcing them to take responsibility for compromises such as observing EU migration policy. Indeed, in 2017 the PS’s frustrated hard-liners quit the government while its more moderate MPs (including the then-leader) split off into a new faction called Blue Reform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet in the election, the PS’s voters backed the party’s old stalwarts, while Blue Reform failed to win any seats. As a result, the PS is now as strong as ever, and more extreme. Its new leader once wrote blog posts affirming racial differences in intelligence and hoping that left-wing female politicians would be raped by migrants. The party’s campaign video (a still from which is pictured above) is a short horror film, in which the people’s fury congeals into a “pissed-off monster” who attacks the country’s masked and traitorous leaders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other parties say they will not negotiate with PS. Antti Rinne, the SDP’s leader, will try to build a coalition that matches the electorate’s move to the left after four years of centre-right rule. His most likely partners are the Greens, who also did well, and the liberal National Coalition. In terms of policy, the leftward shift may be modest. All parties but PS agree on the goal of making the country carbon-neutral by 2035. Extensive hydropower and nuclear energy make this realistic. (Still, notes Ilkka Haavisto of EVA, a think-tank, the PS implied that the government wanted to ban cars.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other big challenge before the next government is benefit reform. The country is moving towards an active, Danish-style employment policy aimed at returning the jobless to work, but the last government demanded that the unemployed find work or training within a short deadline or face cuts in their stipends.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was too harsh, says Joonas Rahkola, head of the SDP’s policy unit. “People have a sense of unfairness, and are insecure about their future.” The party wants to raise the education and elder-care budgets. It should also push companies to sign better contracts with flexworkers, says Hannu Jouhki, head of the country’s trade-union association. Insecure job conditions, he says, can push voters towards populism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As elsewhere in Europe, the election leaves Finland’s parliament more fragmented. It is harder for mainstream parties to form majorities when populists take a sixth or more of the vote. Last week, across the Gulf of Finland in Estonia, the ruling Centre Party broke its campaign promise and cut a coalition deal that included the far-right EKRE party. The centrist Reform party, which finished first in the election in March but lost its chance to form a government, reacted furiously. In Finland, the reaction was more phlegmatic. The Finns have already tried that approach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 01:06:17 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cathedrals are neglected in much of Europe]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/04/16/cathedrals-are-neglected-in-much-of-europe]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BLP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-16T14:06:05Z&quot;&gt;Apr 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE CATHEDRAL of Notre Dame in Paris, and the vast outpouring of sorrow over its semi-destruction by fire on April 15th, epitomises the power of great houses of prayer to touch and inspire people. More palpably than any other kind of monument, they connect visitors with another world: one in which the finest composers, singers, sculptors, glass-makers, embroiderers and craft-workers of a given era joyfully mixed their energies in a vast, disinterested enterprise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To some degree, that enterprise continues as long as the building stands. That alone makes great historic churches a source of fascination, even for those with little interest in Christian worship. People want them to be there, even if they don’t wish to share the cost or join the prayers.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In almost every country in Europe, that creates an acute problem. The cost of maintaining the delicate stone fabric of a cathedral seems to rise geometrically, far out-stripping the ability of small congregations to sustain them. Governments and other secular bodies are minded to help but they also feel compelled, in most places, to respect the independence of the buildings’ historic stewards, in other words the churches.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In England, the established church boasts 42 cathedrals (technically defined as the seat of a bishop), of which 39 are listed as historic buildings whose preservation is both mandated by law and entitled to some public help. (About 12,000 of the 16,000 other places of worship controlled by the Church of England are also listed.) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Church of England likes to call the cathedrals one of its “success stories” with rising numbers of worshippers and visitors, and growing revenue. But as a recent report led by a bishop delicately put it, “recent failures of governance and management within a small number of cathedrals have highlighted vulnerabilities across the sector…” In plain language, at least two cathedrals have run into severe financial difficulties, which better stewardship might have avoided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;English cathedrals are relatively independent bodies, run by a cleric known as a dean who relies on a group of advisers known as a chapter. They are free to raise money in many ways, from concerts to exhibitions to simply charging an admission fee, as about a quarter of them do. In recent weeks Derby Cathedral raised eyebrows by hosting films that included graphic sex scenes and depictions of paganism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Churches in Germany have an advantage. The system of religious taxes (under which people of Catholic or Lutheran heritage pay a levy to their respective denominations) has ensured an ample income stream. Germany’s religious masters have done better at hauling in revenue than at retaining worshippers, the figures would suggest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But a massive fund-raising effort, drawing in generous private-sector donors and ordinary well-wishers in Germany and Britain, was needed for one of the biggest church reconstruction projects of modern times: the rebuilding of the Frauenkirche in Dresden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This showpiece of German Baroque was destroyed, along with much of the city, in a British bombing raid in February 1945. The project, completed in 2005, was a complement to the erection in 1962 of a new cathedral in Coventry, replacing the one wrecked by a German air raid on the English Midlands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most European states subsidise their historically dominant Christian denominations, directly or indirectly, while also leaving the sects’ religious masters relatively autonomous. In Italy, despite the notional separation of Catholic church and state, the two are deeply intertwined, through tax breaks and state help for maintaining the artistic heritage which is one of Italy’s greatest tourist draws. Belgium offers generous help to all its main religions, but Catholic cathedrals still charge stiff admission fees as though they were museums.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In church-state relations, France is an outlier. Under the regime of laïcité, or strict secularism, municipalities took over formal responsibility for Catholic churches; clerics and their congregations are merely users. And clerics, in particular, are thin on the ground. In rural France, it is common for a priest to look after 30 old churches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That paucity of active users prompts municipal authorities to assign a low priority to conserving church buildings. In 2013 a huge neo-Gothic church in the northern French town of Abbeville was dramatically demolished by municipal leaders, who said the place was a safety hazard and too expensive to repair. Hundreds of other French churches may soon have a similar fate. Nor have France’s state authorities done very well at protecting houses of prayer from a wave of vandalism, including arson and desecration, that has afflicted them this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, all over western Europe, churches are closing for lack of worshippers. In the Netherlands, a cardinal predicted in 2013 that two-thirds of the Roman Catholic churches in the country would shut by 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But a diametrically opposing trend is at work further east in Europe. Perhaps the most spectacular act of church reconstruction of recent times was the re-erection of Moscow’s Cathedral of Christ the Saviour, which was dynamited by Stalin in 1931 and thrown back up over five years starting in 1995. It was rebuilt in about a tenth of the time needed for the original construction.&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere in Russia, under a crash building programme decreed by the Russian Orthodox church, at least three new churches are said to be opening per day. And in other parts of central and eastern Europe, from Serbia to Georgia, vast new Orthodox churches now adorn capital cities which were already endowed with many places of prayer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, the Russian church building spree extends far beyond the borders of the motherland. Anyone who takes a short walk along the banks of the Seine from the wreckage of Notre Dame will soon see a boldly modernistic structure, topped with onion domes: this “spiritual and cultural” centre, opened in 2016, was a pet project of President Vladimir Putin’s. It competes hard with an older Russian-style cathedral in Paris which the Muscovite authorities, to their frustration, do not control. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the Russian state media were eager to point out, western Europe is gaining some new Christian places of worship even as many others are destroyed, accidentally or otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;See also&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/15/a-terrible-blaze-devastates-notre-dame-cathedral&quot;&gt;A terrible blaze devastates Notre Dame cathedral (April 15th 2019)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(此域名已被污染，谢谢大家一直以来的支持)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:06:53 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>