<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[“Bacurau”, a violent new film, takes aim at Brazil’s leadership]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/17/bacurau-a-violent-new-film-takes-aim-at-brazils-leadership]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BKP511.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-17T16:12:10Z&quot;&gt;May 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 2018, when Jair Bolsonaro won Brazil’s presidential election, outside observers feared that his proposed public-spending cuts would hurt the country’s creative sector—particularly the film industry, which relies on state funding and tax incentives. Mr Bolsonaro has already subsumed the ministry of culture into a more general “ministry of citizenship”, but the full effects of his policies are yet to be felt. The country is currently enjoying a robust presence at the Cannes film festival, with five movies chosen for the “official selection”. The most interesting and prominent is “Bacurau”, a Western which had its premiere on May 15th. It deploys the conventions of survivalist and militaristic action films to criticise not just Brazil’s current leadership, but all those in power with authoritarian tendencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Set in the near future, “Bacurau” opens in a fictional separatist and self-sufficient town of that name in Brazil’s mountainous interior. The inhabitants live mostly in harmony, sharing resources, paying their respects when a beloved elderly matriarch dies and taking it in turns to keep watch over the only road to the outside world. The early scenes are realistic and richly drawn, with petty squabbles and rekindled love affairs; more unusual is that the local folk routinely take psychotropic drugs, which do not produce any obvious hallucinations but do seem to heighten the senses and bind the community together. “Make the most of life,” one elder proclaims, “for as long as we have life.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For how long will that be? The mayor of the surrounding region, a flashy strongman type named Tony Jr. (Thardelly Lima), has cut off Bacurau’s water supply in a bid to assert control. He rolls through the small town as part of his election campaign, bearing “gifts” like a truck full of second-hand books which are dumped into the dirt. Then comes a larger conspiracy to literally erase Bacurau from the map—as its inhabitants discover when they try to find their home on Google and GPS systems—and soon mobile phones lose signal, too. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most ominous is the arrival in Bacurau of a paramilitary group. Tellingly, they hail not from Brazil but from America. They could be hired mercenary forces or, as their amateurish behaviour indicates, tourists who want to hunt humans for sport. But the distinction hardly matters: they behave as racist psychopaths, lusting for blood and taking pleasure in their kill counts. When they can’t find anyone else to shoot, they shoot each other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although “Bacurau” was in the works for a decade before Mr Bolsonaro’s election, the film’s content &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.apnews.com/30ffa13a136049de87e56a8e7e2e5a77&quot;&gt;became more extreme&lt;/a&gt; as Brazil’s political climate darkened, to match an atmosphere that Kleber Mendonça Filho and Juliano Dornelles, the film-makers, have described as “like a dystopia”. The president has said that left-wing “outlaws” should “be banished from our homeland”, but “Bacurau” makes heroes of outlaws, redefining the relationship between individuals, their homeland and the nation that claims them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such themes are familiar from Mr Filho’s two previous narrative features, “Neighboring Sounds” (2012) and “Aquarius” (2016), which told stories of opposition to the encroachment of modernity in the Brazilian coastal community of Recife. “Bacurau” is less driven by human drama, preferring as it does the surreal violence of a genre movie. Once the villagers take up arms—energised by their pharmaceuticals—the film has the feel of “Red Dawn” if it were set in the fictional town of Macondo from Gabriel García Márquez’s “One Hundred Years of Solitude”. In order to respond to the existential threats, the community mines its own history for battle tactics and weaponry (a key scene features the local museum). “Bacurau” tells a globalised audience as much as a Brazilian one that victory over tyranny must come from within.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 23:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Everybody believed what he said, and investors followed him”—Abraaj’s downfall]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/17/everybody-believed-what-he-said-and-investors-followed-him-abraajs-downfall]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_blm514.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-17T11:50:11Z&quot;&gt;May 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not long ago, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/18/the-biggest-collapse-in-private-equity-history-will-have-a-lasting-impact&quot;&gt;Abraaj&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; was one of the world’s highest-profile private-equity firms. We take a look at its spectacular downfall, and the fate of its charismatic boss, Arif Naqvi. This weekend &lt;strong&gt;Australian &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/11/australias-voters-are-poised-to-punish-the-government&quot;&gt;voters&lt;/a&gt; will elect a new parliament&lt;/strong&gt;. How can politicians win back a disillusioned electorate? And why do &lt;strong&gt;sausages&lt;/strong&gt; feature so strongly on voting day? Runtime: 21min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/privateiniquity-theabraajcase&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 22:40:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Supreme Court could hear another gay wedding cake case]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/17/the-supreme-court-could-hear-another-gay-wedding-cake-case]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_USP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-17T08:46:33Z&quot;&gt;May 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN RECENT years, the Supreme Court has made a habit of waving a gavel and turning blockbuster cases into duds. In the last year, two great reckonings—a pair of challenges to partisan gerrymandering and a tiff over a Colorado baker who refused to make a cake celebrating a gay wedding—were both defused with narrow rulings that steered around the heart of the disputes. The strategy of avoidance has its virtues: contentious questions continue to be asked, discussions advance. But as Brett Kavanaugh noted in another context during his Senate confirmation hearing last autumn, “what comes around goes around”. The questions often end up back in the justices’ laps. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That seems to be the case with gay-wedding cakes. Last June, the Supreme Court &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2018/06/05/the-supreme-courts-artful-dodge-over-gay-wedding-cakes&quot;&gt;flicked away&lt;/a&gt; &lt;em&gt;Masterpiece Cakeshop v Colorado Civil Rights Commission&lt;/em&gt; with an artful dodge. Rather than address the fundamental conflict—anti-discrimination protections for gay people rubbing up against business owners’ First Amendment claims to run their shops in line with their conscience—seven justices found an escape route. The trouble with Colorado’s Civil Rights Commission wasn’t its decision to enforce the state’s public-accommodations law against the Christian baker who had turned away two men. The constitutional violation lay in hostility vocalised by two of the civil-rights commissioners against the baker during their deliberations. The Christian cake artist was deprived of a commission that was “neutral” and “tolerant” of his faith, Justice Anthony Kennedy wrote. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By pinning the First Amendment harm on a pair of purportedly anti-religious messages, Justice Kennedy made the decision about procedure, not substance. He avoided addressing the constitutionality of the decision to require the baker to make cakes for all comers. That question, he wrote, will have to be resolved “in the future” when similar cases arise. The future may be now. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2013, Rachel Cryer and her mother walked into Sweetcakes By Melissa, a bakery in Gresham, Oregon. They wanted to order a custom wedding cake for Rachel and her fiancée, Laurel Bowman. But when Aaron Klein, the proprietor, heard the cake was for two women, according to the bakery’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/DocketPDF/18/18-547/67534/20181019155709188_Klein%20Cert%20Petition.pdf&quot;&gt;petition&lt;/a&gt;, he “apologised and said that, because of their religious beliefs, he and his wife could not create a custom-designed cake for that purpose”. The Kleins serve gay customers but will not make them wedding cakes because they “do not believe that other types of interpersonal unions are marriages, and they believe it is sinful to celebrate them as such”. Mr Klein cited a line from Leviticus that gay relations are “an abomination”, a comment Ms Cryer’s mother reported to her daughter, who was already in the car. Ms Cryer and Ms Bowman both “experienced emotional distress”, their &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/DocketPDF/18/18-547/81680/20190125113544928_KLEIN%20Brief%2018-547%20Melissa.pdf&quot;&gt;brief&lt;/a&gt; reports, and Rachel “no longer wanted to participate in the planning of her wedding because of the constant fear that she would again be refused service based on her sexual orientation”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The couple then complained to Oregon’s Bureau of Labour and Industries, which found that the Kleins had violated the state law requiring “full and equal accommodations, advantages, facilities and privileges of any place of public accommodation, without any distinction, discrimination or restriction on account of sexual orientation”. The fine was hefty—$135,000—and Sweetcakes soon went out of business. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The complaints the petitioners raise in &lt;em&gt;Klein v. Oregon Bureau of Labour and Industries &lt;/em&gt;are familiar. It is a violation of free speech and freedom of religion, they argue, to coerce a business owner to contravene his conscience. But the Kleins take their case one significant step further than Jack Phillips (the Colorado baker) did in &lt;em&gt;Masterpiece Cakeshop&lt;/em&gt;: they are asking the Supreme Court to overrule &lt;em&gt;Employment Division v Smith,&lt;/em&gt; a 5-4 ruling written by the late Justice Antonin Scalia in 1990. In &lt;em&gt;Smith&lt;/em&gt;, Mr Scalia disappointed two members of the Native American Church who were fired from their jobs for taking peyote, a hallucinogen used in their religious rituals. The church members have no right to unemployment compensation, Mr Scalia concluded, since they were sacked for breaking the law. As Oregon’s drug laws were “neutral” and “generally applicable” and did not target any particular religion, they did not violate the constitution. Mere incidental burdens on one’s religious practice are inevitable and cannot be considered infringements on religious liberty. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Smith&lt;/em&gt; was unpopular, and Congress soon passed the Religious Freedom Restoration Act (RFRA) to restore a higher level of protection for religious free exercise. The Supreme Court partially struck down RFRA in 1997, finding its strictures with regard to state governments to exceed Congress’s power. The upshot: the law continues to bind the federal government but no longer limits the power of states to impinge on the religious lives of its inhabitants. So in line with &lt;em&gt;Smith&lt;/em&gt;, the Oregon Court of Appeals &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://casetext.com/case/klein-v-or-bureau-of-labor-indus-1&quot;&gt;rejected&lt;/a&gt; the Sweetcakes owners’ religious liberty claim. The fine “does not impermissibly burden the Kleins&amp;#x27; right to the free exercise”, the court held, “because it simply requires their compliance with a neutral law of general applicability, and the Kleins have made no showing that the state targeted them for enforcement because of their religious beliefs”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many commentators and several justices have had unkind words for &lt;em&gt;Smith&lt;/em&gt; over the years. In his &lt;em&gt;Masterpiece Cakeshop&lt;/em&gt; concurrence, Justice Neil Gorsuch (who sits in the &lt;em&gt;Smith&lt;/em&gt; author’s old chair) wrote “&lt;em&gt;Smith&lt;/em&gt; remains controversial in many quarters”. And in January, Justice Samuel Alito (joined by Justices Gorsuch, Kavanaugh and Clarence Thomas) &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/18pdf/18-12_d18e.pdf&quot;&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt; the decision “drastically cut back on the protection provided by the Free Exercise Clause”. &lt;em&gt;Smith&lt;/em&gt; is an “anomaly”, the Kleins say, and should be abandoned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a season when the court is showing new vigour for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2018/07/19/how-the-decline-of-unions-will-change-america&quot;&gt;overturning&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.scotusblog.com/case-files/cases/south-dakota-v-wayfair-inc/&quot;&gt;precedent&lt;/a&gt; (prompting an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/18pdf/17-1299_8njq.pdf&quot;&gt;outcry&lt;/a&gt; from Justice Stephen Breyer on May 13th), several justices may be seriously be thinking about granting a hearing to &lt;em&gt;Klein&lt;/em&gt; to add &lt;em&gt;Smith&lt;/em&gt; to the ash heap of abandoned rulings. But the Supreme Court has been tarrying on whether to take the case onto its docket. At the justices&amp;#x27; private conference on May 16th, &lt;em&gt;Klein&lt;/em&gt; appeared on the “discuss list” for the ninth time since the beginning of March. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 22:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The businesses that benefit from sanctions, the struggle against the Taliban, and Senegal&#x27;s fancy sheep]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/16/the-businesses-that-benefit-from-sanctions-the-struggle-against-the-taliban-and-senegals-fancy-sheep]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_5.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-16T17:12:13Z&quot;&gt;May 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A selection of three essential articles read aloud from the latest issue of The Economist. This week, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/16/a-new-kind-of-cold-war&quot;&gt;proliferating sanctions&lt;/a&gt; create both risks and unexpected business &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/18/sanctions-create-business-risks-and-opportunities&quot;&gt;opportunities&lt;/a&gt;. Why the feeble Afghan government is losing the war against the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/18/why-afghanistans-government-is-losing-the-war-with-the-taliban&quot;&gt;Taliban&lt;/a&gt; (10:23). And a tale of golden fleeces: why people in Senegal pay a fortune for fancy &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/18/why-people-in-senegal-pay-a-fortune-for-fancy-sheep&quot;&gt;sheep&lt;/a&gt; (20:19). Runtime: 23 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-may16th2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 08:24:49 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why San Francisco banned the use of facial-recognition technology]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/16/why-san-francisco-banned-the-use-of-facial-recognition-technology]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_USP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-16T16:58:37Z&quot;&gt;May 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON MAY 14th, San Francisco’s legislature voted to ban city agencies from using facial-recognition technology. Leading the charge was Aaron Peskin, a member of the city&amp;#x27;s Board of Supervisors, the legislative body. In January, when he introduced the measure, he said he had “yet to be persuaded that there is any beneficial use of this technology that outweighs the potential for government actors to use it for coercive and oppressive ends.” That argument proved compelling. Just one of the city’s nine supervisors opposed the ban (though she acknowledged it was “a well-intended piece of legislation”) and the mayor will probably soon sign it into law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The measure does not ban private citizens or businesses from using facial=recognition technology, or from sharing with police what any facial-recognition enabled cameras gather, subject to board approval. Taylor Swift used the technology to identify stalkers; stadiums have used it to identify banned fans and people transmitting data to bookies. Both of those uses remain legal in San Francisco. The bill does not prevent the technology’s use at airports and ports, which are federally regulated. Nor will anyone who is already using it have to stop: San Francisco’s police department has not deployed it. The ban is designed not to stop abuses, but to prevent them, and to ensure that citizens have a voice in how they are watched and policed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The potential for abuse is vast. Technology such as facial-recognition cameras and automatic licence-plate readers can gather images constantly and store them indefinitely. They make surveillance cheap and invisible. Compiling a record of, say, everyone who walks or drives past a given intersection over the course of a day no longer requires teams of police officers to stand on the corner noting what they see. That type of surveillance costs money and manpower, and lets people see that they are being seen. Cameras atop light-posts are effectively invisible (generally, people only see them when they look for them), always on and feed images into a searchable database where they can reside forever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some may shrug, believing that since their phones already track them, and their social-media accounts provide a record of their preferences, travel, and in many cases political beliefs, one more incursion on their privacy does not amount to much. But facial-recognition technology is rather different. A person can choose to leave their phone at home, or delete their social-media accounts. To avoid being tracked in a city blanketed with facial-recognition cameras, they would have to stay home. As pro-police as most Americans are, most would probably prefer to be able to cross the street without the government knowing exactly where and when they did so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What this type of technology really imperils is the space for disobedience built into any humane system of laws. It narrows—and makes possible it possible to eliminate—a tension: on one hand, people want laws to be enforced consistently and impartially, as they should. But they also do not want to be fined every time they jaywalk or exceed the speed limit. Anyone inclined to scoff at the notion of governments enforcing all the laws all of the time should bear in mind how local governments&amp;#x27; budgets depend on fines and fees from on their citizens. That sort of enforcement may not happen tomorrow, but facial-recognition enabled cameras make it possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America is not yet at that point. Facial-recognition is not currently widely used. It is reported not to work especially well in non-controlled settings—it cannot always compare and identify people at odd angles, in motion and under bad lighting. It grows less accurate as a database gets larger, and it is especially bad at accurately identifying non-white people. But it is getting better and more popular.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most places are neither as tech-savvy nor as liberal as San Francisco and they may not support an outright ban. But other places should take a hard look at the other mandate enacted by San Francisco’s legislation. It requires city agencies to obtain approval from the city’s board of supervisors before they buy any surveillance technology, to write policies governing its use and to report annually on how often and why they used it. It does not bar agencies from obtaining the technology they deem appropriate; it just prevents them from doing so in secret.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This sort of oversight should be routine. But it is rare. Just nine cities (and one county) have similar ordinances on the books, with roughly another two dozen cities and states considering them. Banning technology that the police want might be a step too far for some cities. But ensuring that those empowered to kill and arrest in the community’s name must be accountable to the community is not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 08:24:48 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alexis Tsipras sails into a social media storm in Greece]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/16/alexis-tsipras-sails-into-a-social-media-storm-in-greece]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_eup503_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-16T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;ALEXIS TSIPRAS has been talking up his left-wing credentials as he campaigns for the European parliament election on May 26th, which is widely seen as a test run for a Greek general election due by late October. In speeches, the prime minister makes a point of distancing the ruling Syriza party from the corrupt, high-living elite he blames for plunging the country into an unprecedented eight-year recession.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Last week, though, Mr Tsipras took a roasting on social media: photos of him lounging on an Athens tycoon’s yacht last August appeared on scores of Greek websites. The premier’s unannounced holiday was also criticised as disrespectful to the memory of 102 people who had been killed in a devastating forest fire the previous month. Many of the deaths could have been prevented, investigators argued, were it not for bungling by the police and the fire service.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Some Syriza aides worry that Mr Tsipras is losing touch with voters. He recently spent a week on a leisurely campaign tour on Crete with Pavlos Polakis, the outspoken deputy health minister. Many Greeks were shocked when Mr Polakis blasted a young, wheelchair-bound psychiatrist, a European parliament candidate with the opposition New Democracy party, for using procedures intended for people with special needs to get a job at a state hospital. He ignored calls to apologise from  cabinet colleagues. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Mr Tsipras shrugged off the incident, calling Mr Polakis “a blunt-spoken islander”. When Kyriakos Mitsotakis, the leader of New Democracy, demanded a parliamentary vote to censure him, the prime minister raised the stakes by calling for a vote of confidence in his minority Syriza government.   &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Syriza survived that vote  thanks to backing from right-wing and independent MPs. It helped, too, that Mr Tsipras announced a pre-election economic package worth around €1bn ($1.1bn) during the confidence debate, to be delivered before May 26th. A one-off payment to pensioners will cost €800m, while a huge cut of 11 percentage points in value added tax, from 24% to 13%, on food and drink served in cafes and restaurants will reduce revenues by an estimated €600m. Mr Tsipras has already postponed a commitment to Greece’s creditors, the EU and the International Monetary Fund, to lower the income-tax threshold. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Syriza is still trailing New Democracy by a wide margin, according to opinion polls. But two polls published last week showed the gap shrinking from 8-9 points to 6-7 points. Voters are unfazed by Mr Tsipras’ choice of holiday companions, it seems, if he comes up with tax breaks and generous handout.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2019 08:24:47 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[An artist revisits famous images from the Kosovo war]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/16/an-artist-revisits-famous-images-from-the-kosovo-war]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BKP510.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-16T15:48:13Z&quot;&gt;May 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A MAN looks beyond the camera, his eyes imploring and filled with tears. He holds up his wallet, showing two passport-sized photographs of young children—they are standing against a standard studio background and smiling. The man has been recently moved from a prison where he was brutally tortured; his face is red, evidence of the boiling water that has been thrown on him. It is a tragic image, taken in 1999 by Peter Turnley, a photojournalist who was documenting the Kosovo war. An estimated 13,500 people were killed or went missing during the conflict, which lasted from February 1998 to June 1999; it is thought to have caused &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC1446925/&quot;&gt;one of the largest population displacements in Europe since the second world war&lt;/a&gt;. Photographs such as this one communicated the personal suffering behind the headlines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Marking the 20th anniversary of the end of the war, Alban Muja, a Kosovan artist, has made three of these images the starting point of an installation at the Venice Biennale. In three films, entitled “Family Album”, he interviews four child refugees, now adults, who were the subject of the photos. Lit against a dark background, the participants discuss their flight from Kosovo, the moment the photo was taken and the impact that its dissemination had on their families. “We asked them to describe the image, but through the image, they talk about what their family experienced,” Mr Muja says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp509.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp509.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp509.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp509.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp509.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp509.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp509.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp509.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp509.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp509.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the photos were published internationally, they became equally well-known in Kosovo itself, and all of the interviewees mention the strange kind of fame they achieved in their home country. Agim, at two years old, was pictured being passed through a barbed wire fence in a photo taken by Carol Guzy, a Pulitzer prize-winning journalist. He explains that he was uninterested in the image as a child—although his parents talked about it constantly—but was surprised to see it printed on a billboard. Whether they liked it or not, these children’s faces became part of history and of their country’s self-conception after independence was declared in 2008.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This formed part of the impetus for “Family Album”: Mr Muja wanted to offer these individuals some agency. Besa was pictured swaddled in blankets and breastfeeding from her mother at only six months old, a long line of refugees snaking out behind them. Besim and Jehona, the two children separated from their father (they reunited with him in Mitrovica after the war), discovered that the photograph was being given away as part of a NATO-themed collectible series from a chewing-gum brand. “Our idea was to focus totally on their story, to give the attention completely to them,” Mr Muja says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp507.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp507.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp507.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp507.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp507.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp507.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp507.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp507.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp507.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;Aged 18, the artist himself fled the violence in Kosovo for a refugee camp in Spain: the official opening date of the exhibition was chosen to coincide with the night his family left their home. It was a photo in the family album (pictured) that sparked his interest in this project to begin with: a snapshot of Mr Muja with José María Aznar, the Spanish prime minister at the time, who was visiting the camp. “When I was nominated for the [Kosovan] pavilion, I was sure I was going to start from that image,” he says. “But I thought it would be much more important if I were to go beyond that, not only telling my personal story, but to research other images.”&lt;p&gt;This strategy is particularly notable at this year’s Biennale, where Christian Büchel, a Swiss-Icelandic artist, has been &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.nytimes.com/2019/05/06/arts/design/migrant-boat-venice-biennale-christian-buchel.html&quot;&gt;making headlines&lt;/a&gt; with his installation in a former shipyards. “Barca Nostra” exhibits the remains of a fishing vessel that capsized in 2015, killing hundreds of migrants who had packed into its hull. However, monumental and soulless, Mr Büchel’s work does little to help a privileged Western audience reconsider the struggles of migrants. Mr Muja’s work, by contrast, rejects spectacle in favour of refugees’ voices. It forces the viewer to consider how the images shown in the news affect those who are portrayed in them. “The idea was not just to talk about only the Kosovo war, to address something that is happening even now as well,” Mr Muja says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Family Album” continues at the Republic of Kosovo Pavilion at the Venice Biennale until November 24th&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 23:43:07 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Democracy is floundering: we need to fix it or lose it]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/05/16/democracy-is-floundering-we-need-to-fix-it-or-lose-it]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_OPP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-16T12:47:45Z&quot;&gt;May 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE WORLD may turn bleak without good governance. “A new dark age could descend in some regions where tyrants abuse their subjects and where jihadists or criminal gangs roam freely to terrorise dispossessed populations.” Or so say Nathan Gardels and Nicolas Berggruen in “Renovating Democracy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The book is a romp through all that’s going wrong with politics, from populists on the rise, robots stealing jobs, climate change being ignored and technocrats bereft of fresh ideas. Helpfully, the pair focus on solutions, from “universal basic capital” (financial support from the state so people invest) to finding common ground between China and America to ensure stability. Without this accord, they foresee “swaths of pandemonium” that “surround gated outposts that are linked to one another but [are] divorced from their planetary hinterland in a kind of global apartheid system.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s sobering stuff, and from an unlikely source. Mr Berggruen is a billionaire investor who has parlayed his wealth into a foundation, the Berggruen Institute, that supports good governance and big ideas. Mr Gardels is a co-founder of the institute and the editor of its media offshoot, The WorldPost. The Economist’s Open Future initiative questioned the authors in a short interview. It is followed by an excerpt from the book, on relations between China and America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; *   &lt;span &gt; &lt;/span&gt;*   &lt;span &gt; &lt;/span&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: You argue that we need to &amp;quot;renovate democracy.&amp;quot; But another way to see things is that democracy is working just fine, it’s just that the outcomes don&amp;#x27;t appeal to comfortable cosmopolitans... What makes you convinced that democracy is broken?&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp503.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp503.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp503.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp503.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp503.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp503.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp503.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp503.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp503.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nathan Gardels and Nicolas Berggruen:&lt;/strong&gt; Well, what we are seeing is the result of elections. But democracy is as much about what happens outside the ballot box: impartial rules, practices, institutions—and political culture—that are not only inclusive, but that foster the reasoned discourse, negotiation and compromise necessary to reach a governing consensus in diverse societies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In recent decades this system has decayed. The mainstream political parties were captured by the organised special interests of an insider establishment that failed to address the dislocations of globalisation and disruptions of rapid technological change. This led to a deep distrust of governing institutions by all those left behind. Such disaffection gained more traction than ever before because of the participatory power of social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When an unresponsive elite forsakes the average citizen in a system legitimated by popular sovereignty—and fortified by social media—demagogues who fashion themselves as tribunes of the people ride the rage to power. Thus the Brexiteers and Trump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The danger now is that the fevered populists are throwing the baby out with the bathwater, assaulting the very norms and institutional checks and balances that guarantee the enduring survival of republics. The revolt against a moribund political class has transmuted into a revolt against governance itself. The result is protracted polarisation and paralysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The chief challenge now is not for partisans to put their teams back in power through elections, but to mend the breach of distrust between the institutions of self-government and the public. This can be done by integrating social networks and more direct democracy into the system. It needs to be “mediated” by new, deliberative practices that complement representative government and compensate for its waning legitimacy. In our book we call this “participation without populism.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To take but one example, if such a platform for citizen’s deliberation linked to a public vote had been in place before the Brexit referendum, all the consequences we now know would have been aired and the outcome would have been different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Messrs Gardels and Berggruen: The point here is that, as digital capitalism divorces employment and income from productivity growth and wealth creation, making a living through gainful work will diminish. The best way to address inequality then is to spread the equity around by fostering an ownership share by all in companies where productivity growth is driven by intelligent machines that displace jobs. The aim is to enhance the skills and assets of the less well off in the first place—that is, “pre-distribution”—instead of only redistributing the wealth of others after the fact. We call this universal basic capital in the book.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: Among your solutions to the problems of wealth inequality is a scheme for people to own an equity stake in the robots that will run tomorrow&amp;#x27;s economy. How would that work?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Messrs Gardels and Berggruen:&lt;/strong&gt; The point here is that, as digital capitalism divorces employment and income from productivity growth and wealth creation, making a living through gainful work will diminish. The best way to address inequality then is to spread the equity around by fostering an ownership share by all in companies where productivity growth is driven by intelligent machines that displace jobs. The aim is to enhance the skills and assets of the less well off in the first place—that is, “pre-distribution”—instead of only redistributing the wealth of others after the fact. We call this universal basic capital in the book.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This can be done in a conventional way through savings accounts in which all participate who are invested in mutual-fund-type instruments. “Platform cooperatives” are another way: for example, everyone in a neighborhood could own a piece of ride-sharing services that operate there, or those who share their personal medical data would get a royalty payment from pharmaceutical inventions based on that data. The public could be assigned equity shares of any IPO by companies that benefited from publicly funded R&amp;amp;D. Another way, as California Governor Gavin Newsom has proposed, is a “data dividend” for the use of your personal data by big tech.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;T&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;he Economist: You call for a pact between America and China to ensure global order. What is the role of Europe in this world? Will Africa and Latin America need to &amp;quot;choose sides,&amp;quot; so to speak?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Messrs Gardels and Berggruen:&lt;/strong&gt; The return of China to centre stage, not least through its Belt and Road initiative that will revitalise Eurasia, shifts the centre of gravity of the world order eastward. To maintain a civilisational presence in this new constellation, the bond between America and Europe is more important than ever. In a way, China’s rise forges a new common identity for the West.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; At the same time, within this common identity, Europe’s social model can soften the harsher edges of America’s free-for-all market mentality. For example, it has already done so on digital privacy and leading the way on “flexicurity” policies, as some Nordic nations have, that protect workers instead of jobs through universal social benefits not linked to employment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; If things are left to float as they presently are, Latin America, and Africa in particular, will have to choose. But there is an alternative. Instead of flatly rejecting China’s Belt and Road project like Stalin did the Marshall Plan, the West could join it and thereby ensure more transparency and debt sustainability. Further, Europe in particular, could complement China’s hard infrastructure investments in Africa with soft-infrastructure investment in health, education and good governance. This would not only mitigate the need to choose sides, but also stem the growing flow of migration northward from the Africa continent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: You write: &amp;quot;A new dark age could descend in some regions where tyrants abuse their subjects and where jihadists or criminal gangs roam freely to terrorize dispossessed populations.&amp;quot; The alternative is a strongman to restore order. How can we realistically find a democratic solution?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Messrs Gardels and Berggruen:&lt;/strong&gt; Such forces arise when there is a vacuum of power and authority. The refugee and immigration crisis emanating from Central America, for example, is not the result of strong states persecuting their citizens, but of weak states that can’t protect them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this respect, the Western military interventions and misguided attempts to “nation-build” other’s nations, for example in Libya and Iraq, have worsened the situation. ISIS arose in such a vacuum.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To fill the vacuum, first comes security, the rule of law, sound governance and development. Then comes democracy, which can only organically emerge out of those conditions. Change will only take hold if made by those who own it. To put the cart of democracy defined by the pro-forma exercise of elections before the horse does not work. It inevitably deepens the divisions in society instead of repairing them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: Many problems you identify are about managing pluralism. The world is pressed together like never before, and perhaps we&amp;#x27;ve globalised quicker than our mindsets could adapt. Is there a solution to the tribalism, which is influencing our politics?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Messrs Gardels and Berggruen:&lt;/strong&gt; It is no surprise that those left behind by the enormous and rapid changes of recent years are seized by anxiety and the sense they’ve lost control over their destiny to distant institutions run by strangers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While economic globalisation and technology have moved the world toward convergence of unprecedented scope and at a swift clip, the cultural and political imagination engenders the opposite. It creates a search for shelter within the familiar ways of life, that register a dignity of recognition among one’s own kind and constitute identity against the swell of seemingly anonymous forces.  When people retreat into their own suffering, better angels lose their wings. Then politics becomes tribal: us versus them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tribalism will only diminish to the extent the excluded recover a meaningful role in owning their future. Above all, that means renovating the practices and institutions of democratic deliberation so they are genuinely inclusive instead of captured by organised, special interests or demagogues who play on emotions without delivering the goods.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; *   &lt;span &gt; &lt;/span&gt;*   &lt;span &gt; &lt;/span&gt;*&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp502.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp502.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp502.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp502.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp502.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp502.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp502.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp502.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190518_opp502.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;One World, Many Systems&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From “Renovating Democracy” (University of California Press, 2019) by Nathan Gardels and Nicolas Berggruen&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;As national sovereignty reasserts itself and one size of globalization does not fit all, one world with many systems will characterize the international order in the decades ahead. A new modus vivendi that accepts this reality must be found among different cultures and civilizations now tied together as never before in a web of mutual dependence—a web in which the weight of the global economy has shifted from the once-regnant developed world to the emerging economies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For this evolution to unfold with a modicum of stability, the success or failure of diverse models of governance that arise out of plural civilizational and cultural contexts must rest on competition over results, not on the dogma of a dominant ideology, interference by others, or imposition by force—in short, a global system of “diverse equilibrium” in which the power of example, not the example of power, prevails. That is what globalization in which “one size does not fit all” will look like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paradoxically, Donald Trump’s “America First” posture may turn out to be the midwife of such a new equilibrium. By rejecting the Paris Climate Accord, pulling out of trade agreements, parting ways with the United States’ European allies, and shirking the country’s long-standing liberal internationalism, he is paving the way for an alternative order in which the United States as a nation-state is no longer the dominant player. By default, those who move in to fill the vacuum will determine the new balance of power. By withdrawing from a leadership role in shaping globalization, the United States doesn’t stop the process; it only opens the path for the rise of new players.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On climate change, for example, we have already seen in response the emergence of a “network of the willing”—ranging from China and the European Union to subnational entities like the state of California—to carry on global cooperation. Through California Governor Jerry Brown’s leadership before he left office earlier this year, 188 subnational entities in 39 countries on 6 continents are pushing ahead to implement the Paris Climate Accord despite its abandonment by official Washington. Former World Trade Organization chief Pascal Lamy even talks of a “plurilateral” world order of nongovernmental organizations, businesses, and subnational entities instead of a “multilateral” order based on nation-states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While all nations and networks must have their respected place in any globally inclusive arrangement, in the end the key pillars of such an order, in which the management of convergent interests is bound by commonly agreed rules, must be the United States and China—the world’s two largest economies, which also represent highly distinct civilizational spheres. For globalization to work, it needs leadership. Yet, as the late Zbigniew Brzezinski pointed out, neither the United States nor China can lead on its own. American power has diminished, and China is not yet ready or able to step up to the plate, and may never be prepared to take on the role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If both fail to buy in as indispensable partners, such an order can’t take hold globally. The urgent concern is that these two giants are headed in opposite directions. As former Australian prime minister Kevin Rudd has eloquently put it, “In the absence of a common narrative shared by the United States and China, the two nations are likely to drift more rapidly apart. Trust builds on itself just as distrust builds on itself as well, compounding into deep enmity over time.” Time is short, and distrust is building.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The alternative to a world order anchored in a partnership of its two most influential nations looks grim. Alongside the new networks of the willing, swaths of pandemonium fostered by the unwilling will likely then surround gated outposts that are linked to one another but divorced from their planetary hinterland in a kind of global apartheid system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new dark age could descend in some regions where tyrants abuse their subjects and where jihadists or criminal gangs roam freely to terrorize dispossessed populations. That so much of this sounds familiar—the brutal carnage of the Syrian civil war being the most tragic case in point—is a frightening indication of just how real the peril is. And, as we have further seen in the enduring refugee crisis and wave of mass migration, those who can flee will seek to breach the gates in search of a better life on the other side. In many ways, this is the price of leaderless globalization left to its own dynamics without effective cooperation or governing institutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the height of the Syrian refugee crisis in 2015, Antonio Guterres, then the United Nations high commissioner for refugees and now the UN secretary general, warned that such a world was already in the making: “We live in a period in which we no longer have a unipolar or bipolar world. We don’t even have a multipolar world; it’s kind of a chaotic world where power relations have become unclear. When power relations are unclear, impunity and unpredictability tend to prosper. That, I believe, is the reality behind the high levels of displacement that are taking place in today’s world.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But partnership between the United States and China is far easier said than done. Unlike the transatlantic order now receding, which was bound together at its core by common cultural and political foundations, the United States and China come from very different civilizational roots. The Middle Kingdom has historically defined itself by its centrality and uniqueness in the world going back millennia; the United States’ comparatively young identity is associated with universality and the mission of spreading its values. China’s geopolitical model has always been that of a dominant power surrounded by tributaries. By contrast, the United States, following the experience of Europe after the Treaty of Westphalia gave birth to the nation-state, has managed its international relations by seeking a global balance of power among states. A “cross-civilizational” partnership between these two traditions is unprecedented.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With respect to China’s role in its own region, Henry Kissinger’s formula is the most realistic arrangement for the next twenty years. “It’s understandable that China wants to keep foreigners from approaching its borders and it therefore undertakes a defense effort to that end,” he says. “I particularly understand it in light of China’s history. It’s also understandable that the United States doesn’t want any region dominated by a superpower, so that creates a certain balance. The two elements in that balance, namely China and the United States, also have to lead in cooperation.” Kissinger has rightly come to understand that, in today’s linked world, we need a fresh approach: partnership must become an integral part of the balance of power in any new geopolitical arrangement. The danger of war looms most menacingly if the balance of power is reduced to only a military dimension. With no common intent on any front, all else will dwell in the dark shadow of distrust in which each will seek advantage over the other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a US-China partnership to work, as Chinese diplomat Fu Ying once told Kissinger, the United States must be able to accept China as “an equal brother.” But that goes both ways: China must also step up with a global perspective on its responsibility that it has never before held—not as an honorary member of the Western club, but as coarchitect of world order. This recognition is the cornerstone of a strategy of evolutionary stability that aims to avoid a power vacuum by maintaining order over the slow course of change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[…]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As difficult as it may be for the United States to share leadership in the Asia-Pacific region that it has dominated for decades, it will also be a big concession for China to embrace the notion of a balance of power instead of a series of tributaries. In the end, where differences remain, the two nations must ensure their mutual interests by accommodating each other with these principles of security: restraint in the use of power, reciprocity in actions taken, transparency over intentions, and sufficient capabilities and resilience to assure the ability to strike back and restore equilibrium if attacked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new global order we envision on the basis of the United States and China as indispensable partners would accommodate the return of diversity from a long interlude of hegemony—for the first time in history “diversity connected in real time”—and would be structured geopolitically as “one world, many systems.” This new rules-based system would be a kind of “Westphalia plus” in which partnerships on global issues of concern to all form a constituent part of the balance of power between and among states—in other words, a system in which trust-building cooperative arrangements and institutions are not an alternative but themselves a factor in the overall configuration of power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To stabilize world order on these terms, the United States and China must serve as guarantors of global public goods—open trade and investment, stable financial flows, climate protection, freedom of travel and navigation, sharing of health knowledge and scientific advances. The cornerstone of a “non-value-based” partnership founded on convergent interests will inevitably have to coexist with “value-based plurilateralism” among the like-minded. Its role would be to mobilize joint efforts of those whose values are aligned in the pursuit of common ends without resort to the use of force or organized subversion against others—with the exception of the most egregious humanitarian violations by a state or organized groups within a state. When values conflict, “taking a stand, not taking sides” would be the modus operandi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;____________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Excerpted from “Renovating Democracy: Governing in the Age of Globalization and Digital Capitalism” by Nathan Gardels and Nicolas Berggruen, published by the University of California Press. © 2019 by the Regents of the University of California.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 23:43:06 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“She is on her way out. But let&#x27;s not waste this good crisis”—Theresa May’s future]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/16/she-is-on-her-way-out-but-lets-not-waste-this-good-crisis-theresa-mays-future]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/may.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-16T11:45:38Z&quot;&gt;May 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS BRITAIN approaches a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/15/britains-bizarre-unwanted-european-election&quot;&gt;European election&lt;/a&gt; it had expected to avoid, we examine how the Brexit mess is dissolving party allegiances. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/27/as-turkeys-economy-slows-attitudes-toward-syrian-refugees-harden&quot;&gt;Turkey&lt;/a&gt; was once praised for the way it treated Syrians fleeing conflict, but that welcome is wearing thin as war has dragged on. Also, kinky and camp meet fraught politics in this year’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/04/when-eurovision-goes-to-israel&quot;&gt;Eurovision&lt;/a&gt; Song Contest. Runtime: 21min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/may-euliveininterestingtimes-brexit&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 23:43:05 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump gets tough on Huawei]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/16/donald-trump-gets-tough-on-huawei]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_wbp505_facebook.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-16T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SOME MAY have wondered why it took so long. An American prohibition against the use of equipment made by Huawei had long been mooted, out of fear that China’s spooks could use it to spy on its geopolitical rival. The largest Chinese telecoms firm has in effect been prevented from selling its kit in America since 2012. Big American mobile operators have already renounced the use of its gear for their fifth-generation (5G) networks. The administration of Donald Trump has attempted to browbeat Western allies into forswearing Huawei too; imposing a ban of its own was expected to help with the cajoling. Until now, the only other country to have enacted one is Australia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the executive order that Donald Trump issued on May 15th, declaring a national emergency, was much broader in scope than most had anticipated. It named neither Huawei nor China explicitly. But it said that “foreign adversaries”, keen to spy on America, were “creating and exploiting vulnerabilities” in local technology and services that store “vast amounts of sensitive information” and “facilitate the digital economy”. It said that unrestricted acquisition or use of such technologies was “an unusual and extraordinary threat to the national security, foreign policy and economy” of America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the ban’s woolliest bits—who counts as a foreign adversary, for instance—should be clarified with the help of American spies within the next 150 days. But if there was any doubt about its chief intended target, a separate ban issued later that day made things crystal clear. The Department of Commerce said that it has added Huawei to a list of companies deemed a risk to American national security. When it takes effect (the timing is unclear), dozens of Huawei’s affiliates will be prohibited from buying hardware and software from American firms without government approval.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a statement, Huawei said it is “ready and willing to engage with the US government and come up with effective measures to ensure product security” and that restricting it would only limit America to “inferior yet more expensive alternatives”. It also said that “unreasonable restrictions” would raise “serious legal issues”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Samm Sacks of New America, a think-tank in Washington, DC, says that this direct interdiction is “a complete shock”. It had for months been talked about among companies and those close to policymakers as the “nuclear option”. Unlike in the case of ZTE, another Chinese telecoms giant that was briefly banned outright from sourcing American parts and software last spring, Huawei can continue to buy them as long as its foreign suppliers secure licences. But companies are being told that there will be no exemptions, according to Ms Sacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Observers nonetheless expect a rush to apply for such licences. Those who doubt, for now, that a blanket American ban is inevitable say its intent is to make Huawei’s kit look like a less dependable option to service providers elsewhere. In Europe, any orders for gear that Huawei had been expecting, for instance, will now be upset. Reports emerged earlier this year of international telecoms carriers stockpiling equipment, as fears of an American ban grew. Some were burnt by the ZTE prohibition, which denied them access to warehouses holding gear that they had already bought.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When ZTE was banned in April 2018, the effect was crippling. In 2016 UBS, a bank, had estimated that at least four-fifths of its products relied on American parts. Chips designed by America’s Qualcomm were in about 70% of its smartphones. ZTE posted a loss of 7bn yuan ($1bn) for 2018, compared with a profit of 4.6bn yuan the previous year. In barely three months the ban brought the company to the brink of bankruptcy, before it earned a reprieve from Mr Trump, after a personal appeal from China’s president, Xi Jinping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Few observers expect Huawei to flirt with bankruptcy in the way ZTE has. But it, too, looks vulnerable. Although its HiSilicon unit designs some of its chips in-house, the company outsources their manufacturing to Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Company, a giant chipmaker, which could be swayed by the Americans. The only other factories capable of producing cutting-edge chips are owned by Samsung, a South Korean firm—and South Korea is another American ally. Like all makers of mobile chips, it relies heavily on intellectual property licensed from ARM, a British firm. Products from its handsets to data centres and cloud-computing services could all be hurt by the ban.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coming amid an intensifying trade war between America and China—and given the ZTE precedent—the ban on Huawei may also be a bargaining chip in talks. At a minimum, it will be used as one with recalcitrant European allies. But as officials hash out the scope of Mr Trump’s executive order, more than just the usual suspects could find themselves ensnared. Ms Sacks says that it could become a “discretionary tool” for America to use against Chinese companies as it sees fit—including against perceived risks to the country’s entire digital infrastructure. Its wording is broad enough to encompass all manner of Chinese technology firms, from e-commerce and digital-payments giants like Alibaba to hardware-makers such as Lenovo. That would be a worrying prospect indeed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 23:43:04 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>