<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Virginia’s governor calls for tougher gun laws]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/04/virginias-governor-calls-for-tougher-gun-laws]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_USP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-04T19:27:11Z&quot;&gt;Jun 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON MAY 31st a gunman walked into a municipal office in Virginia Beach and slaughtered 12 people, most of them colleagues he had worked with for years, before he was killed in a gun battle with police. The killer—whom the police have referred to by name only once, part of a move to strip mass shooters of their notoriety—used two semi-automatic handguns, both bought legally. He also used a silencer and extended ammunition magazines, which are also legal in Virginia. It seems likely that his presence, heavily armed, in the building, was also above board. Thanks to the state’s liberal concealed-carry laws anyone with a licence can walk into a restaurant, shop or office in Virginia carrying a gun. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four days later, Ralph Northam, Virginia’s governor, said he would recall lawmakers to the state Capitol in June to debate a package of gun-control measures. It included, he said, a ban on silencers and high capacity ammunition magazines and new powers for local governments to limit guns in city buildings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It is wrong, it is outrageous, it is unforgivable to turn our municipal centers, our schools, our churches and synagogues and mosques, into battlefields,” he said at a news conference on June 4th. “I will be asking for votes and laws, not thoughts and prayers.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Northam, a Democrat who has long been an advocate of stricter gun controls, said he also wanted lawmakers to vote on bills to compel gun buyers to undergo universal background checks, to limit gun purchases to one a month, and to allow authorities to seize the weapons of those deemed a threat. He said that while mass shootings made headlines, far more Virginians were killed in smaller incidents—1,028 in 2017 alone. He cited the case of a little girl who was shot dead in a park last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twelve years after a student at Virginia Tech killed 32 and wounded 17 with two semi-automatic pistols in a 10-minute rampage in 2007, Virginia has yet to pass any of the stringent gun regulations that have cut gun deaths elsewhere. It is one of 17 states in which more people are killed by guns than car crashes, according to the Centre for American Progress, a think tank. In 2012 Virginia’s lawmakers repealed a law, passed in the wake of the Virginia Tech massacre, which prevented the purchase of more than one gun per person per month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Northam, a doctor who has described treating children and soldiers for bullet wounds, made gun-control a big issue in his campaign for the governorship in 2017. But his efforts have so far failed. Republicans, who hold narrow majorities in Virginia’s House and Senate, have blocked all such efforts, including a push, in January, to ban high-capacity magazines. “They have never received a fair hearing”, Mr Northam said. “I want these pieces of common sense gun safety legislation to get to the floor and let these individuals elected by you, the people, to come to the floor and cast their vote.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One Republican lawmaker did indicate that he was willing to debate gun controls. Addressing a group of protesters who had gathered outside his office to call for gun controls, Thomas Norment, the majority leader in the state Senate, said “there ought to be a meaningful discussion legislatively and in the community about gun control.” But he is also reported to have told the protestors that “nothing would have helped us at Virginia Beach”. The House Speaker, Kirk Cox, meanwhile, described Mr Northam’s announcement as “hasty and suspect when considered against the backdrop of the last few months”—apparently alluding to revelations in February that Mr Northam had donned blackface as a student. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Northam may have more luck with his gun-control push next year. Since 2016, when Hillary Clinton won Virginia, Democrats have stormed elections in the state, taking its three elective offices—governor, lieutenant-governor and attorney-general—and three congressional seats. In November, all seats in the general assembly will be up for election. With Republicans holding a two-seat majority in the House and Senate, Democrats are hoping to flip both. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 05:40:21 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Under left or right, Denmark is set to adopt ever harsher policies against migrants]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/04/under-left-or-right-denmark-is-set-to-adopt-ever-harsher-policies-against-migrants]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_eup502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-04T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR A striking example of how far-right parties can change the politics of a democratic Western country, even without ever holding office, look no further than to wealthy, well-ordered Denmark. The anti-immigrant Danish People’s Party (DPP), which was first elected to the Danish parliament in 1998, has relentlessly pushed mainstream parties into adopting ever harsher policies towards immigrants, often Muslims.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The general election, which takes place on June 5th, will confirm the trend. The country of 5.7m has been ruled since 2015 by a centre-right alliance led by the Venstre party under the prime minister, Lars Løkke Rasmussen. Lacking a majority, Mr Rasmussen has had to rely on the votes of the DPP (which also supported centre-right governments between 2001 and 2011).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Venstre is polling at just 18%, and will probably lose to the Social Democrats (SD), on 29%. The SD ruled Denmark for most of the 20th century and built much of its generous welfare state. But don’t expect it to bring much change when it comes to dealing with foreigners. In the bidding war for Denmark’s increasingly strident anti-immigrant vote, the SD is promising more limits on foreigners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The DPP’s influence has helped to normalise xenophobic and Islamophobic sentiments. Last year Mr Rasmussen rolled out a plan to banish asylum-seekers to an isolated island, once used as a research centre for contagious diseases in animals, if they cannot be deported because of humanitarian concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parliament has passed laws banning women from wearing the burqa or other face coverings in public. It allows officials to confiscate cash, jewellery and other valuables from asylum-seekers, supposedly to pay for the cost of their upkeep in asylum centres. This year it approved a “paradigm shift” under which the country’s asylum policy will focus on repatriation instead of integration. This means the government can deport refugees whose countries it deems safe enough, such as Somalia (even though a Danish delegation that visited the country in 2015 to assess its security situation did not dare leave the airport).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Rasmussen also announced a policy to eradicate “ghettos” by 2030. Denmark defines these as neighbourhoods with lower income and education levels, and higher unemployment and crime rates, than the national average, and over 50% “non-Western” residents. Seeking to avoid the creation of “parallel societies”, the policy forces such areas to cut social housing to 40% of the total housing stock. For example, in Tingbjerg, a suburb of Copenhagen classified as a “hard ghetto”, all homes are social housing. Local housing associations are required to demolish buildings, build new private homes or sell property to investors. The policy also demands that children in these areas must attend publicly funded nurseries and take classes in “Danish values”, or risk losing benefits. Those who commit crimes in the “ghettos” will face harsher punishments than if they commit them elsewhere. Critics say that the policy places a stigma on immigrants; they argue that blaming foreigners ignores the underlying reasons for Denmark’s social problems, such as unemployment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In stark contrast to parties on the left in other Nordic countries, such as Sweden and Finland, the SD has proposed taking these policies even further. Even as she steers her party further to the left economically—pledging to raise taxes on the rich, for instance—the SD leader, Mette Frederiksen (pictured), is moving to the right on immigration. The SD has proposed an annual cap on “non-Western” immigration, and a limit to the share of “non-Western” students that schools are allowed to enrol at one time. Foreign senior citizens who give up their Danish residency would be allowed to take their state pensions with them if they moved back to their countries of origin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Frederiksen has even flirted with the idea of co-operating with the DPP if she wins power. If you can’t beat them, join them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 05:40:20 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tariffs at dawn]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/04/tariffs-at-dawn]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_blm503_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-04T17:50:09Z&quot;&gt;Jun 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PRESIDENT TRUMP has started using &lt;strong&gt;import tariffs&lt;/strong&gt; to win political as well as economic battles. What will be the impact of his latest threats to impose tariffs on Mexican goods? Also, how the Federal Reserve is preparing &lt;strong&gt;for the next economic recession&lt;/strong&gt;. And, how a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/02/charity-begins-at-work&quot;&gt;toxic working environment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; can poison lives even among do-gooders. Simon Long hosts. Runtime: 19 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-tariffsatdawn&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 02:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Chernobyl” is the highest-rated TV series ever]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/04/chernobyl-is-the-highest-rated-tv-series-ever]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_woc177.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AT TWENTY-THREE minutes past one in the morning of April 26th 1986, a safety test at a nuclear reactor in Soviet Ukraine went catastrophically wrong. The resulting steam explosion at the plant near the city of Pripyat, 70 miles north of Kiev, spewed out so much radiation that much of the surrounding area will be uninhabitable for 20,000 years. Harmful isotopes were carried by the winds as far as Ireland within a week. According to some accounts, first responders who were exposed to large doses of radiation suffered agonising deaths. These events, as well as the political intrigue of the Soviet government’s actions, are the subject of HBO’s historical drama series, “Chernobyl”. Following the final episode, which aired in America on June 3rd, it is the highest-rated television series of all time, according to crowd-sourced reviews on IMDb, a film and television rating site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reviewers have given the miniseries stellar ratings. A weighted average of all five episodes calculated by &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; (according to how recently each episode ran and the number of reviews) accords it 9.7 points out of 10. By the same measure, other leading shows—including comparable historical drama series such as “The Crown” and “The People v. O. J. Simpson” (now called “American Crime Story”)—lag behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is more, every episode of “Chernobyl” has been rated by IMDb users at 9.5 or higher, a unique streak. According to &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s analysis of 518 episodes of popular television dramas, the likelihood that any show would produce even four consecutive episodes that each score a 9.5 or above is roughly 0.4%. Apart from “Chernobyl”, only the final four episodes of “Breaking Bad”—previously the highest-rated show—had accomplished this feat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of this is even more impressive given its subject matter. Documentaries typically struggle to gain as much attention as action and fantasy shows such as “Game of Thrones”, and the same is true of historical dramas. Even series about well-known subjects, such as Queen Elizabeth II or the trial of O.J. Simpson, earn user ratings that are typically below those of the most popular shows. In comparison, “Chernobyl” scores better than the greats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The show has also caused a massive spike in interest about the actual disaster. Web traffic to the entry for the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chernobyl_disaster&quot;&gt;Chernobyl nuclear disaster&lt;/a&gt; on Wikipedia, an online encyclopedia, has increased 56-fold since the start of the year. Interest in a comparable nuclear disaster at Japan’s Fukushima Daiichi power plant in 2011 has also increased, though by a more modest 21 times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Editor’s note (June 4th 2019)&lt;/strong&gt;: This piece was originally published on June 3rd and has been updated following the airing of the final episode in America. IMDb reviewers gave it a rating of 9.9 out of ten.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 02:40:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The world according to Donald Trump]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/04/the-world-according-to-donald-trump]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_woc153.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;HOW DOES the world look to President Donald Trump? He certainly likes the pomp and ceremony of foreign monarchies. His first trip abroad as president was to Saudi Arabia, where he took part in a sword dance with King Salman and other Gulf royals. In Japan last month he was treated to a six-course black-tie banquet with Emperor Naruhito, complete with Mt. Fuji-shaped ice cream (not to mention playing golf and watching a sumo match with the prime minister, Shinzo Abe). Making a state visit to Britain, starting on June 3rd, Mr Trump was delighted by his formal dinner with the queen at Buckingham Palace, even though he did not have a procession down the Mall in a gold carriage (for security reasons).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But to judge from his Twitter feed, at least, Mr Trump’s mind is mostly elsewhere when he thinks about the globe. Worldmapper, an academic mapping outfit, analysed nearly 8,300 tweets issued by Mr Trump between his election in November 2016 and May this year. Of these, 1,384 mentioned foreign countries. The president’s &lt;em&gt;idée fixe&lt;/em&gt; is Russia, which he has mentioned in 297 tweets, although this may have more to do with his loathing for Robert Mueller’s investigation into Russian interference in the 2016 presidential election than with the president’s admiration for Vladimir Putin, the Russian strongman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;North Korea—whose leader, Kim Jong Un, Mr Trump has met twice—figured in 163 tweets. The United Kingdom, which enjoys a “special relationship” with America, was mentioned just 22 times, behind both France (37) and Germany (29). Japan has been mentioned 43 times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not that being mentioned in Mr Trump’s tweets is necessarily a sign of friendship. Often the opposite is true. Moments before touching down at Stansted Airport, the president was already on Twitter, issuing a bilious message denouncing Sadiq Khan, London’s mayor, as a “stone cold loser” (no doubt in response to Mr Khan’s criticism of the presidential visit). During his stay in London, Mr Trump harrumphed about Mexico, declaring that it “immediately stop the flow of people and drugs through their country and to our Southern Border.” But Britain’s monarch, at least, seems to have soothed his spirits: “London part of trip is going really well. The Queen and the entire Royal family have been fantastic.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 02:40:11 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why the EU’s sea-rescue mission has no boats]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/06/04/why-the-eus-sea-rescue-mission-has-no-boats]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_BLP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-04T16:28:29Z&quot;&gt;Jun 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT IS one thing to be tasked with saving the lives of vulnerable migrants in the Mediterranean. It is another thing altogether to try to do this without any boats. But this is the job that confronts Vice-Admiral Enrico Credendino, the commander of Operation Sophia, a naval mission organised by the European Union. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The mission was established in 2015 as part of the EU’s response to a crisis that saw over a million undocumented migrants enter Europe that year. A large contingent came from Syria, via Turkey and Greece, but many Africans also made the perilous journey across the Mediterranean from Libya in search of a better life. Operation Sophia, launched at the behest of the Italian government but with support across the EU, was supposed to be a military mission. Supplied, at first, with 19 boats, its objective was to disrupt people-traffickers, many of whom were operating out of Libya. It trained the Libyan coastguard and navy, and helped implement a UN arms embargo off the coast. But in practice, the mission (named after a baby girl born on a rescue boat) was also a humanitarian operation. It has rescued over 44,000 people at sea. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Operation Sophia has become the victim of an anti-migrant backlash in Europe and of quarrels about the regulations governing disembarkation and asylum within the EU. Most people rescued in the Mediterranean have been brought ashore in Italy. Under EU law known as the Dublin regulation, Italy has been responsible for taking care of rescued people and processing their asylum applications. An increasingly frustrated and now populist government in Rome is using Operation Sophia as leverage to try and force their European neighbours to agree on changes to the Dublin regulation. In December, after European ministers failed to agree on where rescue services should take migrants ashore, Italy said the rescued could no longer come to their ports. Germany in turn withdrew its boat from the project, out of apparent frustration with Mr Salvini’s policy. Over months, the project had become more difficult to operate. But rather than ending Operation Sophia altogether, ministers agreed on an unhappy compromise in March: the mission could continue, but without any vessels on the water. It now relies on aeroplanes and the Libyan coastguard to do the job of disrupting smuggling networks. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In recent years migrants seeking to enter Europe have shifted the focus of their attention. In 2016 8,000 arrived by sea in Spain; in 2018 59,000 did. And those who still try to cross the central Mediterranean are attempting longer, more dangerous journeys in flimsier craft that they can hide more easily. As a result the fatality rate for this group is already seven times higher this year than it was in 2018. Human-rights groups also worry that EU co-operation with the Libyan coastguard may be harmful to migrants. They are no longer taken to Italy but are placed in Libyan detention centres where there is a high likelihood of torture, sexual violence, extortion and forced labour. All of which leaves European leaders facing tricky decisions. They may be having some success in reducing the number of undocumented migrants reaching Europe via the central Mediterranean, but the risks to those who choose to make the trip remain considerable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A fictionalised biography of David Hockney]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/06/04/a-fictionalised-biography-of-david-hockney]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_bkp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Life of David Hockney: A Novel.&lt;/strong&gt; By Catherine Cusset. Translated by Teresa Lavender Fagan. &lt;em&gt;Other Press; 192 pages; $15.99 and £12.99&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;READING “LIFE OF DAVID HOCKNEY” somehow mimics the experience of looking at a painting by the artist. Famous for his bright, flat compositions, Mr Hockney re-energised figurative painting at a time when most of his contemporaries considered it “anti-modern”. Catherine Cusset’s writing, translated from the French by Teresa Lavender Fagan, echoes that vivid style. The author moves swiftly through Mr Hockney’s life, painting a fictional portrait of his adolescence in working-class Yorkshire through to his globe-trotting adulthood as one of Britain’s most famous living artists. The result is a compelling picture of a man who himself changed portraiture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Writing an imagined biography of a living artist is a risky move, and perhaps a strange one (novels about dead figures are more common). In her introduction to the English edition, Ms Cusset explains simply that Mr Hockney’s life took hold of her. “When I read about him, something happened. He started to live in my head like a character.” In her writing, the character of Hockney comes fully to life, too. The flesh-and-blood painter agreed to have lunch with Ms Cusset after reading the book, and though she doesn’t include Mr Hockney’s verdict in her introduction, the lunch sounds pleasant enough to indicate that he liked the novel, or, at the very least, appreciated its artifice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After all, Mr Hockney himself is a master of reconstructing the real. Early in the novel, Hockney has a revelation: “Nature and artifice were thus not at odds, any more than were the figurative and abstraction, poetry and graffiti, quotes and originality, playing and reality.” This idea frees him to paint what he wants: California swimming pools, gay couples and naked men, all in bright hues. It also seems to free Ms Cusset to combine the facts of Mr Hockney’s life with her own imagination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In her telling, Hockney is an eternal innocent, almost a Peter Pan figure. He devotes his life in equal measure to art and to the dream of “free love, without ties, without jealousy, without guilt. Just pleasure to give and receive.” Ms Cusset never romanticises this dream. Instead, she traces its progression from idealism to selfishness. By middle age, her Hockney has forgotten how love works, refusing to feel guilt and refusing to take responsibility. It takes a teenager to remind him, with “the clarity of childhood”, that he has to treat others as people, not as subjects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Cusset writes with a nearly childish clarity, too, and the result is both unsettling and effective. For much of the novel, she describes Hockney’s emotions with unusual baldness, flattening his inner life. Like Mr Hockney, she mixes lush visuals with pervasive melancholy, and as her subject reaches belated maturity, her prose grows increasingly nuanced. By the book’s end, the great painter feels fragile and accessible, both a legend and a fallible man. This trajectory mirrors Mr Hockney’s artistic process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Cusset sees Hockney as using portraiture as a way of coming to terms with his life. With “Portrait of an Artist”, he grapples with the failure of his first relationship by painting his ex-boyfriend “as an artist, not as a lover”. In “My Parents”, he allows himself to show the elder Hockneys “chained together, but separated, each enclosed in his or her solitude”. These are emotional, exposed paintings: looking at them feels intimate, sometimes to an unsettling degree. The same could be said of Ms Cusset’s novel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Advertising may make people miserable, but still has its uses]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/04/advertising-may-make-people-miserable-but-still-has-its-uses]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_fnd000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EVERY YEAR, as Americans polish off their Thanksgiving feasts, a particular type of television advertisement begins to air. The details vary, but the plot is always the same: one family member surprises another with the Christmas gift of a luxury car, often adorned with a cartoonishly large bow. The recipient never betrays a hint of the dismay one might expect to see on the face of someone whose partner has without consultation spent tens of thousands of dollars. Such a car can easily cost more than the median annual income of an American household, and most people who see these ads will not be able to afford one. But the envy such spots induce serves an economic purpose, even as it leaves the majority feeling worse about themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ads and other forms of marketing ostensibly serve a straightforward economic role. Firms selling goods and services need to tell consumers about the availability and desirability of their wares, and spend on advertising to do so. By informing consumers about the relative merits of various products, ads improve the quality of purchasing decisions and, conceivably, leave both firms and shoppers better off than they would be in an ad-free world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet there are many ways in which advertising might fall short of this ideal. It need not be honest or representative of the full range of available products, for example. Some firms target impressionable children, in ways which could contribute to long-run health risks. And honest or not, successful ads induce a desire to spend, potentially on things the audience does not need or cannot afford. The information content of advertisements for fancy vacations, bespoke cars or diamond-studded watches does not much matter for people whose budgets cannot accommodate them. Their main takeaway is that others get to enjoy things that they themselves cannot afford. If the effect of advertising is mostly to encourage people to want things that they cannot have, rather than to direct them toward items that are a good match for their needs and tastes, then it is possible that spending on advertising leaves society worse off overall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some recent research suggests this might indeed be the case. A forthcoming paper by Chloé Michel, now at Swiss Re, Michelle Sovinsky of Mannheim University, Eugenio Proto of Bristol University and Andrew Oswald of Warwick University attempts to unpick the effect of advertising on welfare. The researchers used three decades’ worth of survey results from a sample of nearly 1m Europeans, spread across 27 countries, to compare information on self-reported life satisfaction with variation in total advertising spending as a share of GDP. After taking account of other macroeconomic variables such as unemployment, and individuals’ socioeconomic characteristics, they find a significant and inverse relationship between spending on advertisements and national welfare. They estimate that a doubling of ad spending is associated with a subsequent drop in reported satisfaction of 3%—an effect about a quarter as strong as a spell of unemployment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is possible that this result reflects the effect of some other factor which influences both advertising and well-being. And the authors are careful to note that they cannot be certain about the causal mechanism at work. But their findings may illustrate an aspect of the economy that has puzzled some economists for more than a century. In “The Theory of the Leisure Class”, published in 1899, Thorstein Veblen, a Norwegian-American economist, explored the nature of what he termed “conspicuous consumption”. Veblen argued that consumption is not merely about satisfying needs, but is also used to signal status and prestige.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The priciest cars may offer more nifty features and a smoother ride than a cheaper marque, but the vast difference in price is not primarily down to such advantages. Rather, the buyer is paying for such cars’ value as a status symbol, which derives from the fact that very few people can afford one. (Following his insight, economists use the name “Veblen good” for items for which demand rises with price, though it is not the high price itself that generates the increased demand but rather the exclusivity that the high price confers.) These luxury items defy normal economic logic. In the mass market, productivity-boosting innovations that allow firms to sell better products at lower prices are a route to success. For producers of conspicuous-consumption items, such cost-cutting does not conquer the market but destroys it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Less good than a feast&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The notion that people might buy high-cost items in preference to serviceable alternatives simply to set themselves apart from the less well-off would seem absurd, were the economy not chock-a-block with examples, from designer handbags to silver cutlery to oxygenated energy drinks. Advertising enables the process. For goods to grant high status, there must be consumers who want but cannot have them. Ad campaigns featuring sleek cars bedecked with oversized bows add to the value of luxury brands by informing the masses of how desirable they are—and how inaccessible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Veblen, though, saw the rich as a largely unproductive class of capital-owning moochers, who profited off the useful labour of working people (hence, the “leisure class”). In recent decades, however, the share of Americans working long hours has grown, and has risen fastest among those earning the highest wages—an odd exception to the global norm that working time declines with income. The status envy induced by conspicuous consumption may play a role. In rich countries, most people’s basic needs have long since been met. To keep workers striving—those on higher incomes especially—there must always be more desirable consumer goods and services just out of reach. Perpetual dissatisfaction might well boost economic growth by keeping highly productive workers who might otherwise enjoy more time with their families chained to their desks. But it is a funny sort of prosperity that depends on people never being satisfied with their lot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 00:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[With “My Songs” Sting underlines the lasting quality of his music]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/04/with-my-songs-sting-underlines-the-lasting-quality-of-his-music]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_BKP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-04T14:02:25Z&quot;&gt;Jun 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERE IS a category of music superstar who, while they once divided opinion, became cherished as they attained veteran status. Encountering somebody with a harsh word for Elton John or Bruce Springsteen is rare enough to be surprising; the same was true before their deaths of David Bowie and Prince. Then there is another category of those who, while popular, still engender antagonism (if sometimes unfairly). Foremost in that rank are two men who rose to fame at the head of rock bands: Bono, the lead singer of U2, and the frontman of the Police, Sting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even in 1978 Sting was an object of contempt among fans of punk music, who saw him as an interloper, an old-style muso with his roots in jazz, riding punk’s coat-tails into the charts. Perhaps that was true, but it overlooked the fact that Sting was unmistakably a major talent in his own right. He was and has remained an outstanding songwriter. The body of work he has created stands up. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“My Songs”, a new album, is a 15-track overview of Sting’s career, but not a compilation; rather, he has seen fit to re-record a set of his compositions, for the most part so closely to the original versions as to appear redundant. (Artists increasingly revisit their own catalogues in this way, perhaps for licensing and royalty reasons as often as artistic ones.) The few notable differences are puzzling: a funky-house take on “If You Love Somebody Set Them Free”, his first solo single post-Police, feels clunky and outdated; a slightly rockier version of “Demolition Man” sheds no new light on the song.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around half of these tracks were first recorded by the Police, so the title “My Songs” rather makes it sound as if Sting is tetchily wresting them back. Still, why should the man who wrote these songs not take proprietorial pride in them? They are all excellent, and there are plenty more he could have included of the same standard. It is no small thing to have written the exquisite “Fragile”, which has lent itself to a superb, epic reworking by Isaac Hayes; to have created “Walking On The Moon” as a perfect vehicle for the Police’s eerie fusion of reggae and rock; to have fashioned perhaps his most celebrated song, “Every Breath You Take”, which is widely misheard as an account of loving devotion, but which is unsurpassed in pop as an (entirely intentional) account of sinister, obsessive and controlling behaviour. Plenty of renowned artists have accumulated lesser catalogues of music than Sting’s while committing worse sins than being found vaguely irksome by a segment of the public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is also significant to have forged a solo career that rivals or even eclipses his work as part of a successful group: Sting joins Diana Ross, Paul Simon, Michael Jackson, Phil Collins, George Michael, Robbie Williams, Justin Timberlake and Beyoncé, among a few others, in that select club. His most recent new material, “44/876” (2018) —a collaborative album with Shaggy, a reggae star—has charted around the world, some 33 years since his first solo album, “The Dream of the Blue Turtles”, did the same. Perhaps the moment is approaching when nobody considers it worthwhile to dislike Sting any longer, and the best of his music will speak for itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 21:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China erases the Tiananmen story: “It&#x27;s been depressingly effective”]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/04/china-erases-the-tiananmen-story-its-been-depressingly-effective]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_opm502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-04T11:14:43Z&quot;&gt;Jun 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON THE &lt;strong&gt;30th anniversary of the &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/china/2019/05/04/the-communist-party-grapples-with-a-momentous-anniversary&quot;&gt;Tiananmen Square&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; massacre&lt;/strong&gt;, our correspondents recall a dark day and assess &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/china/2019/05/30/many-chinese-know-little-about-the-bloodshed-in-beijing-30-years-ago&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;its legacy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;—not least the Communist Party&amp;#x27;s effort to suppress the memory of how it crushed China&amp;#x27;s pro-democracy movement. Could such widespread dissent flare up in today’s China? Also, why &lt;strong&gt;laws requiring immigrants to speak host-nations’ languages are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/05/25/the-language-struggles-of-immigrants-to-america&quot;&gt;counter-productive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Runtime: 22 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/thirtyyearsofforgetting-tiananmen&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 20:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>