<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[New Zealand’s government drops plans for a capital-gains tax]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/17/new-zealands-government-drops-plans-for-a-capital-gains-tax]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_ASP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE LEADER of the opposition, Simon Bridges, called it an “assault on the Kiwi way of life”. To former politicians it was “stubborn” and “vindictive”. On April 17th New Zealand’s Labour Party succumbed to such pressure and abandoned plans to impose a contentious capital-gains tax on investment properties, shares and business assets. “While I have believed in a CGT, it’s clear many New Zealanders do not,” said Jacinda Ardern, a prime minister more accustomed to applause than defeat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is an embarrassing climbdown for her party, which has campaigned for a capital-gains tax for almost a decade. Practically every other rich country has one. In February a government-appointed advisory group concluded that instituting one would make New Zealand’s tax system fairer, and recommended taxing capital gains at the same rate as the highest incomes. But Labour governs in a coalition with a populist party, New Zealand First. It courts older, rural voters who tend to oppose the levy, and refused to wave it through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Ardern’s party has been stung by the policy before. It campaigned for a capital-gains tax at general elections in 2011 and 2014, and was trounced on both occasions. Polls had shown that a strong majority of New Zealanders still opposed the reform. Yet only about 10% of them would have been affected by a capital-gains tax at all, says Michael Littlewood, of Auckland Law School. And the advisory group had suggested sweetening the pill by using the revenue the tax brought in to lower income taxes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Advocates of the tax hoped it would deter Kiwis from stashing their cash into bricks and mortar and thus cool overheated property prices. The government’s advisory group said it would help reduce the tax system’s coddling of the richest New Zealanders. The country has no stamp duty, or tax on land, estates or inheritance. The wealthy benefit disproportionately from income from property and other investments. As elsewhere, many think it unfair that profits from those assets are taxed lightly or not at all, while those who work for a living must surrender a big chunk of their income.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Businesses, however, were incensed by the advisory group’s proposals. They complained about being “double taxed” on profits from their operations, and on gains when their assets are sold. Opponents argued the tax would have deterred locals from saving for retirement, scared off investors, reduced job growth and driven up the costs of rental accommodation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Zealand’s reliance on agriculture proved another sticking point. Many of its farmers tolerate low incomes knowing that the value of their land will rise over time. They worried that a capital-gains tax would rob them of the opportunity to cash in when they sell their businesses. “Taking that away from them is a bit like taking away subsidies,” admits Michael Cullen, a former Labour finance minister who led the advisory group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Ardern promises not to revive the idea for as long as she is prime minister, meaning that Labour will not renew its campaign for the tax at next year’s election. The opposition National Party will be sad to lose a talking point. The government has wasted millions of dollars on a pointless review, and upset businesses in the process, complains its leader, Simon Bridges. “New Zealanders can’t trust Labour on tax,” he tweeted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 23:06:17 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The race to become Britain’s next PM]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/17/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_WOP008.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- data-infographic-js=&quot;/2019/tory-leadership/js/bundle.js&quot; data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/tory-leadership/css/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/tory-leadership/css/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;O&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt; N MARCH 27TH&lt;/small&gt; Theresa May,
  Britain’s prime minister, promised to stand down as leader of the Conservative
  Party—if Parliament passed her Brexit withdrawal deal. This has been rejected
  three times by the House of Commons. But &lt;small&gt;MP&lt;/small&gt;s have been unable
  to agree on an alternative to Mrs May’s deal, beyond rejecting the idea of a
  no-deal Brexit. The prime minister has decided to seek a second extension to
  the talks with the European Union, and may yet make a fourth attempt to win
  parliamentary approval.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  Whatever happens with Brexit, Mrs May has, in effect, fired the starting
  pistol in the race to succeed her as Tory leader and prime minister. Betfair
  Exchange, a betting website, has been tracking punters’ predictions on the
  next Tory leader. According to the wisdom of the crowd, five Tory candidates
  stand out. On April 2nd, Boris Johnson, the former Foreign Secretary and
  prominent Brexit campaigner, became the favourite to win.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p &gt;Source: Betfair Exchange&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Adrian Wooldridge, our political editor, assesses the chances of five leading Conservative politicians hoping to take the top job in this short film
&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ychDrZ2QzlE&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(此域名已被污染，谢谢大家一直以来的支持)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 23:06:16 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Little Woods” marks out Nia DaCosta as a film-maker to watch]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/04/17/little-woods-marks-out-nia-dacosta-as-a-film-maker-to-watch]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BKP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-17T13:45:59Z&quot;&gt;Apr 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHEN “LITTLE WOODS” premiered to rapturous reviews at the Tribeca Film Festival last year—it currently holds a rare 100% approval rating on Rotten Tomatoes, a review-aggregator site—and was snatched up by Neon, a feted distributor, it signalled the arrival of a promising new voice in film. For her directorial debut, Nia DaCosta (who also wrote the script) has produced a profound work about the practical realities and emotional hardships of poverty, set in an oil boomtown in North Dakota. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The film’s protagonist, Ollie (Tessa Thompson), is eight days from the end of her probation following an arrest for dealing Oxycontin. Though she is trying to stay on the right side of the law, two crises occur at once: the bank’s foreclosure on her home and the pregnancy of her estranged sister, Deb (Lily James). To save the family home and to pay for her sister’s abortion, Ollie is drawn back into a life of crime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These contrivances might seem familiar, even clumsy, in lesser hands, but what makes “Little Woods” compelling are the fresh details crafted by Ms DaCosta. Before she decides to resume dealing drugs, Ollie is living below the poverty line. She makes ends meet by selling coffee and sandwiches to rig workers from the back of her truck. She has no romantic life—a rarity for films with female leads—and her only relationship to speak of is with her sister, whom she rarely sees and does not initially seem to care much for. When Deb comes to her for help, Ollie provides it not out of love or even necessity but from some unspoken understanding that Deb is the only real connection she has.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a simple story, and one which touches on a panoply of current political issues: economic anxiety in rural America, opioid addiction, access to abortions and the cost of health care. Again, the film could have strayed into polemic, but Ms DaCosta keeps the policies in the background to focus on their human repercussions. Eschewing thundering speeches or grand injustices, the film unfolds simply as a series of problems for Ollie to solve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a successful and moving approach, even if it takes some time for the viewer to attune to the film’s quiet realism. What seems to be a premise taken directly from the crime-movie playbook—this is essentially a “one last heist” flick—is made surprising by the absence of thrilling chase scenes, showy cinematography, villainous cops or promises of riches. Instead, “Little Woods” is beholden to the realities of Ollie’s life. There is a natural tension that arises from her situation, but her dilemma is never made to feel like a caper. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even the emotional storyline, so often overdeveloped and melodramatic in films that focus on women, is muted. Through their travails, Ollie and Deb do reaffirm their sororal bond, but that is hardly the point: the point is to avoid destitution. Ms Thompson and Ms James underplay the emotions of their exchanges—neither of them reaches for likeability in their portrayals—and often they seem more like business partners than family. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The critical success of “Little Woods” has already helped Ms DaCosta to land her next project. She has been lined up by Jordan Peele to helm a sequel of “Candyman” (1992), a classic horror film which touched on themes of race, class and urban gentrification. Ms DaCosta is a good fit for the material. She is on her way to becoming one of the foremost chroniclers of America’s “forgotten class”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Little Woods” is released in America on April 19th&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 21:06:20 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[France agonises over the fire that devastated Notre Dame]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/17/france-agonises-over-the-fire-that-devastated-notre-dame]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/articles/20190420_eup001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE CATHEDRAL&lt;/small&gt; of Notre Dame is a “majestic and sublime edifice”, a “vast symphony in stone”, wrote Victor Hugo. “Every surface, every stone of this venerable pile, is a page of the history not only of the country, but of science and of art.” The devastating fire that broke out on April 15th, and destroyed much of the gothic cathedral’s wood-timbered roof and spire, stunned and distressed the French with a force that far exceeded the building’s religious significance. As the flames engulfed the roof, President Emmanuel Macron spoke for many across France when he tweeted that he was witnessing “part of us burn”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why has the fire at Notre Dame stirred such emotion in France? In a city of broad vistas and stolen glimpses, it serves as a fixed point for Parisians; a stable presence that emerges reliably into view, like a much-loved aunt, from bridges across the river Seine. Visited by 13m tourists a year, the cathedral has been the backdrop to countless expressions of awe and romance, as well as been-there selfies. Locals may be riled by the narcissistic crowds, but are proud of what draws them. The 850-year-old cathedral is a national landmark that offers something particular: a form of timelessness, drama and spirituality, to set against the modernity and engineering prowess of the Eiffel Tower.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the night, as firefighters struggled to control the blaze, it looked for a stretch as if the centuries were dissolving in flames. For Parisians, watching in eerie silence on the bridges, the wait was agonising. In his preface to “The Hunchback of Notre Dame”, the novel that reawakened the French to the cathedral’s splendour, Hugo had warned darkly that “soon, perhaps, the Cathedral itself will have vanished from the face of the earth.” As the fire blazed, the visceral fear that Hugo might have been right seemed to touch a profound yearning for Our Lady to survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cathedral had withstood ransacking during the wars of religion, looting during the revolution, two world wars and Nazi occupation, becoming an emblem of resistance in the face of a constantly disrupted history. More than this, Notre Dame is a product of the paradoxes of that history. It is where an emperor, Napoleon, was crowned in 1804, and where the founder of modern republican France, Charles de Gaulle, was remembered upon his death. It was at once a living place of worship for the French Catholic church, and the property of the French secular state: a symbol in itself of the country’s history and its present, in all its glorious contradictions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As he visited the site shortly before midnight, Mr Macron, so often perceived as out of touch, for once found the right words to express this. “Notre Dame de Paris is our history, our literature,” he declared. “The place where we have lived all our great moments, epidemics, wars and liberation. It is the epicentre of our lives and the point from which we measure distance from Paris. This history, it is ours and it is burning.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that those flames have been extinguished, questions will turn to why Notre Dame burned, and how it can be rebuilt. The Paris public prosecutor has opened an investigation, declaring that “nothing suggests it was a deliberate act.” If this was indeed an accident, the focus will be the works to renovate the 19th-century spire, which began last summer. It was the oak-beamed roof above the vaults that proved to be both so flammable, and so difficult for the fire brigade to get to. Thanks to the efforts of 400 firefighters—as well as to the craftsmanship of the 12th- and 13th-century stonemasons who built the soaring stone vaults beneath the roof—the cathedral’s main medieval structure was largely saved. Firefighters also managed to save many religious artefacts and relics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How stable the remaining structure is, and whether the stone has been permanently weakened by the intense heat, say engineers, will have to be assessed once the masonry has cooled. Mr Macron vowed that, no matter what, the cathedral will be rebuilt, and launched a fundraising initiative to that end. In a country that lacks a tradition of private philanthropy, it was notable that France’s richest businessmen vowed to contribute. Two luxury titans, Bernard Arnault and François Pinault, between them pledged €300m ($340m).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The search for somebody to blame will absorb France for some time. Many will want to know exactly what precautions were taken by those working on the renovation, and what exactly was the nature of the disaster-planning for a monument of this scale and national importance, situated amid narrow streets on an inaccessible island in the centre of the city. A broader question is whose responsibility it should be to maintain secular France’s great religious buildings. The government had contributed to the renovation of Notre Dame’s spire. But the cathedral had to raise funds to renew its bells in 2012, and the agreement between the archdiocese and the government over upkeep is unclear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the morning after the fire, tourists gathered along the cobbled quays to get their shot of the old survivor, damaged but unfallen. For locals, sadness at the damage was mixed with deep relief that it had not been far worse. At one point, and after five months of unrest by &lt;em &gt;gilets jaunes&lt;/em&gt; (yellow jackets), the fire seemed to be a ghastly symbol for the torment of France. It broke out just before Mr Macron was due to unveil his response to those protests, and to his “great national debate”, in a speech he promptly had to postpone. The moment was supposed to mark the end of a disaster. Instead, it brought another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Macron now faces a different challenge. The country was already divided, and the president unloved. Today Notre Dame is charred, and Paris, and all of France, is in pain. Just occasionally, such a national drama can help to pull a divided country together. On the night, Mr Macron made a good start. But he has yet to bring closure to his great debate. It will take particular skill to do this while offering solace to a nation still in shock after the drama of Notre Dame.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Europe&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;The agony of Notre Dame&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 20:08:50 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The right-wing Finns Party does well in Finland’s election]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/17/the-right-wing-finns-party-does-well-in-finlands-election]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_EUP002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE FINNS&lt;/small&gt; are the happiest nation in the world, according to the United Nations, and tied with Sweden and Norway for the freest, according to Freedom House. They are also at or near the top in education, not to mention consumption of coffee. But after the national election on April 14th, they have given up their claim to have solved the problem of far-right populism. The Finns Party, an anti-immigrant, Eurosceptic party previously known in English as the True Finns, surged in the final weeks and took 17.5% of the vote, just a whisker behind the winning Social Democrats at 17.7%. The Social Democrats will probably now form a centre-left government, but as in so much of Europe, the far right’s strength will make things complicated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Finns Party’s result was almost exactly the same as in 2015. But after that election, the country’s centre-right National Coalition and Centre parties thought they had tamed them by bringing them into the ruling coalition, forcing them to take responsibility for compromises such as observing &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; migration policy. But in 2017 the Finns’ frustrated hard-liners quit the government while the party’s more moderate &lt;small&gt;MP&lt;/small&gt;s (including the then-leader) split off into a new faction called Blue Reform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the election, voters backed the party’s old stalwarts, while Blue Reform failed to win any seats. The Finns Party is now as strong as ever, and more extreme. Its new leader once wrote blog posts affirming racial differences in intelligence and hoping that left-wing female politicians would be raped by migrants. The party’s campaign video is a short horror film, in which the people’s fury congeals into a “pissed-off monster” who attacks the country’s masked and traitorous leaders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other parties say they will not negotiate with the Finns Party. Antti Rinne, the Social Democrats’ leader, will try to build a coalition that matches the electorate’s move to the left after four years of centre-right rule. His most likely partners are the Greens, who also did well, and the liberal National Coalition. In terms of policy, the leftward shift may be modest. All parties but the Finns agree on the goal of making the country carbon-neutral by 2035. Extensive hydropower and nuclear energy make this realistic. (Still, notes Ilkka Haavisto of &lt;small&gt;EVA&lt;/small&gt;, a think-tank, the Finns Party implied that the government wanted to ban cars.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other big challenge before the next government is benefit reform. The country is moving towards an active, Danish-style employment policy aimed at returning the jobless to work, but the last government demanded that the unemployed find work or training within a short deadline or face cuts to their dole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was too harsh, says Joonas Rahkola of the Social Democrats’ policy unit. “People have a sense of unfairness, and are insecure about their future.” The party wants to raise the education and elder-care budgets. It should also push companies to sign better contracts with flexworkers, says Hannu Jouhki, head of the country’s trade-union association. Insecurity, he says, can push voters towards populism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As elsewhere in Europe, the election leaves Finland’s parliament more fragmented. It is hard for mainstream parties to form majorities when populists take a sixth or more of the vote. Last week, across the Gulf of Finland in Estonia, the ruling Centre Party broke its campaign vow and cut a coalition deal that included the far-right &lt;small&gt;EKRE&lt;/small&gt; party. The centrist Reform party, which finished first in the election in March but lost its chance to form a government, was furious. Still, as Finland shows, marriages with populists seldom last.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Europe&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;The populists hit back&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 20:07:42 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Big carmakers are placing vast bets on electric vehicles]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/04/17/big-carmakers-are-placing-vast-bets-on-electric-vehicles]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_WBP001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;N 1900 ONE&lt;/small&gt; in three cars on American roads ran on volts. Then oil began gushing out of Texas. Cheaper than batteries, and easier to top up, petrol fuelled the rise of mass-produced automobiles. Cost and worries about limited range have kept electric vehicles &lt;small&gt;(EV&lt;/small&gt;s) in a niche ever since. Tesla, which has made battery power sexy again in the past decade, produced just 250,000 units last year, a fraction of what Volkswagen or Toyota churn out annually. For every one of the 2m or so pure &lt;small&gt;EV&lt;/small&gt;s and plug-in hybrids, which combine batteries and internal-combustion engines (&lt;small&gt;ICE&lt;/small&gt;s), sold in 2018, the world’s carmakers shifted 50 petrol or diesel cars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;EV&lt;/small&gt; sales are, however, accelerating as quickly as electric motors themselves. Some industry-watchers reckon that they will account for nearly 15% of the global total by 2025. By then, one in five new cars in China will run on batteries, according to Bloomberg New Energy Finance, a consultancy. The chief reason such optimistic forecasts no longer look outlandish is the entry into the electric race of the car industry’s juggernauts. A survey by Reuters in January put the industry’s total planned &lt;small&gt;EV&lt;/small&gt;-related spending worldwide (including on batteries) at around $300bn over the next five to ten years. From &lt;small&gt;GM&lt;/small&gt; and Geely to Mercedes and Nissan, big carmakers all want to turn out millions of such cars—and turn a profit doing so. Their strategies range from cautious to headstrong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_WBC729.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190420_WBC729.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190420_WBC729.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190420_WBC729.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190420_WBC729.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190420_WBC729.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190420_WBC729.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190420_WBC729.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190420_WBC729.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190420_WBC729.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Making a profitable, mass-produced &lt;small&gt;EV&lt;/small&gt; has proved elusive. A battery powertrain can be three times the price of an &lt;small&gt;ICE&lt;/small&gt;. But a combination of better technology and greater scale may soon allow &lt;small&gt;EV&lt;/small&gt;s to compete on price with petrol vehicles, and enable motorists to drive long distances without the fear of running out of juice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They had better, carmakers are hoping. Worries about climate change and air pollution are prompting authorities around the world to consider phasing out new petrol and diesel engines in the coming decade. In the absence of federal regulations under America’s climate-sceptical president, Donald Trump, some progressive cities and states there are tightening local rules. Fiat Chrysler (whose chairman, John Elkann, sits on the board of &lt;em &gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s parent company) has just agreed to pay Tesla hundreds of millions of euros to count the Californian marque as part of its fleet, and thus avoid steep fines for exceeding average CO&lt;sub&gt;2&lt;/sub&gt;-emissions standards for carmakers due to come into force in the European Union next year. In China, where half the world’s &lt;small&gt;EV&lt;/small&gt;s are already sold, the government sees the electrification of transport as a way to combat choking urban smog—and to overtake the West technologically.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Western premium brands appear best positioned to take an early lead. While batteries remain pricey, fancy marques can offset the cost with the higher prices that their vehicles command. Jaguar and Audi have already broken Tesla’s monopoly at the lucrative top end of the market. Daimler, which owns Mercedes, has committed €10bn ($11.3bn) to its &lt;small&gt;EQ&lt;/small&gt; range and wants 20% of its cars to be fully electric by 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Daimler and &lt;small&gt;BMW&lt;/small&gt;, which has been bruised by losses on its poorly selling i3 electric hatchback, are hedging their bets by backing platforms—the basic architecture of a car—that are able to accommodate petrol and diesel engines as well as electric motors. This should help them contain costs, by avoiding duplication, but involves compromises over battery size and layout. Sacrificing range and interior space in this way may dent brands built on luxury and technological prowess, says Patrick Hummel of &lt;small&gt;UBS&lt;/small&gt;, a bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many mass-market firms are likewise proceeding cautiously. Their thinner margins leave less room to absorb the cost of batteries. Renault of France and South Korea’s Hyundai are nevertheless toying with the idea of a dedicated electric-only platform. &lt;small&gt;PSA&lt;/small&gt; Group has said it plans to electrify more Peugeots, Citroëns and Opels. Fiat Chrysler has made similar noises, though the Tesla tie-up suggests its near-term plans are less ambitious. Toyota’s early bet on hydrogen fuel cells, which lag behind batteries on the road to widespread adoption, had long been a distraction. The Japanese giant has now acknowledged that buyers want battery power. It is planning ten models by the early 2020s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most daring by a long way is &lt;small&gt;VW&lt;/small&gt;. The German group’s heft—it produces 10m cars a year—affords it economies of scale only Toyota could hope to match. The €30bn &lt;small&gt;VW&lt;/small&gt; plans to spend on developing &lt;small&gt;EV&lt;/small&gt;s over the next five years, plus €50bn to fit them with batteries, leaves all other carmakers in the dust. In March Herbert Diess, its chief executive, promised 70 new electric models by 2028, rather than 50 as previously pledged, and 22m &lt;small&gt;EVS&lt;/small&gt; delivered over the next ten years. The company is contemplating a huge investment in a “gigafactory” to supply its own batteries rather than depending on outside suppliers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;VW&lt;/small&gt; is already developing a dedicated platform and converting entire factories to &lt;small&gt;EV &lt;/small&gt;production. The first, at Zwickau in Germany, will eventually turn out 330,000 cars a year for the &lt;small&gt;VW&lt;/small&gt; brand as well as Audi and &lt;small&gt;SEAT&lt;/small&gt;. Its medium-sized &lt;small&gt;ID&lt;/small&gt; hatchback, to be shipped next year, will cost around €30,000, similar to an equivalent diesel-powered Golf, and travel 400-600km (250-370 miles) on a single charge. On April 14th in Shanghai Mr Diess unveiled a sport-utility vehicle to compete with Tesla’s snazzy Model &lt;small&gt;X&lt;/small&gt; in China from 2021. Once the range of &lt;small&gt;EV&lt;/small&gt;s reaches full production in 2022, &lt;small&gt;VW&lt;/small&gt; believes, such models will start breaking even. By 2025, when it hopes one-quarter of its output will be electric, they should be as profitable as petrol cars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Mike Manley, boss of Fiat Chrysler, observers, it is no longer a question of whether carmakers can supply a fleet of &lt;small&gt;EV&lt;/small&gt;s but whether people will pay for them. If governments withdraw generous subsidies which &lt;small&gt;EV&lt;/small&gt;-owners have enjoyed, charging infrastructure fails to materialise or electric cars’ pitiful resale value does not increase, motorists may be reluctant to switch to battery power. Poor sales, combined with the large upfront investments, would hit carmakers’ margins, which for mass-market brands are already about as exciting as a Soviet-era Trabant in mud brown. The financial consequences could be “ugly”, warns Bernstein, an equity-research firm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;Electric field&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the same time, the big carmakers can expect more competition from rivals unburdened by complex &lt;small&gt;ICE&lt;/small&gt; supply chains and large workforces. vw has 40,000 suppliers worldwide and directly employs 660,000 people. Lower capital intensity, and the relative simplicity of &lt;small&gt;EV&lt;/small&gt;s, which use many fewer parts than petrol vehicles and are easier to assemble, is drawing in upstarts. They include Dyson, a British maker of vacuum cleaners, and a series of Chinese Tesla-wannabes, such as &lt;small&gt;NIO&lt;/small&gt; and Byton. Bigger Chinese carmakers, such as Geely and &lt;small&gt;JAC&lt;/small&gt;, have also developed expertise in &lt;small&gt;EV&lt;/small&gt;s. With domestic sales stalling, they are beginning to eye export markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other technological bumps are meanwhile starting to test the industry’s chassis. Self-driving cars and ride-sharing are forcing companies to rethink their established business model. Investing in &lt;small&gt;EV&lt;/small&gt;s now leaves them with less to spend on adapting to everything else. They may be hoping that the electric race will serve as a practice lap for wider oncoming disruption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Business&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Charging ahead&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 20:07:41 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why British wage growth is picking up at last]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/04/17/why-british-wage-growth-is-picking-up-at-last]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BRP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;P&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;ERHAPS NO OTHER&lt;/small&gt; factor better explains why so many Britons want radical change, from voting for Brexit to backing Jeremy Corbyn’s far-left Labour Party. Since the financial crisis of 2008-09 Britain’s wage growth has been dreadful. Adjusting for inflation, wages fell from 2007 to 2017, a worse performance than in any other &lt;small&gt;OECD&lt;/small&gt; country except Mexico or Greece. At last, however, the tables are turning. Data released on April 16th show that nominal pay is growing at about 3.5% a year (see chart), or 1.5% a year in real terms. Can this growth continue to accelerate?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The obvious cause of strengthening pay is the tight labour market. When unemployment hit its post-crisis high of 8.5% in 2011, employers knew that they could get away with offering meagre or no pay rises. Workers’ bargaining power has since grown, as joblessness has fallen. Unemployment is just 3.9%, the lowest in four decades. Britain has about three vacancies for each 100 employee jobs, the highest ratio since the data began in 2001, meaning bosses have to try harder to fill posts. Nominal pay in the hospitality sector, which has a particularly high number of job postings, is growing at 5% a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BRC734.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190420_BRC734.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190420_BRC734.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190420_BRC734.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190420_BRC734.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190420_BRC734.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190420_BRC734.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190420_BRC734.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190420_BRC734.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190420_BRC734.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;A hot jobs market is not the only cause of rising average pay. Another relates to the mix of jobs in the economy. Following the financial crisis, posts in low-productivity, low-paying sectors such as agriculture proliferated. Having more poorly paid positions dragged down the average. Yet lately Britain has created relatively more high-paying jobs. Strawberry-pickers have made way for stock-pickers. In the year to September 2018 the changing composition of the workforce boosted average nominal wage growth by 0.5 percentage points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stronger pay may also owe something to rising productivity. How much workers produce ultimately determines how much they earn. After stagnating in 2007-14, more recently output per hour has grown by about 1% a year in real terms. Silvana Tenreyro of the Bank of England has floated the idea that some of these gains might not have yet shown up in the statistics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The question is whether wage growth will accelerate further. Workers will hope that it does: at its current rate real pay will not return to its pre-crisis peak until 2022. Yet few economists believe Britain will soon resume the healthy productivity growth of the post-war period, which was consistent with real-terms pay rises of some 3% a year. Most economic forecasts have productivity growing at an annual rate of about 1% this year and next.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Already there are signs that firms are struggling to afford the modest pay settlements that their workers are demanding. The cost of staffing per unit of output, a measure of domestically generated inflation, grew by 1.7% in 2017 but by 2.7% last year. To absorb these extra costs some firms are accepting lower profits. Other firms are passing them on to customers, stoking consumer-price inflation, which&lt;small&gt; &lt;/small&gt;hovers around the Bank of England’s target of 2%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now there is little need for the bank to raise interest rates, which would bring down inflation. Uncertainty over Brexit, which is likely to continue until October and perhaps beyond, argues in favour of holding fire. Yet the difficult truth is that Britain’s current rate of wage growth, modest by historical standards, is about as high as it can go without pushing inflation above target. It will be some time before Britons’ pay squeeze is truly over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Britain&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Take it or leave it&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 20:07:40 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The wave of unicorn IPOs reveals Silicon Valley’s groupthink]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/briefing/2019/04/17/the-wave-of-unicorn-ipos-reveals-silicon-valleys-groupthink]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD001_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;F YOU WANT&lt;/small&gt; to go unicorn spotting, take a turn around the brand-new park on top of San Francisco’s Transbay bus terminal. This is not because it is perched on a spectacular, undulating building that itself looks quite like a mythical beast (Moby-Dick, in this case) nor because its tastefully planted flora, all native to flower-power California, offer a particularly enticing equine habitat. It is just that, as a would-be icon of San Francisco’s business district, the park is conveniently placed for looking out on their corporate headquarters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are 88 privately held startups worth more than $1bn each in the San Francisco Bay Area, more than in any other region in the world, and a fair few of them, including Slack, a corporate messaging service, and Instacart, a delivery firm, are hard by the Transbay terminal. You can’t quite see the headquarters of Lyft and Uber, two ride-hailing services, from its leafy roof, but were you to climb the swanky Millennium Tower next door you could.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The hitch is that the park is currently inaccessible. Last September, just six weeks after it opened, cracks found in two steel beams forced the closure of the Transbay terminal’s crowning gardens as well as the rest of it. You can still climb the Millennium Tower—but you need to be aware that the city’s tallest residential building has developed an unwelcome departure from the perpendicular, something which is generating a prodigious amount of litigation and not a little mockery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rather than damaging the emblematic purpose for which this sort of prestige architecture was conceived, such shortcomings enrich it. With buildings and businesses alike, everything looks shiny and new from a distance. The unicorns are exciting businesses from the same Silicon Valley stables as Alphabet (&lt;em &gt;née &lt;/em&gt;Google), Apple and Facebook. Indeed, the production of unicorns has become the dominant part of what the Valley does. And an unprecedented number of the beasts have either just offered their shares to the world through initial public offerings (&lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt;s)—Lyft did so on March 29th—or are gearing up to do so, as Uber will on May 10th. It is not the only such cavalcade; a lot of Chinese unicorns are approaching &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt;s too. Memories of the epic public debuts of Facebook and Google, and also of Alibaba, in China, make this a heady prospect for some investors. The American companies alone stand to raise up to $100bn, according to Kathleen Smith of Renaissance Capital, a fund-cum-research firm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But on closer inspection, there is trouble afoot. Look the market-bound herd of unicorns in the teeth and they are not as impressive as their myth might have you think. Some seem bred for show, not for work; not all of them are up to winning their races. These weaknesses are not just individual quirks; they are signs that the business culture which has tailored itself to churning out such beasts is beginning to suffer from its own structural flaws and lopsidedness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;A knacker’s yard in reverse&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Aileen Lee, the founder of Cowboy Ventures, an investment fund, gave the word “unicorn” its current connotation in 2013, she saw the term as betokening something both wonderful and rare. Back then, that made sense. In 2013 Ms Lee found just 38 unicorns in America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today there are 156, and slightly more than that elsewhere, according to &lt;small&gt;CB&lt;/small&gt; Insights, a data provider. There are three explanations for this population boom: an ideology that sees the rapid creation of companies with very large user bases as the best—possibly the only—business strategy available; an infrastructure that makes it ever easier to follow through on this belief; and a climate in which, until recently, there was not much pressure to take these new companies public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ideological analysis is an odd combination of cornucopianism and constraints. First, the plenty. The Valley believes that “software is eating the world”, and that there is still a lot of the business world for it to eat. As atoms are replaced by bits—or, more prosaically, possessions and activities by convenient services ordered through screens—it becomes possible for industry after industry to be disrupted by startups. But the nature of the disruption means that in any given industry only a very limited number of startups can make good. Network effects, which make the value of the system grow more with each new user the more users it has, mean that the big get bigger while the small stay small, and that the quicker you can get bigger the biggerer you get.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This does not necessarily mean monopoly; some sectors, such as ride-hailing, may support a big fish and a littler one. But it does mean that growing as large as possible as fast as possible—“blitzscaling”—becomes a paramount goal. As Reid Hoffman of Greylock Partners, a venture-capital firm, and the co-author of a book about blitzscaling, puts it: “In a connected world, someone will build an Amazon. The only question is who and how.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This analysis has changed the way that startups are born and bred. During the dotcom boom of the 1990s venture capital was decidedly artisanal. Entrepreneurs came up with an idea, made guesstimates to back it up and pitched it to venture capitalists. If they bought in, the startups would spend much of their multi-million-dollar jackpot on building their infrastructure before rushing to go public, hoping thereby to get their hands on the much larger amounts of money they needed to grow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the debacle of the dotcom bust, things got more serious. As size became increasingly valued, ways to build it were developed. Today there is a “new regime of company formation”, according to Martin Kenney and John Zysman, of the University of California in Davis and Berkeley, respectively, the authors of a paper entitled “Unicorns, Cheshire Cats, and the New Dilemmas of Entrepreneurial Finance”. The design and manufacture of unicorns has become industrialised, and many of the ingredients needed are available on tap as online services. Smartphones let the companies distribute what they offer at home and abroad, social media let them market it and cloud computing lets them ramp up as demand grows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet while the production of unicorns gathered pace and slickness, their disposal did not keep up. The rate at which venture-backed companies move on to the public markets has slowed. In 2013 the average age of a venture-backed American company putting on an &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt; was seven years. By 2018 it had grown to ten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One reason for this was regulation. After the dotcom bubble burst, new rules intended to protect investors, particularly the Sarbanes-Oxley Act, made going public much more burdensome. The &lt;small&gt;JOBS&lt;/small&gt; Act of 2012 subsequently increased the number of shareholders beyond which startups must disclose financial information from 500 to 2,000, excluding holders of stock options. That made it easier to stay private longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;Gates of horn and ivory&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;And there was no significant shortage of private capital willing, indeed eager, to help with that. A dearth of interesting alternative investments and endemic fear of missing out saw institutional investors, often from hedge and sovereign-wealth funds, eager to join in ever larger rounds of financing. As Randy Komisar, a venture capitalist at Kleiner Perkins, puts it: “Silicon Valley’s lust for scaling...is more a result of the desires of capital than the needs of innovation.” Last year investors financed more than 120 rounds of more than $100m, &lt;small&gt;CB&lt;/small&gt; Insights says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At last, though, according to Barrett Daniels, an &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt; expert at Deloitte, an auditing and consulting firm, a number of factors have come together to bring this period of reticence to an end. A lot of venture-capital funds were started around 2010, and they mostly have a ten-year term; investors want to cash out. A number of public listings last year showed that public markets have a big appetite for tech shares. And the window of opportunity may soon close; a global downturn would both limit investors’ appetite and severely test some of the unicorns’ business models.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much the same might happen if a number of &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt;s failed to live up to their hype. So again the incentives are to go big and go quick. The move to the exits is not quite a stampede, but it is a pretty concerted group trot, even a canter. As many as 235 venture-backed American firms have plans to go public this year, says Ms Smith.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To get a sense of the going, &lt;em &gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; has examined a panel of a dozen former and current internet-focused unicorns in Silicon Valley and elsewhere (see chart 1). It is not a random sample, being weighted towards both prominence and accessible data. But it includes most of the larger prospects and covers a range of industries. Uber and Lyft are in transport, Spotify in music-streaming, WeWork in real estate, Meituan and Pinduoduo in Chinese e-commerce. Six are American, five Asian and one European. Like unicorns at large, they are on average ten years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC724.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC724.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC724.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC724.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC724.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC724.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC724.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC724.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC724.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC724.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;These firms are looking at a combined valuation of more than a third of a trillion dollars—roughly, as it happens, the same as that which resulted from the &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt;s of Alibaba (2014), Facebook (2012) and Google (2004). Those &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt;s, which led to the creation of over a trillion dollars of value, were among the most successful ever and have been burned into the memory of fund managers. If you owned those shares you outperformed; if you didn’t you risked being fired.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current herd all seek to suggest that they offer the same sort of opportunity as that illustrious trinity: vast potential markets; limited physical plant and staff; high margins; imposing barriers to entry. They lay stress on their user numbers—2bn of them in all, though not all are frequent customers or paying ones. They claim that the areas they work in are but a subset of the markets they can hope to dominate. Uber and Lyft say that the entire transport industry is their hunting ground, rather than the modest taxi trade; Airbnb is looking at lodging of all sorts. They also point to strong revenue growth of 44% for the median firm in the past quarter compared with the year before. Overheads are scant. They have just $6bn of fixed assets between them, and not many staff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;Queens of air and darkness&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what they also lack, in 11 cases out of 12, are profits. Today, according to Jay Ritter of the University of Florida, 84% of companies pursuing &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt;s have no profits. That is remarkably high. Ten years ago, the proportion was just 33%. To see profitlessness as rampant as today’s you have to go back to the peak of the dotcom boom in 2000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC721.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC721.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC721.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC721.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC721.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC721.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC721.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC721.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC721.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC721.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back then the promise (one soon and spectacularly broken) was that profits would follow once the companies grew. This time round, though, the profit-free companies have already grown. Indeed our panel has burned through $47bn doing so (see chart 2); its companies got through $14bn in 2018 alone. This is profligate even by the standards of Amazon, which before and after its &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt; was seen as a particularly profit-averse company; it had cumulative losses of $3bn between 1995 and 2002. Uber lost almost $4bn just last year, excluding exceptional items.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If all this dearly bought growth has not supplied profits, what will? The unicorns have three answers: yet more growth; more spending by existing customers; and higher margins. The first is not necessarily that plausible. Among the companies in our panel that disclosed the number of customers they have in America, growth slowed to 9% last year. Though priding themselves on their overall user numbers, the firms in our panel are reluctant to reveal details of customer churn—how often customers switch to rival firms or switch off completely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD002_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD002_0.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD002_0.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD002_0.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD002_0.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD002_0.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD002_0.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD002_0.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD002_0.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD002_0.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is more, few of the firms sit behind barriers to entry as strong as those that protected Alibaba, Facebook and Google. They can lose customers as well as gain them. Lots of property companies can rent out office space, as WeWork does. Spotify customers can get music from Apple, too. Drivers often toggle between Lyft and Uber apps; so do passengers. There are already several big Chinese e-commerce firms to choose from.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To counter this concern the companies ask investors to consider “cohort analysis”, which separates out customers by vintage. Lyft says that customers who first used its service in 2015 took 2.7 times as many rides last year as they did back then. WeWork says that in its “mature” offices the revenue for each desk that it rents out is 50% higher than in other locations. The firms also argue that they can sell new stuff both to existing customers and new ones. Perhaps the best-known such strategy is Uber now offering food deliveries through Uber Eats, but the other 11 are expanding their suite of services, too. This, though, reveals something of a tension. If these firms can move on to other people’s turf, can they be sure that their own turf is as well protected as they would like investors to think? Plenty of firms are keen to offer people a diverse range of services through their phones, including Walmart, JPMorgan Chase, Apple, Amazon and Netflix in America and Alibaba and Tencent in China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC739.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC739.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC739.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC739.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC739.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC739.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC739.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC739.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC739.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBC739.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The third line of defence is “operating leverage”: economies of scale will kick in, allowing their margins to soar. This is plausible, but there is little evidence as yet that it is true. For a subset of ten firms for which quarterly data are available, total sales have doubled since mid-2017, which is impressive; but there has been no obvious improvement in operating margins, which were around minus 30% both in aggregate and for the median firm (see chart 3). Contrary to the sales-pitch, some of these firms face high variable costs. Insurance costs for the ride-hailing firms are rising sharply as they provide more trips.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of this necessarily means they are bad businesses. But it does make them look like very pricey ones. All told, the &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt; valuations the companies in our panel have received or are apparently looking for add up to $350bn. Based on a discounted cashflow model, in aggregate the dozen firms will need to increase their sales by a compound annual rate of 49% for ten years to justify that valuation. That is the same as the average growth of Amazon, Alphabet and Facebook in the decades after their &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt;s. In other words, these firms have to be as likely to outperform the very best of the previous crop as to underperform them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that is not enough. Justifying the valuation means not just staggering increases in sales, but also a very large improvement in margins. In aggregate these would have to increase by 34 percentage points. That would be truly unprecedented. The average for Amazon, Facebook and Google was only 19 percentage points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;Public down rounds&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is no secret why the valuations are high. The logic of the unicorn-building business requires it. Firms need not only to get big but also to be seen to be getting big; winning unicorn status and continuing to grow quickly thereafter is important for branding and attracting top talent. Thus every investment round is engineered to create a higher valuation than the previous one; the alternative, a “down round”, is seen as a dismal sign. To ensure that the only way is up, investors coming in at later stages get privileges over earlier ones, such as guaranteed returns. This means that their shares are worth more than those issued earlier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The valuation figure generated by an investment round assumes that all the shares are worth the same as the shares just issued. If you take into account the fact that this is not the case, and that earlier shares are in fact less valuable, it is possible to calculate the degree to which such values are overstated. According to Ilya Strebulaev, who teaches at the Stanford University business school, such calculations show the average unicorn to be overvalued by about 60%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overvaluation does not mean that the coming spate of &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt;s will not go ahead, or that they will not raise money. But it does suggest some rough times ahead. Some unicorns have already floated for less than they were previously said to be worth. Pinterest was privately valued at $12bn but is expected to go public at about $11bn. Others have seen the pop they got at their &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt; swiftly dissipate. When Lyft went public its share price popped 8.7% on the first day of trading, giving it a market capitalisation of $22.4bn. But many got out of the stock, and short sellers piled in. Lyft’s capitalisation is now $16bn, and its shares are now well below their price at the &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That bumpy ride may be an exception. Lyft has threatened to sue Morgan Stanley, an investment bank, for offering a short-selling product to pre-&lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt; investors who are usually bound by agreements not to sell their shares for some time, typically six months (the bank denies the allegations). But if Lyft’s rollercoaster turns out to be the rule, unicorns could become a much less attractive investment and the flow of capital into Silicon Valley could slow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This all suggests that the Valley would be wise to come up with an alternative to blitzscale-and-hope as a strategy. So far, it has not. “I don’t like the model of growth at almost all costs, but I don’t see the end of it yet,” says Mr Komisar. Instead, investors are fine-tuning the unicorn-making machine. Funds will continue to professionalise by using more data and even automated algorithms to make investment decisions, predicts Mike Volpi of Index Ventures. Some venture capitalists are thinking about ways that they might do away with the &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt; entirely. “Firms are getting so big that they no longer can go public,” says Mike Moritz of Sequoia Capital, which has put money into 20 unicorns. “What you need is four to five like-minded investors with a time horizon of 20 years.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A more fundamental threat to the model is the possibility that barriers to entry and the benefits of size are both getting harder to acquire and offering less value to their possessors. The tech industry has benefited from a legal exceptionalism, particularly when offering services to consumers. The existing giants took full advantage of Western governments’ haplessness. They successfully lobbied to avoid being held responsible for the content produced by their users, or restricted from doing what they pleased with personal data, or bothered by pesky antitrust laws. Regulators were often overpowered by blitzscaling startups, rushing for size.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now the world is undergoing what could be called the “great pivot”, in reference to the about-face startups perform when they see that their original idea does not work. Politically, the dark sides of some online services—disinformation campaigns, data leaks, monopolistic behaviour and so on—are getting harder to ignore. Regulators have started pushing back. The effects of Europe’s strict new privacy law, the General Data Protection Regulation, are being felt around the world. Britain, a bellwether in online regulation, is considering both sweeping new regulations of online content and stricter antitrust laws. The advantages and perquisites of unregulated size are under challenge; so are the routes by which it can be attained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;Time to cultivate the garden&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond this there appears to be a growing concern that the innovation produced by some unicorns does not leave society better off. Whether the benefits of being able to run more and more of one’s life through screens outweigh the costs remains an open question, argues Dan Breznitz of the University of Toronto. There are real benefits. But critics point to real downsides, too. Increased congestion and other environmental costs, a weakening of public transport systems, the precarious lives of the workers who make these platforms function and a more friable body politic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The wave of &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt;s is unlikely to reverse these trends. Indeed it may exacerbate them, especially if the firms do less than spectacularly. Google almost quadrupled in value in the year after floating, which bought tech a lot of diffuse goodwill. No one expects Uber to do that. If today’s unicorns turn out to have created most of their value for private investors before floating, the public will take note.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD003_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD003_0.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD003_0.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD003_0.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD003_0.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD003_0.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD003_0.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD003_0.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD003_0.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190420_FBD003_0.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;How should Silicon Valley react? Tim O’Reilly, a publisher who serves as one of the industry’s intellectual leaders, argues that it needs a deep rethink. “The pursuit of monopoly has led Silicon Valley astray,” he recently told the readers of &lt;em &gt;Quartz&lt;/em&gt;, a website. “The goal for Lyft and Uber—and for all of the entrepreneurs being urged to blitzscale—should be to make their companies more sustainable, not just more explosive.” But if the logic of the sort of technologies the Valley develops is indeed inherently monopolistic, game theory suggests that that may be hard to do. What value is there in a sustainable business model that gets outcompeted by a blitzscaler?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Again the park on top of the Transbay terminal is an apt metaphor. It is lovely and airy; but it is hemmed in by corporate buildings whose workers enjoy an ease of access to its flowers and fountains denied to &lt;em &gt;hoi polloi&lt;/em&gt;. It is a walled garden, even if it has some gates. Meanwhile the terminal on which it sits is still a decade away from becoming the transport hub it is meant to be. Things that are gleaming and shiny and particularly nice for the better connected are not bad in themselves, even when they are hyped. But they are hardly the be-all and end-all of human innovation, inspiration and aspiration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Briefing&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Herd instincts&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 20:07:39 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why the middle-aged are replacing teenagers in maternity wards]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/04/17/why-the-middle-aged-are-replacing-teenagers-in-maternity-wards]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BRP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;N HER 20S&lt;/small&gt;, Claire Fenelon was much too busy to have children. After going to university as a mature student, she spent a year in Australia then a few months in France, picking up the language. “I didn’t want to feel I was missing out,” she says. But by the time she was ready to settle down, she struggled to find the right man. At 39, she froze her eggs. Eight years later and still lacking a partner, she decided to “go solo”, giving birth to a son with the help of a sperm donor. “I was desperate to have kids,” she says. “But I didn’t want to have them with the wrong person.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Fenelon belongs to a growing cohort of middle-aged women on maternity wards. As in other rich countries, the fertility rate in England and Wales is dwindling. But among women aged 40 and over the conception rate is rising. It jumped by 2.6% in 2017 and has more than doubled since 1990, according to statistics published on April 15th. Meanwhile, at the other end of the age spectrum, an even starker change is afoot. The official figures chart the tenth consecutive annual fall in the rate of teenage pregnancies. Since 2007 the conception rate for 15- to 17-year-old girls has dived by 57%. The conception rates of the youngest and oldest mothers are now close to converging (see chart). Middle-aged maternity may soon be more common than teenage pregnancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BRC726.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190420_BRC726.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190420_BRC726.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190420_BRC726.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190420_BRC726.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190420_BRC726.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190420_BRC726.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190420_BRC726.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190420_BRC726.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190420_BRC726.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Advances in health care help to explain the convergence. Although assisted conception accounts for only a small proportion of pregnancies, it is growing more popular and more successful. Between 1991 and 2016, birth rates from &lt;em &gt;in vitro&lt;/em&gt; fertilisation treatment increased by more than 85%. In 2016 more than 20,000 babies were born following &lt;small&gt;IVF&lt;/small&gt; (out of a total of 696,000 births that year). About three-fifths of women who use it are 35 or over. Demand is likely to increase as women learn of others whose treatment has been successful. Ms Fenelon was inspired by a magazine article about egg-freezing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Labour governments of 1997-2010 pioneered a public-health strategy to curb rates of teen pregnancy. Nurses manned separate sexual-health clinics for young people, so teenagers did not run the risk of bumping into their parents at family planning centres. Careers advisers were trained to offer health advice as well as tips about jobs, and social workers and foster carers were encouraged to identify those most at risk of an early pregnancy and talk to them about relationships. Doctors were taught how to insert long-acting reversible contraception, such as implants, which are less prone to human error than condoms or the Pill. A study published in the &lt;em &gt;Lancet&lt;/em&gt;, a medical journal, in 2016 concluded that the strategy had “probably contributed” to the falling under-18 conception rate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But government intervention in England cannot explain why the teenage-pregnancy rate began to fall at roughly the same time in Scotland, which was not covered by the strategy, and also dipped elsewhere in Europe, points out Peter Craig of Glasgow University. And since many women who give birth in their 40s do not rely on assisted conception, social factors must also have played a part. “The best form of contraception is aspiration,” says Penelope Law, a gynaecologist. Women in their teens and 20s are much more likely than in previous generations to prioritise education and work over starting a family.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Studies have found that female educational enrolment is strongly associated with delaying cohabitation, marriage and childbirth. In the ten years from 2006, the female higher-education participation rate rose by ten percentage points in England, to 56%. In a survey of women at a family planning clinic in Scotland, a third of those who wanted children cited not being at the right stage in their career or concerns that having children would affect success at work as a reason why they had not yet had a child. Many more said they were “enjoying life as it is” or attributed the delay to issues with their current relationship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the national convergence masks persistent regional divides. The over-40s’ conception rate in London is more than double that in the North East, which has a far higher rate of teenage pregnancy than the capital. In Middlesbrough, a northern town, the rate of teenage conception is 145% above the national average, and ticking up. If opportunities are not spread more evenly across the country, northerners may be left holding the baby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Britain&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Maybe later, baby&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(此域名已被污染，谢谢大家一直以来的支持)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 20:07:38 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tech’s new stars have it all—except a path to high profits]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/04/17/techs-new-stars-have-it-all-except-a-path-to-high-profits]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190420_LDD001_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;NVESTORS OFTEN&lt;/small&gt; describe the world of business in terms of animals, such as bears, bulls, hawks, doves and dogs. Right now, mere ponies are being presented as unicorns: privately held tech firms worth over $1bn that are supposedly strong and world-beating—miraculous almost. Next month Uber will raise some $10bn in what may turn out to be this year’s biggest initial public offering (&lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt;). It will be America’s third-biggest-ever tech &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt;, after Alibaba and Facebook. Airbnb and WeWork could follow Lyft, which has already floated, and Pinterest, which was set to do so as &lt;em &gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; went to press. In China, an &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt; wave that began last year rumbles on. Thanks to fashionable products and armies of users, these firms have a total valuation in the hundreds of billions of dollars. They and their venture-capital (&lt;small&gt;VC&lt;/small&gt;) backers are rushing to sell shares at high prices to mutual funds and pension schemes run for ordinary people. There is, however, a problem with the unicorns: their business models.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we report this week, a dozen unicorns that have listed, or are likely to, posted combined losses of $14bn last year. Their cumulative losses are $47bn (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/node/21763121&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Briefing&lt;/a&gt;). Their services, from ride-hailing to office rental, are often deeply discounted in order to supercharge revenue growth. The justification for this is the Silicon Valley doctrine of “blitzscaling” in order to conquer “winner-takes-all” markets—or in plain English, conducting a high-speed land grab in the hope of finding gold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet some unicorns lack the economies of scale and barriers to entry that their promoters proclaim. At the same time, tighter regulation will constrain their freedom to move fast and break things. Investors should demand lower prices in the &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt;s, or stay away. Tech entrepreneurs and their backers need to rethink what has become an unsustainable approach to building firms and commercialising ideas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today’s unicorn-breeding industry would not have been possible 25 years ago. In 1994 only $6bn flowed into &lt;small&gt;VC&lt;/small&gt; funds, which doled out cheques in the single-digit millions. Before Amazon staged its &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt; in 1997 it had raised a total of only $10m. Three things changed. Growing fast became easier thanks to cloud computing, smartphones and social media, which let startups spread rapidly around the world. Low interest rates left investors chasing returns. And a tiny elite of superstar firms, including Google, Facebook and China’s Alibaba and Tencent, proved that huge markets, high profits and natural monopolies, along with limited physical assets and light regulation, were the secret to untold riches. Suddenly tech became all about applying this magic formula to as many industries as possible, using piles of money to speed up the process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Make no mistake, the unicorns are more substantial than the turkeys of the 2000 tech bubble, such as Pets.com, which went bust ten months after its &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt;. Ride apps are more convenient than taxis, food delivery is lightning quick, and streaming music is better than downloading files. Like Google and Alibaba, the unicorns have large user bases. Their core businesses can avoid owning physical assets by outsourcing their &lt;small&gt;IT&lt;/small&gt; to cloud providers. As &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt; documents point out, their sales are growing fast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The big worry is that their losses reflect not temporary growing pains but markets which are contested and customers who are promiscuous. In the key digital monopolies, the network becomes more valuable to each user the more people use it—hence Facebook’s 67% market share in social networking. The unicorns’ dynamics are not as compelling. Despite subsidies, ride-sharing customers are not locked in to one firm. No wonder Lyft’s shares have fallen by over 20% below their &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt; price. Anyone can lease an office and rent out desks, not just WeWork. Some unicorns have to fight other richly funded rivals and established firms. Spotify, which listed in 2018, has a 34% share of music streaming in America and is going head-to-head with Apple.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because the unicorns’ markets are contested, margins have not consistently improved, despite fast-rising sales. Managers are terrified of cutting their vast marketing spending, for fear of losing customers. Many firms are scrambling to develop ancillary products to try to make money from their users. And without deep moats around their businesses a permanent question-mark hangs over the unicorns: if Uber really is worth $100bn, after investing only $15bn or so, why wouldn’t its rivals keep trying their luck, or an established tech giant be tempted in?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;External forces will make blitzscaling harder, too. The earlier generation of firms did not face many rules—few legislators had imagined the internet—so they could charge ahead first and beg forgiveness later. The unicorns followed suit: Airbnb sidestepped taxes on hotels and Uber drove through regulations on taxi-licensing. Today a reaction is in full swing, including over digital taxes and data and content laws. The unicorns’ investor circulars have pages dedicated to their legal dangers and gory regulatory risks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All this is good for consumers. Money is being thrown at them; the subsidy to the public from the dozen firms amounts to $20bn a year. Whereas the commanding heights of the tech industry, such as search and social media, have been monopolised, the unicorns are at least creating competition in other areas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Investors, meanwhile, need to hold their nerve. It is tempting to extrapolate the triumph of Google and Alibaba to an entire new group of firms. In fact, most unicorns face a long war of attrition and soggy margins. Eventually, struggling firms may be bought. And here another risk arises: most unicorns cap outside investors’ voting rights (Uber is an exception), and many have “poison pills” too, making takeovers hard and constraining investors’ ability to intervene if the firms do not eventually find a way to make enough profits to justify their &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt; valuations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And what of Silicon Valley and China’s bustling tech hubs, where the unicorn idea was dreamed up? Billions of dollars are flowing to &lt;small&gt;VC&lt;/small&gt;s, tech founders and employees. The familiar question is how many luxury homes, philanthropic vanity projects and personal space programmes they will pay for. The urgent question is how this capital will be recycled into new technology firms. The blitzscale philosophy of buying customers at any price is peaking. After the unicorns, a new and more convincing species of startup will have to be engineered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Leaders&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;The trouble with tech unicorns&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 20:07:37 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>