<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[A plane crash in Moscow raises safety questions about the Sukhoi Superjet]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/gulliver/2019/05/07/a-plane-crash-in-moscow-raises-safety-questions-about-the-sukhoi-superjet]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_BLP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T15:58:00Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;ON MAY 5TH a Sukhoi Superjet operated by Aeroflot, Russia’s flag carrier, erupted in flames while attempting an emergency landing at Sheremetyevo Airport in Moscow. CCTV footage shows the airliner make a hard landing, bounce perhaps 20ft in the air, and plunge back down with sufficient force to break the undercarriage and set the fuel tanks alight. At least 41 of the 78 passengers and crew died.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Too little is known at this early stage to make informed assessments of the cause of the crash. Some survivors have claimed that the aircraft was struck by lightning shortly after take-off. That should have been an unremarkable if unnerving event. The average commercial jet will be struck by lightning once a year. Complications almost never arise because modern airframes are designed to conduct electrical currents safely across their exterior surfaces. If, as some have suggested, the lightning caused damage to the Superjet’s internal electrical components, questions will need to be asked about the design of the aircraft. Equally, investigators will need to know why the pilots attempted an emergency landing without first dumping fuel in order to reduce the risk of damage if the kerosene ignited.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;The Soviet Union had a torrid air-safety record, but over the past decade Russia’s airlines, and particularly state-owned Aeroflot, have moved into line with global standards. Aeroflot is included on the Operational Safety Audit registry run by the International Air Transport Association, an international trade body which certifies airlines to the highest measurable standards of any recognised global organisation. Air crashes are still more common in Russia than in many other countries, but its pilots have to contend with one of the most extreme climates on the planet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;And so attention has focused on Sukhoi, the Russian state-owned planemaker that manufactures the Superjet. The plane does not suffer the problems of many Soviet-era airliners. It has suffered only one other fatal accident, in 2012, when a demonstration flight in Indonesia crashed, killing 45 people, due to pilot error. The jet has lost favour with carriers over the past year, not so much because of any design errors, but because of problems relating, in particular, to engine maintenance. These problems have been costly for certain airlines as Sukhoi’s failure to develop a global maintenance network has resulted in a shortage of spare parts. This factor alone has been off-putting for airlines. Citijet of Ireland, Brussels Airlines and Adria Airways of Slovenia have already dumped the craft. After the latest crash, Yamal Airlines of Russia cancelled its planned purchase of 10 Superjets. Even if investigators exonerate Sukhoi of any blame for the crash, the planemaker is unlikely to convince any new airlines to fly the jet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 00:07:05 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Punters are betting a princely sum on the royal baby’s name]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/07/punters-are-betting-a-princely-sum-on-the-royal-babys-name]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_woc667.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR AN event shrouded in secrecy, yesterday’s royal birth has had gamblers reaching for their pockets. Ever since the Duke and Duchess of Sussex announced in October 2018 that they were expecting a child “in the spring”, they have shared scant information about their due date, let alone the expected sex of their first child. The baby boy’s arrival even caught some news organisations by surprise, with lunchtime “push” notifications that the Duchess had gone into labour being followed swiftly by reports that she had given birth many hours earlier. Despite this uncertainty, or perhaps because of it, a number of bookmakers have allowed punters to bet on the royal baby’s arrival date, sex, weight and name.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far, the public’s predictive powers have been weak. On Saturday two major bookmakers were giving the chances of a baby girl a 75% likelihood, and just 35% for a boy. (A higher percentage in such a binary market reflects more money being staked on it, and the extra 10% is how bookies make money regardless of the outcome). One gambling firm reports a healthy profit on bets that Ms Markle would give birth in April. And a late flurry of wagers over the weekend on the child’s name saw Diana usurped as the leading contender in favour of Ivy, which at one point had a probability of 41%—a huge prediction given that the sex had not yet been revealed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With all gambling activity now focused on the royal moniker, an industry spokesman estimates that the £500,000 wagered on the name so far could double by April 8th, when the announcement is expected. Alexander and Spencer are currently the leading contenders at 19%. If the gambling public’s predictions so far are anything to go by, expect another surprise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;More on the royal family:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.1843magazine.com/features/can-meghan-markle-modernise-the-monarchy&quot;&gt;Can Meghan Markle modernise the monarchy?&lt;/a&gt; [July 2018]&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/03/08/is-girls-education-the-great-leap-forward-for-feminism&quot;&gt;The Economist asks with Meghan Markle, Annie Lennox, Adwoa Aboah, Julia Gillard and other guests&lt;/a&gt; [March 2019]&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/international/2019/04/27/how-monarchies-survive-modernity&quot;&gt;How monarchies survive modernity&lt;/a&gt; [April 2019]&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;
&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/WIOfEHlVp_c&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 22:07:28 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[An exhibition of material and visual culture from the Calais “Jungle”]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/07/an-exhibition-of-material-and-visual-culture-from-the-calais-jungle]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_BKP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T13:27:29Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AT THE back of the Pitt Rivers Museum in Oxford, beyond the Mexican caricature masks and Siberian underwear made from reindeer hide, is a small room with a big show. The first thing you see at the entrance is a hand-stencilled sign that says: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Welcome to the Jungle&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pop. 8143&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Children 1496&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Unaccompanied 1291”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The “Jungle” here is the Calais Jungle, an encampment for migrants and refugees who, having crossed from Africa and the Middle East, eked out an existence outside the city in northern France while they waited for passage to Britain. The official version is that the camp was in use between January 2015 and October 2016, after which 6,400 migrants were removed in 170 buses, with the aim, according to &lt;em&gt;Le Monde&lt;/em&gt;, of resettling them in different parts of France. On October 26th 2016 the French interior ministry announced that the Calais “Jungle” had been taken apart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a counterpoint to this narrative, Dan Hicks, a professor of archaeology at Oxford University, and a French colleague, Sarah Mallet, set about telling a different, and ongoing, story. Through drawings, photographs, objects and audio recordings—most of them borrowed from volunteers who worked in the camp—they have turned a political irritation into a powerful human drama about cruelty and kindness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.oapen.org/viewer/web/viewer.html?file=http://www.oapen.org/document/1004862&quot;&gt;The book that accompanies the show&lt;/a&gt; describes in detail how the authorities on both sides of the Channel helped create the beginnings of what Theresa May, when she was home secretary, described as “a really hostile environment for illegal migrants”. Residents of the “Jungle” are treated to “an endless guerrilla siege”, walled in by concrete and barbed wire, their tents cut open with blades and sprayed with teargas and then burned. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What might, in other hands, have been voyeurism or a piece of poverty tourism turns out to be anything but. The Pitt Rivers opened in 1884, the same year as the Berlin Conference that partitioned Africa. Like other anthropology museums of the time, it subscribed to the vogue for placing human beings across the world in various categories of  “us” and “them”, with Europeans sitting at the top of a supposed human hierarchy. Conscious of this history—“our national borders and anthropology museums are both Victorian technologies of classification,” the exhibition notes say; “they were designed to forge differences between people”—the curators have chosen to highlight the drama and boredom of everyday life in a migrant camp. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp502.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;A series of delicate pencil-and-wash drawings tell individual stories of young men such as Abdul, a 17-year-old Afghan who was eight years old when his father was killed by the Taliban, forcing him to flee to Pakistan and then Iran. He is in the “Jungle”; his 15-year-old brother is in Turkey. Children’s cut-out figures, crayon drawings and schoolwork show how much effort is made to give young people an education. A blue wooden cross with a slanted crossbeam (pictured), which was given to the Bishop of Bangor after he visited the camp, tells of St Michael’s, the makeshift Orthodox church established there for those who had fled Eritrea.&lt;p&gt;The “Jungle” landscapes of Calais began to emerge not in January 2015 but as far back as the 1990s, the curators say. They are still there. The official government line, in Britain as well as France, may well be that the area has been cleared. But a brief email (printed out and pinned up at the end of the exhibition), which an agency called Help Refugees sends the curators every month, says that on May 2nd this year there were “1,000 displaced people living between Calais and Dunkirk, over 280 of which are unaccompanied children. This number of children has doubled in two months.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Migrants fleeing poverty and war is one of Europe’s biggest political challenges. As this exhibition shows, how Europeans decide to treat them is a profound moral test, too. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Lande: The Calais ‘Jungle’ and Beyond” is at the Pitt Rivers Museum, Oxford, until November 29th. Read more: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/prospero/2018/01/08/a-thoughtful-dramatisation-of-life-in-the-calais-jungle&quot;&gt;A thoughtful dramatisation of life in the Calais “Jungle”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 21:06:44 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“We’ve failed to grasp how deep Erdogan&#x27;s playbook is”—Istanbul’s election rerun]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/07/weve-failed-to-grasp-how-deep-erdogans-playbook-is-istanbuls-election-rerun]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_blp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T10:27:18Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TURKEY&amp;#x27;S RULING AK party never conceded defeat in Istanbul’s mayoral election in March. Now the result has been annulled, and a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/07/turkey-cancels-the-oppositions-victory-in-the-istanbul-election&quot;&gt;rerun&lt;/a&gt; ordered, to the dismay of opposition politicians and Western governments. A trade deal between China and America has been thrown into &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/06/the-us-china-trade-talks-are-at-risk-of-breakdown&quot;&gt;doubt&lt;/a&gt; thanks to a presidential tweet. And why more women are colonising a genre of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/05/04/female-mcs-are-changing-brazilian-funk-music&quot;&gt;Brazilian music&lt;/a&gt; known for its misogyny. Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/mayormaynot-turkey-selectionre-run&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 21:06:43 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Turkey cancels the opposition’s victory in the Istanbul election]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/07/turkey-cancels-the-oppositions-victory-in-the-istanbul-election]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_eup501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEFORE THE evening of May 6th, and despite the miserable state of their country&amp;#x27;s democracy under President Recep Tayyip Erdogan, Turks could console themselves with the thought that, on election day, they could anyway vote freely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That assurance was dashed when the country’s electoral board cancelled the result of the mayoral election in Istanbul conducted on March 31st. It ordered a new one for June 23rd, thereby deposing Ekrem Imamoglu, the first opposition politician to preside over Turkey’s biggest city in a quarter century.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkey’s descent into autocracy appeared to plumb new depths overnight. The markets braced for more turmoil. The lira has slumped by more than 3% since the announcement, reaching its lowest level in seven months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The drama had been in the making since late March, when voters in Istanbul handed Mr Imamoglu a narrow yet shocking victory. That was a bitter setback for Mr Erdogan, his Justice and Development (AK) party and their mayoral candidate, a former prime minister. AK immediately contested the outcome. The morning after the vote, the city woke up to banners and billboards heralding victory—for Mr Erdogan and his party.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Newspapers managed by the president’s cronies accused the opposition of conspiring with terrorists to steal the election. AK complained that tens of thousands of former bureaucrats sacked following an attempted coup in 2016 should not have been allowed to vote. Mr Erdogan claimed to have unearthed evidence of other “organised crimes” at the ballot box. Late last week, prosecutors launched dozens of investigations related to AK’s claims, questioning some 100 people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the end, the election board voted to annul the election, citing improprieties in the appointment of some polling-station officials. AK hardliners applauded. Mr Erdogan’s communications director called the decision a “victory for our democracy”. The opposition called it a disgrace. Appearing before a crowd of supporters in his Istanbul neighbourhood, Mr Imamoglu came out swinging, condemning the board for caving in to pressure from the president and his men. “You elected the president under the same rules last year, and you held a referendum and changed the constitution under the same rules,” he said. If Mr Imamoglu’s election can be undone, then “the constitution is questionable, and so is the presidential election.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analysts see Mr Erdogan’s fingerprints on the decision, and warn that Turkey and free elections no longer belong in the same sentence. “For nearly 70 years, there was a consensus in Turkey that political power changed through the ballot box, and that consensus came to an end today,” says Soner Cagaptay of the Washington Institute for Near East Policy, an American think-tank. “I thought there was one institution in Turkey that could act somewhat independently,” said Kemal Kirisci, a senior fellow at the Brookings Institution, “and I was wrong.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The opposition appears unlikely to boycott the repeat election, however, or to stage mass protests. (Mr Imamoglu’s Republican People’s Party suggested as much on May 7th.) Fear is a big factor. Of the millions of Turks who took part in the last big wave of protests in 2013, hundreds have been hauled through the courts. One, a respected philanthropist, has spent nearly two years in prison on outlandish coup charges. He and 15 others face life sentences. Mr Erdogan already brands the opposition as terrorists and provocateurs. Demonstrations would risk playing right into his hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Imamoglu, whose campaign had succeeded against seemingly insurmountable odds, appears in no mood to surrender. Some observers reckon Mr Erdogan may have miscalculated, and that his actions will give Mr Imamoglu an even larger margin of victory next month. Others warn that Turkey’s strongman may go to extremes to wrest back control of the city that elected him mayor three decades ago, a position he used as a springboard to national power. “Erdogan did not call a new election to roll the dice and see what happens,” says Howard Eissenstat, an expert at the Project on Middle East Democracy, an advocacy group in Washington, DC. “The cost of losing [again] would be an unacceptable demonstration of weakness.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 21:06:42 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Line of Duty” goes off the rails]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/06/line-of-duty-goes-off-the-rails]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_BKP511.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-06T17:37:55Z&quot;&gt;May 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUNDAY NIGHT is the time when the British population is most likely to gather round the TV and watch a programme simultaneously. The BBC has often devoted this slot to period dramas such as “Poldark” and “Howard’s End”, but the focus has shifted somewhat to thrillers. “The Night Manager”, a lavish adaptation of a novel by John Le Carré, was a huge hit in 2016; the latest ratings success has been “Line of Duty”, which ended its fifth season on May 5th. An estimated 9.6m people tuned in to watch the last episode. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The series deals with the issue of police corruption, focusing on the AC-12 unit (AC stands for anti-corruption) in an unnamed British city. Police corruption is a TV staple, relying as it does on the dilemma described by the Roman poet Juvenal: &lt;em&gt;Quis custodiet ipsos custodes&lt;/em&gt;—who guards the guards? The BBC produced “Between the Lines”, a similar series, in the 1990s, and probed the Met’s shady methods in “Undercover” in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much of the credit for the success of “Line of Duty” must go to Jed Mercurio, the writer, who has mastered the knack of producing enough cliffhangers to keep viewers watching from week to week. He ruthlessly kills off key characters and prevents the narrative from becoming too predictable. Mr Mercurio had &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/prospero/2018/09/20/why-britain-has-gone-mad-for-bodyguard&quot;&gt;enormous success last year with “Bodyguard”&lt;/a&gt;, a flashy series based on a traumatised ex-soldier (played by Richard Madden), tasked with protecting the home secretary (Keeley Hawes). Lashings of sex, bomb blasts, shootings and betrayals duly followed. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Line of Duty” began in 2012 as a more low-key affair but the show has gradually increased the body count—and reduced the plausibility—over the years. The second series was the best, featuring a compelling performance from Ms Hawes as Lindsay Denton, the police officer under investigation. The best elements of the show were all in place here: the audience was kept guessing about Denton’s motives; there were interrogation scenes in which she turned the table on her questioners; and the AC-12 team was hampered by corrupt officers within its own ranks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each series has revolved around a guest star, playing the officer under investigation—Lennie James and Thandie Newton were particular standouts. By centering the show’s focus on the “villains”, who were often covering up a catastrophic mistake, Mr Mercurio divided the audience’s loyalty. There was a temptation to hope that the rogue officers got away with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alas, the latest series has been the weakest of the five. The lead suspect, played by Stephen Graham, was killed off too early for his story to be satisfying. Instead, the main drama revolved around the hunt for “H”, the senior policeman apparently behind a gang of criminals which has dogged the AC-12 unit throughout the show’s history. All the evidence apparently pointed to the head of the unit, Ted Hastings (Adrian Dunbar), who had previously been portrayed as an old-fashioned, straight-arrow  type.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This twist stretched credibility for all the wrong reasons. Whether Hastings was a criminal mastermind, smart enough to deceive his colleagues for years, or just a honest police officer being framed, he would never have been stupid enough to leave £50,000 in an envelope in plain sight in his hotel room. (The hotel, too, must have the most honest cleaning staff in the world.) The focus on Hastings also gave his sidekicks, Kate Fleming and Steve Arnott (Vicky McClure and Martin Compston) too little to do, bar deliver some clunky expositional dialogue.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And without giving too much away, the final twist involved a dying detective who gave a crucial clue by using his fingers to transmit Morse code. Really? This was pure hokum. Several seemingly vital clues as to the identity of H, left scattered through the series, were explained away in a dissatisfying fashion. Instead of being served lemon sole, the audience had a plate of red herrings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news for fans is that there will be a sixth series, in which Mr Mercurio has the chance to return to form. Anna Maxwell Martin, as an icily ruthless chief superintendent, is also a welcome addition to the cast. In their line of duty, viewers will hope that the next series gives AC-12 some lines of plausibility as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 01:06:36 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Terry McAuliffe is focusing on Virginia]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/06/why-terry-mcauliffe-is-focusing-on-virginia]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_USP512.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-06T18:21:27Z&quot;&gt;May 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ONCE IT became clear that Joe Biden was running for president, the chances that Terry McAuliffe, the former governor of Virginia, would go after the Democratic nomination himself evaporated. Mr Biden, the former vice-president, fills a lane Mr McAuliffe believed could have given him some running room: centre-left in a field of mostly hard-left candidates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now Mr McAuliffe, a long-time ally of the Clintons, has chosen a different path, returning to his former role as a high-decibel, energetic fundraiser and organiser for the Democratic Party. Mr McAuliffe, who was elected governor in 2013, was a front man for Bill and Hillary Clinton in their presidential campaigns. He once called himself a “salesman” and Bill Clinton’s presidency was his “product”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; “I’m staying home to do what I need to do to help Virginians,” he told CNN in late April after announcing he would serve as campaigner in chief for Democrats running for the House and Senate in elections in November.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The elections could scarcely be more important. The anti-Trump tsunami that in 2016 tipped Virginia to Hillary Clinton—it was the only Southern state she carried—hit again in 2017. Ralph Northam was elected governor in a landslide and Democrats nearly took back the House of Delegates, the larger of the two legislative chambers, winning a stunning 15 seats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shift won’t be complete until Democrats again control the legislature. They need two seats each in the House and Virginia Senate to end roughly two decades in the minority and give the party total sway over state government—the governorship, the legislature and the courts—for the first time in nearly 30 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ahead of big elections, governors tend to provide legislative caucuses and candidates with financial and infrastructural backing. But since admitting in February that he had donned blackface as a student, Mr Northam’s fundraising has atrophied. Despite polls that suggest Virginians want to move on from his embarrassment, the governor is a rare sight on the campaign trail. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Things could improve for Mr Northam. There are signs his fundraising is picking up. He may become more visible on the campaign trail. And recent breakthroughs in policy, from road financing to criminal sentencing, are reminders that Mr Northam remains an effective governor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But with his popularity dented among younger, rigidly liberal voters who constitute a fast-growing slice of the electorate, Democrats are looking to other big names to fill the void. They include the state’s two US senators—Mark Warner and Tim Kaine—and three new members of the House delegation: Abigail Spanberger, Jennifer Wexton and Elaine Luria. All have successfully harnessed the Democratic Party’s largely suburban, increasingly multi-hued base and regularly communicate with it. And lending their names to those of legislative candidates potentially helps when they stand for re-election to Congress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But as members of Congress, they are subject to federal fundraising rules that limit how much cash they can generate for home-state candidates. Mr McAuliffe has no such encumbrances. In Virginia, there are no limits on fundraising or spending, freeing him to return to what he excelled at as candidate and governor: squeezing big-dollar contributions from business, interest groups and lobbyists. When he ran for governor, Mr McAuliffe raised $38m, nearly twice what his Republican opponent managed and about $4m more than Mr Northam collected for his campaign two years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once in office, Mr McAuliffe set up a political treasury, in part to finance legislative candidates. It collected more than $10m. Thanks largely to gerrymandering, it did not achieve much: Republicans retained control of the General Assembly under his watch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fund will be available to him now. In campaigning for legislative candidates, Mr McAuliffe will be talking up Mr Northam’s agenda and the promise of more achievements should voters install a Democratic majority. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Mr McAuliffe may also have to answer for his own embarrassments. As governor he was strong on job creation, laying the foundation for a deal, closed by Mr Northam, under which Amazon would locate its East Coast headquarters in Northern Virginia. The online giant vows to bring 25,000 jobs to the Washington, DC suburb over the next decade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But a much smaller project remains a big headache. Mr McAuliffe committed $1.4m in public funds to a proposed, Chinese-run factory in rural Virginia that would manufacture anti-pollution equipment for motor vehicles. The plant never opened and the company refused to return the money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, Democrats believe voters have a largely charitable opinion of Mr McAuliffe. His approval rating was just over 50% when he left the governorship—a job he loved and is not ruling out seeking again in 2021. Perhaps 2019 will be his warm-up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:06:37 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[For Western leaders, Ramadan is a time to reassure the world of Islam]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/05/06/for-western-leaders-ramadan-is-a-time-to-reassure-the-world-of-islam]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_blp903.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-06T08:31:21Z&quot;&gt;May 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AT LEAST since 1805, Western heads of government have been making delicate judgments over how exactly to signal their respect for the Muslim fasting month of Ramadan. On December 9th of that year, Thomas Jefferson changed the time of a White House dinner from the usual 3.30 pm to “precisely at sunset”. The shift was made to accommodate the religious obligations of a guest from Tunis who was playing an important role in negotiations to free the young republic from the threat of North African pirates.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In more recent times, leaders of the democratic world have taken the period of daybreak-to-dusk abstinence, the latest enactment of which began at sunset on May 5th, as a cue to salute and reassure Muslims everywhere, in their own countries and around the world. Often they attend or host at least one iftar, the communal meal consumed when darkness falls. Even President Donald Trump and his administration have begun to acknowledge the importance of Ramadan, despite the Islamo-sceptical feelings of many of his supporters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2017, Mr Trump’s first full year in office, both the White House and the State Department broke with the practice of hosting iftar dinners, and a presidential message of greeting contained the acid assertion that the sacred month “strengthens awareness of our shared obligation to reject violence”. But Mr Trump resumed the practice of hosting a White House iftar last year (though he was criticised for inviting mainly foreign diplomats rather than Muslim compatriots). Last year’s communication spoke more positively of the “richness” that Islam brought to America’s “religious tapestry”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year’s Ramadan salutation was warmer still. In words that might have been taken from a Friday mosque sermon Mr Trump declared: “During Ramadan, Muslims fast from dawn to dusk, recite passages from the Koran, and perform benevolent acts of charity and good will towards others. By doing so, they develop a renewed sense of purpose in their own spiritual journey, deepening their appreciation for God’s grace and mercy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The American president is not the only Western leader to have used the holy month to counter the impression of being hostile to Islam. In 2015, Canada’s then Conservative prime minister, Stephen Harper, became the first leader of his country to host an iftar: this was despite the widespread perception that his party was playing to anti-Muslim sentiment by, for example, banning face veils during citizenship ceremonies.  His Liberal successor, Justin Trudeau, has been even warmer in his acknowledgement of Ramadan. In one of the first messages issued by a Western leader this year, he said the fast “honours the values at the heart of Islam, like compassion and service to others”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In constitutionally secular France, the head of state could hardly stage anything remotely resembling a religious ritual in his own residence. But President Emmanuel Macron made a pointed gesture in 2017 by attending an iftar laid on by the French Council of the Muslim Faith (CFCM). He said he wanted to thank Muslim leaders for their support in fighting terrorism. But they were disappointed when he failed to repeat the courtesy last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;German politicians, too, know how to practise Ramadan diplomacy. In 2015, Chancellor Angela Merkel made a maiden appearance at the annual iftar hosted in Berlin by her foreign ministry. She wanted to make the point that the Muslim faith has a place in German life, despite statements to the contrary by members of her own coalition and challengers on the far-right. “It is obvious that Islam is a part of Germany,” she said, knowing that the statement was far from self-evident to many of her compatriots. Two years later, Iran’s foreign minister, Mohammad Javad Zarif, was invited to the German foreign ministry’s sundown dinner as part of a delicate rapprochement between Berlin and Tehran.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Britain, where officially organised iftar meals and Ramadan wishes have been standard practice in recent years, the government was a bit slower than usual this year in wishing Muslims well for their month of abstinence. But Theresa May, the prime minister who like Mrs Merkel is a Christian cleric’s daughter, used her Twitter feed to observe that “Ramadan represents the universal values of peace, reflection, devotion and charity”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 22:51:31 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“I’ve trained for this my whole career”—YouTube’s CEO on a mountain of moderating]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/06/ive-trained-for-this-my-whole-career-youtubes-ceo-on-a-mountain-of-moderating]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/youtube.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-06T09:55:10Z&quot;&gt;May 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;span &gt;SUSAN WOJCICKI, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/briefing/2019/05/04/the-tricky-task-of-policing-youtube&quot;&gt;YouTube&amp;#x27;&lt;/a&gt;s chief executive, tells our correspondent that moderating the streaming giant&amp;#x27;s content is her biggest challenge. No wonder: every minute, 500 hours-worth of it is added. Also, how West African research is being used to address gun violence in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/04/applying-lessons-from-war-torn-africa-to-chicago&quot;&gt;Chicago&lt;/a&gt;. And a look at the declining number of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/international/2019/04/27/how-monarchies-survive-modernity&quot;&gt;royal families&lt;/a&gt;, and why some that have survived will stick around. Runtime: 23 min &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/everythinginmoderation-youtube&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 19:06:27 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Over a third of graduates in Britain are too educated for their jobs]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/06/over-a-third-of-graduates-in-britain-are-too-educated-for-their-jobs]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_wocfne.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-06T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TEENAGERS THINK they know everything (much to their parents’ chagrin). Graduates in Britain actually do know much more than they need to in order to do their jobs, and so earn less than they could.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are the depressing findings of a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.ons.gov.uk/economy/nationalaccounts/uksectoraccounts/compendium/economicreview/april2019/overeducationandhourlywagesintheuklabourmarket2006to2017&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; by the Office for National Statistics, a British government agency. It looked at population surveys from 2006 to 2017 and compared academic attainment of workers against the average educational level for their occupation. It found that 34% of those who graduated after 2007 were overeducated for their jobs, compared with 22% of those who left university before 1992. The most overeducated age cohort is 35- to 49-year-olds, with men and women equally affected. Migrants tend to be the most overeducated, as are people working in London (where most migrants live).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overeducation can happen for different reasons. Graduates may not have enough information about job opportunities to find a job that fits their academic qualifications. Or there may be an oversupply of educated people in the labour market. But the consequences are bad for both employers and employees. Being overeducated for a job means that people do not use the skills they learnt at university, hurting productivity and wages. Overeducated workers earn between 3% and 8% less compared with the wage of a worker with a similar level of education who is matched to the right job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But all this bad news doesn’t weaken the overall case for staying in education. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://assets.publishing.service.gov.uk/government/uploads/system/uploads/attachment_data/file/797308/GLMS_2018_publication_main_text.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Data&lt;/a&gt; from the Department of Education released this month show that the median graduate salary in Britain for workers aged 16 to 64 was $13,170 more than that of non-graduates. The disparity was greatest for postgraduates: they take home an additional $7,900 a year. The Institute of Fiscal Studies has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.ifs.org.uk/publications/13731&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;found&lt;/a&gt; that the wage premium is particularly marked for women: holders of degrees earn on average 28% more than those without such qualifications (there is an 8% premium for men). That is probably related to the fact that non-graduate women have children earlier and are more likely to be in part-time work. Overeducation is a problem, then, but it still pays to study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 19:06:26 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>