<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[EU leaders settle on a new team to run the club]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/charlemagnes-notebook/2019/07/02/eu-leaders-settle-on-a-new-team-to-run-the-club]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BLP510.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-02T21:36:35Z&quot;&gt;Jul 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;URSULA von der Leyen will be the new president of the European Commission and Christine Lagarde will be the new president of the European Central Bank (ECB). That, at least, is the proposal of the EU’s heads of government, who met in Brussels today for an unexpected third day of talks on the allocation of the EU’s top jobs. The European Council, which comprises the heads of government of the 28 member states, initially gathered on Sunday evening. They negotiated through the night and into yesterday morning, at which point Donald Tusk, the council president, extended proceedings to give leaders a chance to sleep and regroup. Today a deal was reached.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angela Merkel and Emmanuel Macron, Europe’s two most powerful leaders, had initially put forward a package that would have seen Frans Timmermans, a Dutch social democrat, lead the commission. Mr Timmermans was a so-called “Spitzenkandidat” or lead candidate. In other words, his political family had designated him its candidate for the commission job ahead of the European election which took place from May 23rd to May 26th. In some eyes, the Spitzenkandidaten of the various parties had a mandate from the voters (evidence suggest few voters knew who any of them were and even fewer voted to give them a mandate). But Mr Timmermans proved a difficult choice. Leaders of the European People’s Party (EPP), the centre-right group of parties that includes Mrs Merkel’s Christian Democratic Union (CDU) in Germany, objected to the allocation of the powerful commission job to a social democrat. Central Europeans dislike Mr Timmermans for his record of taking on governments like that of Poland for their illiberal excesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having failed to agree on a package of appointments with a Timmermans-led commission at its core, today leaders cast their gaze elsewhere. Mr Macron suggested Ms von der Leyen, the German defence minister. A moderate in the CDU, she belongs to the EPP. She is acceptable to the central Europeans, having increased Germany’s military commitment to the defence of NATO’s eastern borders. She was a capable families minister and has pushed to modernise Germany’s armed forces (with patchy results). So she made a broadly acceptable candidate to lead the EU’s executive. With that role settled, the other big jobs fell into place. Mr Macron got a French president of the ECB in Ms Lagarde, who currently leads the IMF. Liberals, who gained seats in the European election and had hoped to clinch the commission, get the presidency of the European Council in the form of Charles Michel, Belgium’s prime minister. Social democrats get Josep Borrell, Spain’s foreign minister, in the role of EU high representative for foreign and security policy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The package is not perfect, but nor is it terrible. Ms von der Leyen, though not dazzlingly charismatic, is a mature and moderate administrator who speaks fluent English. Mr Borrell will be the most heavyweight figure to serve as high representative since the job’s creation in 2009. Mr Michel is a decent deal-broker (you have to be, in Belgium&amp;#x27;s messy politics). And Ms Lagarde is a capable communicator who has said sensible things about the euro-zone, avoiding the ideological hawkishness of her German counterparts. Overall the deal is a win for Mr Macron, who may have killed off the Spitzenkandidat system (which he dislikes) while getting friendly faces into both the commission and the ECB. But all is not yet settled. Ms von der Leyen must be approved by the European Parliament. She will probably clear this hurdle, but European politics is fragmented and unpredictable these days. If she is rejected, the whole package will fall apart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 06:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cori Gauff announces herself at Wimbledon]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/07/02/cori-gauff-announces-herself-at-wimbledon]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BLP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-02T19:23:11Z&quot;&gt;Jul 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT IS hard to avoid the impression that the tennis world has witnessed a changing of the guard. On July 1st , the opening day of the 2019 Championships at Wimbledon, Cori Gauff, a 15-year-old American prospect, upset the five-times champion Venus Williams in straight sets. Ms Williams, aged 39, was not the highest-ranked player to fall on the first day of the tournament; that honour belonged to the reigning US Open champion, Naomi Osaka, the second seed. But no first-round winner has garnered more attention than Ms Gauff, whose youth causes her to establish new records every time she steps on court. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She is so young that Ms Williams had collected her first two Wimbledon trophies before Ms Gauff was born. The teenager was the youngest ever to gain a place in the draw via qualifying, winning three matches without dropping a set in order to do so. Ranked only 313th among women players (to Ms Williams’ 44th), Ms Gauff is only the 8th woman this century to win a grand-slam match before her 16th birthday, and the youngest since Anna Kournikova carved her way through three rounds at the 1996 US Open. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Kournikova, however, serves as a reminder that not all teenage sensations become superstars. Of the last seven women to win a grand-slam match at 15, none have advanced past the semi-final of a major tournament, or ascended above 7th in the Women’s Tennis Association (WTA) rankings. (Two of them, 20-year-old Catherine Bellis and 17-year-old Marta Kostyuk, may still do so). Thus although Ms Gauff is unquestionably the best 15-year-old tennis player right now, years’ worth of obstacles lie in her path to greatness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far, she has held her own against much more experienced competition. On court, there is little to distinguish Ms Gauff from her elders. She stands 1.78m tall, and serves as powerfully as Ms Williams—herself one of the most effective servers in the game’s history. Her average first serve on July 1st was clocked at 107 miles per hour (172 km/h), slightly faster than her opponent’s deliveries. Her typical second serve proved more effective than Ms Williams’s comparably cautious offerings. She possesses strong groundstrokes on both the forehand and backside sides, cracking winners with 8% of her shots, in line with the tour average.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although it is tougher to judge a player’s mental assets after a handful of professional matches, early signs suggest that Ms Gauff is unusually mature for her age. Her match against Ms Williams took place on the biggest stage of her career, against a legendary opponent. “I have never played on a court so big, but I had to remind myself that the lines on the court are the same size,” she later declared. Nevertheless, she seemed unperturbed by the sorts of hiccups that often derail young players. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the final set, she had to overcome two particularly severe hiccups. After double-faulting on the fifth and sixth points of her first service game, she immediately bounced back, winning two points with a protracted rally and a strong first serve, to secure the game. In the eighth game of the set, she double-faulted twice more, surrendering a one-break advantage and falling to 4-4 in the second set. But again, she held her nerve and regained the break in the following game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The immediate challenge facing Ms Gauff is to sustain her level of play. In the second round, she will face Magdalena Rybarikova, an unseeded Slovakian known for her grass-court prowess. If Ms Gauff advances further, her likely third-round opponent will be the 17th seed, Madison Keys, a one-time prodigy who recorded her first US Open win in 2011 as a 16-year-old. The big-hitting Ms Keys will force Ms Gauff to confront an opponent much like herself, only stronger and even more powerful. Ms Williams was one of the most accomplished competitors in the draw, but the unheralded Ms Rybarikova may prove an even stiffer test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Ms Gauff, this week’s array of opponents is only the beginning. The tennis season spans ten months of the year and demands stamina on a different scale than is required to win a few matches. Many youngsters with the talent to score upsets are unable to translate early success into a noteworthy career. Ms Gauff won the Roland Garros girls’ singles title in Paris last year, an early indicator of future stardom. Yet of the other 17 women who have won a junior singles title since the 2014 US Open, only one—a 17-year-old American, Amanda Anisimova—has won a tour-level title. Indeed, the balance of power in the modern game has shifted to veterans such as the 31-year-old Wimbledon defending champion, Angelique Kerber, who did not win her first match at the All England Club until she was 22. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is far too early, then, to designate Ms Gauff as the successor to Ms Williams, let alone her even more accomplished sister, Serena. But that does not make the teenager’s exploits any less impressive. It is rare to see a player so dramatically announce her presence on the sport’s biggest stage. If she manages to negotiate the difficult route to the top of the game, fans can look back on July 1st’s upset as a clear starting point from which her ascent began.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 04:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Brexit and the city]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/07/02/brexit-and-the-city]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/moneytalks_brexit_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-02T18:00:56Z&quot;&gt;Jul 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LONDON&lt;/strong&gt; IS home to the world’s biggest international financial centre. But &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/27/can-the-city-survive-brexit&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brexit threatens to cut the City off from its most important single foreign market.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Tamzin Booth, The Economist’s Britain business editor, investigates whether the City of London can survive Brexit and how &lt;strong&gt;other cities across Europe, like Frankfurt, are vying to win their rival’s&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/29/londons-reign-as-the-worlds-capital-of-capital-is-at-risk&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;business.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; What is at stake on both sides of the Channel, and are there any winners in this battle? Runtime: 22 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-brexitandthecity&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id420929545?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/2Yvo8QxZf7WlSEsIwKjtX4&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWVjb25vbWlzdG1vbmV5dGFsa3M&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=18377&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/Business--Economics-Podcasts/The-Economist-Money-Talks-p603831/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 04:40:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America’s economic expansion is now the longest on record]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/07/02/americas-economic-expansion-is-now-the-longest-on-record]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_WOC339_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I DON’T THINK that expansions just die of old age,” Janet Yellen, a former chairwoman of the Federal Reserve, told economists at a conference in Atlanta on January 4th. That theory may soon be put to the test. As of today, the economic expansion that began in America in June 2009 has continued, uninterrupted, for more than 120 months (3,654 days to be exact), making it the longest in history. The previous record, according to the National Bureau of Economic Research (NBER), America’s official arbiter of recessions, was the ten-year boom that took place between 1991 and 2001.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The business cycle has been getting longer for some time. Between 1945 and 1981, American economic expansions lasted for three years and eight months, on average. Since then they have stretched on for more than eight years. But as they have grown lengthier, they have become weaker, too. During the ten business cycles recorded between 1949 and 2007, the economy grew by an annual rate of 4.7% a year, on average. Since 2009, though, growth has averaged just 2.3%. What is more, GDP per person, a measure of economic growth that strips out the effects of a growing population, has inched up by just 1.5% a year. Across the previous ten cycles, it grew by an average of 3.3% a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are signs the party may be coming to an end. Investment bears point to an inverted yield curve (when yields on long-term bonds fell below those on short-term ones), historically an accurate harbinger of recessions. Trade wars could also trigger a downturn. Yet professional forecasters surveyed by the Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia reckon that there is just a one-in-five chance that a recession will hit next year. They still expect America’s economy to be growing by 1.7% 12 months from now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, recessions are hard to predict; that is what makes them so disruptive. “As Janet says, expansions don’t die of old age,” Ben Bernanke told conference-goers in January, agreeing with his successor at the Fed. “I like to say they get murdered instead.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 04:40:11 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How a victim of the cultural revolution mastered economics]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/07/02/how-a-victim-of-the-cultural-revolution-mastered-economics]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_FND000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE STUDENTS embarking on an economics doctorate at the University of California, Berkeley, this autumn face a daunting obstacle: Econ 201A, a course in microeconomic theory inflicted on all new recruits. Over 16 weeks they must acquaint themselves with some of the most formalised parts of economics, including Houthakker’s Axiom, the Slutsky matrix and Afriat’s theorem. According to one instructor, between five and seven class members (out of 20 to 25) usually receive a grade of B- or worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But anyone losing heart should take inspiration from a past student, Weijian Shan. He tried the course in 1982 after becoming one of America’s first PhD students from communist China. As he recounts in “Out of the Gobi”, his memoir published earlier this year, he had not taken a mathematics class beyond the age of 12. His faculty adviser, Janet Yellen, who would later chair the Federal Reserve, and George Akerlof, who would later win a Nobel prize, worried that the difficulties of Econ 201A would be “insurmountable”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shan, however, had already surmounted more than most. After his schooling was cut short in 1966 by the Cultural Revolution, he was “sent down” to the countryside, like millions of other city kids. He joined a Construction Army Corps in the Gobi desert, trying to create farms out of salty clay in a “place that birds don’t care to shit”. They dug ditches, made bricks and harvested wheat, three of the four most tiring things in the world, according to one squad member. (The fourth was sex, which they were spared.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His march to Berkeley was long. He arrived in the Gobi knowing only a few sayings and slogans in English (“Long live Chairman Mao”). But in 1975 he was chosen by his peers and bosses to study the language in Beijing. He won nomination only after first ingratiating himself with his company by memorising the official rules and referee signals of volleyball, which made him a respected referee of platoon matches. The English he learnt in Beijing helped him win an Asia Foundation scholarship to study in America after it restored formal diplomatic ties with China in 1979. Having earned an MBA in a year at the University of San Francisco, he embarked on his PhD at Berkeley’s business school.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his study of economics Mr Shan had one or two things going for him. Economics is the science of scarcity, a subject with which he had intimate acquaintance. Deep in the Gobi, a day’s walk from their settlement, half a box of matches could cost 50kg of potatoes. When Americans dismiss something as “bullshit”, Mr Shan recalls the patties of cow dung they used to treasure as fuel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The construction corps taught him other economic concepts, such as “value-added” and its opposite: their company turned 750,000kg of seeds into just 70,000kg of grain. He experienced the power of the division of labour. Even with utmost industry his team could make only 200 bricks per person in a day if they each mixed, moulded and moved the materials. But by dividing those tasks between them they could make two-thirds more. He also learnt the value of capital. His platoon could have made 20,000 bricks per day with a simple mixing machine, but no one would provide the 3,000 yuan (about $1,300 at the official exchange rate) to buy it. Mr Shan wonders if he was the first hard labourer with “such a burning desire to be exploited by capital”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The pigshed academy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Mr Shan’s educational resurgence was nonetheless remarkable. Even by 1990 just 0.4% of Chinese born in 1951-55 held a university degree (see chart). The Cultural Revolution was like a mad natural experiment, depriving some people of a university education for reasons unrelated to their ability. Their loss has thus helped economists calculate the worth of a college education, which is otherwise difficult to estimate because college-goers are often more able than other people, even before they get there. According to a 2015 study by John Giles of the World Bank, Albert Park of the Hong Kong University of Science and Technology, and Meiyan Wang of the Chinese Academy of Social Sciences, about three-quarters of the returns to college in China reflect the skills and credentials that universities confer. But a quarter reflects the intrinsic abilities of the people they admit. Mr Shan’s education yielded a rich harvest. But he was also an unusually good seed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One benefit of university is guidance. Mr Shan’s efforts to educate himself in the desert lacked system or direction. He retreated to a pigs’ kitchen, where vegetable roots, skins and leaves were boiled, to read whatever he could find: an aviation magazine, Mao’s speeches, a pesticide manual. For this reason, he feels his “little house of knowledge is built on sand”. (The vastly more privileged students of today can also struggle to study systematically, because of the surfeit of claims on their attention. Their houses can be dangerously top-heavy.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shan enjoyed Econ 201A, eventually. But he had to abandon his first attempt, returning only after taking the mathematics class that Ms Yellen and Mr Akerlof had recommended. The maths textbook was over 400 pages long. He read it seven times. “I would have enjoyed studying in a more leisurely manner,” he writes, but “I had so much ground to make up.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He followed his PhD with a brief stint at the World Bank and a longer spell as a professor at Wharton. He founded the China Economic Review (which in 1990 published an article by a 32-year-old Yi Gang, who now heads China’s central bank), then entered the financial world, becoming a big shot in private equity at Newbridge Capital. During long negotiations in hotel conference rooms he would marvel at the luxury of round-the-clock room service. His colleagues would tell him to shut up and gain some weight.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the Cultural Revolution ended in 1976 and reforms began, Mr Shan, like his country, had a lot of potential—and a lot of ground to make up. Since then they have both been compelling examples of convergence. When capital, of the human or physical variety, is scarce, the returns to investment can be high. And after the rigours of the past both were accustomed to the deferred gratification that heavy investment requires. The man who eventually mastered Econ 201A is an economics lesson in himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 01:40:52 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Two new documentaries survey ecological battlegrounds]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/07/02/two-new-documentaries-survey-ecological-battlegrounds]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BKP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-02T14:55:08Z&quot;&gt;Jul 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE FOCAL points of landscape art changed in the 1970s and 1980s. Where painters and photographers from Caspar David Friedrich to Ansel Adams had homed in on awe-inspiring, untouched vistas with mountains, valleys and lakes, a new generation of artists focused instead on grey car parks, nuclear-test sites and the vast swathes of land being cleared for suburban development. “Landscape is no longer an aesthetic refuge,” Rebecca Solnit, a writer, historian and activist, observed in 1990, “but a battleground.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That idea is dramatised in two new documentaries about mankind’s despoliation of the planet: “Earth”, directed by Nicolas Geyrhalter, and “Anthropocene: The Human Epoch” by Edward Burtynsky, Jennifer Baichwal and Nicholas de Pencier. Both films use drones to range across the globe and capture scenes of environmental degradation, including thousands of poached elephant tusks confiscated by the Kenyan government, the startlingly colourful waterways of the Atacama desert (polluted in the production of lithium), and the gleaming white caverns of the Carrara marble mine in Italy. In “Anthropocene” these devastated landscapes (pictured top and below)—shot in bold colours and majestic wide angles—have a strange and almost improper beauty. “Earth”, meanwhile, favours an approach which is both more subtle and more powerful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BKP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190706_BKP505.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190706_BKP505.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190706_BKP505.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190706_BKP505.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190706_BKP505.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190706_BKP505.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190706_BKP505.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190706_BKP505.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190706_BKP505.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Anthropocene” is an anthology of misery, filmed by three different directors but strung together by an overarching voiceover which provides context and factual information in each new scene. By contrast, “Earth” does away with voiceover and mixes drone footage with other perspectives. The viewer is shown a giant earth-moving machine from high above, hacking away at a mountain in Hungary, followed by the man who operates it—the camera follows close behind as he walks the hundreds of metres up the vast metal contraption to his cabin. Later, enjoying a lunchtime sandwich, the worker talks of his alarm at the rapidly shrinking glaciers in the region where he goes on holiday every year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Geyrhalter anchors “Earth” (pictured below) in interviews with labourers in the mining trade (something of a departure for a director who has often preferred an observational mode). An American foreman engaged in levelling a range in California expresses unease about the speed with which he and his team can destroy vast, ancient lands in a matter of months: “Do I want to tear the hills down? No!” Yet he sees no other option given the demands of the market. A worker employed at a mine in Spain, a site once exploited by the ancient Romans, muses on the rise and fall of empires, and how they always sow the seeds of their own destruction. These unexpectedly lyrical conversations make the point that climate change is as much a tale of the absurdities of human psychology, and the contradictions that it can tolerate, as it is about rainforests, oil deposits, eco-systems and emissions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;These films imply that more effort should be made to probe the underlying motivations for ecological damage, be they economic, psychological or political. Neither film offers easy solutions. The spectacular approach of “Anthropocene” is unsatisfying: after surveying the various battlegrounds from high above, the viewer has no better understanding of the causes of the war, let alone how to end it. Climate devastation is portrayed almost as a catastrophe visited upon Earth by malevolent outside forces. “Earth” imparts a slim measure of hope: if environmental ruin is a human phenomenon, then it is also within humans’ power to stop it. Persuading them to care about it in the first place, however, remains a surprisingly difficult artistic challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Earth” is screening in Britain now. “Anthropocene: The Human Epoch” will be released in America in September&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 23:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[British Jews trace Iberian heritage to retain EU citizenship]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/07/02/british-jews-trace-iberian-heritage-to-retain-eu-citizenship]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BRP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ELLA RACHAMIM can remember the moment she discovered Britain had voted to leave the European Union as if it were yesterday. Rather than turn off the television and go to sleep, the disappointed Remain-voter picked up her laptop and navigated to the website of the Portuguese government. The research begun that night has led Dr Rachamim, a paediatrician from London, to the brink of receiving a Portuguese passport. Her only connection to the country, and her sole qualification for citizenship, is that her ancestors were expelled from it during a bout of anti-Semitism half a millennium ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A year before the Brexit referendum of 2016, Portugal and Spain passed laws which offered Sephardic Jews—those whose families once lived on the Iberian peninsula—a path to citizenship. Each country intended the gesture to act as recompense for the forcible exile of Jews in the 1490s, in one of the first acts of the Spanish Inquisition. But the two countries have unwittingly offered a lifeline for Remainers anxious to retain EU citizenship after Britain leaves the bloc. “I really want to be European, I want my kids to be European,” says Dr Rachamim. To guarantee her three children’s ability to live and work across the continent, she has sought Spanish passports for them, on top of her own application to Portugal. The cost will run to more than £10,000 ($12,650).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She is not alone. A friend and fellow Sephardic Jew, Fran Leigh, has also embarked on the expensive process. “I wanted to prove to my child that freedom of movement is the most precious thing we can have as human beings,” she says. Campus, an Israeli firm which has been helping to manage applications by Sephardim, says the majority of its British clients are Remainers. “It comes in waves,” says Eylon Kasif, a company spokesman. “Every time Theresa May did a speech about the Brexit.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far at least 420 British Jews have been granted Portuguese passports under the new law; a handful more have obtained passports from Spain (whose rules are stricter, at least for adults). The process requires applicants to demonstrate ancestry dating back to at least the mid-18th century, when Sephardim arrived in England. David Mendoza, a genealogist, says this is fairly straightforward, as the tight-knit community’s synagogue kept excellent records. Nobody knows for sure how many of Britain’s 280,000 or so Jews have Sephardic heritage; Mr Mendoza estimates that the number is in the tens of thousands. He has helped about 200 people research their ancestry in order to claim Spanish or Portuguese citizenship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among their reasons for wanting to secure an EU passport before Brexit, some Sephardim cite concerns about rising anti-Semitism. Dr Rachamim believes the referendum unleashed racism that had been simmering under the surface. “Even though the Holocaust didn’t directly affect my family, I always felt there was this thread of fear that it would happen again,” she says. Britain’s equality watchdog is investigating whether the opposition Labour Party illegally discriminated against Jews. Jewish leaders recently condemned the party’s “disgraceful step backwards in its half-baked ‘fight’ against anti-Semitism,” after it readmitted (and later re-suspended) Chris Williamson, an MP accused of showing prejudice towards Jews.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Portuguese Jewish groups advertise what they say is a friendlier environment in their country. The Jewish Community in Porto claims there is “no anti-Semitism in the city”, making it perhaps the “best safe haven for Jews in Europe.” Mr Mendoza, a ninth-generation Londoner, is wary of such language, noting that it could even inadvertently reinforce anti-Semitic tropes which cast Jews as rootless wanderers. “My family unpacked their bags over 300 years ago. It sounds a little bit hysterical to me, to be honest,” he says. Most Sephardim claiming citizenship in Iberia come from countries such as Turkey or Venezuela, where political conflict is of a different order to that in Britain. “The whole world is very strange at the moment,” he concedes. “But for Jews, England has been since the times of Cromwell a good place to live.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 23:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“A nasty kind of confrontational mood”—Hong Kong’s protests boil over]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/07/02/a-nasty-kind-of-confrontational-mood-hong-kongs-protests-boil-over]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_blm502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-02T11:33:55Z&quot;&gt;Jul 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PROTESTORS ARE in a defiant mood—a hard core of them has smashed up &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/30/hong-kong-protesters-storm-the-legislative-council&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hong Kong’s Legislative Council&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/a&gt; But demonstrations aren’t going to make the territory any more &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/china/2019/06/29/xi-jinping-sees-protests-in-hong-kong-as-a-threat-to-the-party&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;free.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; The state-owned investment vehicles known as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/15/gulf-states-are-becoming-more-adventurous-investors&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;sovereign-wealth funds&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; are usually cautious; those of the Gulf region are proving much more adventurous and less transparent. And, a look at the future of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/06/15/what-happens-to-those-who-die-poor-or-unclaimed-in-nyc&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New York’s island of the dead.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/902fff00-95e9-4f30-9b22-fd9912738936&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 21:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hong Kong protesters storm the legislative council]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/30/hong-kong-protesters-storm-the-legislative-council]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_CNP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-30T16:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE DAY began with an official celebration of the return of Hong Kong to China on July 1st. It ended in the ransacking of a government building and tear gas. The televised chaos, including scenes of protesters violently smashing their way into and trashing the Legislative Council building, where some displayed the British and colonial-era flags, represent the latest test for Carrie Lam, the chief executive of Hong Kong, and for Xi Jinping, her ultimate boss in Beijing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A wave of massive protests in recent weeks has left them searching for how best to respond to the demands of citizens of Hong Kong, who fear that their freedoms are being whittled away under Chinese rule. Opposition has been galvanised, in particular, by a bill that would make it possible for people accused of crimes in mainland China to be sent there to face trial. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On June 15th Ms Lam had tried to appease protesters by postponing consideration of the bill. But protesters have called for it to be withdrawn entirely. Many have also called on Ms Lam to resign. In response Hong Kong leaders have tried thus far a mixture of patience, contrition and hard-nosed police tactics. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The day started with a new note of contrition from Ms Lam. The ceremony marking the 22nd anniversary of the handover was held at Hong Kong’s exhibition centre, where dignitaries watched a broadcast of the raising of the Chinese flag. In her remarks Ms Lam departed from the usual convention of opining on the progress of the city under Chinese rule, promising instead that her government would listen to the demands of the people and be more open. Meanwhile, on the streets outside, protesters were facing off with police. The contrast was stark. Television stations were using split screens to juxtapose the pomp of the ceremony with the running street battles outside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At around 2pm thousands of protesters left Victoria Park as part of a police-sanctioned march through the city. This was the third huge peaceful march to take place in under a month. Whereas the others had ended at Tamar Park, home to Hong Kong’s central government offices and Legislative Council (which is known as Legco), this time organisers asked the crowds to continue westward past the government buildings. Most obeyed. But several thousand protesters, most of them younger, veered right to help form a swelling crowd around Legco.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many wore masks to protect themselves from tear gas (and facial recognition technology). Some donned goggles to guard against pepper spray and helmets to protect from truncheons. Human supply chains passed along umbrellas, rolls of cling-film, cable-ties, pairs of scissors and bottles of water to the front line. Protesters uprooted metal fences from surrounding streets and dragged heavy bollards and bins to barricade the streets. Like all of the protests which have shaken the city in the past month, there was no obvious leader. Communications were shouted or conveyed by hand signals. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After being criticised for using excessive force, including rubber bullets, on protesters on June 12th, Hong Kong’s police force had become more passive. By the early evening protesters had smashed large glass doors and gained access to an atrium at Legco. Metal gates inside might have stopped them there, but within hours protestors had breached that defence as well. They swiftly made their way to the council chamber, a circular room where the city’s 70 lawmakers convene. Some smashed fittings and sprayed anti-government and pro-democracy graffiti on the walls while others read out their demands, which included universal suffrage for Hong Kong. Many regard the Hong Kong government as a puppet of central-government leaders in Beijing.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In this leaderless movement, decisions are made collectively on the hoof, or by emotional fiat of the moment. &lt;em&gt;Apple Daily&lt;/em&gt;, a newspaper, reported that one man inside the chamber was offering protesters the choice of whether to stay or leave. Police said that they would arrest anyone who had gone inside the building. Shortly after midnight police in riot gear cleared the streets near Legco with tear gas. Protesters withdrew from the chamber before police pushed their way in.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Some commentators were incredulous that security services had allowed Legco to be stormed in the first place. But others mused that the violence and chaos played into the hands of the authorities.The protesters&amp;#x27; display of Hong Kong’s old colonial flag in the chamber was a symbolic rebuke of the handover 22 years ago. That sort of provocation could help the government and pro-Beijing media cast protesters in a negative light. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On July 2nd Ms Lam held a 4am press conference in which she took a more defiant stance than in her handover speech, condemning the storming of Legco and declaring that authorities would &amp;quot;pursue any illegal acts&amp;quot; by protesters. But she also said she was willing to listen to the concerns voiced in the protests. O&lt;span&gt;rganisers say that more than &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;500,000&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; people participated&lt;/span&gt; in the protest march on July 1st. However authorities respond to the ransacking of Legco by several hundred protesters, they still must contend with millions of others in Hong Kong who have taken to the streets in recent weeks to register their dismay with the direction of their city under Chinese rule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 09:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hong Kong protesters storm the legislative council]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/07/01/hong-kong-protesters-storm-the-legislative-council]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_CNP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE DAY began with an official celebration of the return of Hong Kong to China on July 1st. It ended in the ransacking of a government building and tear gas. The televised chaos, including scenes of protesters violently smashing their way into and trashing the Legislative Council building, where some displayed the British and colonial-era flags, represent the latest test for Carrie Lam, the chief executive of Hong Kong, and for Xi Jinping, her ultimate boss in Beijing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A wave of massive protests in recent weeks has left them searching for how best to respond to the demands of citizens of Hong Kong, who fear that their freedoms are being whittled away under Chinese rule. Opposition has been galvanised, in particular, by a bill that would make it possible for people accused of crimes in mainland China to be sent there to face trial. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On June 15th Ms Lam had tried to appease protesters by postponing consideration of the bill. But protesters have called for it to be withdrawn entirely. Many have also called on Ms Lam to resign. In response Hong Kong leaders have tried thus far a mixture of patience, contrition and hard-nosed police tactics. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The day started with a new note of contrition from Ms Lam. The ceremony marking the 22nd anniversary of the handover was held at Hong Kong’s exhibition centre, where dignitaries watched a broadcast of the raising of the Chinese flag. In her remarks Ms Lam departed from the usual convention of opining on the progress of the city under Chinese rule, promising instead that her government would listen to the demands of the people and be more open. Meanwhile, on the streets outside, protesters were facing off with police. The contrast was stark. Television stations were using split screens to juxtapose the pomp of the ceremony with the running street battles outside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At around 2pm thousands of protesters left Victoria Park as part of a police-sanctioned march through the city. This was the third huge peaceful march to take place in under a month. Whereas the others had ended at Tamar Park, home to Hong Kong’s central government offices and Legislative Council (which is known as Legco), this time organisers asked the crowds to continue westward past the government buildings. Most obeyed. But several thousand protesters, most of them younger, veered right to help form a swelling crowd around Legco.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many wore masks to protect themselves from tear gas (and facial recognition technology). Some donned goggles to guard against pepper spray and helmets to protect from truncheons. Human supply chains passed along umbrellas, rolls of cling-film, cable-ties, pairs of scissors and bottles of water to the front line. Protesters uprooted metal fences from surrounding streets and dragged heavy bollards and bins to barricade the streets. Like all of the protests which have shaken the city in the past month, there was no obvious leader. Communications were shouted or conveyed by hand signals. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After being criticised for using excessive force, including rubber bullets, on protesters on June 12th, Hong Kong’s police force had become more passive. By the early evening protesters had smashed large glass doors and gained access to an atrium at Legco. Metal gates inside might have stopped them there, but within hours protestors had breached that defence as well. They swiftly made their way to the council chamber, a circular room where the city’s 70 lawmakers convene. Some smashed fittings and sprayed anti-government and pro-democracy graffiti on the walls while others read out their demands, which included universal suffrage for Hong Kong. Many regard the Hong Kong government as a puppet of central-government leaders in Beijing.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In this leaderless movement, decisions are made collectively on the hoof, or by emotional fiat of the moment. &lt;em&gt;Apple Daily&lt;/em&gt;, a newspaper, reported that one man inside the chamber was offering protesters the choice of whether to stay or leave. Police said that they would arrest anyone who had gone inside the building. Shortly after midnight police in riot gear cleared the streets near Legco with tear gas. Protesters withdrew from the chamber before police pushed their way in.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Some commentators were incredulous that security services had allowed Legco to be stormed in the first place. But others mused that the violence and chaos played into the hands of the authorities.The protesters&amp;#x27; display of Hong Kong’s old colonial flag in the chamber was a symbolic rebuke of the handover 22 years ago. That sort of provocation could help the government and pro-Beijing media cast protesters in a negative light. Organisers says more than a half-million people participated in the protest march. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It is unclear how Ms Lam, or Mr Xi, will greet the new day on July 2nd. But however they respond to the storming of Legco by several hundred protesters, they still must contend with millions of others in Hong Kong who have taken to the streets in recent weeks to register their dismay with the direction of their city under Chinese rule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 05:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>