<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Our essay competition for young people]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/26/our-essay-competition-for-young-people]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190617_OFD100_google_now_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-26T15:11:59Z&quot;&gt;Jun 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;THE ECONOMIST&lt;/em&gt;’s Open Future initiative was begun last year to make the case for political, economic and social freedoms at a time when these values are under assault. We want this exploration of ideas to involve our critics as well as our supporters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of the initiative we are holding an essay contest. It is open to people between 16 and 25 years old. Essays should be no longer than 1,000 words. The deadline for submissions is July 31st 2019. Please read the formal &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/19/terms-and-conditions-for-young-peoples-essay-contests&quot;&gt;terms of the competition&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The winning essay will be published on &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;&amp;#x27;s Open Future website and the winner will be invited to attend one of the three Open Future Festival events, to be held simultaneously in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://events.economist.com/events-conferences/asia/open-future-festival-hong-kong&quot;&gt;Hong Kong&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://events.economist.com/events-conferences/emea/open-future-festival-manchester/&quot;&gt;Manchester&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://events.economist.com/events-conferences/americas/open-future-festival-chicago/&quot;&gt;Chicago&lt;/a&gt; on Saturday October 5th 2019. &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; will pay for travel and accommodation; if the winner is under 18, we will pay for a guardian to accompany the winner as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Essays should answer the question by taking a stance and making a case based on arguments and facts. We will select the best essays based on the quality of their arguments, not the extent to which they align with our views. Though good writing is important, judges will make allowances for those for whom English is not their first language.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Essayists should email their submissions by &lt;strong&gt;July 31st 2019&lt;/strong&gt;, with the subject “Open Future essay contest” to: &lt;strong&gt;OpenFuture@Economist.com&lt;/strong&gt;. Please send only one, final submission, and place the text in the body of the email: we cannot accept attachments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The essay question is:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What fundamental economic and political change, if any, is needed for an effective response to climate change?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Description: For decades the world has been aware that human activity is heating up the planet to dangerous levels, with potentially calamitous consequences. Despite efforts by government, business and individuals to curtail the trend, carbon emissions are still rising. Perhaps new thinking is needed, since previous attempts to deal with the problem have failed. So what might be done?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Again, please do read the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/19/terms-and-conditions-for-young-peoples-essay-contests&quot;&gt;terms&lt;/a&gt; of the competition. We are a global organisation and we operate a strict privacy policy around the world. How we will use your personal data is spelled out in the terms of the competition, and how we handle personal data more generally is in our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economistgroup.com/results_and_governance/governance/privacy/&quot;&gt;privacy policy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By entering the competition, you agree to the terms of the competition, and you agree to us processing and using your personal data for the purposes described in the terms—including to administer the contest, to attribute winning entries and runners-up publicly and for promotional purposes. We will not use your details to market other services to you unless you specifically give us permission to do so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We encourage you to read last year’s winning essays &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2018/09/10/fresh-ideas-on-how-to-fix-the-world&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good luck!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 23:40:24 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The life and times of Liam Gallagher]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/26/the-life-and-times-of-liam-gallagher]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_BKP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-26T15:00:44Z&quot;&gt;Jun 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“WIBBLING RIVALRY” is 14-and-a-half minutes of vitriol. Released as a single in 1995, it is a recording of a heated, sweary argument between Noel and Liam Gallagher, then two up-and-coming musicians, during an interview with &lt;em&gt;NME&lt;/em&gt;. In the years that followed the brothers found great fame as part of Oasis, a Britpop group, but the hostilities persisted, with physical fights on stage and legal action off it. In 2009 Noel quit the band just moments before a performance at Rock en Seine, a music festival near Paris. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is in that heated moment that “Liam: As It Was”, a new documentary film, begins. Noel’s departure from the band seemed to be musical fratricide. Liam, along with other members of Oasis, rebranded as “Beady Eye” but they could not recapture the magic of what had come before. The venues got smaller, and their position on line-ups less prominent. “Fuck knows who I am,” Liam says in a clip taken later that year, and personal difficulties soon followed professional ones. In 2014 he divorced Nicole Appleton, his wife and partner of 14 years, following the revelation of a (second) love-child. Beady Eye also disbanded that year with a simple tweet: “Beady Eye are no longer. Thanks for all your support. LGx”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Made by Chris Lightening and Gavin Fitzgerald, “Liam: As It Was” documents the younger Gallagher’s downfall and his comeback. He takes a hands-on approach to the songwriting and production of his first solo album, “As You Were” (2017)—a notable contrast to his time in Oasis, where Noel assumed sole creative responsibility. On tour, Liam is precious with his voice and concerned when it begins to falter under the strain of so many performances. He no longer smokes during the day or drinks as much; he goes to bed at a decent hour. “I only take two grams of coke before I go stage,” he quips. “I used to do eight.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The film offers a little insight into the nature of his personal life. It shows Liam, one of British music’s biggest personalities, in more subdued moods: taking morning jogs, visiting his ageing mother and content in a new relationship with Debbie Gwyther, his manager. When his two teen-aged sons join him on tour in Amsterdam, they flip the bird to each other and talk about getting high. The viewer gets the sense Liam thinks he was absent from their lives—“their mothers did a good job,” he observes—but this thought is not explored further. More jarring is the sudden appearance of Molly Moorish, his 21-year-old daughter from an extra-marital affair; the film-makers choose to ignore an interview given in 2018, wherein Liam said he “just never got round to” meeting her. “Liam: As It Was” is more interested in the musical renaissance than the man himself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The viewer senses that the final missing piece in this tale of redemption is Noel. When Liam visits the Gallagher family home in Burnage, Manchester, he looks round the room he shared with his brother, happily explaining how their feud really began (he urinated on Noel’s stereo). When Liam is asked what he would do if they met after ten years of estrangement, he says he is unsure—that he might give Noel a “love bite”. Liam’s social-media provocations (“To all you [Noel Gallagher] fanboys I can and will sing any song he wrote bigger better than him even if I was kicked in the bollox by a wood pigeon”) and invitations (“...I forgive you now let’s get the BIG O back together and stop f***ing about the drinks are on me LG x”) are considered by the film’s talking-heads as child-like manifestations of love. He misses his brother, and, as explained by those closest to him, he wonders what Noel thinks when he releases new music. Indeed, Noel’s mark on the film goes beyond mere sentiment. After watching the film ahead of its premiere, he refused to allow any Oasis songs to feature. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Liam: As It Was” is screening in Britain now&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 22:40:45 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The global economy is on a knife-edge]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/25/the-global-economy-is-on-a-knife-edge]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_fnd000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE GLOBAL economic mood has taken to whipsawing between gloom and optimism. It can be hard to keep pace. This newspaper warned readers to prepare for “the next recession” in 2015 and 2018, pausing in 2017 to hail “the world economy’s surprising rise”. Lately, the periods of alarm and alacrity seem to have shortened. Markets began 2019 on the rebound and then took fright—only to surge in recent weeks. It is tempting to see the swings as mistaken attempts to find narratives in noise. But they have been accompanied by very real economic wobbles. Trade growth slumped in 2015, rebounded and is now decelerating. Global output, as reflected in measures of purchasing managers’ activity, bounced along with market gyrations, sinking in 2015 and lurching upward in 2017 before falling this year to levels not seen since the depths of the euro-area crisis. Rather than noise, the mood swings reflect investors’ attempts to work out which of two very different equilibria an unsettled global economy will land on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You might suppose that such uncertainty would be the norm. Though highly integrated, the global economy lacks a centralised, stabilising hand, like a national Treasury or central bank. During the financial crisis, the members of the G20 managed an impressive degree of policy co-ordination. But the desire to co-operate has rather waned since then. America’s Federal Reserve has some ability to call a global tune; Silvia Miranda-Agrippino of Northwestern University and Hélène Rey of the London Business School argue that American monetary policy strongly influences the global financial cycle. Similarly Emine Boz and Gita Gopinath of the IMF and Mikkel Plagborg-Moller of Princeton University reckon that fluctuations in the dollar have an enormous influence on volume of global trade. But in a world of flexible exchange rates countries should still enjoy plenty of room to go their own way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The world’s problem, however, seems less that national governments are working at cross-purposes, and more that policymakers are torn between incompatible aims. Take central banks. The world’s monetary maestros are eager to leave behind the near-zero interest rates that have prevailed since the financial crisis. But the soft spots into which the global economy keeps stumbling suggest that this desire may be inconsistent with steady, robust growth. Last year the Fed raised its benchmark interest rate by a percentage point, to 2.4%, and reckoned it would rise above 3% by the end of 2019. After its meeting on June 19th, however, Jerome Powell, its chairman, all but told markets to expect rate cuts later this year, “in light of increased uncertainties”. Other central banks have also chosen to beat a hasty retreat. The European Central Bank (ECB) ended its programme of stimulative asset purchases in December 2018 and suggested that its policy rates could rise in 2019. But at its June meeting it too abandoned talk of rate rises for discussions of the need for additional stimulus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Governments are likewise conflicted. China’s leaders want to rebalance their economy away from excessive investment and to shrink the role of state-owned firms. They keenly feel the need to depend less on rapid growth in credit. Yet both domestic tranquillity and the ability to project power abroad depend on economic growth. Whenever steps toward economic reform cause too rapid a slowdown, China’s government quickly returns to stimulus. In response to the sudden slowing late last year, it flooded the economy with credit, zapping the global economy with a jolt of energy. New data reveal that China’s total debt-to-GDP ratio, excluding the financial sector, leapt by more than five percentage points in the first quarter of 2019, to nearly 250% of GDP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile President Donald Trump is trying to harangue the Fed into a more accommodative monetary policy in the run-up to next year’s elections. But he is unwilling to abandon his belligerent approach to trade relations. At a meeting of the G20 on June 28th and 29th he and Xi Jinping, his Chinese counterpart, are expected to hold talks regarding their intensifying trade war. Unless they resolve a number of significant disputes America will probably extend its tariffs to an additional $300bn of Chinese imports. So far America’s tariffs have probably had only modest macroeconomic effects, though their impact is growing. But markets’ tendency to reel in the face of trade-war escalations suggests a growing concern that the present is prologue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stick a fork in it&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;World leaders must always manage trade-offs between competing aims. So why are policy conflicts unsettling markets just now? Except during financial crises (and none appears imminent), economic growth is rarely so balanced on a knife-edge. But interest rates around the world remain very low, leaving little tolerance for policy correction. In the euro area both short-term and long-term interest rates are close to or even below zero. New ECB easing, if it occurs, will mostly help the economy by pushing down the value of the euro and boosting European exporters, at the expense of firms elsewhere. America’s position is not much better. When markets were expecting rate increases, the Fed could give a sagging economy a boost simply by delaying them. But markets now expect the Fed to cut rates by at least 0.75 percentage points during the next year. It can either disappoint them and risk adding to pessimism, or move rates much of the way back to zero.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Any misstep by Mr Trump or Mr Xi thus leaves central banks hard-pressed to keep economies on an even keel. And a central-bank slip-up, such as one interest-rate rise too many, increases the strain on already-conflicted governments. As slackening global demand crimps purchases of Chinese exports, for instance, the trade-off between domestic deleveraging and robust growth in Beijing becomes much starker. The global mood has not yet settled, meaning that a happy outcome remains possible. But if policymakers do not decide soon to put growth ahead of their other goals, the next turn toward pessimism could be decisive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 20:40:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“There’s tolerance but not political activism”—gay rights in Japan]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/26/theres-tolerance-but-not-political-activism-gay-rights-in-japan]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_blm509.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-26T09:42:33Z&quot;&gt;Jun 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A BILL to recognise &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://espresso.economist.com/769315063304083a2049bd02b23440ca&quot;&gt;same-sex marriage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; has failed in Japan’s parliament, exposing a widening divide between the views of its politicians and the values of its people. For some officials, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/22/burundis-eternal-supreme-guide-enforces-an-election-tax&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Burundi’s election tax&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is an excuse for extortion; for some citizens, a reason to flee the country. And, why you should be circumspect about that next &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/20/the-promotion-curse&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;promotion opportunity&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/0ac4ca9a-dd95-4ab3-97d1-ab4d0db731a5&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 19:40:35 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The frontline of the NHS is being reinvented]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/26/the-frontline-of-the-nhs-is-being-reinvented]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_brd001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-26T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE NATIONAL HEALTH SERVICE is free, so it is also rationed. Family doctors, known as general practitioners (GPs), act as the first port of call for patients; friendly gatekeepers to the rest of the service who refer people to specialists only if needed. But in some parts of the country, including St Austell on the Cornish coast, access to the rationers is itself now rationed. “You can’t book an appointment to see me here,” explains Stewart Smith, a 38-year-old GP, one of a team in charge of an innovative new medical centre. “You go on a list and then we triage you.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is an approach that will soon be familiar to more patients. Simon Stevens, chief executive of NHS England, has said that being a GP is arguably the most important job in the country. There is, however, a severe shortage of them. According to the Nuffield Trust, a think-tank, there are 58 GPs per 100,000 people, down from 66 in 2009—the first sustained fall since the 1960s. Only half of patients say they almost always see their preferred doctor, down from 65% six years ago. The average consultation lasts just nine minutes, among the quickest in the rich world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the NHS hopes to train and recruit new family doctors, the gap won’t be plugged any time soon. A new five-year contract to fund GP practices will eventually include £891m ($1.1bn) a year for 20,000 extra clinical staff, such as pharmacists and physiotherapists, with the first cash for such roles arriving on July 1st. To access the money, practices will have to form networks, which, it is hoped, will help them take advantage of economies of scale and do more to prevent illnesses rather than treating them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the four practices serving St Austell merged in 2015, it was an opportunity to reconsider how they did things. The GPs kept a diary, noting precisely what they got up to during the day. It turned out that lots could be done by others: administrators could take care of some communication with hospitals, physios could see people with bad backs and psychiatric nurses those with anxiety. So now they do. Only patients with the most complicated or urgent problems make it to a doctor. As a result, each GP is responsible for 3,800 locals, compared with an average of 2,000 in the rest of Cornwall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although few practices have made changes on the scale of St Austell Healthcare, across England the number of clinical staff other than GPs has grown by more than a third since 2015. The logic behind the introduction of these new roles is compelling, says Ben Gershlick of the Health Foundation, another think-tank. The NHS estimates that 30% of GPs’ time is spent on musculoskeletal problems, for instance, which could often be handled by a physiotherapist. Another estimate suggests 11% of their day is taken up by paperwork. Doctors complain that they are overworked, and growing numbers retire early. They are also expensive: the starting salary for a GP is £57,655, whereas a physio costs around half as much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NHS leaders hope the new workers will help practices play a more active role in their community, linking up with services provided by local authorities and charities. Each network will be responsible for a population of 30,000-50,000. The plan is that they will use data analysis to intervene early to prevent illness, and that practices will often share the new staff with others in their network.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those that are further down the road sing the benefits of the new approach. Caroline Taylor of the Beechwood Medical Centre in Halifax says that new roles quickly show their worth. Her practice took in a “work wellness adviser” employed by the council. The adviser’s goal was to help ten people over the age of 50 with poor mental health back to work in a year—a task which she completed in just six weeks. In St Austell two pharmacists last year helped to cut more than £140,000 from prescribing costs. Far fewer staff now report that they are burnt out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working in a team will nevertheless require a big shift in mindset for many doctors, particularly those in surgeries that have never before employed anyone else aside from the odd nurse. One worry is that practices will end up doing what they must to get the extra funding, but little more. There are also more practical problems. Seven in ten GPs say their practices are too cramped to provide new services, and it is not clear where some of the extra staff will be hired from.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the biggest problem is that patients have grown used to having a doctor on demand. Although those who no longer have to queue for an appointment may be happy, others might feel fobbed off if diverted to another clinician. A study published last year by Charlotte Paddison of the Nuffield Trust, and colleagues, in the &lt;em&gt;British Medical Journal&lt;/em&gt; found that patients have less trust in the care provided by a nurse if they initially expected to see a doctor. Patients who have a close relationship with their GP tend to be more satisfied and enjoy better health outcomes than others.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But other evidence suggests that, for some conditions, nurses provide care that is as good or better than that provided by GPs. The aim, says Nav Chana of the National Association of Primary Care, which helped develop the new approach, is therefore to use small teams of doctors and other clinical staff to replicate the sort of relationship with patients that used to be more common. Just parachuting in “a lot of people who look like doctors” will not raise standards, he warns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shortage of GPs leaves the NHS with little choice but to try something new. “A lot of the world has either copied or is trying to copy English primary care,” in particular its openness to all and the continuity of care that it provides, says Dr Chana. Keeping these strengths, while changing how primary care works, is the task NHS officials are now facing up to. Even if they succeed, it will take time for the public to adjust. Having explained the benefits of the new way of doing things, one GP pauses, before adding: “I should say, though, patients don’t love it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 19:40:34 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gambia’s former dictator is accused of rape, on top of other crimes]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/26/gambias-former-dictator-is-accused-of-rape-on-top-of-other-crimes]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_map504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-26T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHEN FATOU JALLOW was crowned as Gambia’s beauty queen in 2014, it was one of the happiest days of her life. But it was the prelude to a nightmare. Soon afterwards Yahya Jammeh, then the country’s dictator, asked the 18-year-old to marry him. Ms Jallow refused, but Mr Jammeh’s aides kept calling. After accepting an invitation to his home to attend a religious event, Ms Jallow was drugged and raped by Mr Jammeh. “He asked me what made me think that I could deny him,” she recalls. “I kept screaming and he kept telling me no one could hear me.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Jallow’s torment was far from an isolated case in a dictatorship reviled for its many abuses. Human Rights Watch and TRIAL International, rights groups based in New York and Geneva respectively, have detailed several other allegations of rampant sexual abuse, violence and coercion by Mr Jammeh and his aides. Their report, released today, includes accounts from three women who allege the former dictator raped and sexually assaulted them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Jammeh, who had seized power in a coup in 1994, was ousted in early 2017 after losing an election in late 2016. But public anger against him lives on in Gambia, stoked by a stream of new revelations about the horrors of his rule. Many have emerged in testimony before a Truth, Reparations and Reconciliation Commission established by Gambia’s new president, Adama Barrow, to investigate the old regime’s crimes and recommend prosecutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Jammeh’s henchmen known as “the junglers” and his intelligence agency killed and tortured thousands. Journalists and activists disappeared in the night, and families often never saw the victims’ bodies again. Many were thrown into an airless dungeon known as the “crocodile hole” beneath the headquarters of Mr Jammeh’s intelligence agency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The longer he ruled, the more crazed Mr Jammeh became. He once detained and drugged an estimated 1,000 villagers with a powerful hallucinogenic drug because he thought that witchcraft was responsible for the death of a family member. He also claimed to be able to cure people of HIV with his bare hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also stole just about everything that was not nailed down in a poor country of about 2m people. When he fled into exile in Equatorial Guinea he did so in his Rolls-Royce, leaving the state’s coffers empty. Human-rights groups and many of Mr Jammeh’s former victims hope that they can get him to stand trial for his crimes. To do so they hope to generate enough international pressure on Equatorial Guinea to force its president, Teodoro Obiang, to hand him over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reed Brody, an American lawyer working with Human Rights Watch, points out that many of Mr Jammeh’s victims came from other west African countries, including Ghana and Ivory Coast. These included 56 west African migrants who were massacred in 2005 by Mr Jammeh’s men. Mr Brody think that the latest rape allegations will add further pressure. “Rape is one of the vilest of crimes,” Mr Brody says. “It’s going to be harder and harder for Obiang to keep protecting Jammeh.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Jallow managed to escape Gambia and now lives in Canada, where she is studying social care. Talking about what happened “is my duty to other girls,” says Ms Jallow. “I am willing to open the gate and make sure that this man will one day face justice. I want to send a message to men in our society, that we’re not property, that we’re not goats.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 18:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[An underwhelming start to the “ultimate” Israeli-Palestinian deal]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/25/an-underwhelming-start-to-the-ultimate-israeli-palestinian-deal]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_map503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-25T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT COULD have been Davos, or any of the other conferences on the annual circuit for the world’s wealthy. Jared Kushner, the son-in-law and a senior adviser to America’s president, took the stage to offer his vision for solving the Israeli-Palestinian conflict. The combatants, he lectured, were “trapped in an inefficient framework of the past”. Their obstinacy is a barrier to turning the West Bank and Gaza into “a bustling commercial and tourist centre”. If 70 years of warfare would simply come to a halt, “we can turn this region from a victim of past conflicts into a model for commerce and advancement across the world.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before he took office in 2017 Donald Trump vowed to broker the “ultimate deal” between Israelis and Palestinians. To oversee the effort he chose, Mr Kushner, a real-estate developer with no experience in diplomacy or the Middle East. The result has been about as expected. There is still no political plan for resolving the underlying conflict and its many thorny issues: borders, refugees or the status of Jerusalem, and the very notion of Palestinian statehood. Its release has been repeatedly delayed; diplomats hint that it may remain on the shelf until Mr Trump’s second term, if he wins one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead Mr Kushner organised this two-day confab in Bahrain. Dubbed the “Peace to Prosperity” workshop, the centrepiece is a 96-page plan that pledges $50bn worth of investment in Palestine and neighbouring countries after a peace deal. The document, to be fair, is impressive in scope. It suggests projects to boost agriculture and tourism, fix Palestine’s infrastructure and improve governance. All of this would be funded by a mix of grants, concessional loans and private-sector money, from the wealthy Gulf states and elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Missing amidst all this detail, however, is anything about the Israeli occupation, in its various forms, of the West Bank and Gaza Strip, or of schism between the Palestinian leaders in the two territories. The plan presupposes that the noxious politics of the conflict have simply vanished. Mr Kushner proposes spending $5bn to connect the West Bank and Gaza, for example. Israel has undertaken to do this for years but never has, because the link is not simply a matter of building a monorail. It raises political and security questions for Israel. Another proposal calls for $2bn to give the Palestinians 5G wireless infrastructure. Entrepreneurs would be thrilled. But there is no mention of how to overcome objections from the Israeli army, which let the West Bank install 3G only last year (a decade after the rest of the world).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As it stands, then, the plan is thoroughly unrealistic. That is the point, Mr Kushner’s supporters argue. It is meant to offer the Palestinians a peace dividend, an incentive to accept his (perhaps) forthcoming political vision. They certainly need economic help. Unemployment in the West Bank is 17%. In Gaza it is as high as 55%. Adjusted for inflation, GDP per person is almost unchanged from 20 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But to the Palestinians this smells like a bribe from a hostile president. Mr Trump cut all American aid to them—even $25m in funding for hospitals in East Jerusalem that treat, among other things, children with cancer. He overturned decades of precedent to recognise Jerusalem as Israel’s capital. And aides hint that the political plan will give the Palestinians far less than the sovereign state along the pre-1967 borders that they demand. America’s ambassador to Israel, David Friedman, said this month that Israel had the right to annex some territory in the West Bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So the Palestinians are boycotting the event. Their president, Mahmoud Abbas, refused to send anyone from his government. “The deal of shame will go to hell,” he said in May. The private sector also declined invitations. Of the 5m Palestinians in the occupied territories, the only publicly-confirmed attendee is Ashraf al-Jabari, a former secret-police officer who has turned into a businessman and has cultivated unusual ties with Israeli settlers in his home town of Hebron. He also has a history of writing bum cheques&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Few of the other attendees are enthusiastic. “We tried to find the lowest level of representation that wouldn’t be offensive,” quips a European diplomat in Tel Aviv. Jordan and Egypt sent only their deputy finance ministers. With the Palestinians boycotting, Arab states were reluctant to share a stage with Israeli officials. But the latter weren’t invited either because of Arab misgivings (though some Israeli businessmen did come). Even press coverage is limited: organisers did not allow most foreign journalists covering the Middle East to attend. They did accredit reporters from six Israeli outlets, who have sent slightly fawning dispatches. The country’s largest newspaper, Israel Hayom, which backs both Mr Trump and the Israeli prime minister, Binyamin Netanyahu, dubbed Bahrain the “island of hope”, an odd appellation for a kingdom that crushed a popular uprising in 2011.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And that, perhaps, points to the real outcome of the workshop. It is the most public manifestation of a long and mostly private rapprochement between Israel and the Gulf states, one the Trump administration is keen to promote. The event will do nothing to end the Israeli-Palestinian conflict. But it is another sign that the Gulf states are looking to move past that conflict. Though they are not quite ready to recognise Israel, they see it as an important regional power, an ally against a shared threat from Iran. The Palestinians have far less to offer. “All we have is our moral power,” says Mkhaimer Abu Saada, a political analyst in Gaza. That still counts for something—but less and less with each passing day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 04:41:07 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is the most dangerous drug?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/25/what-is-the-most-dangerous-drug]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_woc294.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY IS ALCOHOL legal but many other intoxicants not? That question is the subject of a report published today by the Global Commission on Drug Policy, an independent group of 26 former presidents and other bigwigs. They conclude that, as far as the scientific evidence is concerned, current drug laws have no rhyme or reason to them. The commission blames the UN’s drug classification system, which sorts some 300 psychoactive substances into “schedules” according to their harms and benefits. Some, such as morphine, have medical uses. Others, such as psilocybin (the active ingredient in magic mushrooms), are used mostly recreationally. Drugs without any apparent medical utility are automatically placed in the most dangerous category—and subjected to the strictest criminal penalties—regardless of the risk they pose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flaws of the UN’s system have been evident for years. In 2010 a group of British drug experts ranked 20 popular intoxicating substances on 16 physical, psychological and social harms, including those done to non-users, such as crime and family breakdown. Alcohol came out as the most harmful, followed by heroin and crack cocaine. Psychedelic “party” drugs, including ecstasy, LSD and mushrooms, were deemed mostly benign—with harm scores less than half that of tobacco—despite being lumped with cocaine and heroin in the UN’s classification system. This ranking is not without its own idiosyncrasies, many of which reflect how drugs are currently used and regulated. Alcohol’s position at the top is partly the result of its widespread use, which causes greater harms to others (crack cocaine is considered the most harmful drug for the user). Drugs such as heroin, meanwhile, would be ranked lower if users could always buy an unadulterated dose, and did not have to resort to sharing needles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Designing laws for drugs that are consistent with their dangers and benefits requires predicting how drug markets will respond. Difficult as that may be, it is the way forward, argues the Global Commission. The zero-tolerance approach adopted by many governments has led to a host of social problems, including soaring prison costs and ill-health. “It is past high time to accept the fact that a society without drugs is an illusion,” the report argues. Regulating drugs in a more sensible manner would make them safer—and not just for those who take them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 03:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bargaining chips—the US-China tech war]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/25/bargaining-chips-the-us-china-tech-war]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_blm508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-25T19:00:56Z&quot;&gt;Jun 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE TRADE war between &lt;strong&gt;America and China&lt;/strong&gt; is intensifying after America blacklisted five more Chinese technology entities. Will this jeopardise any talk of a trade deal &lt;b&gt;at the upcoming G20 summit&lt;/b&gt;? Could low-denomination treasury bills help Italy’s cash-strapped economy? Also, a new way of working called &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/13/for-the-future-look-to-the-past&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“ghost work”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Phil Coggan hosts. Runtime: 17 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/0d818142-e5b7-4da0-927b-42a380d79b62&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 02:40:24 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Overmatched policymakers risk toppling the world economy into trouble]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/25/overmatched-policymakers-risk-toppling-the-world-economy-into-trouble]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_fnd000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE GLOBAL economic mood has taken to whipsawing between gloom and optimism. It can be hard to keep pace. This newspaper warned readers to prepare for “the next recession” in 2015 and 2018, pausing in 2017 to hail “the world economy’s surprising rise”. Lately, the periods of alarm and alacrity seem to have shortened. Markets began 2019 on the rebound and then took fright—only to surge in recent weeks. It is tempting to see the swings as mistaken attempts to find narratives in noise. But they have been accompanied by very real economic wobbles. Trade growth slumped in 2015, rebounded and is now decelerating. Global output, as reflected in measures of purchasing managers’ activity, bounced along with market gyrations, sinking in 2015 and lurching upward in 2017 before falling this year to levels not seen since the depths of the euro-area crisis. Rather than noise, the mood swings reflect investors’ attempts to work out which of two very different equilibria an unsettled global economy will land on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You might suppose that such uncertainty would be the norm. Though highly integrated, the global economy lacks a centralised, stabilising hand, like a national Treasury or central bank. During the financial crisis, the members of the G20 managed an impressive degree of policy co-ordination. But the desire to co-operate has rather waned since then. America’s Federal Reserve has some ability to call a global tune; Silvia Miranda-Agrippino of Northwestern University and Hélène Rey of the London Business School argue that American monetary policy strongly influences the global financial cycle. Similarly Emine Boz and Gita Gopinath of the IMF and Mikkel Plagborg-Moller of Princeton University reckon that fluctuations in the dollar have an enormous influence on volume of global trade. But in a world of flexible exchange rates countries should still enjoy plenty of room to go their own way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The world’s problem, however, seems less that national governments are working at cross-purposes, and more that policymakers are torn between incompatible aims. Take central banks. The world’s monetary maestros are eager to leave behind the near-zero interest rates that have prevailed since the financial crisis. But the soft spots into which the global economy keeps stumbling suggest that this desire may be inconsistent with steady, robust growth. Last year the Fed raised its benchmark interest rate by a percentage point, to 2.4%, and reckoned it would rise above 3% by the end of 2019. After its meeting on June 19th, however, Jerome Powell, its chairman, all but told markets to expect rate cuts later this year, “in light of increased uncertainties”. Other central banks have also chosen to beat a hasty retreat. The European Central Bank (ECB) ended its programme of stimulative asset purchases in December 2018 and suggested that its policy rates could rise in 2019. But at its June meeting it too abandoned talk of rate rises for discussions of the need for additional stimulus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Governments are likewise conflicted. China’s leaders want to rebalance their economy away from excessive investment and to shrink the role of state-owned firms. They keenly feel the need to depend less on rapid growth in credit. Yet both domestic tranquillity and the ability to project power abroad depend on economic growth. Whenever steps toward economic reform cause too rapid a slowdown, China’s government quickly returns to stimulus. In response to the sudden slowing late last year, it flooded the economy with credit, zapping the global economy with a jolt of energy. New data reveal that China’s total debt-to-GDP ratio, excluding the financial sector, leapt by more than five percentage points in the first quarter of 2019, to nearly 250% of GDP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile President Donald Trump is trying to harangue the Fed into a more accommodative monetary policy in the run-up to next year’s elections. But he is unwilling to abandon his belligerent approach to trade relations. At a meeting of the G20 on June 28th and 29th he and Xi Jinping, his Chinese counterpart, are expected to hold talks regarding their intensifying trade war. Unless they resolve a number of significant disputes America will probably extend its tariffs to an additional $300bn of Chinese imports. So far America’s tariffs have probably had only modest macroeconomic effects, though their impact is growing. But markets’ tendency to reel in the face of trade-war escalations suggests a growing concern that the present is prologue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stick a fork in it&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;World leaders must always manage trade-offs between competing aims. So why are policy conflicts unsettling markets just now? Except during financial crises (and none appears imminent), economic growth is rarely so balanced on a knife-edge. But interest rates around the world remain very low, leaving little tolerance for policy correction. In the euro area both short-term and long-term interest rates are close to or even below zero. New ECB easing, if it occurs, will mostly help the economy by pushing down the value of the euro and boosting European exporters, at the expense of firms elsewhere. America’s position is not much better. When markets were expecting rate increases, the Fed could give a sagging economy a boost simply by delaying them. But markets now expect the Fed to cut rates by at least 0.75 percentage points during the next year. It can either disappoint them and risk adding to pessimism, or move rates much of the way back to zero.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Any misstep by Mr Trump or Mr Xi thus leaves central banks hard-pressed to keep economies on an even keel. And a central-bank slip-up, such as one interest-rate rise too many, increases the strain on already-conflicted governments. As slackening global demand crimps purchases of Chinese exports, for instance, the trade-off between domestic deleveraging and robust growth in Beijing becomes much starker. The global mood has not yet settled, meaning that a happy outcome remains possible. But if policymakers do not decide soon to put growth ahead of their other goals, the next turn toward pessimism could be decisive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 02:40:22 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>