<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Ukraine elects Volodymyr Zelensky, TV star and political neophyte]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/22/ukraine-elects-volodymyr-zelensky-tv-star-and-political-neophyte]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/articles/000_1ft9pb.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-22T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WITH DANCE music blaring, drinks flowing, and ping-pong balls flying about, Volodymyr Zelensky’s election-day headquarters in Kiev felt like a nightclub. Mr Zelensky (pictured) had reason to party: as expected, the comedian-cum-candidate trounced the incumbent, Petro Poroshenko, in the presidential run-off election on April 21st. He racked up a stunning 73% of the vote against the president’s 24%. Despite having no political experience and only a vague policy platform, voters entrusted him with the helm of a country that needs radical reform and is still enmeshed in a simmering war with Russia. Best known for playing a schoolteacher who becomes president in a popular TV series called “Servant of the People”, Mr Zelensky entered his election-night festivities to the theme song from the show he has made a reality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A native Russian-speaker of Jewish heritage hailing from the south-eastern city of Kryvyi Rih, Mr Zelensky galvanised support from across the country. He carried all but one of the 25 Ukrainian regions where voting was held. (Crimea, which Russia annexed in 2014, did not hold an election.) His slick campaign targeted voters online and through social media, while largely eschewing conventional campaigning in the form of rallies and interviews. He offered broadly popular promises to maintain Ukraine’s Western-leaning course, to end the war, and to fight corruption, while proffering few specifics and promising to crowdsource important appointments and policies. He emerged as the projection of voters’ frustration with Mr Poroshenko’s checkered leadership and of their hopes for a better future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite widespread fears about challenges to the legitimacy of the vote, election day passed off smoothly. An emboldened civil society and free press helped hold politicians to account. “Information has been plentiful and accessible, no one has pressured me, this is my choice,” one Kievan nurse said after casting a vote for Mr Zelensky. Mr Poroshenko conceded promptly, promising to “accept the will of the Ukrainian people”. Five years after its revolution, Ukraine has seen competitive elections unseat a sitting president in a peaceful transition of power—a rarity in the post-Soviet region and a genuinely impressive achievement. In his first remarks after exit polls became public, Mr Zelensky nodded to this reality, and the example it may set: “To all the countries of the former Soviet Union: look at us, everything is possible.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Poroshenko’s campaign was a crude appeal to patriotism. He ran under the slogan of “Army, Language, Faith”, playing up his successes at securing an independent Ukrainian Orthodox Church and visa-free travel to the European Union. He sought to paint Mr Zelensky as dangerously inexperienced and beholden to outside interests. “He is a bright candy wrapper,” Mr Poroshenko said in a debate ahead of the vote. “There are Russians inside and fugitive oligarchs,” he added, referring to Mr Zelensky’s murky ties with Ihor Kolomoisky, a controversial oligarch whose TV channel airs his shows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both the successes and the reservations about his opponent were reasonable points to draw attention to. But voters instead focused on Mr Poroshenko’s failure to fulfil the promises of the revolution that swept him to power five years ago. With corruption still rife and GDP per head in Ukraine the lowest in Europe, just 9% of Ukrainians have confidence in their government, the lowest level in the world. “I voted for Poroshenko [in 2014], but things haven’t got better,” said Nadezhda Tsaplyuk, who voted for Mr Zelensky in the district in Kiev where Mr Poroshenko won more support than anywhere else in the city in 2014. “Sure we have visa-free [travel to the EU], but I don’t have the money to go anywhere.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This malaise fuelled Mr Zelensky’s rise. Many Ukrainians expressed their choice in terms of opposition to the current regime, rather than enthusiasm for the candidate himself. “People are voting against the old authorities,” Daniil Bychenok, an 18-year-old student, said. “We don’t know what we’re voting for.” In the run-up to the vote, polls showed that 60% of those who planned to support Mr Zelensky saw it as a protest vote. “Zelensky is winning because we can’t live like this any longer,” says Vladimir Bazhanov, a pensioner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Expectations for Mr Zelensky, in turn, are as high as confidence in the current regime is low. “He’ll jail a few of them and everything will get better,” Olga Podolskaya, a retired lawyer, predicted hopefully. Promising vague but radical change proved to be an effective campaign strategy. But Mr Zelensky may struggle to fulfill the hopes voters have for him. “People are waiting for a miracle, but there won’t be any miracles,” Volodymyr Fesenko, a political analyst, said ahead of the vote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite his huge victory, Mr Zelensky will face many challenges once he takes office. Rival parties will still control parliament, the Rada, which holds significant power in Ukraine’s mixed system. He will need to turn his new party, Servant of the People, named after his TV show, into a real political machine if he wants to gain control of the Rada in the autumn. Vladimir Putin still has many tools to put pressure on his new counterpart. Ukraine’s loan agreement with the International Monetary Fund stipulates further increases in household gas prices this year, measures that have already proved deeply unpopular. Disappointment from unmet expectations, in fact, is the subject of the second season of Mr Zelensky’s show, entitled “From Love to Impeachment”. As one Zelensky aide says, “We know what can happen: we wrote this all already.” After the post-election buzz wears off, the thankless reality of governing will begin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 18:06:53 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A massacre on Easter in Sri Lanka kills at least 290 people]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/21/a-massacre-on-easter-in-sri-lanka-kills-at-least-290-people]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-21T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update (22nd April 2019):&lt;/strong&gt; This is a moving news story. The death toll will be updated as it rises. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT HAS BEEN nearly ten years since the guns fell silent in Sri Lanka’s civil war. But bloodshed returned with a vengeance on Easter Sunday when a succession of explosions ripped through three churches packed with worshippers, and three five-star hotels. At least 290 people were killed and hundreds more were injured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The coincidence of the attacks with the upcoming anniversary of the Sri Lankan army’s defeat of the Tamil Tiger rebels on May 19th—ending a war that pitted the ethnic Tamil and a largely Hindu minority, against the Sinhalese Buddhist majority—may be just that. The authorities are being cautious about apportioning blame, particularly because of the recent history of communal violence on the island, both during and after the war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A senior police official said there were signs the six blasts were all suicide bombings. This was a favourite tactic of the Liberation Tigers of Tamil Eelam, but no fingers are being pointed at any Tamil groups. And suicide tactics, especially aimed at religious targets and foreign tourists, are also a hallmark of international jihadist groups. Yet the country has little history of jihadist activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The explosions were the deadliest attacks in the country since the end of the war. They took place in close succession beginning at around 8.30am. The first was at the St Sebastian Church in Negombo, a Catholic-majority area. Photographs showed tiles blown off a blackened roof and bloodied bodies on the ground. Two other explosions occurred at St Anthony’s Church in Colombo (another Catholic church), and at the Zion Church (Evangelical) in Batticaloa, around 220km east of the capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 30 minutes later, there were explosions at the Shangri-La, the Kingsbury and the Cinnamon Grand hotels in Colombo. All are five-star venues and many of the victims were enjoying Easter breakfast special offers. At least 11 foreigners were confirmed killed. Among the nationalities were Indian, Turkish, Portuguese, British and joint US-UK nationals. The authorities counted the bodies of 25 more people presumed to be foreign. The US State Department said “several” Americans had been killed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two more explosions took place later in the day, in which eight people were killed, but they appear to be related to security forces’ raids on terrorists’ suspected hideouts. Seven people were arrested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main hospital in Colombo was a scene of chaos, with hysterical relatives swarming the narrow road leading to the emergency unit amid a steady flow of ambulances. As news of the attacks spread via social media, police rushed to churches around the country and sent worshippers home. Cardinal Malcolm Ranjith, the head of the Catholic church, cancelled all other services. Security forces were later deployed to guard churches, hotels and the international airport. The government cancelled school for children whose new terms were starting Monday. Universities were declared indefinitely closed. A countrywide police curfew came into effect in the afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whoever the perpetrators may be, there are worries that the blasts will stir renewed inter-communal strife. Of Sri Lanka’s population of more than 20m people, about 75% are Sinhalese (who are mostly Buddhists). Tamils, living mostly in the north and east, make up about 11% and are predominantly Hindu. The rebellion by the Tamil Tigers lasted for 27 years. Muslims make up about 9% of the population and speak Tamil. Although they did not join the Tamil Tigers’s rebellion—and indeed some were evicted from the north by them—after the war Muslims have become the target of Buddhist-nationalist attacks. Christians, mostly Roman Catholics, make up about 7% of the population and straddle the Sinhalese-Tamil divide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The puzzle was why the Catholic church was targeted,” said Jayadeva Uyangoda, a political scientist. The spread of Catholicism dates to 1505 with Portuguese colonisation and subsequent proselytisation. Catholics permeate all levels of governance, the private sector and even the army, but they were not a particular focus of Tamil Tiger attacks during the civil war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;St Anthony’s church is patronised by both Tamils and Sinhalese, including non-Christians. Any assaults in recent times against Christians—also by Buddhist extremist groups—have been aimed against new Evangelical churches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hence the speculation about “foreign actors”, as Cardinal Ranjith put it—in particular Muslim extremists. Only a few dozen Sri Lankan Muslims are thought to have joined the tens of thousands of foreigners who volunteered to fight with the Islamic State group in Iraq and Syria. Some have worried about more radical forms of Islam being introduced to the island by contact with foreign preachers. Most alarming, in January Sri Lankan police said they uncovered a large cache of explosives at an IS training camp in the north of the country; it was apparently intended for use against several Buddhist monuments in the ancient city of Anuradhapura.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One reason to worry about the possible radicalisation of Muslims is that Sinhalese Buddhist extremists have sought to instigate and co-ordinate mob violence against them. A traffic incident in 2018 in which a Sinhalese truck driver was assaulted by four Muslim men (and subsequently died) resulted in days of attacks on Muslim homes and businesses and a large number of injuries. In 2014, there was Buddhist-Muslim sectarian violence in several towns in the south fired by the racist speech by a Buddhist monk, Galagodatte Gnarasara, who is now in prison for contempt of court (on a separate matter).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the Easter bombings, as rumours and incendiary anti-Muslim comments spread like wildfire, the government swiftly shut down all social-media platforms, including WhatsApp, Viber, Facebook and YouTube.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the hunt for the perpetrators begins, Sri Lanka will be counting the cost of a day of carnage it had not expected. The Catholic church is preparing for mass funerals, which the government has said it will pay for. The country as a whole has suffered a blow to its lucrative tourism sector. Until Easter day it had enjoyed a reputation as one of the safest countries for holidaymakers. That has changed utterly, along with much else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 18:06:52 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A massacre on Easter Sunday in Sri Lanka kills 290 people]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/21/a-massacre-on-easter-sunday-in-sri-lanka-kills-290-people]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-21T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update (22nd April 2019):&lt;/strong&gt; This is a moving news story. The death toll will be updated as it rises. &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT HAS BEEN nearly ten years since the guns fell silent in Sri Lanka’s civil war. But bloodshed returned with a vengeance on Easter Sunday when a succession of explosions ripped through three churches packed with worshippers, and three five-star hotels. At least 290 people were killed and hundreds more were injured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The coincidence of the attacks with the upcoming anniversary of the Sri Lankan army’s defeat of the Tamil Tiger rebels on May 19th—ending a war that pitted the ethnic Tamil and a largely Hindu minority, against the Sinhalese Buddhist majority—may be just that. The authorities are being cautious about apportioning blame, particularly because of the recent history of communal violence on the island, both during and after the war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A senior police official said there were signs the six blasts were all suicide bombings. This was a favourite tactic of the Liberation Tigers of Tamil Eelam, but no fingers are being pointed at any Tamil groups. And suicide tactics, especially aimed at religious targets and foreign tourists, are also a hallmark of international jihadist groups. Yet the country has little history of jihadist activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The explosions were the deadliest attacks in the country since the end of the war. They took place in close succession beginning at around 8.30am. The first was at the St Sebastian Church in Negombo, a Catholic-majority area. Photographs showed tiles blown off a blackened roof and bloodied bodies on the ground. Two other explosions occurred at St Anthony’s Church in Colombo (another Catholic church), and at the Zion Church (Evangelical) in Batticaloa, around 220km east of the capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 30 minutes later, there were explosions at the Shangri-La, the Kingsbury and the Cinnamon Grand hotels in Colombo. All are five-star venues and many of the victims were enjoying Easter breakfast special offers. At least 11 foreigners were confirmed killed. Among the nationalities were Indian, Turkish, Portuguese, British and joint US-UK nationals. The authorities counted the bodies of 25 more people presumed to be foreign. The US State Department said “several” Americans had been killed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two more explosions took place later in the day, in which eight people were killed, but they appear to be related to security forces’ raids on terrorists’ suspected hideouts. Seven people were arrested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main hospital in Colombo was a scene of chaos, with hysterical relatives swarming the narrow road leading to the emergency unit amid a steady flow of ambulances. As news of the attacks spread via social media, police rushed to churches around the country and sent worshippers home. Cardinal Malcolm Ranjith, the head of the Catholic church, cancelled all other services. Security forces were later deployed to guard churches, hotels and the international airport. The government cancelled school for children whose new terms were starting Monday. Universities were declared indefinitely closed. A countrywide police curfew came into effect in the afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whoever the perpetrators may be, there are worries that the blasts will stir renewed inter-communal strife. Of Sri Lanka’s population of more than 20m people, about 75% are Sinhalese (who are mostly Buddhists). Tamils, living mostly in the north and east, make up about 11% and are predominantly Hindu. The rebellion by the Tamil Tigers lasted for 27 years. Muslims make up about 9% of the population and speak Tamil. Although they did not join the Tamil Tigers’s rebellion—and indeed some were evicted from the north by them—after the war Muslims have become the target of Budhist-nationalist attacks. Christians, mostly Roman Catholics, make up about 7% of the population and straddle the Sinhalese-Tamil divide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The puzzle was why the Catholic church was targeted,” said Jayadeva Uyangoda, a political scientist. The spread of Catholicism dates to 1505 with Portuguese colonisation and subsequent proselytisation. Catholics permeate all levels of governance, the private sector and even the army, but they were not a particular focus of Tamil Tiger attacks during the civil war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;St Anthony’s church is patronised by both Tamils and Sinhalese, including non-Christians. Any assaults in recent times against Christians—also by Buddhist extremist groups—have been aimed against new Evangelical churches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hence the speculation about “foreign actors”, as Cardinal Ranjith put it—in particular Muslim extremists. Only a few dozen Sri Lankan Muslims are thought to have joined the tens of thousands of foreigners who volunteered to fight with the Islamic State group in Iraq and Syria. Some have worried about more radical forms of Islam being introduced to the island by contact with foreign preachers. Most alarming, in January Sri Lankan police said they uncovered a large cache of explosives at an IS training camp in the north of the country; it was apparently intended for use against several Buddhist monuments in the ancient city of Anuradhapura.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One reason to worry about the possible radicalisation of Muslims is that Sinhalese Buddhist extremists have sought to instigate and co-ordinate mob violence against them. A traffic incident in 2018 in which a Sinhalese truck driver was assaulted by four Muslim men (and subsequently died) resulted in days of attacks on Muslim homes and businesses and a large number of injuries. In 2014, there was Buddhist-Muslim sectarian violence in several towns in the south fired by the racist speech by a Buddhist monk, Galagodatte Gnarasara, who is now in prison for contempt of court (on a separate matter).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the Easter bombings, as rumours and incendiary anti-Muslim comments spread like wildfire, the government swiftly shut down all social-media platforms, including WhatsApp, Viber, Facebook and YouTube.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the hunt for the perpetrators begins, Sri Lanka will be counting the cost of a day of carnage it had not expected. The Catholic church is preparing for mass funerals, which the government has said it will pay for. The country as a whole has suffered a blow to its lucrative tourism sector. Until Easter day it had enjoyed a reputation as one of the safest countries for holidaymakers. That has changed utterly, along with much else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 16:54:24 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Easter massacre in Sri Lanka kills more than 200 people]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/21/easter-massacre-in-sri-lanka-kills-more-than-200-people]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-21T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IT HAS BEEN nearly ten years since the guns fell silent in Sri Lanka’s civil war. But bloodshed returned with a vengeance on Easter Sunday when a succession of explosions ripped through three churches packed with worshippers, and three five-star hotels. At least 207 people were killed and hundreds more were injured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The coincidence of the attacks with the upcoming anniversary of the Sri Lankan army’s defeat of the Tamil Tiger rebels on May 19th—ending a war that pitted the ethnic Tamil and a largely Hindu minority, against the Sinhalese Buddhist majority—may be just that. The authorities are being cautious about apportioning blame, particularly because of the recent history of communal violence on the island, both during and after the war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A senior police official said there were signs the six blasts were all suicide bombings. This was a favourite tactic of the Liberation Tigers of Tamil Eelam, but no fingers are being pointed at any Tamil groups. And suicide tactics, especially aimed at religious targets and foreign tourists, are also a hallmark of international jihadist groups. Yet the country has little history of jihadist activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The explosions were the deadliest attacks in the country since the end of the war. They took place in close succession beginning around 8.30 am. The first was at the St Sebastian Church in Negombo, a Catholic-majority area. Photographs showed tiles blown off a blackened roof and bloodied bodies on the ground. Two other explosions occurred at St Anthony’s Church in Colombo (another Catholic church), and at the Zion Church (Evangelical) in Batticaloa, around 220km east of the capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 30 minutes later, there were explosions at the Shangri-La, the Kingsbury and the Cinnamon Grand hotels in Colombo. All are five-star venues and many of the victims were enjoying Easter breakfast special offers. At least 11 foreigners were confirmed killed. Among the nationalities were Indian, Turkish, Portuguese, British and joint US-UK nationals. The authorities counted the bodies of 25 more people presumed to be foreign. The US State Department said “several” Americans had been killed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two more explosions took place later in the day, in which eight people were killed, but they appear to be related to security forces’ raids on terrorists’ suspected hideouts. Seven people were arrested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main hospital in Colombo was a scene of chaos, with hysterical relatives swarming the narrow road leading to the emergency unit amid a steady flow of ambulances. As news of the attacks spread via social media, police rushed to churches around the country and sent worshippers home. Cardinal Malcolm Ranjith, the head of the Catholic church, cancelled all other services. Security forces were later deployed to guard churches, hotels and the international airport. The government cancelled school for children whose new terms were starting Monday. Universities were declared indefinitely closed. A countrywide police curfew came into effect in the afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whoever the perpetrators may be, there are worries that the blasts will stir renewed inter-communal strife. Of Sri Lanka’s population of more than 20m people, about 75% are Sinhalese (who are mostly Buddhists). Tamils, living mostly in the north and east, make up about 11% and are predominantly Hindu. The rebellion by the Tamil Tigers lasted for 27 years. Muslims make up about 9% and speak Tamil. Although they did not join the Tamil Tigers’s rebellion—and indeed some were evicted from the north by them—after the war Muslims have become the target of Budhist nationalist attacks. Christians, mostly Roman Catholics, make up about 7% of the population and straddle the Sinhalese-Tamil divide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The puzzle was why the Catholic church was targeted,” said Jayadeva Uyangoda, a political scientist. The spread of Catholicism dates to 1505 with Portuguese colonisation and subsequent proselytization. Catholics permeate all levels of governance, the private sector and even the army, but they were not a particular focus of Tamil Tiger attacks during the civil war.&lt;br/&gt;St Anthony’s church is patronised by both Tamils and Sinhalese, including non-Christians. Any assaults in recent times against Christians—also by Buddhist extremist groups—have been aimed against new Evangelical churches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hence the speculation about “foreign actors”, as Cardinal Ranjith put it—in particular Muslim extremists. Only a few dozen Sri Lankan Muslims are thought to have joined the tens of thousands of foreigners who volunteered to fight with the Islamic State group in Iraq and Syria. Some have worried about more radical forms of Islam being introduced to the island by contact with foreign preachers. Most alarming, in January Sri Lankan police said they uncovered a large cache of explosives at an IS training camp in the north of the country; it was apparently intended for use against several Buddhist monuments in the ancient city of Anuradhapura.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One reason to worry about the possible radicalisation of Muslims is that Sinhalese Buddhist extremists have sought to instigate and coordinate mob violence against them. A traffic incident in 2018 in which a Sinhalese truck driver was assaulted by four Muslim men (and subsequently died) resulted in days of attacks on Muslim homes and businesses and a large number of injuries. Earlier, in 2014, there was Buddhist-Muslim sectarian violence in several towns in the south fired by the racist speech by a Buddhist monk, Galagodatte Gnarasara, who is now in prison for contempt of court (on a separate matter).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the Easter bombings, as rumours and incendiary anti-Muslim comments spread like wildfire, the government swiftly shut down all social-media platforms, including WhatsApp, Viber, Facebook and YouTube.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the hunt for the perpetrators begins, Sri Lanka will be counting the cost of a day of carnage it had not expected. The Catholic church is preparing for mass funerals, which the government has said it will pay for. The country as a whole has suffered a blow to its lucrative tourism sector. Until Easter day it had enjoyed a reputation as one of the safest countries for holidaymakers. That has changed utterly, along with much else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 03:14:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Easter day massacre in Sri Lanka kills more than 200 people]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/21/easter-day-massacre-in-sri-lanka-kills-more-than-200-people]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-21T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;IT HAS BEEN nearly ten years since the guns fell silent in Sri Lanka’s civil war. But bloodshed returned with a vengeance on Easter day when a succession of explosions ripped through three churches packed with worshippers, and three five-star hotels. At least 207 people were killed and hundreds more were injured.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The coincidence of the attacks with the upcoming anniversary of the Sri Lankan army’s defeat of the Tamil Tiger rebels on May 19th—ending a war that pitted the ethnic Tamil and a largely Hindu minority, against the Sinhalese Buddhist majority—may be just that. The authorities are being cautious about apportioning blame, particularly because of the recent history of communal violence on the island, both during and after the war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A senior police official said there were signs the six blasts were all suicide bombings. This was a favourite tactic of the Liberation Tigers of Tamil Eelam, but no fingers are being pointed at any Tamil groups. And suicide tactics, especially aimed at religious targets and foreign tourists, are also a hallmark of international jihadist groups. Yet the country has little history of jihadist activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The explosions were the deadliest attacks in the country since the end of the war. They took place in close succession beginning around 8.30 am. The first was at the St Sebastian Church in Negombo, a Catholic-majority area. Photographs showed tiles blown off a blackened roof and bloodied bodies on the ground. Two other explosions occurred at St Anthony’s Church in Colombo (another Catholic church), and at the Zion Church (Evangelical) in Batticaloa, around 220km east of the capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 30 minutes later, there were explosions at the Shangri-La, the Kingsbury and the Cinnamon Grand hotels in Colombo. All are five-star venues and many of the victims were enjoying Easter breakfast special offers. At least 11 foreigners were confirmed killed. Among the nationalities were Indian, Turkish, Portuguese, British and joint US-UK nationals. The authorities counted the bodies of 25 more people presumed to be foreign. The US State Department said “several” Americans had been killed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two more explosions took place later in the day, in which eight people were killed, but they appear to be related to security forces’ raids on terrorists’ suspected hideouts. Seven people were arrested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main hospital in Colombo was a scene of chaos, with hysterical relatives swarming the narrow road leading to the emergency unit amid a steady flow of ambulances. As news of the attacks spread via social media, police rushed to churches around the country and sent worshippers home. Cardinal Malcolm Ranjith, the head of the Catholic church, cancelled all other services. Security forces were later deployed to guard churches, hotels and the international airport. The government cancelled school for children whose new terms were starting Monday. Universities were declared indefinitely closed. A countrywide police curfew came into effect in the afternoon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whoever the perpetrators may be, there are worries that the blasts will stir renewed inter-communal strife. Of Sri Lanka’s population of more than 20m people, about 75% are Sinhalese (who are mostly Buddhists). Tamils, living mostly in the north and east, make up about 11% and are predominantly Hindu. The rebellion by the Tamil Tigers lasted for 27 years. Muslims make up about 9% and speak Tamil. Although they did not join the Tamil Tigers’s rebellion—and indeed some were evicted from the north by them—after the war Muslims have become the target of Budhist nationalist attacks. Christians, mostly Roman Catholics, make up about 7% of the population and straddle the Sinhalese-Tamil divide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The puzzle was why the Catholic church was targeted,” said Jayadeva Uyangoda, a political scientist. The spread of Catholicism dates to 1505 with Portuguese colonisation and subsequent proselytization. Catholics permeate all levels of governance, the private sector and even the army, but they were not a particular focus of Tamil Tiger attacks during the civil war.&lt;br/&gt;St Anthony’s church is patronised by both Tamils and Sinhalese, including non-Christians. Any assaults in recent times against Christians—also by Buddhist extremist groups—have been aimed against new Evangelical churches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hence the speculation about “foreign actors”, as Cardinal Ranjith put it—in particular Muslim extremists. Only a few dozen Sri Lankan Muslims are thought to have joined the tens of thousands of foreigners who volunteered to fight with the Islamic State group in Iraq and Syria. Some have worried about more radical forms of Islam being introduced to the island by contact with foreign preachers. Most alarming, in January Sri Lankan police said they uncovered a large cache of explosives at an IS training camp in the north of the country; it was apparently intended for use against several Buddhist monuments in the ancient city of Anuradhapura.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One reason to worry about the possible radicalisation of Muslims is that Sinhalese Buddhist extremists have sought to instigate and coordinate mob violence against them. A traffic incident in 2018 in which a Sinhalese truck driver was assaulted by four Muslim men (and subsequently died) resulted in days of attacks on Muslim homes and businesses and a large number of injuries. Earlier, in 2014, there was Buddhist-Muslim sectarian violence in several towns in the south fired by the racist speech by a Buddhist monk, Galagodatte Gnarasara, who is now in prison for contempt of court (on a separate matter).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the Easter bombings, as rumours and incendiary anti-Muslim comments spread like wildfire, the government swiftly shut down all social-media platforms, including WhatsApp, Viber, Facebook and YouTube.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the hunt for the perpetrators begins, Sri Lanka will be counting the cost of a day of carnage it had not expected. The Catholic church is preparing for mass funerals, which the government has said it will pay for. The country as a whole has suffered a blow to its lucrative tourism sector. Until Easter day it had enjoyed a reputation as one of the safest countries for holidaymakers. That has changed utterly, along with much else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2019 02:06:34 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can opera seduce a new generation?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/19/can-opera-seduce-a-new-generation]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_blp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-19T16:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ANNE MCELVOY goes backstage at New York’s newest arts centre, the Shed, to talk to Renée Fleming, a Grammy-winning soprano. They discuss bending the rules of genre and gender opposite Ben Whishaw in “Norma Jeane Baker of Troy”, why opera isn’t in trouble, and how to reclaim the title of “diva” for the 21st century. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-reneefleming&quot; width=&quot;500&amp;amp;quot;&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com&amp;amp;gt;Apple Podcasts | &amp;amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com https:=&quot;&quot; spotify=&quot;&quot; com=&quot;&quot; show=&quot;&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWVjb25vbWlzdGFza3M&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=142125&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/Business--Economics-Podcasts/The-Economist-Asks-p999213/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 00:06:40 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[On “Game of Thrones”, Conservatism, Israel and Lidl]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/bagehots-notebook/2019/04/19/on-game-of-thrones-conservatism-israel-and-lidl]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_blp909.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-19T10:08:16Z&quot;&gt;Apr 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“GAME of Thrones”, which, in case you hadn’t noticed, returned for its eighth and final season this week, has already had a profound impact on the television industry (if you’re a TV producer with an idea for a multi-series drama your chances of getting a green light have skyrocketed). Let’s hope it has an equally profound impact on the history industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past few decades academics have focused on history from below—hence all those university seminars on bastardy in 15th-century Nottingham and hand-loom weavers in 18th-century Lincoln. They have done this for obvious intellectual reasons: Karl Marx’s contention that “the history of all hitherto existing societies is the history of class struggle” is undoubtedly a powerful insight. Added to this is a sociological reason: the vast expansion of the universities (and the arrival of a more socially and ethnically diverse student population) means that historians are reluctant to teach the same thing as they did when they were training a future ruling class. A changing student body requires a changing curriculum. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Game of Thrones” suggests they were doubly wrong. They are wrong about demand: even in a democratic age people are fixated on the old-fashioned history of kings and queens: that is the history of people who combine something that is quite unusual (lots of power) with other things that are quite usual (personal quirks and family quarrels). History may be in decline as an option in universities precisely because it focuses so much on history from below rather than on history from above. In some ways “Game of Thrones” is a dramatic presentation of Walter Bagehot’s great insight about the British monarchy, that it thrived in a democratic age precisely because it humanised power by putting a family and its foibles on the throne.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They are also wrong about something more fundamental. “Game of Thrones” is compelling precisely because it recognises that dynastic struggles have often taken precedence over class struggles. Up until the first world war, the world was run by a collection of dynasties that possessed every human foible imaginable (from insanity to dwarfism to incestuous longings) and who spent their lives playing the game of thrones: forming dynastic alliances, sometimes even marrying their relatives, going to war over rival family claims to the throne and, above all, scheming to maximise their power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Game of Thrones” gets a remarkable number of big things right about the nature of dynastic societies. One is that the dynastic principle eliminates the difference between the public and private realms, a difference that is fundamental to democratic and meritocratic societies. Public life in a dynasty is shaped by the personal foibles of the monarch. Power is wielded by people who can get physically close to the king. The world’s oldest political offices are all related to the monarch’s physical needs—looking after his horse or falcons, or guarding his bedchamber—and were usually reserved for members of his own family or the most blue-blooded aristocrats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A second is that dynasties put biology at the heart of society. The fate of kingdoms depends on the physical fitness of kings and their ability to produce male heirs (Britain arguably had its first Brexit, the Reformation, because of Henry VIII’s difficulties in producing a male heir). Political dynasties can become global powers if they can marry the right people and produce enough children (the Saxe-Coburgs were the greatest dynasty builders of the 18th and 19th centuries, succeeding first in capturing the British throne and then, because of Queen Victoria’s clever marriage scheming, putting their progeny on the thrones of most of Europe). Royal daughters had to expect to be pawns in the game of alliance building.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of which leads me to unveil my idea for an HBO production of my own: a history of the Habsburg dynasty. This would be relatively cheap by the standards of recent productions: most of the great Habsburg palaces are still intact and Vienna’s museums are stuffed full of suits of armour, portraits, furniture, table settings etc. And the story is every bit as weird as the story of the “Game of Thrones”. The Habsburgs were so prone to in-breeding that people joked that they married their cousins and slept with their siblings. Charles II of Spain was a mass of genetic problems: his head was too big for his body and his tongue was too big for his mouth, so that he had difficulty speaking, and constantly drooled; his first wife complained that he suffered from premature ejaculation and his second wife that he was impotent; as if that wasn’t enough, he also suffered from convulsions. He died at 39, mercifully without an heir. These personal peccadilloes didn’t prevent the Hapsburgs from becoming champion players of the game of thrones, producing one of the most far-flung and enduring empires the world has seen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;**** &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“CONSERVATIVE” is one of those words that comes with an implied question: what is it that you want to conserve? Britain’s Conservative Party is in such turmoil at the moment because it is at sixes and sevens over its answer to this question. In the Cameron-Osborne years it wanted to conserve the Clinton-Blair consensus: that is a combination of free-market economics (symbolised by support for globalisation), social liberalism (symbolised by support for gay marriage) and government activism, particularly in the creation of human capital. That was always an elite project that failed to stir the emotions of most conservative voters and, when it came to gay marriage and hyper-globalisation, may well have repelled them. But it was an elite project that was destroyed in the flames of the Iraq war, arguably the first and last war of neo-conservative globalisation, and the 2008 financial crisis. Now the battle is on between three different answers to the question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most powerful is the nation-state. The heart of Brexit is not racism (as some Remainers annoyingly claim) or a desire to be truly global as opposed to narrowly European-focused (as Boris Johnson pretends). It is the desire to restore the sovereignty of the nation-state. Brexiteers don’t just dislike the demands that the European Union poses in terms of agreeing to its rules and regulations. They dislike the idea, beloved of some if not all in Brussels, that the nation-state is an anachronism that we need to get beyond. The fury of the Brexiteers’ resistance to Theresa May’s half-way house approach to Brexit, combined with the flight of many Conservative voters to the Brexit Party, suggests that, to survive, the Conservative Party may have no choice but to become the party of the nation-state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This defence of the nation-state is linked to a broader defence of the traditional British way of life: that is, Britain’s green and pleasant land (Michael Gove’s agenda at the department of the environment); its provincial cities (the devolution initiative and the creation of new mayors); its built environment (the department of housing’s “building beautiful” initiative which has been sadly overshadowed by the row about Sir Roger Scruton).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A second answer is the traditional values of family and faith. This is the answer that the Cameroons most disliked. Proclaiming a faith in God or a belief in the traditional family was a sure way of getting yourself kicked off the Notting Hill dinner-party invitation list. But they were not alone: Theresa May, the daughter of a vicar and a regular churchgoer, initially embraced transgender rights on the grounds that it was the new gay marriage. The Conservative grassroots are rather more tradition-minded than this, particularly when it comes to transgender activists. Jacob Rees-Mogg has demonstrated that you can win a large grassroots following by speaking out unashamedly for “faith and family”, particularly if you link defence of faith and family to defence of the nation-state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A third answer is the capitalist system. The Conservative Party has traditionally been the party of business and the City—indeed there was a time, between the wars, when the party was actually dominated by businessmen such as Stanley Baldwin, whose family owned an ironworks, and Neville Chamberlain, whose family once produced a third of the world’s nails. I suspect that Hammond, the chancellor of the exchequer, believes that his party’s main job is to create a favourable environment for business, though he doesn’t exactly wear his political philosophy on his sleeve. The same may be true of Jeremy Hunt, the foreign secretary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A closely connected answer is “freedom”. Many Tories regard the defence of capitalism as part of a broader defence of freedom. (They also argue, from a public-relations point of view, that “freedom” is a much easier sell than “capitalism”.) Liz Truss, Mr Hammond’s underling as chief secretary of the Treasury and a woman who exudes leadership ambition from every paw, is a leading proponent of this school. Her shtick is to update Mrs Thatcher’s freedom agenda for a populist age: continue with the Thatcherite policies of deregulating markets and encouraging competition but also put a heavy emphasis on the gig economy and social liberalism. Her aim is to reinforce the Thatcherite revolution by showing young people that their personal interests, both as consumers and as young professionals, lies in embracing the start-up economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some Conservatives would no doubt argue that the proper answer to the question is “all of the above”: you need a fusion of all these things for each one of them to make sense—for example, you can’t defend Britain’s built environment without having the wherewithal provided by a successful economy. They would also argue that defending Britain’s nation-state—particularly the nation-state’s ability to generate wealth—sometimes entails sacrificing sovereignty to the European Union.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This “fusionist” position is the default position of the party’s pragmatic establishment. But the logic of current politics—not just because of the Brexit debate but also because of the surge of populism—is to force people to make choices that they’ve previously been able to avoid. Conservatives increasingly feel that they have to make a choice between the nation-state and business—and indeed between traditional values and business. Businesses have made it abundantly clear that they have little time for small-minded nationalism. The global market is their God. They have also made it pretty clear that they don’t have that much time for other important conservative virtues such as defending the family or community: Hollywood pumps out material that undermines the traditional families. Big companies such as HSBC (which has plastered London with annoying ads) is determined to prove how woke it is. Big data companies yoke the values of the millennium left with the business practices of the robber barons. I’m sure that Boris Johnson expressed the views of a growing number of Conservatives when he splutterd “fuck business”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;**** &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;PROGNOSTICATORS are always thinking that they have discovered “the future” in some bit of the world or other. Hegel thought that he had discovered it in Prussia and John Reed in Soviet Russia (“I have seen the future and it works”). In the 1960s there was almost a consensus that the future lay in California. At the risk of sounding as idiotic as John Reed I would like to nominate Israel. I recently spent a week in that extraordinary country in order to get a break from writing about Brexit. I was repeatedly struck by the extent to which Israel prefigures trends that are spreading around much of the world: the rise of religion and nationalism; the coexistence of a high-tech sector with orthodox communities; the division of society into rival communities that are so hostile to each other that they need to be kept apart by a wall; and the rise of strongmen leaders who argue, in effect, that the imperatives of national security override namby-pamby worries about civil rights.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the wake of the second world war the survivors of the Holocaust drew a sharply different conclusion from Nazism than the victorious Allies. The Allies concluded that nationalism needed to be constrained or even, in the case of the architects of the European Union, transcended. By contrast Zionists concluded that the Jewish people needed a nation-state of their own where they could be made safe from any potential enemies—and where they could allow their culture to flourish as never before. Today dreams of a post-nationalist future are dying and the idea that peoples need a place that they can call home for reasons of both self-fulfilment and self-protection is once more on the rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;****&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;DURING my Israel adventure I stopped off at a motor stop between Jerusalem and Nazareth. I was struck by the way that Arabs in traditional dress mixed easily with Israeli soldiers (though who knows what was going on in their heads). I was also impressed by the way that a familiar modern economy and a traditional barter economy seemed to co-exist—having handed over my money for a cappuccino in exactly the same way as I would in London, I was approached by Bedouin hawkers trying to sell cordless drills and rides on a camel. How exotic! I thought until I recalled my own experiences back in England. I frequently visit Liddle to buy necessities (bread, grapes, chocolate) only to emerge with a cordless drill or a “smart bicycle helmet” that signals which way you’re turning. The prices are so low that it seems foolish to pass by the jumble of weird goods placed in the centre of the store. All Liddle needs now is a camel or two&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;****&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;BACK from the Holy Land I went to the dentist with a toothache. The dentist poked around for a bit, ummed and erred, and referred me to a root-canal specialist. I showed up to the specialist full of dread about the pain, not to mention the cost, of another root canal. A bit more poking and prodding and the specialist pronounced that she couldn’t find anything wrong with my root canals. So why the persistent toothache? She asked me if I had been under any unusual pressure that might have resulted in me clenching my teeth together more than usual. When I replied that I was a political journalist writing about Brexit she immediately pronounced that “that would explain it…it’s bad enough for the rest of us without having to write about it”. Brexit is a toothache as well as a headache. I’m sending my dental bill to Boris Johnson. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2019 00:06:39 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to hack the freeconomy]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/news/2019/04/19/how-to-hack-the-freeconomy]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_EFD003.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-19T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This piece is from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.1843magazine.com/&quot;&gt;1843&lt;/a&gt;, our sister magazine of ideas, lifestyle and culture. It was published in the April/May 2019 issue.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190406_OPP601_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190406_OPP601_0.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190406_OPP601_0.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190406_OPP601_0.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190406_OPP601_0.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190406_OPP601_0.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190406_OPP601_0.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190406_OPP601_0.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190406_OPP601_0.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190406_OPP601_0.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;ONE EVENING a few months ago, I had dinner at a restaurant in San Francisco called Dirty Habit. It was aptly named. One of my companions that night was a friend from the tech industry – he had studied at Stanford Graduate School of Business and been an executive at a self-driving-car firm before founding his own startup. But as we ate, he flaunted a different sort of achievement: he had lived in the Bay Area for years and never paid for a mattress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My friend, who asked not to be named, approached this challenge methodically. First he compiled a spreadsheet of all the mattress firms’ free trials and return policies. Then he proceeded to take advantage of them one by one, “buying” six mattresses in turn and returning them just before the deadline, at no extra cost – and getting all his money back. He usually made the switch just before he moved apartments, so he didn’t have to lug a heavy mattress across town. As he described his strategy, I found myself torn between admiration and disgust. His ruse was ingenious, but was creating an Excel file about bedding really the best use of his time?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking advantage of promotions is a worldwide phenomenon, but techies stalk deals with extraordinary ingenuity. The perks of the “freeconomy” range from the quotidian to the luxurious. Startups, flush with funding from venture capitalists and eager to grab the attention of new customers, offer free food delivery, prepared meal kits, grocery-shopping, dog-walking, errand-running, moving, laundry and ride-hailing. Some techies boast that they have even figured out how to get free nights on Airbnb and nearly free flights from JetSmarter, which offers on-demand private jets. San Francisco is now more expensive to live in than any other city in America, but the biggest irony of its freeconomy is that the people who are the most adept at exploiting it are the people who need its benefits least: well-to-do nerds with high-paying jobs that come with plenty of benefits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I used to think I was, if not a freeconomy professional, at least a high-level amateur. Since I moved back to San Francisco, my home town, four years ago, I have learnt the local tradecraft. Locals often use multiple email accounts and different credit cards when signing up for apps so that they appear to be a first-time customer. I play hard to get, wandering away from a service for months only to sprint back as soon as they offer me a coupon. When I need a ride, I play Uber against Lyft to see which ride-hailing service offers the better deal. I’m currently using Lyft: they offered me 25% off ten rides.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have come to realise, however, that I am nothing but a novice. One popular route to free riches involves a “referral code”, which gives each person who uses it a credit for helping secure new customers. Felix, who runs a startup in San Francisco, has taken this to extremes. He accomplished what he calls his “Bay Area hack” by buying around $600 in advertisements on Google and placing his referral code from Uber in each ad. He spent hours fine-tuning his approach until his ads often had a higher click-through rate than Uber’s own. For each person who signed up to Uber’s service through his ad, he received a credit. He eventually amassed $30,000 in credits, which allowed him to ride around the city in Uber’s cars and eat three meals a day from UberEats, the company’s food-delivery service, for a whole year without paying a cent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Companies know consumers try to take advantage of them, but some entrepreneurs choose to be wilfully blind to it. “A little bit of you doesn’t want to find out,” says Sean Behr, the boss of Stratim. “You want to believe your product has traction.” His startup, which offers parking services to companies, had to pivot its business away from cheap on-demand valet parking when consumers like me exploited it feverishly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The freeconomy may ultimately fizzle out when the tech boom sputters and venture capitalists grow less comfortable with their cash being used to win new customers at any cost. In the meantime, this bargain-hunting tells us three things about the mindsets of techies in Silicon Valley. First, to compete with giants like Google in a cut-throat talent market, companies are offering their employees a huge variety of perks, from meditation rooms to concierge services to egg-freezing for women. This corporate munificence has led to entitlement. Techies expect all companies, not just their employers, to take care of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second, techies are more concerned about getting a good deal than they are about ownership – which explains why people are willing to return mattresses and why many techies get their sheets from a company that offers free samples. For them, living in the Bay Area feels like being at the centre of a well-funded research lab where local startups test new ideas and services to see how well they fare. “I love San Francisco. You see the future that will never work,” one high-profile entrepreneur mused at a dinner party, as a delivery person cycled up a steep hill in a far-flung part of the city to deliver food from miles away at almost no cost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Third, and most importantly, exploiting the freeconomy is a way to take back control. Tech companies have amassed fortunes by tracking consumers, gathering as much data as they can about them, predicting what they are looking for and manipulating them to spend as much time with their products as possible. This is especially true for firms like Facebook that are now under fire for making money out of surveilling consumers across the internet. But plenty of other companies make it their business to know consumers: they employ people to study users’ locations and behaviour in order to lure them in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For my mattress-scheming friend, getting free things from companies “in some small way allows you to reclaim sovereignty on your own internal state. It’s David versus Goliath. It’s sticking up for the individual over the company.” And who doesn’t like rooting for the little guy, even if his slingshot was heavily discounted?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The author, Alexandra Suich Bass, is West Coast correspondent for &lt;/em&gt;The Economist&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 20:06:32 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[At Easter, beware chocolate-scoffing dogs]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/19/at-easter-beware-chocolate-scoffing-dogs]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_WOC760.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-19T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EASTER-EGG hunts are a delight for children, a pain for parents to organise—and potentially lethal for the family pooch. The worst a chocolate binge can do for a mischievous four-year-old is a dizzying sugar high. For dogs, however, the theobromine found in cocoa beans can cause vomiting, diarrhoea and seizures. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://veterinaryrecord.bmj.com/content/vetrec/181/25/684.full.pdf&quot;&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; of British vet clinics between 2012 and 2017 found a large spike in canine chocolate intoxication in the weeks around Easter. Some 60% of vets reported such a case in 2018. (A similar problem occurs at Christmas.)&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Fortunately, all of the poorly pets in the sample recovered from their snack-induced ailments. But owners should beware: a pup with a sweet tooth will stop at nothing to get its fill. The study’s authors report examples of dogs slurping chocolate liqueurs and cups of cocoa. Chocolate oranges and Toblerones are especially popular, with one naughty boy guzzling six of both. The worst offender managed to consume an entire “garden of Easter eggs hidden for a large party of small children”. Pity the parents who had to clear up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 20:06:31 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What to make of the Mueller report]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/04/19/what-to-make-of-the-mueller-report]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_blp908.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-19T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE MOST eagerly anticipated work of American literature has finally been published, albeit with a few parts missing, which only make it seem more tantalising. Robert Mueller’s report has been downloaded almost 100,000 times from government websites. Many more people will have looked at copies emailed by friends or hosted on media websites. The interest in a government report more than 400 pages long is understandable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Mueller spent nearly two years investigating links between the Russian government and President Donald Trump’s campaign. Last month the attorney-general, William Barr, released a four-page summary, stating that the report did not establish that anyone involved with Mr Trump’s campaign “conspired or co-ordinated with Russia” in its election-interference efforts, nor did it establish that Mr Trump committed obstruction of justice. Mr Trump treated that summary as dispositive. No collusion, no obstruction, “Complete and Total EXONERATION,” as he tweeted. The full report paints a different picture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first 170 pages concern Russia. They begin by laying out the scope of Russia’s influence operation. Some of this may be familiar to those who perused two previous indictments issued by Mr Mueller’s team. One was against members of the GRU, Russia’s military-intelligence agency, who hacked into and stole emails from servers belonging to the Democratic Party and to people working for Hillary Clinton’s campaign. The other was against the Internet Research Agency (IRA), a Russian troll farm run by a Russian businessman closely linked to Vladimir Putin, which engaged in a social-media campaign to sow discord and damage Mrs Clinton’s campaign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though Americans have understandably been focused on the evidence about whether the president was complicit in a foreign power’s attempt to sway the election, this part of the report is arguably the most important part from the point of view of protecting future elections. Unfortunately, America’s deep political divisions are all too easy to exploit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;IRA staff sitting in St Petersburg (the one on the Neva rather than on Tampa Bay) pretended to be Americans on social media and staked out divisive positions on either end of the political spectrum, passing themselves off as supporters of Mr Trump, or of Black Lives Matter. The outfit also organised multiple real-world events, starting with a “confederate rally” in Houston in late 2015, as well as several pro-Trump rallies in Florida, New York and Pennsylvania (a state that Mr Trump won narrowly and unexpectedly). Some rallies, the report explains, drew few attendees; others drew hundreds. Candidate Trump pointed to one event organised by the IRA in Florida as evidence of his popularity there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Russian government and the Trump campaign were working to the same purpose, and each hoped the other would help it out. But as Mr Barr noted in both his written summary and his press conference, Mr Mueller’s team did not establish that anyone from Mr Trump’s campaign conspired or coordinated with Russia in those efforts. Here is the how Mr Mueller’s team put it:&lt;br/&gt;“Although the investigation established that the Russian government perceived it would benefit from a Trump presidency and worked to secure that outcome, and that the Campaign expected it would benefit electorally from information stolen through Russian efforts, the investigation did not establish that members of the Trump Campaign conspired or coordinated with the Russian government in its election interference activities.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This judgment turns on the absence of any agreement, explicit or implicit, between the parties to conspire, which seems fair. Nevertheless, the enthusiasm of Trump campaign members for working with people with ties to a government that kills journalists, imprisons political rivals and had recently pulled off the first land grab in Europe since the second world war, is quite something to see when it is all put in the same place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paul Manafort, Mr Trump’s campaign chair, who was deep in debt to a Russian oligarch, shared internal polling data with Konstantin Kilimnik, one of his Kiev-based employees with apparent links to both that oligarch and Russian intelligence. Even Rick Gates, Mr Manafort’s right-hand man, believed Mr Kilimnik was a “spy”. That did not stop Mr Manafort from meeting Mr Kilimnik. George Papadopoulos, a junior foreign-policy advisor who pleaded guilty to lying to federal investigators, tried to let the campaign know early on that the Russians had compromising material on Mrs Clinton (nobody thought to tell the FBI). Donald Trump junior arranged a meeting with a Russian lawyer who promised “dirt” on Mrs Clinton. And of course Mr Trump himself was pursuing a Trump Tower Moscow project until just five months before the election, while simultaneously pushing for better relations with Moscow. None of this may have been illegal, but had voters known about it they may have made a different choice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The report’s second part deals with obstruction of justice. Both in his summary and again in his press conference, Mr Barr noted that Mr Mueller declined to make a “traditional prosecutorial judgment” regarding whether to bring charges. Guiding that reluctance was long-standing policy against indicting a sitting president, which, wrote Mr Mueller, led him “not to apply an approach that could potentially result in a judgment that the president committed crimes.” Because no charges could be brought, Mr Trump would have no chance to clear his name at trial. But, Mr Mueller continues, “if we had confidence after a thorough investigation of the facts that the President clearly did not commit obstruction of justice, we would so state…Accordingly, while this report does not conclude that the President committed a crime, neither does it exonerate him.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sustaining an obstruction charge requires three things: an obstructive act, a connection between that act and an actual or contemplated criminal proceeding, and corrupt intent. Mr Mueller comes closest to accusing Mr Trump of meeting those three conditions in the firing of James Comey, a former FBI director, six days after Mr Comey declined to publicly state that Mr Trump was not personally under investigation. Afterwards he told the Russian foreign minister, “I faced great pressure because of Russia. That’s taken off.” That could be an obstructive act because, although it did not stop the investigation into his campaign’s links with Russia, it could affect how Mr Comey’s successor conducted that investigation. But Mr Mueller leaves open whether Mr Trump’s motive was a desire to impede the investigation, or simple anger that a subordinate failed to do as told.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nor is that the only occasion on which the president tried to influence the investigation. He tried to get the White House Counsel to remove Mr Mueller, and then to deny that he had made that request. He tried to get Jeff Sessions, the former attorney-general, to curtail the terms of Mr Mueller’s investigation, and to rescind his recusal from overseeing it. He tried to prevent the disclosure of embarrassing emails. He seemed to dangle a pardon before Mr Manafort. After Michael Cohen, his former lawyer, began cooperating with Mr Mueller, Mr Trump called him a “rat”, and publicly insulted his family. As Mr Mueller notes, “the president&amp;#x27;s efforts to influence the investigation were mostly unsuccessful, but that is largely because the persons who surrounded the president declined to carry out orders or accede to his requests.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The striking thing about this section, when read in full, is how self-wounding Mr Trump’s behaviour has been. Had he simply kept quiet, and let Mr Mueller complete his investigation into his campaign’s links into Russia, the obstruction investigation never would have happened. Instead, he interfered clumsily on many occasions, allowing the special counsel to amass a damning record of the president’s truculence, dishonesty and contempt for federal investigators.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Barr said in his press conference that Mr Trump “was frustrated and angered by a sincere belief that the investigation was undermining his presidency.” But all presidents are harassed and attacked by the opposition party; none in recent memory have responded as Mr Trump has. Mr Barr also said that the White House has “fully co-operated” with Mr Mueller’s investigation. But Mr Trump never agreed to be interviewed by Mr Mueller’s team. Instead, he provided written answers to questions, which, said Mr Mueller, were “insufficien[t]…the President stated on more than 30 occasions that he “does not ‘recall’ or ‘remember’ or have an ‘independent recollection’” of information called for by the questions. Other answers were ‘incomplete or imprecise’.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Barr also stated that Mr Mueller “did not indicate that his purpose was to leave the decision [whether Mr Trump obstructed justice] to Congress…it was my prerogative as attorney general to make that decision.” Mr Mueller’s report is not so clear: “Congress has authority,” he wrote, “to prohibit a president’s corrupt use of his authority…The conclusion that Congress may apply the obstruction laws to the president’s corrupt exercise of the powers of office accords with our constitutional system of checks and balances and the principle that no person is above the law.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seems unlikely that Congress will do so: the Democratic leadership in the House has sensibly concluded that impeachment proceedings could backfire politically. There is nothing in the new report that will suddenly persuade Republicans in the Senate to abandon the president. It is nonetheless an extraordinary document.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can read the whole thing for yourself &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.justice.gov/storage/report.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 17:07:28 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>