<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Alan García, Peru’s ex-president, kills himself before being arrested]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/04/17/alan-garcia-perus-ex-president-kills-himself-before-being-arrested]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_AMP502_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-17T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;ON THE evening of April 16th, Alan García, Peru’s former president, went on the radio to declare he was innocent of accusations of corruption that were swirling around. Rumours of his likely arrest were pure supposition, he insisted: “I can tell you that I was not born to steal.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;But when police officers went to his home in Lima the next morning to detain him, Mr García asked to make a phone call, went into a room and closed the door, according to the interior minister, Carlos Morán. Minutes later, a shot rang out, and police found Mr García sitting on a chair with a bullet wound to his head. He died a few hours later in a hospital. Mr García perished as he had lived as a politician—surrounded by controversy.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;He was one of several senior figures caught up in a corruption case that is convulsing Peruvian political life; two other presidents are either in detention or have served time in jail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;The scandal stems from the Lava Jato (“Car Wash”) investigation in Brazil, which has spread to other countries. Brazilian prosecutors have won convictions for 155 people, and prison sentences totalling more than 2,000 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;One major part of the investigation concerns Odebrecht, a Brazilian construction company, which has been found to have paid billions of dollars in bribes to politicians across Latin America in exchange for lucrative contracts. In Peru more than a dozen politicians, including Mr García, have been implicated since 2016. Last November, prosecutors barred him from leaving the country for 18 months while he was investigated in several Odebrecht-linked cases, particularly allegations of taking bribes in 2008 in connection with the construction of the metro in Lima. He sought asylum in the Uruguayan embassy in Lima, which was denied. In April, details of corruption involving his confidants started to leak; senior Odebrecht officials were set to testify next month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Mr García’s first term in office, from 1985 to 1990, was marked by disastrous populist policies. In 1989, inflation rocketed above 7,000% and economic output shrank by 12%. But his second term, from 2006 to 2011, went much better. A free-trade agreement with the United States set the stage for subsequent deals with China, the European Union and a number of other countries. Average economic growth was impressive, at about 7% per year, and inflation and unemployment remained low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Although he oversaw strong economic growth, Mr García’s terms were marked by allegations of graft. Two years after the first ended in 1990 he went into exile in Colombia, living between there and France for eight years to avoid prosecution. He returned to make a remarkable political comeback after the statute of limitations had run out in 2001, and won an election in 2006. After his second term ended in 2011, he was again investigated, only to be let off the hook on technicalities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;The Lava Jato investigation was too extensive to escape, however. It has exposed the corruption and incompetence at the heart of Peruvian politics. Prosecutors have asked the United States to extradite Alejandro Toledo, Mr García’s predecessor, who stands accused of accepting a $20m bribe from Odebrecht (he denies the allegation). Both of Mr García’s successors are also implicated: Ollanta Humala spent nearly nine months in prison. He was released a year ago this month, pending trial for allegedly receiving $3m in undeclared campaign funds from the construction giant. Pedro Pablo Kuczynski was detained on April 10th on similar charges, but was then taken to hospital suffering from high blood pressure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;The Odebrecht net has also ensnared Keiko Fujimori, the leader of the conservative Popular Force party and daughter of a former president, Alberto Fujimori. Both are sitting in prison. She is there for allegedly accepting a $1m campaign contribution from Odebrecht. Her father was convicted of violating human rights during his presidency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Mr García may have ended his torment. But the consequences of the Odebrecht scandal will be felt for years to come.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 08:08:50 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alberta’s new premier plans to abolish the carbon tax]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/04/17/albertas-new-premier-plans-to-abolish-the-carbon-tax]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_AMP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-17T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“HELP IS on the way, and hope is on the horizon,” proclaimed Jason Kenney after his United Conservative Party decisively won the election in Alberta, an oil-producing province in western Canada, on April 16th. He was talking to Albertans depressed by a downturn in the oil industry, which has pushed up unemployment and left empty a quarter of the office space in Calgary, the province’s biggest city. For Justin Trudeau, Canada’s Liberal prime minister, Mr Kenney’s victory is more a source of worry than of hope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although Alberta’s slump was largely caused by factors beyond the province’s control—notably the fall in oil prices in 2014-15—voters took their anger out on the government of Rachel Notley of the left-leaning New Democratic Party. Her election four years ago had been a first for a province with a reputation for Texas-like conservatism and suspicion of the federal authorities in Ottawa. Ms Notley is a defender of the province’s oil industry, which extracts the stuff expensively from tar sands. She lobbied hard for an expansion of the Trans Mountain pipeline to take more oil to the Pacific coast for export.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But she is also an environmentalist, and introduced a carbon tax, now C$30 ($22) a tonne, to discourage greenhouse-gas emissions. In striking this balance she had an ally in Mr Trudeau, who championed the pipeline but also passed a law requiring provinces to set a price on carbon emissions or to submit to one imposed by the federal government.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much of Canada has resisted that grand bargain. The province of British Columbia, the pipeline’s terminus, remains opposed to the project on environmental grounds. In August 2018 the federal government took it over from Kinder Morgan, the frustrated US-based firm trying to build it. Moreover, four provinces led by conservative premiers—Ontario, Manitoba, Saskatchewan and New Brunswick—are fighting Mr Trudeau’s carbon price in the courts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberta will now join them. Mr Kenney, a former federal immigration minister described by Maclean’s, a magazine, as a “Guinness-sipping nerd”, is expected swiftly to kill the provincial carbon tax. He plans to raise an emissions cap on tar sands oil production and slow down plans to eliminate coal-fired electricity. He has threatened to cut off British Columbia from shipments of Alberta’s oil if it continues to oppose the pipeline expansion. Mr Kenney also promises to bring “tens of thousands of jobs” to Alberta by slashing environmental and labour regulation, and by reducing the corporate-tax rate from 12% to 8%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At first glance, his victory will pose additional problems for Mr Trudeau, who has been hurt by allegations that his office put improper pressure on the country’s attorney-general to drop the prosecution of a Quebec-based engineering company. He faces a re-election battle in October. But Mr Trudeau may not mind a fight over climate policy. According to a poll conducted in March by Abacus Data, 69% of Canadians say climate change is one of the top five issues they will consider when they vote. Just 28% of Canadians are firmly opposed to a carbon tax.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The federal government has the power to override British Columbia’s opposition to the pipeline expansion. It could do so as early as May 22nd. That gives Mr Trudeau some hope that he can rescue his energy grand bargain, despite Mr Kenney’s opposition to the carbon tax.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alberta’s new premier may benefit from an upturn in the province’s growth. The unemployment rate was 6.9% in March. That is still 1.1 percentage points above the national rate, but it is well below the peak of 9.1% in November 2016. TD Financial Group, a bank, predicts that Alberta’s economy will grow by 2.4% in real terms next year, the fastest rate in the country, thanks in part to a rise in oil prices. The sunnier outlook has nothing to do with the new premier’s pro-oil policies. That will not stop him from taking the credit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 04:10:38 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Indonesia’s president wins a second term]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/17/indonesias-president-wins-a-second-term]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_ASP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-17T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE RESULTS was never really in doubt. On April 17th, just hours after polling stations closed, pollsters released preliminary estimates showing that Indonesia’s president, Joko Widodo (better known as Jokowi) had won a second term in office. He is thought to have clinched about 55% of the vote, against 45% for his opponent, Prabowo Subianto, a former general. The contest was a replay of the previous race, in 2014, which Jokowi won by a slightly narrower margin. On April 18th the election commission will announce the preliminary result, before an official, certified outcome to be released in May. Its numbers may differ fractionally from those of the pollsters, but the outcome will be the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Voters&amp;#x27; enduring support for Jokowi can be partly explained by his sensible policies. Outside a polling station in a village near Jakarta, Suyagina, a housewife, says it is now much easier for her to buy medicines thanks to Jokowi&amp;#x27;s expansion of health-insurance coverage. Rachman, a middle-aged voter sporting enormous sunglasses and a crisp white shirt, says the president’s much-needed investment in infrastructure has helped, too. And Jokowi has managed the economy reasonably well, keeping inflation low and growth solid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Jokowi&amp;#x27;s likely victory is also thanks to cynical politicking. One weakness of his previous campaign was a perceived lack of piety, which put off some voters. Rumours circulating on social media claimed that he was a closet Christian—a potential handicap in the world’s biggest Muslim-majority country. This time Jokowi shielded himself from such accusations by picking a hardline Muslim cleric, Ma&amp;#x27;ruf Amin, as his running-mate. The vice-president-elect wants the country to adopt Islamic law and is keen to ban homosexual acts as well as some Muslim sects he considers heretical.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jokowi has also cosied up to the army to counter Mr Prabowo’s nationalism. He has peppered his inner circle with retired generals and is considering reserving some jobs in the civil service jobs for soldiers. In the fashion of Indonesia’s former strongmen, he has used the police, prosecutors and bureaucrats to make life difficult for his most vocal opponents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But despite Jokowi’s use of such underhand tactics, his victory still looks likely to be smaller than expected. He was hoping to claim over 60% of the vote—the tally with which his predecessor was re-elected. Opinion polls before the election had given him a 20-percentage-point lead. Experts put the disappointing showing partly down to Mr Prabowo&amp;#x27;s strong electoral machine, which helped to turn out wavering supporters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How Mr Prabowo will respond to another defeat is unclear. In 2014 he cried foul and challenged the result in the constitutional court. He also encouraged his supporters to take to the streets. That could happen again. He has already claimed that his own party&amp;#x27;s tally shows him to be the true victor, a finding which is entirely at odds with that of most pollsters. At a press conference outside his house in Jakarta he told supporters to guard ballot boxes, implying that the other side had cheated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Mr Prabowo’s supporters do protest against the result, that would blight a well-run election. Coordinating balloting for 187m registered voters across a rugged and sprawling archipelago of 17,000 islands is no small feat. Yet voting mostly went smoothly and participants seemed glad of the chance to take part. The biggest source of disruption was confusion over the long list of candidates. Voters were not only picking a president, but a national legislature and provincial, local and municipal assemblies too. That meant many voters had to wrestle with five different ballot papers, some of which were the size of a poster, with hundreds of choices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results of races other than the presidential one are still trickling in. It looks as though the make-up of the national parliament will remain much the same. The victors of local battles could take some time to be declared.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preliminary data also suggest that turnout has jumped by about five percentage points since the 2014 election, to around 80%. That would make it the biggest election ever conducted in a single day, anywhere. That is probably thanks to a concerted campaign to turn out the vote by politicians on both sides. Businesses joined in the effort. Hundreds of them, from cinemas to sushi restaurants, offered discounts to those who had voted and could prove it with an ink-stained finger.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A high turnout may be one of the few things about the election that pleases Jokowi. Both he and his party, PDI-P, fared worse than expected. A heftier victory would have allowed him to sideline his conservative vice-president and the armed forces. And had PDI-P claimed more seats it would have been able to reduce its reliance on its five coalition partners. Jokowi has made compromises to ensure re-election, but failed to consolidate his power as a result. Those compromises may haunt him in his second term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 04:10:37 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How AI powers Amazon]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/17/how-ai-powers-amazon]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/babbage_9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-17T19:02:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMAZON’S USE of artificial intelligence has long outstripped Facebook’s and Google’s. Just how ingrained is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/04/13/amazons-empire-rests-on-its-low-key-approach-to-ai&quot;&gt;AI at Amazon&lt;/a&gt;? Also, David Wallace Wells, a journalist and author, explains the diminishing optimism of the climate-change movement. And how natural disasters &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/04/20/memories-of-disaster-fade-fast&quot;&gt;fade from memory&lt;/a&gt;. Kenneth Cukier hosts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistbabbage/babbage-am-ai-zon&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id508376907?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/0BCUrdrOb3tvfIwazeLBUH&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWVjb25vbWlzdGJhYmJhZ2U&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=142124&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Economist-Babbage-p401958/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 03:14:54 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[An Easter-weekend travel special, on our daily podcast]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/19/an-easter-weekend-travel-special-on-our-daily-podcast]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/the_intelligence_57.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-19T11:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EASTER WEEKEND is a busy travel time in many parts of the world. If you’re unlucky, you may have to pass through a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/international/2018/01/04/which-are-the-worlds-worst-airports&quot;&gt;terrible airport&lt;/a&gt; (we talk about the world’s worst). Or perhaps you’ll splash out and take one of the many sleeper train services that are cropping up (we discuss why train travel is such a draw, particularly for artists). Or you might get &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/international/2018/09/06/people-say-they-hate-traffic-jams-but-are-oddly-tolerant-of-them&quot;&gt;stuck in traffic&lt;/a&gt; (we visit the places where traffic jams are seen as opportunity rather than nuisance). Safe travels! Runtime: 22 min.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/planes-trainsandautomobiles-thetravailsoftravel&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 02:07:53 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Trouble in tech unicornland, the tragedy of Notre Dame, and Pakistan’s avian diplomacy]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/18/trouble-in-tech-unicornland-the-tragedy-of-notre-dame-and-pakistans-avian-diplomacy]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-18T16:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THIS WEEK: the trouble with tech unicorns. These billion-dollar businesses seem to have it all—except a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/04/17/techs-new-stars-have-it-all-except-a-path-to-high-profits&quot;&gt;path to high profits&lt;/a&gt;. Next, why has a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/04/20/why-people-care-about-ancient-buildings&quot;&gt;fire at Notre Dame cathedral&lt;/a&gt; attracted more attention than the recent deadly floods in Mozambique (9:35)? And why Pakistan &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/20/why-pakistan-lets-arab-bigwigs-set-falcons-on-rare-birds&quot;&gt;risks exterminating&lt;/a&gt; a bird that lays golden eggs (15’04).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-april18th2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 02:07:52 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The [redacted] Mueller report, and more from our daily podcast]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/18/the-redacted-mueller-report-and-more-from-our-daily-podcast]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/the_intelligence_56.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-18T11:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TODAY SEES the release of most of Robert Mueller’s report into links between the Russian government and the Trump campaign. What lies behind the redactions, and what investigations are still to play out? Politicians have dabbled in comedy for decades, but comedians who take up politics are an increasingly potent force. And why Pakistani citizens don’t seem to mind that their local doctor might be a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/03/28/why-pakistan-has-so-many-quacks&quot;&gt;total quack&lt;/a&gt;. Runtime: 21 min.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/-redacted-themuellerreport&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2019 02:07:51 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[New Zealand’s government drops plans for a capital-gains tax]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/17/new-zealands-government-drops-plans-for-a-capital-gains-tax]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_ASP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE LEADER of the opposition, Simon Bridges, called it an “assault on the Kiwi way of life”. To former politicians it was “stubborn” and “vindictive”. On April 17th New Zealand’s Labour Party succumbed to such pressure and abandoned plans to impose a contentious capital-gains tax on investment properties, shares and business assets. “While I have believed in a CGT, it’s clear many New Zealanders do not,” said Jacinda Ardern, a prime minister more accustomed to applause than defeat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is an embarrassing climbdown for her party, which has campaigned for a capital-gains tax for almost a decade. Practically every other rich country has one. In February a government-appointed advisory group concluded that instituting one would make New Zealand’s tax system fairer, and recommended taxing capital gains at the same rate as the highest incomes. But Labour governs in a coalition with a populist party, New Zealand First. It courts older, rural voters who tend to oppose the levy, and refused to wave it through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Ardern’s party has been stung by the policy before. It campaigned for a capital-gains tax at general elections in 2011 and 2014, and was trounced on both occasions. Polls had shown that a strong majority of New Zealanders still opposed the reform. Yet only about 10% of them would have been affected by a capital-gains tax at all, says Michael Littlewood, of Auckland Law School. And the advisory group had suggested sweetening the pill by using the revenue the tax brought in to lower income taxes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Advocates of the tax hoped it would deter Kiwis from stashing their cash into bricks and mortar and thus cool overheated property prices. The government’s advisory group said it would help reduce the tax system’s coddling of the richest New Zealanders. The country has no stamp duty, or tax on land, estates or inheritance. The wealthy benefit disproportionately from income from property and other investments. As elsewhere, many think it unfair that profits from those assets are taxed lightly or not at all, while those who work for a living must surrender a big chunk of their income.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Businesses, however, were incensed by the advisory group’s proposals. They complained about being “double taxed” on profits from their operations, and on gains when their assets are sold. Opponents argued the tax would have deterred locals from saving for retirement, scared off investors, reduced job growth and driven up the costs of rental accommodation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New Zealand’s reliance on agriculture proved another sticking point. Many of its farmers tolerate low incomes knowing that the value of their land will rise over time. They worried that a capital-gains tax would rob them of the opportunity to cash in when they sell their businesses. “Taking that away from them is a bit like taking away subsidies,” admits Michael Cullen, a former Labour finance minister who led the advisory group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Ardern promises not to revive the idea for as long as she is prime minister, meaning that Labour will not renew its campaign for the tax at next year’s election. The opposition National Party will be sad to lose a talking point. The government has wasted millions of dollars on a pointless review, and upset businesses in the process, complains its leader, Simon Bridges. “New Zealanders can’t trust Labour on tax,” he tweeted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 23:06:17 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The race to become Britain’s next PM]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/17/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_WOP008.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- data-infographic-js=&quot;/2019/tory-leadership/js/bundle.js&quot; data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/tory-leadership/css/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/tory-leadership/css/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;O&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt; N MARCH 27TH&lt;/small&gt; Theresa May,
  Britain’s prime minister, promised to stand down as leader of the Conservative
  Party—if Parliament passed her Brexit withdrawal deal. This has been rejected
  three times by the House of Commons. But &lt;small&gt;MP&lt;/small&gt;s have been unable
  to agree on an alternative to Mrs May’s deal, beyond rejecting the idea of a
  no-deal Brexit. The prime minister has decided to seek a second extension to
  the talks with the European Union, and may yet make a fourth attempt to win
  parliamentary approval.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;
  Whatever happens with Brexit, Mrs May has, in effect, fired the starting
  pistol in the race to succeed her as Tory leader and prime minister. Betfair
  Exchange, a betting website, has been tracking punters’ predictions on the
  next Tory leader. According to the wisdom of the crowd, five Tory candidates
  stand out. On April 2nd, Boris Johnson, the former Foreign Secretary and
  prominent Brexit campaigner, became the favourite to win.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p &gt;Source: Betfair Exchange&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Adrian Wooldridge, our political editor, assesses the chances of five leading Conservative politicians hoping to take the top job in this short film
&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ychDrZ2QzlE&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 23:06:16 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Little Woods” marks out Nia DaCosta as a film-maker to watch]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/04/17/little-woods-marks-out-nia-dacosta-as-a-film-maker-to-watch]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BKP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-17T13:45:59Z&quot;&gt;Apr 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHEN “LITTLE WOODS” premiered to rapturous reviews at the Tribeca Film Festival last year—it currently holds a rare 100% approval rating on Rotten Tomatoes, a review-aggregator site—and was snatched up by Neon, a feted distributor, it signalled the arrival of a promising new voice in film. For her directorial debut, Nia DaCosta (who also wrote the script) has produced a profound work about the practical realities and emotional hardships of poverty, set in an oil boomtown in North Dakota. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The film’s protagonist, Ollie (Tessa Thompson), is eight days from the end of her probation following an arrest for dealing Oxycontin. Though she is trying to stay on the right side of the law, two crises occur at once: the bank’s foreclosure on her home and the pregnancy of her estranged sister, Deb (Lily James). To save the family home and to pay for her sister’s abortion, Ollie is drawn back into a life of crime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These contrivances might seem familiar, even clumsy, in lesser hands, but what makes “Little Woods” compelling are the fresh details crafted by Ms DaCosta. Before she decides to resume dealing drugs, Ollie is living below the poverty line. She makes ends meet by selling coffee and sandwiches to rig workers from the back of her truck. She has no romantic life—a rarity for films with female leads—and her only relationship to speak of is with her sister, whom she rarely sees and does not initially seem to care much for. When Deb comes to her for help, Ollie provides it not out of love or even necessity but from some unspoken understanding that Deb is the only real connection she has.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a simple story, and one which touches on a panoply of current political issues: economic anxiety in rural America, opioid addiction, access to abortions and the cost of health care. Again, the film could have strayed into polemic, but Ms DaCosta keeps the policies in the background to focus on their human repercussions. Eschewing thundering speeches or grand injustices, the film unfolds simply as a series of problems for Ollie to solve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a successful and moving approach, even if it takes some time for the viewer to attune to the film’s quiet realism. What seems to be a premise taken directly from the crime-movie playbook—this is essentially a “one last heist” flick—is made surprising by the absence of thrilling chase scenes, showy cinematography, villainous cops or promises of riches. Instead, “Little Woods” is beholden to the realities of Ollie’s life. There is a natural tension that arises from her situation, but her dilemma is never made to feel like a caper. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even the emotional storyline, so often overdeveloped and melodramatic in films that focus on women, is muted. Through their travails, Ollie and Deb do reaffirm their sororal bond, but that is hardly the point: the point is to avoid destitution. Ms Thompson and Ms James underplay the emotions of their exchanges—neither of them reaches for likeability in their portrayals—and often they seem more like business partners than family. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The critical success of “Little Woods” has already helped Ms DaCosta to land her next project. She has been lined up by Jordan Peele to helm a sequel of “Candyman” (1992), a classic horror film which touched on themes of race, class and urban gentrification. Ms DaCosta is a good fit for the material. She is on her way to becoming one of the foremost chroniclers of America’s “forgotten class”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Little Woods” is released in America on April 19th&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 21:06:20 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>