<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Joe Biden and Donald Trump trade insults in Iowa]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/12/joe-biden-and-donald-trump-trade-insults-in-iowa]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_blp904.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-12T02:46:06Z&quot;&gt;Jun 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEARLY 17 MONTHS before voting day, it is beginning to feel as if the first days of two-person campaigning for the 2020 presidential election have already begun. Both President Donald Trump and Joe Biden, the front-runner in a crowded field of candidates for the Democratic nomination, were on the stump in Iowa on June 11th. Mr Biden focused on the eastern portion of the state, including flood-hit Davenport on the Mississippi. Mr Trump toured an ethanol plant in the far west followed by a political fundraising dinner in Des Moines, the state capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each man has good reason to show his face in Iowa. Mr Biden was making some diplomatic amends. He had seemed to snub Iowa’s Democrats on June 8th and 9th, by failing to join 19 (out of 23) candidates running for the Democratic nomination at an event in Cedar Rapids. (He claimed a prior commitment, at his granddaughter’s school graduation in Washington). Given his strong lead in the polls Mr Biden can probably afford to stand apart from the fray. Nonetheless he must avoid any suggestion that, at the age of 76, he lacks the energy for a scrap or that he is aloof from ordinary voters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump, meanwhile, is wary of losing support from rural Midwesterners who backed him heartily in 2016. The president attended a rally in northern Wisconsin in late April. He knows rural folk in the region have suffered in the past couple of years. That has happened in part due to his chaotic approach to international trade. Confrontations with China have led to a dramatic fall in demand for soy-bean exports, while higher prices for imported steel have pushed up equipment costs. Economic uncertainty and terrible spring flooding have hit rural areas. Federal financial relief has flowed but farmers take that grudgingly, reluctant to be seen as ever more reliant on subsidies and other government hand-outs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Appearing in Iowa simultaneously probably suits both men for another reason. It is a chance for each to test how they might spar close-up. Mr Biden is not guaranteed to win the Democratic nomination, but Mr Trump evidently judges that is likely to. And the president’s frequent attacks almost certainly bolster Mr Biden among Democratic primary voters. The president called Mr Biden “a loser”, “weak mentally” and lacking in energy, on June 11th. Such comments suck attention away from other Democratic candidates and may suggest, at least to Democrats, that the president is rattled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent opinion polls, reportedly including a private Republican one, suggest that Mr Biden is more popular than the president in many battleground states. Mr Biden may calculate that the more he gets under Mr Trump’s skin, the further ahead he can pull from the rest of the primary field. And because most Democrat voters seem to care more about ejecting the incumbent from the White House than any particular ideology, they are likely to back a nominee who is best placed for the confrontation. That is likely to mean coalescing around a front-runner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Biden’s comments on June 11th, in Davenport, seemed designed to provoke the president. He called Mr Trump an “existential threat” to America and its values, then jeered that Mr Trump knew nothing about trade and economics. According to excerpts of that speech, released early in the morning and leapt upon by the media, it also contained the observation that supermarket cashiers grasped better than the president that American consumers—not foreign producers—pay the price for his imposing tariffs on imports. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why then is Mr Trump focusing on Mr Biden if doing so helps an already popular opponent become the Democratic nominee? It may be that Mr Trump is too undisciplined to behave differently. Or he might simply believe Mr Biden is destined to be his opponent. If so, he will want as much time as possible to develop lines of attack, hoping to characterise Mr Biden as weak, unenergetic, or an establishment insider, well before Election Day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump sees an advantage in dwelling on Mr Biden’s age and biography. “He’s a different guy,” the president said as he left the White House for Iowa. “He looks different than he used to. He acts different than he used to. He’s even slower than he used to be.” The president is hardly youthful: he turns 73 this week. But he can try to pitch himself not only as younger than the Democrat, but as a relative outsider. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Biden as vice-president, spent eight years in the White House, and has already struggled a little in defending a political record that spans several decades. Last week he changed his position on whether there should be federal funding for abortions (he used to be against, but is now in favour). Mr Trump, after four years in office, may have the gall to claim that he is an insurgent. After all, that worked among many voters in the Midwest last time around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 11:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The benefits of pre-schooling may extend for generations]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/11/the-benefits-of-pre-schooling-may-extend-for-generations]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_USP502_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-11T18:29:16Z&quot;&gt;Jun 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMERICA HAS fewer of its three- and four-year-old children in pre-school than other rich nations. But it is beginning to catch up. Between 2002 and 2017, the proportion of four-year-olds enrolled in state pre-kindergarten programmes rose from 14% to 33%. And a big, bipartisan push is underway to get more children into education before they start school. Three Republican-leaning states—Georgia, Florida and Oklahoma—have introduced universal pre-kindergarten. Several contenders for the Democratic presidential nomination, including Joe Biden, Bernie Sanders and Elizabeth Warren, boast universal pre-school policies in their campaigns. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analyses of large-scale pre-school programmes in the last few years have often been disappointing. But the potential value of pre-school has become clear as participants in long-run studies have grown older. Two new papers look at the long-term effects of perhaps the best known of these, a 1960s-era pilot programme, on both the former pre-schoolers and their children. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Between 1962 and 1965, 128 African-American children from the Perry Elementary School district in Ypsilanti, Michigan were enrolled in an experiment. After being sorted into two groups with similar IQs, gender balance, and socio-economic backgrounds, a coin toss selected one of the groups to receive two-and-a-half hours of pre-school education each weekday for the two years before they entered primary school. They also received an hour-and-a-half of home visits a week from Perry Elementary teachers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since then, the participants have been repeatedly surveyed; most recently, most of them were interviewed at the age of 55. James Heckman and Ganesh Karapakula, economists, have examined the long-gathered results in two new papers, using techniques designed to factor in the experiment’s small size, flaws in the randomisation process and missing survey responses. The researchers found that the pre-schooled kids—and in particular the boys—have had considerably different lives as a result. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pre-schooled group, they found, had about half the average number of violent felony convictions as the control group. Males in that group spent an average of 27 days in jail between the ages of 20 and 50 compared to 136 days for boys in the control group. They also had more success in employment, increased earnings in mid-adulthood and better health. Perry Pre-school Project boys are significantly more likely to have been in stable marital relationships. And the effects appear to persist across generations: the children of beneficiaries have fewer school suspensions, higher levels of education and employment and lower levels of criminal activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another pre-school experiment that has been followed up over years, the Abecedarian Project in North Carolina, which divided 111 children into a test and control group, suggests similar results. Both programmes were expensive, small and run by committed teams, involving a greater level of intervention than the large-scale pre-kindergarten programs being rolled out today. The home visits may have made a particular difference. The researchers report suggestive evidence that the Perry project had some of its biggest effects outside school. Male participants interviewed in their 50s were far less likely to report having been verbally abused by an adult when they were children, having felt neglected, or having been abducted by one parent to hide from another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Large-scale pre-school progammes do not compare well to these small experiments. While there is widespread research evidence suggesting that pre-schooling yields immediate learning gains, these fade over time. Researchers studying children randomly assigned to the Tennessee Voluntary Pre-kindergarten Programme, for example, found that while participants performed better on a battery of achievement tests at the end, the achievement gap subsequently reversed. And analysis of the rollout of universal pre-Kindergarten in Georgia suggests that there were no significant changes in test scores at fourth grade (around the age of 9-10) among those exposed to the programme compared to similar students from other states where it was was not rolled out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some studies do suggest more positive results for disadvantaged subgroups.Results from a pre-school programme in Texas found improvements for low-income students and those who were not proficient in English. The first national randomised evaluation of the Head Start programme, which gives matching grants to states providing early education, health care and nutrition services to children as well as training in parenting, found it made a great difference to cognitive achievement during pre-school. That benefit faded, but it persisted up until first grade for a subsample of Spanish speakers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of this suggests pre-school programmes are difficult to deliver effectively to thousands rather than tens of children. The design of such programmes is also important. Elizabeth Cascio, an economist from Dartmouth College, used the nationally representative Early Childhood Longitudinal Study of children born in 2001 to study the impact of different pre-school programmess across America. She found that universal programmes can improve the reading ability of four-year-olds from low-income families, while means-tested programmes have no impact. This, she suggests, may be because universal programmes are higher-quality and more rigorous academically.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The big and sustained effects of the Perry programme suggest that intergenerational inequality can be permanently reduced by early childhood interventions. The priority for policy makers is to figure out how that can be achieved—at scale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 05:40:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[All the presidents men—who will lead the ECB?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/11/all-the-presidents-men-who-will-lead-the-ecb]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_blm504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-11T16:00:05Z&quot;&gt;Jun 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERE ARE no women in the running to take over as the &lt;strong&gt;next President of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/04/13/mario-draghis-successor-at-the-ecb-has-plenty-to-do&quot;&gt;European Central Bank&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;later this year. We take a look at the most hotly tipped candidates. Also, the problems at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/06/troubles-at-the-woodford-investment-group-point-to-a-wider-trend&quot;&gt;Woodford&lt;/a&gt; investment management group &lt;/strong&gt;show that&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;even star fund managers can struggle to outperform the market. And why do &lt;strong&gt;German billionaires&lt;/strong&gt; avoid the limelight? Simon Long hosts. Runtime: 19 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-allthepresidentsmen&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 03:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Europe’s secularists worry about the rise of Christian-nativist populism]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/06/11/europes-secularists-worry-about-the-rise-of-christian-nativist-populism]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_BLP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-11T15:36:15Z&quot;&gt;Jun 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AROUND 15 years ago, when the machinery of the European Union was being refashioned into its present form, one of the hottest debates concerned what role, if any, would be set aside for God. The Vatican and some mainly Catholic states, like Poland, wanted theistic language in the EU’s constitutional treaty; a secular camp led by France was opposed. In the end, the nearest thing to a spiritual reference was a statement in the treaty’s preamble that signatories were “drawing inspiration from the cultural, religious and humanist inheritance of Europe…”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In another clunky compromise, Article 17 of the subsequent Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union obliges the EU’s institutions to conduct an “open, transparent and regular” dialogue with churches and other religious groups, and also with philosophical and non-confessional organisations. On the secular side, the European Humanist Federation, grouping about 60 smaller bodies in more than 20 countries, is the EU’s main interlocutor. It counterbalances the advisory role of outfits like the Conference of European Churches, which is mainly Protestant and Orthodox, and COMECE, the Catholic bishops’ group. Both those bodies maintain active lobbying operations around the EU’s institutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The religious types and the secularists are still squabbling about how much access they should enjoy to the upper echelons of the Euro-bureaucracy. In recent weeks a tempest erupted in the teacups of Strasbourg when it emerged that Mairead McGuinness, an Irish politician who is one of the European Parliament’s vice-presidents, had mooted the idea of intensifying the legislature’s exchanges with Article 17 partners. Instead of merely attending three seminars a year, they might be invited to meet officials involved in the planning of parliamentary business, enabling them to flag up matters of concern. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms McGuiness adamantly insisted that these proposals, leaked by an investigative reporter, Sian Norris, were merely being floated, and that any enhanced access would be granted in equal measure to religious and secular groups. But Virginie Rozière, a French MEP and staunch advocate of secularism, said it was “completely crazy” to contemplate any change that boosted the churches’ role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite this sparring, the pompous expression “cultural, religious and humanist inheritance” does actually correspond to something real. Whether they are on the Christian Democratic centre-right or the generally more secularist centre-left, most European politicians, and ultimately their voters, have in recent years shared many common ideals: a belief in a universal franchise, freedom of speech, the rule of law and due process, and antipathy to racism. In their understanding of Europe’s past, some would emphasise the Judaeo-Christian inheritance, while others would stress the struggle against clerical authority proclaimed by the Enlightenment. But none would aspire to re-impose Christianity by top-down methods. After all, the advent of Christian Democracy after 1945 marked a final break with Christian authoritarianism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite all that, the delegates who met in Iceland recently for the annual gathering of the European Humanist Federation saw troubling portents on the horizon. A whole range of threats to the enlightened order were cited by Giulio Ercolessi, an Italian liberal who is the federation’s president. As he put it:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Human Rights, individual liberties, the rule of law, the secular character of our institutions and the very idea of constitutional democracy are under attack, in the world and also in our continent…Scientific achievements that have made our lives healthier and easier in the last decades are called into question…Religious fundamentalism conspires [to use] religious traditions as weapons to be brandished against newcomers, in the hands of fear-mongers of the worst sort…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the developments that troubles Mr Ercolessi and his fellow humanists is the rise across Europe of the populist, xenophobic right, which often dresses itself in religious or Christian-nativist clothing, even though its leaders are not usually very devout. Parties of roughly that stripe have already taken centre-stage in Hungary, Italy and Austria. In last month’s European elections the nationalist right made substantial gains in Britain and France. Such parties are not, in general, openly opposed to liberal democracy or the rule of law; but some of their supporters are less than respectful of those values.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may be a sign of the times that Europe’s most important Christian Democrat, Germany’s Chancellor, Angela Merkel, felt obliged to say, in an interview with CNN after the European ballot: “We have to face up to the spectres of the past...we have to tell our young people what history has brought us... why we are for democracy, why we stand up against intolerance [and] why we show no tolerance of violations of human rights.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Ercolessi was also preoccupied with a less obvious consequence of the current wave of migration into Europe. Given that many of the new arrivals are from countries dominated by Islam or other conservative religious beliefs, he detected a widespread concern even on the European centre-left that waves of migration might increase the number of ultra-conservative immigrant micro-communities, portending a “new obscurantism” on the continent. Such fears were palpable across the political spectrum in France and the Netherlands, said Mr Ercolessi. As a result, anti-immigrant sentiments could be heard even from progressive politicians.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best way to counter all this, in Mr Ercolessi’s view, is to showcase an important but neglected fact: many of the new arrivals in Europe are not bringing ultra-conservative religion with them, but fleeing from it. These include at least some people from the Middle East who face persecution because they are LGBT or atheist or members of a religious minority.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short, the influx of newcomers from poor and often brutal places, and the complex political consequences of that influx, are a challenge to Europe’s “cultural, religious and humanist inheritance” as the treaty-writers, with a mixture of political expediency and inspiration, described it. People of many different metaphysical beliefs will be needed to defend that inheritance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 03:39:55 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How compatible are democracy and capitalism?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/11/how-compatible-are-democracy-and-capitalism]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_fnd000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-11T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;OF LATE THE world’s older democracies have begun to look more vulnerable than venerable. America seems destined for a constitutional showdown between the executive and the legislature. Brexit has mired Britain in a constitutional morass of its own. Such troubles could be mistaken for a comeuppance. In recent years political economists have argued that rising inequality in the Anglo-American world must eventually threaten the foundations of democracy; a book on the theme by Thomas Piketty, a French economist, has sold well over a million copies. That argument channels a time-worn view, held by thinkers from Karl Marx to Friedrich Hayek, that democracy and capitalism may prove incompatible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As powerfully as such arguments are made, the past century or so tells a different story. The club of rich democracies is not easy to join, but those who get in tend to stay there. Since the dawn of industrialisation, no advanced capitalist democracy has fallen out of the ranks of high-income countries or regressed permanently into authoritarianism. This is not a coincidence, say Torben Iversen of Harvard University and David Soskice of the London School of Economics, in their recent book, “Democracy and Prosperity”. Rather, they write, in advanced economies democracy and capitalism tend to reinforce each other. It is a reassuring message, but one that will face severe tests in years to come.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Economists and political theorists have imagined all sorts of ways capitalist democracies might fail. The oldest is the worry that grasping masses will vote to expropriate the wealth (hard-earned or not) of entrepreneurs and landowners—and without secure property rights there can be no capitalism. Hayek thought that the governments of the early 20th century, in responding to the concerns of the masses, had over-centralised economic decision-making, a road that led eventually to totalitarianism. Other thinkers followed Marx in reckoning that it was the greed of the capitalists that would do the greatest harm. Joseph Schumpeter feared that as firms grew more powerful, they might push a country towards corporatism and clientelism, winning monopoly rights that would generate profits they could share with politicians. Mr Piketty and others say that inequality naturally rises in capitalist countries, and that political power becomes concentrated alongside economic power in an unstable way. Other economists, like Dani Rodrik, have argued that full participation in the global economy forces a country to give up a degree of either national sovereignty or democracy. Lowering barriers to trade means harmonising trade and regulatory policies with other countries, for instance, which reduces each government’s ability to accommodate domestic preferences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if capitalism and democracy are such uneasy bedfellows, what explains their long co-existence in the rich world? Mr Iversen and Mr Soskice see capitalism and democracy as potentially mutually supporting, with three stabilising pillars. One is a strong government, which constrains the power of large firms and labour unions, and ensures competitive markets. Weaker countries find it harder to resist the short-term expediency of securing power by protecting monopolies. The second is a sizeable middle class, forming a political bloc that shares in the prosperity created by a capitalist economy. A bargain is struck in which the state provides mass higher education on generous terms, while encouraging the development of frontier industries that demand skilled workers. Middle-class households thus reckon that economic growth is likely to benefit them and their children. (Rising inequality is not a threat to capitalist democracies, the authors reckon, because middle-class voters care little about the poor and do not support broader redistribution that could raise their tax bills.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Providing the education, infrastructure and social safety net that support a prosperous middle class requires substantial tax revenue. For the system to hold a third pillar is needed: large firms that are not very mobile. Before recent rapid globalisation that was no problem. Yet even now firms are more rooted than commonly thought. Though multinationals are adept at shifting production and profits around the world, in a knowledge economy leading firms cannot break their connections to networks of skilled individuals like those in London, New York or Silicon Valley. Their complex business plans and frontier technologies require the know-how developed and dispersed through these local networks. That increases the power of the state relative to firms, and allows it to tax and spend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Middlemarch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Quibble with the details, but the overarching story—immobile companies giving governments a degree of sovereignty, which they self-interestedly use to boost the middle classes—seems a plausible account of the stability of advanced capitalist democracies. It leaves plenty to be concerned about, however. It hinges on the middle classes feeling confident about the economy. A sharp slowdown in growth in real median incomes, as in America and Britain in recent years, might not send voters rushing to the barricades, but could strengthen the appeal of movements that threaten to disturb the status quo. Governments, too, are becoming less responsive to middle-class priorities. America’s is too dysfunctional, and Britain’s too distracted by Brexit, to focus on improving education, infrastructure and the competitiveness of markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demographic change might also take a toll: older and whiter generations may not much care whether a would-be middle class that does not look like them has opportunities to advance or not. Then, too, the authors may have underestimated the corrosive effect of inequality. Threatening to leave is not the only way the rich can wield power. They control mass media, fund think-thanks and spend on or become political candidates. Proud democracies may well survive this period of turmoil. But it would be a mistake to assume survival is foreordained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 03:39:54 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to spot a recession]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/11/how-to-spot-a-recession]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_woc909.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-11T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BY ALMOST any measure, America’s economy is in fine fettle. GDP growth is robust. Unemployment is nearing a 50-year low. And the stockmarket is up by a whopping 50% since 2016. Yet, for all the positive economic news, there is no shortage of hand-wringing on Wall Street about a looming recession. But precisely when will it strike? Economic statistics are often published months after the fact; by the time a recession is officially underway, there is often little investors and policymakers can do about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One new clue comes from a new book by Claudia Sahm, an economist at the Federal Reserve, who has developed a new method for predicting economic downturns. In “Recession Ready: Fiscal Policies to Stabilize the American Economy”, Ms Sahm argues that when the three-month average unemployment rate is at least 0.5 percentage points above its minimum from the previous 12 months, the economy is in a recession. This simple measure, it turns out, has correctly called every recession in America since 1970. In January 2008, for example, Ms Sahm’s index warned of the coming Great Recession. The index had also flashed red in early 2001, amid the bursting of the dotcom bubble. Today, conditions are considerably less dire. With unemployment just 0.07 percentage points above its minimum of the past year, the “Sahm recession indicator” suggests that the chance of a downturn occurring in the next year is just 20%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Sahm’s unemployment-based index resembles many other popular leading indicators. It matches up closely with the slope of the yield curve, which plots interest rates on short- and long-term government bonds, long considered one of the most reliable barometers of economic health. Typically this curve steepens when investors are more bullish on the economy, and expect higher growth and rising interest rates, and flattens (or even inverts) when they anticipate a slowdown. Ms Sahm’s index also matches The Economist’s own “R-word index”, which measures the prospects for a future downturn based on the number of times that newspapers publish the word “recession”. This spikes when recessions are on the minds of traders and the financial journalists who write about them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Sahm’s measure has some advantages over its peers. It shows clear delineations between periods of recession and growth. It also appears to detect few, if any, false positives. Where her recession indicator falls short is on timeliness. After all, the ability to anticipate a recession is far more useful than knowing when you are in one. The yield curve predicted both the 2001 and 2008 recessions about a year in advance, and the R-word index ticked up at about the same time. The unemployment-based measure, on the other hand, would have given investors a head-start of just a few months. Today, the yield curve suggests that a recession may be imminent and America’s leading newspapers are discussing recessions more often than at any point since 2012. Ms Sahm’s work may soon be put to the test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 03:39:53 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[In “Dirty God”, a woman navigates life in the wake of a brutal attack]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/11/in-dirty-god-a-woman-navigates-life-in-the-wake-of-a-brutal-attack]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_BKP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-11T17:10:26Z&quot;&gt;Jun 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“MONSTER”. THIS is the first word Rae says upon seeing her mother Jade (Vicky Knight) after the slew of operations and skin grafts she has had since her ex-boyfriend threw acid in her face. Not the best response, obviously, but Rae is two. Lisa (Katherine Kelly), Jade’s mother, is old enough to know better: “But it’s a nice monster, Rae,” she explains to the little girl. There are some wounds that no procedures can heal, but as scarred emotionally and physically as Jade is, she has been pronounced ready to leave hospital to try to put her life back together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Dirty God” is directed by Sacha Polak, the Dutch film-maker known for “Hemel” (2012) and “Zurich” (2015), both of which won prizes at the Berlin film festival. The movie is startling for its raw tactility: the opening credits play over close-ups of Jade’s burned skin, pitted and gnawed where the acid fell. (The actress, Ms Knight, is herself the survivor of an arson attack; burns cover a third of her body and, when not acting, she works in the burn unit where she was treated.) These shots linger like they might over a foreign landscape, and indeed when Jade leaves the cocoon of her hospital ward, she finds that the topography of her world has changed utterly, even through so much has stayed the same. She is still living in her mother’s small council flat in London, filled with shop-lifted clothes that Lisa sells, while Jade’s best friend, Shami (Rebecca Stone) lives a few floors down. But now Rae cries in fear when Jade tries to hold her and, unbeknownst to the heroine, her mother has been allowing members of her ex-boyfriend’s family to visit: a betrayal that Lisa doesn’t seem able to understand or acknowledge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Polak has resisted the temptation to create a stereotypical victim. Jade swears, makes bad decisions, burps in the faces of strangers, makes friends and crude jokes, and glories in the pleasure to be had from sex and masturbation. On her first night home from hospital she goes out clubbing with Shami, happy for her mother to take responsibility for Rae. The night is a disaster: Jade endures the horrified stares of men who once would have made a pass and Shami has started dating Naz, with whom Jade shared a flirtation before the attack. Jade is soon scouring the internet for a plastic surgeon who might be able to restore her smooth, unblemished skin—and perhaps her old life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of the real monster of the piece, Jade’s ex-boyfriend, the viewer sees blessedly little. He appears to Jade in dreams as a creature with clawed hands and a ruff of crow-black feathers. When she does see him in the flesh, in court, she is so scared that her bladder releases, urine spurting dark and wet into the fabric of her fawn-coloured trousers. Small wonder she seeks release from her appearance, at one point, in a full black niqab. ”You’re not one of those wotsits now are you now?” Lisa asks. “How’s this going to help?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ultimately, of course, Lisa is right. Neither hiding behind borrowed face coverings nor investing in too-good-to-be-true promises of surgery in Morocco are the answer. Instead Jade has to accept the unacceptable and pursue, with grace, happiness in her new life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Dirty God” is screening in Britain now&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 00:45:03 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Advocates of a liberal, secular Europe worry for the future]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/06/11/advocates-of-a-liberal-secular-europe-worry-for-the-future]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_BLP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-11T15:36:15Z&quot;&gt;Jun 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AROUND 15 years ago, when the machinery of the European Union was being refashioned into its present form, one of the hottest debates concerned what role, if any, would be set aside for God. The Vatican and some mainly Catholic states, like Poland, wanted theistic language in the EU’s constitutional treaty; a secular camp led by France was opposed. In the end, the nearest thing to a spiritual reference was a statement in the treaty’s preamble that signatories were “drawing inspiration from the cultural, religious and humanist inheritance of Europe…”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In another clunky compromise, Article 17 of the subsequent Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union obliges the EU’s institutions to conduct an “open, transparent and regular” dialogue with churches and other religious groups, and also with philosophical and non-confessional organisations. On the secular side, the European Humanist Federation, grouping about 60 smaller bodies in more than 20 countries, is the EU’s main interlocutor. It counterbalances the advisory role of outfits like the Conference of European Churches, which is mainly Protestant and Orthodox, and COMECE, the Catholic bishops’ group. Both those bodies maintain active lobbying operations around the EU’s institutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The religious types and the secularists are still squabbling about how much access they should enjoy to the upper echelons of the Euro-bureaucracy. In recent weeks a tempest erupted in the teacups of Strasbourg when it emerged that Mairead McGuinness, an Irish politician who is one of the European Parliament’s vice-presidents, had mooted the idea of intensifying the legislature’s exchanges with Article 17 partners. Instead of merely attending three seminars a year, they might be invited to meet officials involved in the planning of parliamentary business, enabling them to flag up matters of concern. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms McGuiness adamantly insisted that these proposals, leaked by an investigative reporter, Sian Norris, were merely being floated, and that any enhanced access would be granted in equal measure to religious and secular groups. But Virginie Rozière, a French MEP and staunch advocate of secularism, said it was “completely crazy” to contemplate any change that boosted the churches’ role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite this sparring, the pompous expression “cultural, religious and humanist inheritance” does actually correspond to something real. Whether they are on the Christian Democratic centre-right or the generally more secularist centre-left, most European politicians, and ultimately their voters, have in recent years shared many common ideals: a belief in a universal franchise, freedom of speech, the rule of law and due process, and antipathy to racism. In their understanding of Europe’s past, some would emphasise the Judaeo-Christian inheritance, while others would stress the struggle against clerical authority proclaimed by the Enlightenment. But none would aspire to re-impose Christianity by top-down methods. After all, the advent of Christian Democracy after 1945 marked a final break with Christian authoritarianism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite all that, the delegates who met in Iceland recently for the annual gathering of the European Humanist Federation saw troubling portents on the horizon. A whole range of threats to the enlightened order were cited by Giulio Ercolessi, an Italian liberal who is the federation’s president. As he put it:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Human Rights, individual liberties, the rule of law, the secular character of our institutions and the very idea of constitutional democracy are under attack, in the world and also in our continent…Scientific achievements that have made our lives healthier and easier in the last decades are called into question…Religious fundamentalism conspires [to use] religious traditions as weapons to be brandished against newcomers, in the hands of fear-mongers of the worst sort…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the developments that troubles Mr Ercolessi and his fellow humanists is the rise across Europe of the populist, xenophobic right, which often dresses itself in religious or Christian-nativist clothing, even though its leaders are not usually very devout. Parties of roughly that stripe have already taken centre-stage in Hungary, Italy and Austria. In last month’s European elections the nationalist right made substantial gains in Britain and France. Such parties are not, in general, openly opposed to liberal democracy or the rule of law; but some of their supporters are less than respectful of those values.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may be a sign of the times that Europe’s most important Christian Democrat, Germany’s Chancellor, Angela Merkel, felt obliged to say, in an interview with CNN after the European ballot: “We have to face up to the spectres of the past...we have to tell our young people what history has brought us... why we are for democracy, why we stand up against intolerance [and] why we show no tolerance of violations of human rights.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Ercolessi was also preoccupied with a less obvious consequence of the current wave of migration into Europe. Given that many of the new arrivals are from countries dominated by Islam or other conservative religious beliefs, he detected a widespread concern even on the European centre-left that waves of migration might increase the number of ultra-conservative immigrant micro-communities, portending a “new obscurantism” on the continent. Such fears were palpable across the political spectrum in France and the Netherlands, said Mr Ercolessi. As a result, anti-immigrant sentiments could be heard even from progressive politicians.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best way to counter all this, in Mr Ercolessi’s view, is to showcase an important but neglected fact: many of the new arrivals in Europe are not bringing ultra-conservative religion with them, but fleeing from it. These include at least some people from the Middle East who face persecution because they are LGBT or atheist or members of a religious minority.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short, the influx of newcomers from poor and often brutal places, and the complex political consequences of that influx, are a challenge to Europe’s “cultural, religious and humanist inheritance” as the treaty-writers, with a mixture of political expediency and inspiration, described it. People of many different metaphysical beliefs will be needed to defend that inheritance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 00:17:24 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The race to become Britain’s next PM]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/11/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-10T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HERESA MAY&lt;/small&gt; stepped down as leader of the Conservative Party on June 7th. She will remain as prime minister until her successor is chosen. Nominations for the Tory leadership closed on June 10th, to be followed by several rounds of voting among MPs to whittle down the ten candidates, a process that will take a week or two. The MPs will then send two names to party members who will make the final choice. The result of their vote will be announced before Parliament rises for summer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Betfair Exchange, a gambling website, has been tracking punters’ predictions on the next Tory leader. According to the wisdom of the betting crowd, a handful of candidates stand out. But there is only one clear frontrunner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Friday&amp;#x27;s edition of &lt;i&gt;The Economist asks&lt;/i&gt;, Anne McElvoy spoke to Jeremy Hunt and Rory Stewart about their leadership plans: &lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-whocanleadbritainthroughbrexit-&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adrian Wooldridge, our political editor, assesses the chances of some of the leading Conservative politicians hoping to take the top job in this short film: &lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ychDrZ2QzlE&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.betfair.com/exchange/plus/politics&quot;&gt;Betfair Exchange&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 22:18:26 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thousands of children are abused in Senegal’s religious schools]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/11/thousands-of-children-are-abused-in-senegals-religious-schools]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_map501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-11T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;MBAR LIFTS up his trousers and points at the marks where the chains wore his skin away. He was 11 when his father sent him from his village to a religious school on the outskirts of Senegal’s holy city of Touba. His teacher made him recite passages from the Koran in the morning. Then Mbar (not his real name) was sent out to the streets to beg for money for his master until night fell. If he misbehaved, he was beaten or starved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After two years Mbar ran away to his village. But his father sent him to another school. This time he was not made to beg. Instead, he was chained to the classroom wall. “I couldn’t move. They used to bring me a bucket to pee in,” says Mbar, in a cracked voice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senegal is one of Africa’s more successful countries. It is peaceful. Its government functions relatively well and the economy is growing at 7% a year. But along the old boulevards of Dakar, the capital, thousands of &lt;em&gt;talibé&lt;/em&gt;—the “seekers” attending nearby religious schools—beg for change. Some boys are as young as four. Many families send their sons to such schools, or &lt;em&gt;daaras&lt;/em&gt;, where they memorise the Koran. Some do so for religious reasons but, for many, &lt;em&gt;daaras&lt;/em&gt; offer the only opportunity for children to get a basic education. Many &lt;em&gt;marabouts&lt;/em&gt;, or religious teachers, respect children’s rights. And begging has long been accepted as a way of teaching &lt;em&gt;talibés&lt;/em&gt; humility and funding their education.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But because the system is almost completely unregulated, rackets flourish. A new report by PPDH, a coalition of Senegalese rights groups, and Human Rights Watch (HRW) in New York, documents some of the abuse suffered by the estimated 100,000 children who are forced to beg.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Isolated far away from home, dozens of boys sleep in filthy rooms. They are given just enough food to survive. If they fail to meet their begging quota of about $1 per day, or try to escape, they may be beaten, starved or chained for weeks at a time. Many are sexually abused. According to a psychologist at Samu Social, a centre working with boys in Dakar, many children try to kill themselves or hurt themselves deliberately so they will need medical attention and can get out of the &lt;em&gt;daaras&lt;/em&gt;. From 2017 to 2018, researchers recorded at least 16 incidents in which children died from beatings, neglect or poor conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of the boys come from farms or villages in Senegal, but some are also trafficked from the Gambia, Guinea Bissau and Mali. Agents go to rural areas and promise parents that the boys will study at the most prestigious religious schools in Senegal. The costs for the traffickers are minimal. They pay border guards about $1 a child to smuggle them in from Gambia, says Issa Kouyaté, who runs Maison de la Gare, a &lt;em&gt;talibé&lt;/em&gt; shelter in Saint Louis, a city in northern Senegal. Once they get the boys to the major cities, they can make money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Government officials have repeatedly pledged to deal with the problem but their attempts have been half-hearted, at best. The &lt;em&gt;daaras&lt;/em&gt; are powerful institutions and the &lt;em&gt;marabouts&lt;/em&gt; can influence the way people vote in elections. Politicians and officials compete for their support and are reluctant to interfere in religious affairs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2013 a law was drafted which sought to establish minimum standards for &lt;em&gt;daaras&lt;/em&gt;. It is yet to be passed by parliament. In 2016 President Macky Sall spoke about taking the children off the streets and jailing those who forced them to beg. But official figures show that only about 300 children were helped in 2018. Children often beg openly outside police stations and the &lt;em&gt;marabouts&lt;/em&gt; who abuse them rarely face justice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All this may be storing up trouble for Senegal. “You have a large population of impoverished, abused children, isolated away from their families. I can’t think of a more perfect target population for criminals,” says Jeffrey Bawa of the United Nations Office of Drugs and Crime, a UN agency, adding that the boys were also likely to be future targets for Islamist recruiters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mbar was chained to the wall for a month. An older, stronger boy kept the keys for the chains in his robe and disciplined the children when the &lt;em&gt;marabout&lt;/em&gt; was away. Mbar saw him rape a younger boy several times. One night when the older boy was sleeping, he left his robe on the floor near Mbar, who found the keys and unlocked himself from the wall. He couldn’t find the key for the chains around his ankles but it was enough. He jumped out of the window and shuffled towards the distant lights of a main road. Strangers helped him out of his chains and took him to a shelter in Dakar. After almost a year of eating good food, he is beginning to grow again and dreams of becoming a footballer. If only Senegal could make similar efforts to leave the &lt;em&gt;talibé&lt;/em&gt; system behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jun 2019 20:40:18 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>