<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[After years as an underdog, Tiger Woods is a favourite once again]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/05/15/after-years-as-an-underdog-tiger-woods-is-a-favourite-once-again]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BLP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T22:09:21Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE PGA Championship has long been to men’s golf what the Australian Open is to tennis: the ugly stepchild among the sport’s four major annual tournaments. The Masters sets itself apart for occurring at the same venue every year, fielding the smallest number of players and maintaining &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.golf-monthly.co.uk/tour/us-masters/masters-history-records/masters-green-jacket-126753&quot;&gt;quaint&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.thoughtco.com/on-the-menu-the-champions-dinner-at-the-masters-1564552&quot;&gt;traditions&lt;/a&gt;. The U.S. Open is distinguished by famously punishing courses, which are sometimes so brutal that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2018_U.S._Open_(golf)&quot;&gt;no one finishes below par&lt;/a&gt;. And the Open Championship, known as the British Open outside the United Kingdom, is the oldest of the four (it began in 1860); the only one not played in America; and is regularly held on coastal &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Links_(golf)&quot;&gt;links courses&lt;/a&gt;, characterised by firm greens and shifting winds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for the PGA? From 1916 to 1957, it was the only major with a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Match_play&quot;&gt;match-play format&lt;/a&gt;. But ever since it adopted the same 72-hole stroke-play format as the others, it has lacked a clear identity. Its only unique characteristic is reserving 20 spaces in the field for resident professionals at golf clubs, slightly diluting its level of competition. Aside from that, it mimics the U.S. Open, but has historically been played at less prestigious courses. The event’s occasional use of the slogan “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.youtube.com/watch?v=cg6Rr_ZthCA&quot;&gt;This Is Major&lt;/a&gt;” carried a distinct note of protesting too much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This weekend, however, the PGA Championship will be the focus not just of keen golf fans but of the sporting world at large. In advance of the 2019 season, the event was moved from August to May. This made it the second major of the year rather than the fourth, and created a regular drumbeat of one major per month from April through July. And fortuitously, after an 11-year-long drought, the 43-year-old Tiger Woods stormed back from scandal and injury to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/04/14/tiger-woods-wins-his-fifth-masters-in-a-comeback-for-the-ages&quot;&gt;win the 15th major of his career at the Masters last month&lt;/a&gt;. All of a sudden, Mr Woods’s quest to surpass Jack Nicklaus’s record of 18 major victories looks very much alive. This year’s PGA Championship, held on the Bethpage Black Course in New York state—a test so difficult its &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://nypost.com/2019/05/14/pga-championship-the-fight-behind-bethpage-blacks-famous-sign&quot;&gt;warning sign has become a golf-world meme&lt;/a&gt;—represents Mr Woods’s first opportunity to narrow his deficit relative to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://thegolfnewsnet.com/golfnewsnetteam/2016/10/06/why-jack-nicklaus-called-golden-bear-nickname-logo-99551&quot;&gt;Golden Bear&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EAGLE, &lt;i&gt;The Economist&lt;/i&gt;’s statistical prediction system for major tournaments, returns for the PGA as well, after taking a mild bruising at the Masters. (You can follow its predictions, which update live every two minutes, at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://eagle.economist.com&quot;&gt;http://eagle.economist.com&lt;/a&gt;.) Although our model recognised that Mr Woods had played well enough during his comeback to rank among golf’s elite once again, its evaluation of his prowess was somewhat &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/06/our-masters-forecast-is-lukewarm-on-tiger-woods&quot;&gt;more conservative than that of betting markets&lt;/a&gt;. At the time, EAGLE considered him the ninth-best player in the world, with around a 2% chance of victory; punters put him third or fourth, with roughly a 5% chance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that Mr Woods has proven he is still capable of winning a major, bettors’ view of him has improved once again. His current market price corresponds to a 6.6% chance of winning the PGA, making him the narrow fourth-favourite behind Dustin Johnson (8.5%), Brooks Koepka (7.8%), and Rory McIlroy (7.3%). No one else exceeds 5%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet EAGLE, undeterred by the toll Mr Woods may have taken on its reputation last month, is a stubborn bird. Mr Woods has not played in any events since his Masters victory, giving the model a paltry four new rounds’ worth of data with which to update its assessment of him. Moreover, his triumph at Augusta National was slightly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/04/16/tiger-woods-made-our-golf-model-look-silly-have-we-learned-a-lesson&quot;&gt;less impressive than it appears&lt;/a&gt;. He beat the field’s average score by a modest ten strokes, a margin that historically has been sufficient to win a major just 8% of the time. By that measure, his showing at the Masters was actually slightly worse than he did at last year’s PGA Championship, when he was the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.economist.com/game-theory/2018/08/14/despite-woodss-charge-the-pga-was-brooks-koepkas-to-lose&quot;&gt;runner-up to Mr Koepka&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Woods is not the only betting favourite about whom EAGLE harbours reservations. The model is just as cautious about Mr Koepka, who claimed the last PGA Championship by two strokes over Mr Woods, and then lost this year’s Masters to him by a single shot. More than any other golfer at the moment, Mr Koepka seems to play up or down to the importance of the competition. He has won three of the past six majors he has entered, and tied for second in another. Yet these successes have alternated with missteps that should be rarer for an elite player, such as an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.pgatour.com/roundrecap/2018/r060/2/36689.html&quot;&gt;eight-over-par second round&lt;/a&gt; at the Tour Championship last September, which Mr Woods won. Blending the good with the bad, the sometimes erratic Mr Koepka’s average scores during the 67 rounds he has played since winning the PGA Championship rank just 15th in this year’s field.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The notion that some players rise to the occasion while others wilt under pressure is not necessarily only the stuff of hagiographic nostalgia films. In fact, predictions for scores in majors can be modestly improved by taking account of the gap between players’ past performances in majors and their work in other events. However, this effect is exceedingly small. And its biggest beneficiary is not Mr Koepka but rather Jason Day, who historically has played about a full stroke per round better in majors than he has on lesser stages. EAGLE agrees with punters that Mr Koepka and Mr Woods, the winner and runner-up at the last PGA Championship, have similar chances of lofting the Wanamaker Trophy this time. However, it puts those probabilities in the range of 2.5-3%, less than half the markets’ estimate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By definition, win probabilities are zero-sum. As a result, if Mr Woods and Mr Koepka stand less of a chance than is popularly thought, someone else must be under-valued. As it has been for every major since the start of 2018, EAGLE’s top pick to win is Mr Johnson. He has just reclaimed the top spot in the official world rankings from Justin Rose, and for good reason. After adjusting for playing conditions, Mr Johnson’s average scores during the past nine months are 0.13 strokes per round better than those of Mr McIlroy, and 0.31 strokes per round better than anyone else’s. However, these two superstars’ prowess is no secret. The chances of victory EAGLE assigns to them, at 6.8% and 4.4%, are actually slightly below those seen in betting markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So where might a bettor looking to make a buck—or simply a fan hoping to impress friends with her savvy—turn to look for a surprise winner? Among top-tier players, the one who has received curiously little buzz in advance of the event is Paul Casey. Mr Casey is to an extent Mr Koepka’s mirror image: he has 19 professional victories, but has never won a major. Moreover, he has missed the cut in each of the past two majors, as well as in the prestigious Players Championship. At the age of 41, his best years are likely behind him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nonetheless, Mr Casey is off to a blazing start to 2019. He successully defended his 2018 title against a strong field at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Valspar_Championship&quot;&gt;Valspar Championship&lt;/a&gt;, and has secured four more top-five finishes in his past nine events. He currently sits 12th in both the official world rankings and EAGLE’s, just a bit behind Mr Woods. At this stage of his career, Mr Casey probably is not quite the player that Mr Woods is. But Mr Woods’s chances of winning the PGA Championship are surely not five times greater than Mr Casey’s, as the markets suggest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The focus of the television cameras will rarely waver from the likes of Mr Woods and Mr McIlroy during the early days of the event. However, the chaotic nature of golf is such that the eventual victor is likely to come from the long tail of players with records even less distinguished than Mr Casey’s. Among players with odds longer than 100 to one, EAGLE is partial to Webb Simpson, who won the U.S. Open in 2012 and finished fifth in the Masters last month; Matthew Fitzpatrick, an up-and-coming British youngster still hunting for his first major; and Joost Luiten, a Dutchman who holds the rare distinction of having made both a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.sbnation.com/2017/8/10/16127984/pga-championship-2017-joost-luiten-hole-in-one-ace&quot;&gt;hole-in-one in a major&lt;/a&gt; and a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Xq4RJu6ZbUw&quot;&gt;rarer-than-rare albatross&lt;/a&gt;. The annals of PGA Championship victors include most of the greats, but also unheralded champions like &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yang_Yong-eun&quot;&gt;Y.E. Yang&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Keegan_Bradley&quot;&gt;Keegan Bradley&lt;/a&gt;. In a sport as unpredictable as golf, no one can be counted out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 08:41:50 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Depression is increasing among Americans reaching middle age]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/15/depression-is-increasing-among-americans-reaching-middle-age]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_USP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T18:18:52Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE RECENT REVERSAL in life expectancy in America has focused much attention on the “deaths of despair” of poorly educated middle-aged white men. According to the Centres for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC) overall life expectancy fell for the second time in three years in 2017, driven by a surge in opioid overdoses and suicide, at which whites are most at risk. But a new paper by Lauren Gaydosh, a sociologist at the Center for Medicine Health and Society at Vanderbilt University suggests that unhappiness and its symptoms are widespread in middle age Americans of all races and ethnicities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Gaydosh and her colleagues used data from the National Longitudinal Study of Adolescent to Adult Health to track the health and behaviour of a group of Americans first surveyed in the mid-1990s when they were teenagers. They were most recently interviewed in 2016 when they were in their late 30s and 40s. The researchers studied the data on depressive symptoms and reported contemplation of suicide. They also tracked behaviours including heavy drinking and marijuana use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results suggest that depressive symptoms, thoughts of suicide, drinking and marijuana use all fell during the period when respondents were in their twenties and then increased during the last decade as they entered their thirties and early forties.  This pattern was similar across all groups: whites, blacks and Hispanics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strikingly, the researchers found that for depressive symptoms in particular, average rates amongst blacks and Hispanics were higher than among whites. In the most recent round of the survey, one third of blacks with a high school education or less reported that they had been diagnosed with depression or anxiety. That was slightly higher than the proportion of less-educated whites.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While thoughts of suicide were slightly higher on average amongst less-educated whites than other groups, the pattern of change over time was similar. Again, heavy drinking was higher amongst whites than other groups, but both the uptick in drinking as well as smoking marijuana in the last ten years was driven by those whites surveyed who had more than a high school education, not the less-educated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the study’s conclusion that misery is spreading across the whole cohort reaching middle age, it also suggests that opioid abuse along with other prescription drug abuse and illegal drug use remain much higher amongst non-college educated whites. Other research has shown that whites commit suicide at a higher rate than blacks and Hispanics: according to the CDC, white non-Hispanic Americans commit suicide at around three times the rate of blacks and Hispanics, with the highest and growing toll amongst older men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reasons why poorly educated white men are unhappy are well documented. In research published by the National Bureau of Economic Research Margherita Borella, an economist, found for that white, non-college-educated Americans born in the 1960s face shorter life expectancies, higher medical expenses, and lower wages compared with those born in the 1940s. This suggests that increased suicide rates among white men may be caused in part by a decline in income and status. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet poorly educated white men remain better off than women and minorities. According to Pew Research, in 2018 working women earned 85% of what working men earned per hour. The average black American earned 65%  as much as a white in 2016, only marginally up from 59% in 1970.  For Hispanic workers the wage ratio actually fell from 74% to 65% over that period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How should policy makers respond in a way that is both effective and equitable? In a paper published for the National Bureau of Economic Research in April, William Dow, a public health specialist, reported that suicides were lower in states that have increased the minimum wage and provided more generous credits through the EITC (earned income tax credit), a refundable tax credit for low income individuals and families. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier research by William Evans and Craig Garthwaite, economists, suggests that increasing the EITC also improves self-reported mental health measures among its recipients. Because of lower incomes, minorities and women are more likely to be eligible for EITC payments, and to benefit from minimum wage increases. All of this suggests that a stronger safety net would speed progress toward a more equal America—and reduce the anguish of some who may see themselves losing from the process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 06:44:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Uber is trying to disrupt the road-freight business]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/15/uber-is-trying-to-disrupt-the-road-freight-business]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_wbp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FLORIDA 595 is unappealing, even by truck-stop standards. Odour from a landfill next door permeates the humid air. Planes from a nearby airport buzz overhead. The average American trucker spends two-thirds of working time either in places like this or loadless on the road. So the wheelmen propping up the bar at 595 are giddy about a new breed of smartphone app. For a few years startups like Cargomatic and Convoy have been helping drivers maximise their gainful time behind the wheel by digitising the matching of shipments with lorries. Convoy called itself “Uber for freight”—until 2017, when Uber launched exactly that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Uber had presented itself as just a ride-hailing firm, analysts reckon, it would not have fetched an $82bn valuation when it listed in New York on May 10th. That was predicated on the platform’s potential to disrupt all road transport. Investors are having second thoughts: Uber’s share price fell sharply in its first two days as a public company, before regaining some ground, perhaps on the realisation that the firm may struggle to make money anytime soon. Uber Freight is a case in point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On paper, the market the app could disrupt looks huge. Global spending on road freight reached $3.8trn in 2017, says Armstrong &amp;amp; Associates, a consultancy. Companies in America spent over $700bn; freight rates grew by 30% last year owing to a surfeit of cargo and a shortage of drivers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In practice, only $72bn of American shipments is managed by brokers; most of the rest travels on company lorries. Digital brokers’ slice is wafer-thin. Zion Market Research predicts that their global turnover will increase from around $1bn to $21bn between 2017 and 2026. Uber would need to dominate this market to rival its $9bn in revenue from ride-hailing in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Uber touts freight as its third-most-important business after ride-hailing and food delivery. It made up nearly 3% of the firm’s revenues in 2018, but bookings grew by almost 450% that year—faster than any other division. Bill Driegert, boss of Uber Freight, thinks that it can grab most of the brokers’ $72bn, not just the digital bit. No rival can match its software or traffic data—both applicable to lorry logistics, Mr Driegert boasts. Brand recognition, he believes, should help win over drivers reluctant to take jobs from apps no one has heard of.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But unlike ride-hailing, which Uber more or less invented, it is a late arrival to freight. Its earlier efforts to disrupt haulage with the purchase of Otto, a startup developing self-driving lorries, came to naught. Grand plans to expand abroad—in March it presented a European app—run up against home-grown incumbents: Timocom of Germany and Teleroute of Belgium in Europe, and Rivigo, a hit Indian app, in Asia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At home, conventional brokers have shown digital savvy. Goldman Sachs, a bank, estimates that from January to September last year Uber Freight accounted for 30% of haulage-app downloads. That is impressive, but shy of the combined 40% for the three apps from big brokers: C.H. Robinson’s Navisphere, J.B. Hunt’s Carrier 360 and DAT’s Load Board. The boom in road freight provides these companies with cash to plough into apps and algorithms. Landstar, another big broker, claims that a recent software upgrade cut the time needed to process a delivery by nearly a third.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chris O’Brien, C.H. Robinson’s chief commercial officer, disputes the idea that the startups’ data on traffic are better. Lorry routes differ from taxi rides. Brokers can bolt on services—warehousing, last-mile delivery, assistance with customs or unforeseen problems—onto basic haulage. Here, Uber is miles behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brokers see their main threat coming not from Uber’s headquarters in San Francisco but from Seattle, home to Amazon. The e-commerce juggernaut launched an app in 2017 to help lorry drivers deliver merchandise to its warehouses. It is rumoured to be working on its own service. Unlike Uber, it has plenty of experience delivering cargo. It sits on more cash than Uber or the brokers. It may not take long to appear in their rear-view mirrors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 06:44:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Alabama’s lawmakers want to challenge Roe v Wade]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/15/alabamas-lawmakers-want-to-challenge-roe-v-wade]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_usp001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEVER HAS the war sparked by &lt;em&gt;Roe v Wade&lt;/em&gt;, the 1973 Supreme Court ruling that declared abortion a constitutional right, been as intense as it is now. Lawmakers in conservative states are passing “heartbeat” bills banning abortion from the moment a heartbeat is detectable, around the sixth week of pregnancy—flagrantly violating &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt;. To defend abortion rights some liberal states are extending them, by making it easier to have abortions in the third trimester. That has encouraged President Donald Trump to mount a fresh assault on late abortions, which he routinely characterises as babies being “ripped” from their mothers’ wombs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most uncompromising attack on &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt; has been launched in Alabama. On May 14th the state’s Senate passed a bill that would effectively ban abortion outright. If it is signed into law by the governor, as seems likely, it will constitute the harshest abortion legislation passed in America in half a century. “The heartbeat bills don’t really tackle what &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt; is about,” says Eric Johnston, president of the Alabama Pro-life Coalition, alluding to &lt;em&gt;Roe’s&lt;/em&gt; protection of abortion until a fetus is viable, at around 24 weeks. “It seemed like the right time to challenge it properly.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bill, which the softly-spoken Mr Johnston wrote, does not mess around. Comparing abortion to the most murderous atrocities of the 20th century—“German death camps, Chinese purges, Stalin’s gulags, Cambodian killing fields, and the Rwandan genocide”—it makes performing one a felony, punishable by up to 99 years in prison. Because the bill defines a fetus as “a human being…regardless of viability” its sponsors resisted attempts, by Republican as well as Democratic senators, to allow exceptions in cases of rape or incest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The law will be struck down in the courts, just as heartbeat bills have been elsewhere, most recently in Kentucky and Iowa. Similar laws passed recently in Mississippi and in Georgia will meet the same fate, as will several more making their way through state legislatures if they become law. That is the purpose of extreme abortion laws—to prompt legal cases in the hope that one might come before the new conservative majority at the Supreme Court, which will use it to overturn &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until recently anti-abortionists were engaged in a stealthier battle. Rather than challenging &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt; directly they chiselled away, introducing state-level regulations so burdensome that clinics were forced to close. As social conservatives retreated in the culture war over gay marriage, they advanced over abortion. Between 2011 and 2017, more than 400 abortion restrictions have been introduced across America—more than a third of the total since 1973, according to the Guttmacher Institute. Eight states have only one abortion clinic left.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump’s appointment of two conservative Supreme Court justices has emboldened some pro-lifers to adopt a more aggressive strategy. Their hopes of directly overturning &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt; were boosted on May 13th when the justices voted 5-4 along ideological lines to overturn a 40-year-old precedent in a case unrelated to abortion. The move, wrote Stephen Breyer, one of the liberal justices, “can only cause one to wonder which cases the Court will overrule next.” Lest anyone wondered what sort of case he had in mind, he cited &lt;em&gt;Planned Parenthood v Casey&lt;/em&gt;, a ruling from 1992 that upheld &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some pro-life activists are cautious about the prospects of overturning &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt;. Clarke Forsythe, senior lawyer for Americans United for Life, which has drawn up successful state-level abortion regulations, says his organisation watches carefully every time the court overturns a precedent: “it happens more often than many imagine”. But he also points out that the court, and in particular Chief Justice John Roberts, seem in no hurry to overturn Roe. He does not expect the justices to take on a direct challenge for “two or three years”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is probably right. Casting himself as a pro-life warrior is useful for Mr Trump, who needs to keep the support of conservative evangelicals in 2020. But actually repealing &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt; before the next presidential election would be an electoral disaster for Republicans, since a large majority of Americans believe abortions should be legal up to the third trimester.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Undermining early abortion rights can be risky for state lawmakers, too. Georgia, which last week became the fourth state this year to pass a heartbeat bill, has long been a deeply conservative state. But it is becoming more diverse and urban, as the inroads made by Democrats in November’s mid-terms attest. A recent poll found that more voters in the state opposed the heartbeat bill than supported it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 03:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Saving face: San Francisco&#x27;s ban on recognition technology]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/15/saving-face-san-franciscos-ban-on-recognition-technology]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/babbage_13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T18:25:13Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;LEGISLATORS IN San Francisco have just voted to ban the use of facial recognition—is this a victory for privacy or a setback for technology? Also, new research on how machine learning can be used to predict the likelihood of breast cancer. And Amazon&amp;#x27;s boss, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/15/to-understand-the-tech-lords-look-to-their-libraries&quot;&gt;Jeff Bezos&lt;/a&gt;, draws inspiration from science fiction in his aim to build space habitats. Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistbabbage/babbage-facingthefuture-&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 02:41:52 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jeremy Kyle and the media’s treatment of mental health]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/15/jeremy-kyle-and-the-medias-treatment-of-mental-health]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_brp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE FIRST episode of “Expedition Robinson”, a Swedish television programme, aired in September 1997. A precursor to “Survivor”, a hit American show, it was one of the first examples of so-called reality television, and the first exhibit in a debate on the effects of such shows on those who take part. Two months before the series aired, one of its cast, Sinisa Savija, had committed suicide after becoming the first person to be voted off. The producers responded by mostly editing him out of the broadcast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two decades later, attitudes have changed. On May 15th, in the middle of “mental-health awareness week”, ITV announced that it would cancel “The Jeremy Kyle Show”, a popular daytime programme that featured real people arguing furiously about infidelity, alcoholism, drug use and the like. A week earlier a participant, Steven Dymond, had been found dead after failing a lie-detector test on camera.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Worry about the welfare of reality-TV subjects is not new. Two former contestants on “Love Island”, another ITV show, have killed themselves in the past year. In 2016 the New York Post counted 21 suicides by American reality-TV participants since 2004.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet it is the Jeremy Kyle incident that looks most like becoming, as one MP put it, a “watershed moment”. One reason may be the programme’s vulnerable subjects. The families berating each other in episodes such as “My transgender love rival is trying to steal my husband!” are softer targets than the young wannabes who go on “Love Island” hoping for a career as a minor celebrity. Ten years of austerity have made poor-bashing less popular than elite-bashing. And viewers with an appetite for Kyle-style public shaming can nowadays get it on Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there may be a more optimistic reason. There has been a “sea change” in attitudes to mental health, says Paul Farmer, the boss of Mind, a charity. Public figures, from MPs to royals, have spoken openly about their mental battles. “What starts off invisible, moves towards taboo, becomes acceptable. We’ve seen it in cancer, race, sexuality, disability and we see it in mental health,” says David Crepaz-Keay of the Mental Health Foundation, another charity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of people saying they were willing to live with someone who suffered from mental illness increased from 57% in 2009 to 72% in 2016. Those willing to work with them rose from 69% to 80%. And the media’s framing of mental-health issues has improved, shifting to being mainly non-stigmatising in 2016, according to Time to Change, a charity. The end of “The Jeremy Kyle Show” will presumably do no harm to this balance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 02:41:51 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America’s avocado supply is set to tighten]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/15/americas-avocado-supply-is-set-to-tighten]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_woc053.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;THE MARKET for avocados has undergone a transformation unlike that of any other fruit (yes, fruit) over the past few decades—from chic canapé of the 1970s to millennial staple today. In 2018 Americans consumed 3.5kg (7.7lbs) of avocado per person—nearly four times the level in 2000. Even McDonald’s is serving up guacamole. Yet the outlook for American avocado lovers is a concern.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;In California last year, where 80% of America’s avocados are grown, heatwaves and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2018/11/17/despite-californias-inferno-global-wildfires-are-fizzling-out&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;wildfires&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; destroyed trees. This year was always destined to be a little less satisfying for farmers, as the alternate-year-bearing nature of avocado trees means that a large crop is followed by a smaller yield the following year. But rains and cold weather have exacerbated the problem, with this year threatening to be the worst harvest in over a decade.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Imports have risen sharply as American demand has grown. In the mid-1990s the Department of Agriculture (USDA) lifted an 83-year-old ban on Mexican avocados. Imports from Mexico, where avocados can be grown all year round, made up a staggering 87% of American avocado consumption in 2017-18. The USDA is forecasting this share to rise to 93% for the coming season.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span id=&quot;docs-internal-guid-3fd080b3-7fff-eb20-4b94-ee87817dd094&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Additional imports may also come from Chile and Peru. But the nature of the crop means that farmers can sit on their harvest and wait for prices to surge, as avocados can hang on trees for several months without rotting. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;On April 1st the price for Mexican Hass avocados rose by a third—the biggest one-day price rise in almost a decade. This may be down to a combination of factors: America’s increased threats to close the border and Mexican farmers waiting for Cinco de Mayo, a major festival on May 5th, to hike prices. The threat of new tariffs, border frictions and a low harvest in California might cause even more price volatility in the coming months. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Millennials might want to try something else on their toast.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 01:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Britain’s bizarre, unwanted European election]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/15/britains-bizarre-unwanted-european-election]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_brp001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FEATHERSTONE Working Men’s Club, near Pontefract, has never seen anything like it. On a sunny May morning, a mass of Brexit Party supporters, armed with placards and warmed up by a tub-thumping speech from Ann Widdecombe, a former Tory minister, chant “Nig-el, Nig-el” as their hero clambers on to the platform. This month’s European election, Nigel Farage shouts, is about democracy and the betrayal of voters. Mentions of Theresa May, the Conservative prime minister, or Yvette Cooper, the local Labour MP, are greeted with howls of “Traitor!”. Outside, a kind soul from the Communist Party of Great Britain (Marxist-Leninist) distributes leaflets pointing out that his party also backs Brexit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Farage’s new party thrives on protest. Its supporters enjoy nothing more than being told their vote to leave the European Union in June 2016 has been betrayed by the establishment, the London elite, a useless prime minister, the civil service, treacherous MPs and the BBC. Mr Farage, who went from private school to a career in the City, is himself a prime elite specimen. Yet he manages to pose as an anti-establishment rebel. In a Labour stronghold, he raises cheers by denouncing Jeremy Corbyn as an Islington leftie. He offers no policies—they are promised only after the election—and does not even explain why Brexit is a good idea. His message is simple: we must walk out in October with no deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By any standards the European election taking place in Britain on May 23rd is bizarre. Nobody wanted it, as Brexit was meant to have happened on March 29th. But Parliament’s repeated refusal to pass the government’s Brexit deal was followed by a European Council decision to extend the deadline until October 31st. So Britain is having to join the rest of the EU in voting for a fresh set of MEPs next week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the face of it the result should not matter much. If a Brexit deal is passed before the summer recess, as the government still hopes, British MEPs will barely have time to take their seats. Both main parties play down the ballot’s importance. The Tories are invisible on the campaign trail, failing even to produce a manifesto. Labour is little better, as its leadership is divided over whether to support another referendum. Yet the smaller parties are enjoying themselves—and doing well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BRC055.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190518_BRC055.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190518_BRC055.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190518_BRC055.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190518_BRC055.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190518_BRC055.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190518_BRC055.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190518_BRC055.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190518_BRC055.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190518_BRC055.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The outcome will depend heavily on turnout. In European elections it is usually small (last time, in 2014, it was 35%). Yet this one may see turnout rise, as both pro- and anti-Brexit forces have been energised. Pollsters find that voters now identify more strongly with Remain or Leave than with their usual parties. The result is that support is bleeding from the Tories to the Brexit Party and, to a lesser extent, from Labour to the Liberal Democrats, Greens and Change UK (see chart).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The focus is on Mr Farage’s Brexit Party, as it has a good chance of coming first. Yet, given the Tories’ calamitous meltdown over Brexit, this would not be so extraordinary. In 2014, after all, Mr Farage led the UK Independence Party into pole position. The bigger surprise is the fall-off in Labour support. Mr Corbyn’s ambivalence on Brexit seems to be driving many Remain voters to the smaller parties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These three, especially the new Change UK, have come under justified attack for splitting the Remain vote. Change UK members claim this is less damaging than it seems, as they appeal to voters disillusioned by the Lib Dems or hostile to the Greens. If the three together score in the high 20s, they will do almost as well as the Brexit Party in vote share, though probably not in terms of seats. Yet Change UK is having a tough time, not least over its poor organisation and branding. This week its lead candidate in Scotland pulled out, asking voters to back the Lib Dems. The party has no candidate in the Peterborough by-election on June 6th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The biggest question is what impact next week’s election might have on Brexit and British politics. The Brexit deal still seems stuck. Brussels has switched off; no further negotiations are taking place. But Mrs May has announced that in early June she will bring the withdrawal agreement bill before the House of Commons. Her hope is that the Brexit Party’s success may shock Tory and Labour MPs into voting for the deal after all. She will also argue that, if the bill fails, the only alternative is a no-deal Brexit. Yet these arguments are weak. Labour still looks unlikely to back the bill. So do the Northern Irish Democratic Unionists and the hardline Tory Brexiteers. And no-deal is not the only alternative, as Brussels seems prepared to grant yet another extension of the deadline to avert it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effect of the election on Mrs May’s own position may be more dramatic. As &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; went to press she was trying to fend off another attempt by the 1922 committee of Tory backbench MPs to change its rules to allow a leadership challenge. Even if she avoids such a contest, most ministers and MPs expect her to go soon. If her attempt to pass the Brexit bill fails, she will be under intense pressure to accelerate the timetable for her departure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What might her successor do? This is where the Brexit Party’s influence will count. It is not going away after the European election. Indeed, Mr Farage claims to be ready to run candidates, including himself, in any general election too. And for many Tories, the prospect of the Brexit Party eating away at their vote means their party must back a no-deal Brexit to survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This may not be the right conclusion, however. For the Brexit Party’s success is also doing something else: making a Labour victory in a future election more likely. And here is the ultimate irony for those vociferous Farage supporters. Their actions could yet mean a Labour-led government overturns Brexit altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 01:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[In Venice, a “library of exile” reflects on displacement and language]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/15/in-venice-a-library-of-exile-reflects-on-displacement-and-language]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BKP503_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T14:55:27Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE ATENEO VENETO, a grand 16th-century palace near the Fenice Opera House, once hosted a fraternal order which cared for convicted prisoners in their final days. For the past 200 years, however, the site has been a forum for discussion, drawing together people from the city’s many communities to contemplate art, literature, science and politics. Now it is home to a different set of noisy and troubled souls. In the Aula Magna room—where scenes of conflagration adorn the ceiling—stands a porcelain box filled with 2,000 books by exiled writers, from Ovid, through Dante, Voltaire and Victor Hugo, to the present day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the heart of this piece by Edmund de Waal, a British ceramicist and writer, is a lost library. In 1938, weeks after the Nazi invasion of Austria, his great-grandfather’s home on the Ringstrasse in Vienna was stormed and the library was seized and Aryanised. The story of the tragic dispersal of that household formed the basis of Mr de Waal’s bestselling family memoir, “The Hare with Amber Eyes” (2010). “This is a project that I have always dreamed of doing,” he says of the Venice show. “It is about exile—what it means to move to another country, to speak another language.” He reckons it will be “the most significant sculpture of [his] life”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exhibition, entitled “psalm” after a book in the Old Testament, exists in two parts. In the Jewish Museum in the Venetian Ghetto, Mr de Waal has installed ten works of porcelain, marble and gold that reflect on the cultural heritage of the area (he is the first contemporary artist to create a major project for the Ghetto). In the Ateneo Veneto, he covered the exterior of his library in gold leaf, which was then coated with white porcelain slip, a kind of slurry. On that surface he has etched the names of more than 60 lost libraries, including Alexandria, Nineveh, the Rabbinical libraries of Lvov and Odessa, Aleppo, Mosul and the classical collection of Viktor von Ephrussi, his great-grandfather. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;Inside the library, alongside the shelves, are four glass vitrines holding small porcelain works. Mr de Waal says the layout of the space is intended to evoke the edition of the Talmud created by Daniel Bomberg, a Christian printer, in Venice in the early 16th century—around the same time the Ateneo was built. The project reflects the city’s long history “as a place of translation, a space to sit and read and be,” he says; the books are arranged chronologically by country, though most have been translated from their original language, and visitors are encouraged to seek out titles in their own tongue as well as those that have been translated from it. Readers search for the nations they know, and within them the writers they have loved and followed even as they fled abroad. Your correspondent was born in Africa, and was happy to find volumes by Patrice Nganang from Cameroon and Ngugi wa Thiong’o, a Kenyan writer who has said that “resistance is the best way of keeping alive.”&lt;p&gt;In the tumult of the Venice Biennale, there is something special about any spot that is quiet. The project encourages the visitor to reflect on returns, a theme that recurs throughout the artist’s work. Mr de Waal’s great-grandfather’s books were never recovered, probably dispersed throughout Austria or destroyed, but with this new “library of exile” he has devised his own kind of restitution. The exhibition will travel to Germany, to the Japanisches Palais in Dresden—which was operating as a public library when it was partially destroyed during the second world war—and then to the old King’s Library at the British Museum. After that, Mr de Waal aims to give the 2,000 books to the city of Mosul, which will house them in the new library the city is building to replace the one destroyed by Islamic State. He plans to add 800 books of his own, including the 18th-century edition of Voltaire that his grandmother managed to save from the Ephrussi library before she went into exile herself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“psalm”, an exhibition in two parts, continues in Venice until September 29th. The “library of exile” will be presented at the Japanisches Palais in Dresden from November 2019 to February 2020, and at the British Museum in London in 2020&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[To understand the tech lords, look to their libraries]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/15/to-understand-the-tech-lords-look-to-their-libraries]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_ldp501_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;LITERARY TYPES have long been sniffy about science fiction. Ian McEwan, a feted British novelist, has been at pains to distance his most recent book, about an intelligent android, from “sci-fi”, even though the idea is one of the most picked-over tropes in the genre. Such snobbery is misplaced. Humans are technological animals. Science fiction explores how that power might be used, what sorts of worlds might be built with it and what sublime new estrangements and transcendence may follow. It is a literature of ideas, and, as John Maynard Keynes observed (in a different context), the world is ruled by little else. To see the force of Keynes’s point, consider how the world’s richest man plans to spend his fortune.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On May 9th Jeff Bezos outlined his thoughts about the future of humanity. The founder of Amazon sells $1bn-worth of shares a year to fund his rocket company, Blue Origin, which wants to cut the cost of space flight, put tourists into space and help return humans to the moon. That is only the first part of a grander scheme to spread humanity throughout the solar system in artificial habitats. He is not alone. Elon Musk founded SpaceX with the goal of establishing a self-sufficient colony on Mars. Yuri Milner, a Russian tycoon, has promised $100m to send a robot to Alpha Centauri, the closest star system to the sun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Bezos is open about his influences. He grew up reading Isaac Asimov and Robert Heinlein, with their stories of rebellious lunar colonies, idiot-savant robots and societies founded on “psychohistory”, an amalgam of economics, history and what is now called big data. “Star Trek”, with its humane, liberal and internationalist re-imagining of the American frontier spirit, was another favourite. Decades later, Mr Bezos is using his money to help bring such a future about, rather as Heinlein’s D D Harriman did in “The Man Who Sold the Moon”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scratch a Silicon Valley nerd and chances are you will find similar influences, and similar ideas about how the future should look. One of the tech industry’s favourite writers is Iain M Banks, a Scottish socialist whose knockabout space operas were set in and around “the Culture”, a spacefaring utopia. Amid worries about superintelligent computers and robots taking jobs, they are a tonic. In Mr Banks’s society robots have indeed taken all the jobs, but the result is inexhaustible material abundance. Sentient beings, organic or artificial, are free to flourish. Everything is run by nigh-omnipotent and mostly benevolent AI philosopher-kings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His influence runs deep. A meeting room at DeepMind, a big AI firm, is named in his honour. When Mark Zuckerberg, the boss of Facebook, ran a book club in 2015, only two of his 23 recommendations were novels. Mr Banks’s “The Player of Games” was one. (“The Three-Body Problem”, a piece of science fiction by Liu Cixin, was the other). Mr Musk named SpaceX’s rocket-recovery “droneships” after AI-animated spaceships in Mr Banks’s “Culture” books. In 2018 Mr Bezos announced plans to film those books, as well as Larry Niven’s “Ringworld” and “Snow Crash”, a cyberpunk novel by Neal Stephenson—who was, for some of Blue Origin’s early days, its only employee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of Silicon Valley’s favourite stories feature grand, mostly benign futures. Of course, technology can change people, as well as the societies they build. Ursula le Guin has speculated about how societies might look when genetic engineering makes seemingly basic biological categories, like sex, fluid and malleable. Those who worry more about the perils of technology than its promises will find plenty to chew on, too. “1984” needs no introduction. Masayoshi Son, the boss of Softbank, worries about the “Singularity”, when machine intelligence exponentially exceeds the human sort and technological progress escapes all attempts at control. The term was popularised by Vernor Vinge, an American computer scientist and sci-fi author, and remains a popular topic in tech circles. Margaret Atwood has written of societies in the aftermath of technological apocalypses—although she, like Mr McEwan, resists the “sci-fi” label. Kim Stanley Robinson’s “New York 2140” is set in that city after it has been flooded by climate change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-ianmcewan&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One influential proponent of a less starry-eyed attitude to the future is William Gibson, who made his name by rejecting the togas-and-crystal-spires view common in mid-century sci-fi. His “high tech and low life” style of fiction, in which hacker gangs steal information for money and the rich grow ever more detached from the societies that sustain them, was prescient. Two of his aphorisms—that “the future is already here, it’s just not evenly distributed” and “the street finds its own use for things”—have become received wisdom for futurists. If you want to understand how those who are building the future think, ignore the snobs. Sci-fi is the place to start. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>