<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Why “The Wild Bunch” ranks among the most influential Westerns]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/18/why-the-wild-bunch-ranks-among-the-most-influential-westerns]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_BKP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T15:14:49Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 1969 three Westerns vied for supremacy. “True Grit”, the first to be released, was a nostalgic throwback. It featured a veteran star of the saddle, John Wayne, as Rooster Cogburn, a one-eyed lawman who comes out of retirement to help a precocious little girl (it won Wayne his only Oscar). “Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid”, which arrived a few months later, had a more modern sensibility. Its pair of outlaws—Paul Newman and Robert Redford, the two most watchable heartthrobs of the era—were transformed into fun-loving folk heroes; it went on to become the highest-grossing film at the American box office that year. But it was “The Wild Bunch”, released 50 years ago on June 18th 1969, which blew fist-sized holes in the genre. It was the least commercially successful film of the lot, but it did the most to change the trajectory of the Western.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the time, cowboys and gunfighters were dominating the small screen on popular shows such as “Gunsmoke”, “Bonanza”, “Rawhide” and “The Westerner” (and providing Clint Eastwood and Steve McQueen with their first glimpse of fame). But on film, the Western had begun its long &lt;em&gt;adios&lt;/em&gt; in the 1950s. “High Noon” (1950), “Shane” (1953) and “The Searchers” (1956) all charted the end of the Wild West, the arrival of civilisation and the hero’s final walk into the sunset. The Spaghetti Western briefly reinvigorated the genre with cheap, nihilistic and stylistically ambitious films, but even Sergio Leone, the maestro of the subgenre, had released the elegiac “Once Upon a Time in the West” in 1968. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ageing outlaws of “The Wild Bunch” are likewise coming to the end of the road. “We’ve got to start thinking beyond our guns,” says Pike Bishop (William Holden), as “those days are closing fast.” Pike leads his gang into one last hold-up, which turns into a massacre when they are ambushed by bounty hunters. The shootout is bloody, bizarre and indiscriminate. Along with the outlaws and lawmen, women, civilians and a tuba player are blown away or trampled by horses. There are no goodies and baddies, just violent, greedy, immoral men and innocents caught in the crossfire. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sam Peckinpah, the director, spoke of violence as “ugly, brutalising and bloody fucking awful”, but he found an aesthetic appeal in it, too. He showed blood spurting from bullet wounds in slow motion. He made use of quick cuts and cacophonous sound design to put the viewer in the middle of the horror and the excitement. The final shootout, between the four remaining members of the Bunch and a Mexican army, surpasses the first in bloody carnage, portraying an ultraviolence unseen in war films—let alone Westerns—at that time. While the movie was being shot in Mexico, Martin Luther King Jr and Bobby Kennedy were assassinated, and riots had broken out from Detroit to New Jersey. The Vietnam war had entered its deadliest period for American troops. The film’s violence reflected that of its time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peckinpah’s outlaws are neither countercultural folk heroes like Butch and Sundance nor noble old-timers like Cogburn. Early in the film Pike utters a starkly murderous command: “If they move, kill ‘em!” He pays lip service to the code of the outlaw—“when you side with a man, you stay with him. And if you can’t do that, you’re like some animal, you’re finished”—but he uses one of his group as a decoy to save his own skin, killing another when the man can’t ride a horse. Pike has alienated and betrayed other friends. In other words, he fails even by his own lax standards, let alone the moral sureties that had once underpinned the genre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The three Hollywood Westerns released the following year, in 1970—“A Man Called Horse”, “Little Big Man” and “Soldier Blue”—were similarly brutal, and they also began to unpick the racist myths that underpinned the genre. Peckinpah’s movie had set a new standard for action cinema. Drink and self-destruction would take their own toll on Peckinpah’s talent, but with “The Wild Bunch” he left an indelible bloody thumbprint on the history of cinema.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 23:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Supreme Court sinks a Republican gerrymander in Virginia]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/18/the-supreme-court-sinks-a-republican-gerrymander-in-virginia]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_USP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T17:55:24Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;CURIOUS VOTING lineups marked three of the four rulings the Supreme Court handed down on June 17th. The arrangement of justices in &lt;em&gt;Virginia House of Delegates v Bethune-Hill,&lt;/em&gt; a 5-4 decision dealing a death-blow to a racially biased gerrymander of Virginia’s state legislative map, was particularly notable. The majority opinion was written by Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg and signed by two fellow liberals, Elena Kagan and Sonia Sotomayor. But the two most conservative jurists on the court, Justices Neil Gorsuch and Clarence Thomas, rounded out the majority. The dissenting quartet comprised three conservatives and Justice Stephen Breyer, who usually votes with the liberals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The matter in &lt;em&gt;Bethune-Hill&lt;/em&gt; differs from that of two partisan gerrymandering cases set to be decided before the end of June. Those challenges,&lt;em&gt; Lamone v Benisek &lt;/em&gt;and&lt;em&gt; Rucho v Common Cause, &lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/03/28/the-supreme-court-does-not-like-gerrymandering&quot;&gt;ask&lt;/a&gt; the justices to do something they have never done: impose a limit on political parties’ efforts to entrench power by drawing district lines that guarantee them a lopsided proportion of seats in Congress or in state legislatures. The Virginia case concerns racial gerrymandering, the practice of unconstitutionally moving voters in and out of districts based on their race, which the Supreme Court has policed for decades. By scuttling a racially gerrymandered map that Republicans adopted in 2011, the Supreme Court sets the stage for a possible Democratic takeover of Virginia’s Senate and House of Delegates when Virginians vote on November 5th 2019. For Republicans, such a loss could come with interest. If the Democrats prevail, they will control the next round of redistricting in 2021 after population data from the 2020 census are reported. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The substantive legal question in &lt;em&gt;Bethune-Hill&lt;/em&gt; was whether Virginia Republicans violated the Equal Protection Clause of the Fourteenth Amendment when they packed black voters into a number of majority-minority districts. The House of Delegates claims it was only trying to comply with the Voting Rights Act of 1965 in sketching a map that allowed minorities to elect their choice of candidates. But the challengers saw the House’s target of 55% black voters in these districts as excessive and designed to dilute black voting influence in surrounding areas. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In their &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/18pdf/18-281_6j37.pdf&quot;&gt;ruling&lt;/a&gt; on June 17th, the Supreme Court did not breathe a word on the heart of the matter. Instead, the five justices in the majority dismissed the House of Delegates’ appeal on the grounds the body does not have “standing” to sue. Justice Ginsburg began by citing a clear provision of Virginia law: “[a]uthority and responsibility for representing the state’s interests in civil litigation...rest exclusively with the state’s attorney-general”. Since Mark Herring, Virginia&amp;#x27;s attorney-general, declined to appeal a lower-court ruling striking down the gerrymandered map and appointing a special master to draw up a fair replacement, the case is closed. Virginia’s House of Delegates may not open it. And as Justice Sotomayor &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/03/19/the-supreme-court-considers-a-racial-gerrymandering-challenge-in-virginia&quot;&gt;observed&lt;/a&gt; during the oral argument, the gerrymandered map, “at best”, is a product of “the legislature as a whole” or “the people of Virginia”—not of the House of Delegates alone. Justice Ginsburg used this idea to respond to the House’s second argument for standing: that the House is independently harmed by the revised electoral maps and should have the right to sue, whatever the attorney-general’s plans may be. Not so, the majority responded. Redistricting is not the sole province of the House—it is entrusted to the General Assembly as a whole, and the House is only half of that institution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his dissent, Justice Samuel Alito explained why the House of Delegates has the right to sue. It should “really go without saying”, he wrote, that changes to an electoral map “have an important impact on the overall work of the body”. If it were not for the significant effects redrawn districts have on “the composition of a legislature” and “the things that a legislature does”, legislators would not take such pains in “drawing, contesting and defending districting plans”. It is “really quite astounding”, he wrote, to “suggest otherwise”. And the question of who serves in an institution matters greatly to it: “Does a string quartet have an interest in the identity of its cellist? Does a basketball team have an interest in the identity of its point guard? Does a board of directors have an interest in the identity of its chairperson?” Clearly, the dissent concludes, “the invalidation of the House’s redistricting plan and its replacement with a court-ordered map would cause the House to suffer a ‘concrete’ injury”, the basic requirement for standing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aside from the political repercussions from the ruling in &lt;em&gt;Bethune-Hill&lt;/em&gt;—enhanced prospects for a Democratic sweep of Virginia’s General Assembly in the autumn—there are two more subtle implications. The first concerns the Supreme Court’s legitimacy. The institution has never been divorced from politics, but nomination battles over President Donald Trump’s two Supreme Court picks have cast the institution in an increasingly ideological—and partisan—light. &lt;em&gt;Bethune-Hill&lt;/em&gt; shows that justices are capable of voting against the interest of the party of the president who nominated them—at least occasionally. The ruling will give Chief Justice John Roberts something to point to when he insists (as he often does) that the justices “serve one nation”, not “one party or interest”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But by signing onto Justice Alito’s dissent, the chief will have a hard time writing or joining an opinion in &lt;em&gt;Rucho&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Lamone&lt;/em&gt; that dismisses the impact of partisanship in redistricting. In the &lt;em&gt;Rucho&lt;/em&gt; oral argument in April, Chief Justice Roberts &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/oral_arguments/argument_transcripts/2018/18-422_5hd5.pdf&quot;&gt;expressed&lt;/a&gt; scepticism that “partisan identification” is the “only basis on which people vote”. Electoral results “can change dramatically” depending on other factors, such as “the particular appeal of individual candidates” or who is at the top of the ticket. This sentiment clashes with the view in Justice Alito’s dissent that an electoral map’s lines—who votes in which district—obviously have “institutional and legislative consequences”. It isn’t clear whether the chief’s decision to sign Justice Alito’s dissent in &lt;em&gt;Bethune-Hill&lt;/em&gt; translates into a willingness to tame the gerrymander—but that mystery should be resolved in a matter of days. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 23:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[On Britain beyond Brexit and the future of Conservatism]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/bagehots-notebook/2019/06/18/on-britain-beyond-brexit-and-the-future-of-conservatism]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_BLP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T12:00:15Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE END-OF-AUSTERITY message has certainly got through to the Centre for Policy Studies (CPS). On June 10th the CPS launched “Britain Beyond Brexit”, a new collection of essays edited by George Freeman and written for the most part by fellow products of the 2010 intake of MPs. The CPS hired the biggest room in 1 George Street—a vast hall decked out with gilt paint and portraits of bearded Victorians—and provided the guests not just with decent sandwiches but also with champagne and cream-and-strawberry scones. Several leadership candidates, such as Sajid Javid and Dominic Raab, made speeches. Penny Mordaunt clucked around like a mother hen (I wonder if her decision to sit out this leadership election might prove that she’s the most sensible member of the class of 2010). Mr Freeman made great claims that his book provides the party with “a new Conservatism for a new generation” and the intellectual tools that it needs to fight the resurgent hard left.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His enthusiasm is infectious. But he claims too much. His book is more of a curate’s egg than a Viagra pill capable of reviving a flagging conservative philosophy, let alone a hand grenade aimed at the headquarters of Corbynism. In his introduction Mr Freeman rightly argues that the Conservative Party is facing a crisis of the same sort of magnitude that it faced in 1848, 1901 and 1945. The political era that was created by Thatcherism is collapsing thanks most obviously to the financial order but also to the fact that Thatcherism doesn’t offer any obvious solution to pressing problems such as over-crowded commuter trains. The various contributors also tackle issues that Conservatives have shied away from, such as the importance of devolution. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet much of the book demonstrates just how difficult it is for a party to refuel intellectually while still in government. The chapter by Matt Hancock, the health secretary, is shockingly bad: a predictable paean of praise to technological innovation bereft of interesting examples and written in a succession of clichés. (One well-read Tory commented acidly that the fact that the chapter was so bad proved that it was written by its purported author rather than by an aide.) The book as a whole is notably free of detailed discussion of subjects such as social care (the issue that killed the party in the last election) or corporate reform. The Conservative Party as a whole will have to do a lot better than this if it is to make a compelling case against a resurgent far-left Labour Party. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;****&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An excellent cover package in this week’s &lt;em&gt;New Statesman&lt;/em&gt; on “The closing of the conservative mind” (with a promise of more to come!). Robert Saunders argues that the Conservative Party has always been much more of a party of ideas than it likes to pretend: its regeneration in the 1940s and particularly in the 1980s came because of its willingness to embrace radical new thinking about the basic building blocks of society. But now in place of ideas the party has nothing but a kamikaze ideology (“Brexit or bust”) and an empty faith in markets and technology (see above). Theresa May was an idea-free zone (compare her to Lord Salisbury or Arthur Balfour). Boris Johnson, her all-but-certain successor, is no more of an intellectual despite his ability to quote Latin tags. There are a few interesting thinkers in the party such as Jesse Norman and Rory Stewart (both, worryingly, Old Etonians) but this is much more the party of Gavin Williamson, the former fireplace salesman who boasts about his lack of interest in political theory, than it is the party of these eccentric “reading men”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The point is well made. But couldn’t it equally well be applied to the Liberal mind or the Labour mind—or perhaps the Western mind in general? The Blair-Cameron-Clinton liberalism that dominated politics in the 1990s and early 2000s is exhausted. This liberalism rested on a simple formula: simply add social liberalism to economic liberalism and you have the ingredients of a good society. The more acute observers of politics always knew that this was too good to be true: Daniel Bell’s “The Cultural Contradictions of Capitalism” demonstrated that social liberalism had the potential to destroy the moral capital that forms the basis of economic liberalism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But over the past few years we have learned that if anything Mr Bell underestimated the contradictions of the position. The biggest problems facing most capitalist societies at the moment stem from the excesses of both forms of liberalism. The excesses of economic liberalism have given us giant corporations that are crushing competition and, in the case of internet companies, developing a sinister form of surveillance capitalism. The excesses of social liberalism have given us various forms of social breakdown that can be seen at their most extreme in America: record levels of broken families; an epidemic of drugs, particularly opioids; millions of men who have dropped out of the labour force and taken to a life of petty crime and binge-watching TV. It’s unfair to blame these problems on social liberalism alone. They have a lot to do with the destruction of manufacturing jobs and the legacy of slavery. But social liberalism clearly has something to do with it: the lightening of prohibitions on self-destructive behaviour leads people to make decisions which, in the long-term, can leave them either addicted to drugs or lacking the skills or self-discipline to become productive members of society. The ultimate example of the failure of the double liberalism is San Francisco, where hundreds of homeless drug addicts live on the streets—and where tech billionaires and would-be-billionaires have to dodge piles of human faeces as they walk to the latest trendy sushi joint. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then there is the Labour mind. The Labour Party has responded to the collapse of neoliberalism not by trying to produce a new progressive synthesis but by re-embracing one of the 20th century’s most blood-stained ideologies. Jeremy Corbyn—a man who makes Theresa May look like an intellectual—has surrounded himself by hard-line Marxists such as Andrew Murray and Seumas Milne who, with their public-school educations, secular fanaticism and appetite for party infighting, come straight out of the pages of David Caute’s “The Fellow-Travellers”. John McDonnell, the shadow chancellor, is clearly one of the cleverest people in parliament, with an appetite for buttressing his Trotskyism with ideas borrowed from other traditions, particularly the co-operative tradition, and an ability to use new ideas (such as taking 10% of shares into public ownership) to serve old purposes. But the fact that he’s such a vigorous walker should not blind us to the fact that he’s walking in the wrong direction and trying to lead his country over a cliff. While this band is in charge the Labour mind is not so much closed as dead. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;****&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;em&gt;New Statesman&lt;/em&gt; cover package coincides, more or less, with the publication of George Will’s new magnum opus, a 640-page study of conservatism called “The Conservative Sensibility” (Mr Will says that he chose “sensibility” rather than “mind” because “mind” was already taken, by Russell Kirk). “The Conservative Sensibility”—a torrent of philosophical musings on the great American and European conservative traditions—is proof that at least one conservative mind is still open. Mr Will still beats all his rivals in his ability to combine high thinking with a shrewd capacity to understand day-to-day American politics. The book’s reception is also proof that it’s not just conservative minds that have closed: when, as a Princeton alumnus, he addressed a group of Princeton students recently, these children of privilege decided to turn their backs on him for various unknown intellectual sins. But Mr Will’s book does also indirectly support the thesis of the closing of the conservative mind: it is hard to think of any of today’s angry young “movement” conservatives surviving in journalism for fifty years, as Mr Will has, and still having enough to say to produce a big book at 78. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 21:40:36 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“He’s never really stopped campaigning”—Trump makes it official]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/18/hes-never-really-stopped-campaigning-trump-makes-it-official]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_blm502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T11:22:14Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AMERICA&amp;#x27;S PRESIDENT&lt;/strong&gt; heads back to the Sunshine State today to announce his candidacy. What to expect this time around? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/17/muhammad-morsi-egypts-only-democratic-ruler-dies-in-court&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Muhammad Morsi&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, Egypt’s first democratically elected president, has died in court. We look back on his troubled leadership and ignominious end. And, this year’s &lt;strong&gt;Women’s World Cup&lt;/strong&gt; is drawing much more attention than past tournaments, in part because of a long-overdue reckoning about money in the sport. Runtime: 20 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/a7a69868-ebe9-4950-8d13-8bac9642d622&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 19:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Facebook wants to create a digital currency]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/18/facebook-wants-to-create-a-worldwide-digital-currency]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_wbp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A GLOBAL DIGITAL currency would make sending money across the world as easy as texting. It would do away with fees, delays and other barriers to the flow of cash. It would give those in less developed countries access to the financial system and a way to protect hard-earned wages against runaway inflation. It could trigger a wave of innovation in finance, much like the internet did in online services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That, in a nutshell, is what on June 18th Facebook promised to launch within a year. Libra, as the social network’s new currency is to be known in honour of an ancient Roman unit of mass (and the word for “pound” in many romance languages), professes to be all about “empower[ing] billions of people”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The potential is indeed enormous. If each of Facebook’s 2.4bn users converted a slice of their savings into libras, it could immediately become one of the world’s most circulated currencies. It could also, if widely adopted, vest unprecedented power in the hands of its issuer. In a tacit acknowledgment that its mishandling of user data, condoning the spread of misinformation and other sins have devalued its stock with policymakers, users and potential partners—though not investors—Facebook wants to outsource the running of Libra to a consortium of trustworthies recruited from the world of finance, technology and NGOs. The consequences for the global financial system could be far-reaching. So could the impact on Facebook’s business.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the project lives up to the mock-ups, buying, selling, holding, sending and receiving libras will be a doddle. It can be done in Facebook’s Messenger app or WhatsApp, another messaging-service-cum-social-network it owns—and, later next year, in a standalone app. All at a tap of a smartphone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far, so familiar. Messenger already offers payments to Americans. WhatsApp is testing a similar function in India. But these services do not cross borders, and require users to have a bank account. Fintech firms like TransferWise, which offer international transfers to the banked, take a 4-5% cut to wire $200—a third less than Western Union but not nothing. Libra will be global and cheap, and require no bank accounts: more bitcoin than Venmo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Except that, unlike bitcoins and other cryptocurrencies, libras will change hands in seconds, not minutes, for next to nothing, not a few dollars. The system should handle 1,000 transactions a second at its launch, and more later, compared with no more than seven a second for bitcoin. The virtual coins will be bought with real money, which will top up the reserve backing the currency. This should prevent wild price swings from bitcoin-like speculation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If it works, Libra could be a money-spinner for Facebook, albeit not directly. Notional transaction fees would not generate much revenue. But libras should allow Facebook to charge more for online ads, by making purchases of advertised products quicker and simpler. It could furnish a new source of data to target adverts, making up for user information Facebook will forgo with the “pivot to privacy”, which Mark Zuckerberg, its boss, proclaimed in March with respect to messaging. Libra would let his company catch up with WeChat, a Chinese super-app which offers payments and other financial services, and whose foreign ambitions are on hold as the Sino-American trade war rages on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technically and financially, Facebook could probably pull off such an ambitious undertaking on its own. Not politically. Its culture is more measured than it was in its early years, when it aspired to “move fast and break things”—but only a bit. Chary consumers may choose not to entrust their money to a social network which has, until recently, leaked their personal data left and right. Unless users appear on board, merchants may be reluctant to embrace the currency, however hassle-free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enter the Libra consortium. The association, to be based in reassuringly staid Geneva, will take over from Facebook before the first libra has been spent and manage the hard-currency reserves. Facebook has enlisted 28 prospective founding members out of an envisaged 100, each with equal voting rights and operating a node in a decentralised system which issues coins. They include financial firms (Visa and Stripe, among others), online services (Spotify, Uber), cryptocurrency wallets (Anchorage, Coinbase), venture capitalists (Andreessen Horowitz, Union Square Ventures) and charities (Kiva, Mercy Corps)—though, for the time being, no banks. Not a libertarian alternative to the existing financial system, in other words, but a complement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To add credibility to its promise, broken in the past, to keep social and financial data strictly separate, Facebook has created a subsidiary, Calibra, to run Libra services within its apps. It is unlikely to face hurdles to uptake from Apple or Google. It is impossible to imagine them expelling Messenger and WhatsApp—and later other providers Facebook is inviting to the open-source project—from their app stores, as they have done with other cryptocurrency offerings, many of which have turned out to be scams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To get Libra going, the consortium will pay merchants to offer discounts to customers who pay in the new currency, financed by a $10m one-off fee each member pays for a seat at the table. Eventually, Facebook would like anybody, not just the consortium, to be able to generate the currency, move it and offer services on top of its “blockchain” (crypto-speak for the database that keeps track of who owns what). At that point, Libra would truly turn into Bitcoin, minus the kinks and the libertarianism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hard currency&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;With a project with so many moving parts, much can go wrong. Although Facebook says it has a working prototype, the technology is untested; sceptics doubt that a 100-node system, let alone a bigger one, could process thousands of transactions per second. Hackers are doubtless champing at the bit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then there are consortium dynamics. Facebook will have to prove to the other 99 Libra members that it is truly prepared to give up control. At the same time, because important decisions need a two-thirds majority, someone has to knock heads together. The history of information technology is littered with initiatives which collapsed under the weight of internal conflict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The biggest barrier may be political. Facebook has apparently consulted many regulators. Initially they should be able to keep tabs on Libra. The providers of digital wallets will have to comply with national rules, like those against money-laundering. Calibra, whose integration into Messenger and WhatsApp will initially make it the dominant wallet, is bound to stoke competition concerns. These may recede as the currency grows bigger and more decentralised, only to be replaced by worries about financial stability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Libra’s success, then, is far from assured. But it could prove useful even if it flops, for it offers a blueprint for how Facebook itself could one day be governed. The Libra Association’s main task is to oversee the blockchain, ensuring, for instance, that Calibra does not enjoy privileged access to it. An equivalent Facebook Association, some observers have ventured, could be composed of representatives of users, advertisers, data-protection authorities and so on. Their job could be to oversee the “social graph”, another database, which lists all of Facebook’s users and the links between them—and to guarantee that Facebook users can post to another social network and vice versa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Calls for a Facebook constitution along these lines have grown louder as the social network’s influence on world affairs, from election-meddling in America to genocide in Myanmar, has become apparent. Mr Zuckerberg is no stranger to such thinking. In 2009 Facebook let users vote on big changes in its privacy policies but abandoned the experiment with global democracy a few years later. Last year Mr Zuckerberg announced that Facebook wanted to set up a “content review board” of independent experts—a kind of “Supreme Court”, in his words, which would make “the final judgment call on what should be acceptable speech”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asked whether Libra could serve as a model for Facebook, David Marcus, who is in charge of the project, replies that it marks “a coming of age, the moment we recognise that there are some things that we shouldn’t control—and a radical departure from the traditional way of operating things”. Perhaps. But checks and balances would almost certainly make Facebook less profitable. It would be ironic if a new digital currency marked the beginning of the end of Facebook’s money-minting days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 19:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Muhammad Morsi, Egypt’s only democratic ruler, dies in court]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/17/muhammad-morsi-egypts-only-democratic-ruler-dies-in-court]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_blp905.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-17T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE cases against Muhammad Morsi, now in their sixth year, long ago took on the air of a Kafka novel. Every few weeks Egypt’s sole democratically-elected president, deposed in a coup in 2013, would appear in court to answer one charge or another. He was accused of espionage and torture, and of stealing livestock. Most Egyptians lost interest, but the wheels of Egyptian justice, a deeply flawed variety, ground on. And then, abruptly, they stopped. Shortly after 6pm on June 17th state television reported that Mr Morsi had died of a heart attack during a court session. He was 67.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Born in the Nile Delta, Mr Morsi trained as an engineer and finished his PhD in America. He returned to Egypt in 1985 and took up a university post in Sharqia governorate, where he had grown up. For the next 15 years he was an academic and a high-climbing member of the Muslim Brotherhood, the Islamist group that was then banned but tolerated by Hosni Mubarak’s government. In 2000 he was elected to parliament—as an independent, since the Brotherhood was not allowed to field candidates. He served only one term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was an unlikely CV for the man who would emerge as Egypt’s president after Mr Mubarak was toppled in the Arab spring of 2011. Indeed, Mr Morsi was not even the Brotherhood’s first choice. The group wanted to run its deputy leader, Khairat al-Shater, a wealthy and well-known businessman. But the army decided that a recent prison term made him ineligible to compete. Mr Morsi was a compromise option—uncharismatic, perhaps, but a trusted member of the group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Egyptian liberals, who split their vote during the election’s first round, did not share Mr Morsi’s Islamist politics, but he seemed the democratic choice, a break from the old regime. Many held their noses and voted for him in the run-off in June 2012 against Ahmed Shafiq, Mr Mubarak’s last prime minister. After his victory was confirmed, Mr Morsi’s first act was to address a crowd in Tahrir Square, the heart of the revolution. There he awkwardly unbuttoned his jacket to show the crowd that he was not wearing a bulletproof vest—a man-of-the-people gesture that he hoped would endear him to the nation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The goodwill was short-lived. Mr Morsi and his allies never got a grip on Egypt’s factious state. From the start the army undermined him, while the intelligence services worked to bring him down. The Mubarak-era courts became a major source of opposition: judges dissolved parliament, in which the Brotherhood held a plurality, and repeatedly blocked Mr Morsi’s efforts to schedule a new election. In November 2012 the president issued a decree that shielded his decisions from judicial review. Anti-Morsi protesters who surrounded his palace were soon attacked by Brotherhood supporters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His edict, and the violence that followed, caused a lasting rupture with the revolutionaries who helped put Mr Morsi in office. When the army removed him in July 2013—led by his hand-picked defence minister, Abdel-Fattah al-Sisi—many were happy to see him go. Even the killing of hundreds of pro-Morsi protesters the following month, a massacre unprecedented in Egypt’s modern history, drew only muted public criticism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Brotherhood is again banned, and now not even tolerated. Once a strict hierarchy, it is no longer a coherent organisation, its leaders crammed into heaving jails or exiled to Doha, Istanbul and European capitals. Nor is there any other source of opposition. In April Egyptians approved constitutional amendments that allow Mr Sisi (now the president) to rule until 2030. An engineer named Ahmed Badawi held a one-man protest on a Cairo street. He was swiftly arrested. Mr Morsi’s death might provide a rallying point for Mr Sisi’s foes. The interior ministry put its forces on alert, and police will surely round up some Brotherhood supporters as a “preventive” measure. But it is unclear whether there is anyone with the standing to lead protests, nor Egyptians willing to risk the consequences of joining them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three hours after Mr Morsi died Egypt’s public prosecutor, acting with unusual alacrity, published a report on his death. Unsurprisingly, it found no signs of mistreatment, so no reason to blame the state. But Mr Morsi’s family had long worried about his health. He was held in solitary confinement in Tora prison, notorious for its grim conditions. Human Rights Watch, a pressure group based in New York, alleges that the diabetic ex-president received inadequate medical care. During a court session he hinted that guards were trying to poison his food. Concerned British lawmakers tried to visit him in prison last year. Amr Darrag, a former minister in Mr Morsi’s government, calls his death “tantamount to state-sponsored murder”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Morsi’s final years are a stark contrast with those of his predecessor, a man who misruled Egypt for 30 years. Mr Mubarak faced his own trial after the revolution. He was held not in Tora prison but in a military hospital in a pleasant Cairo suburb. With the cases against him now dismissed, he is enjoying a peaceful retirement. Mr Morsi was a poor president. But he was the only popularly-elected one in Egypt’s long history. It is a tragic coda for Egypt’s revolution that he spent his final years rotting alone in a cell, his death almost a footnote in a country that long ago slid back into dictatorship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 05:40:27 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Greenland ice sheet is melting unusually fast]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/17/the-greenland-ice-sheet-is-melting-unusually-fast]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_woc543.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;GREENLAND’S misnomer is the result of a marketing campaign by Erik the Red who wished to attract Viking settlers to its icy landscape. Little did he know that the land had been covered in lush forests many millennia before he was born. Nor could he have fathomed that, a millennium after his death, the vast ice sheet would be in rapid retreat.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ice atop Greenland holds enough water to raise global sea levels by more than seven metres, should it all melt and run off into the oceans. For this reason, climate scientists closely monitor its seasonal trends, and in particular how quickly it melts in the spring leading up to the late summer “ice minimum”, after which it starts to grow again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest data shows that the area of melting ice this year is unusually high. On June 12th 712,000 square kilometres of the ice-sheet (over 40% of the total) were melting. This is well outside the norm for the past 40 years (see chart).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several factors are to blame. First, a natural cycle known as the North Atlantic Oscillation is encouraging ice-melt. Then there is long-term warming driven by rising greenhouse-gas emissions. Third, climate change has also weakened the jet stream, allowing a warm and humid weather system to settle over northeastern Greenland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a result, the seasonal ice melt began two weeks early. According to data published on the Polar Portal, a Danish climate-research website, Greenland is currently losing 3bn tonnes of ice every day, roughly three times the average for mid-June in 1981-2010.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The extent of the melting is not entirely unprecedented for this time of year. Researchers have seen similar events in 2002, 2007 and 2012. Each portended a record low at the end of the summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although a switch in the weather could still turn things around, the early melt will result in darker snow and ice, which absorb more sunlight and hastens the melting process, says Thomas Mote of the US National Snow and Ice Data Centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If this year is anything like 2012 [which set the current record for ice melt], then we will get in the region of 1mm of sea-level rise in one year just from Greenland,” says Jason Box, a professor at the Geological Survey of Denmark and Greenland. The oceans are rising by 3.3mm each year because of global warming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greenland may not be green, yet, but it is far less icy than in Erik’s time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 05:40:26 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lee Krasner’s colourful, creative destruction]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/17/lee-krasners-colourful-creative-destruction]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_BKP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-17T17:23:26Z&quot;&gt;Jun 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 1951 Lee Krasner hosted a show of her large, brightly coloured geometric paintings at a gallery in New York. Critics liked it, but the paintings didn’t sell. Distraught, Krasner began working on a series of even bigger pieces—black-and-white drawings that spanned from floor to ceiling—but she decided she hated them, and tore them to pieces. When she returned to the studio a few weeks later, she was surprised. All of a sudden, she said, she saw “a lot of things there that began to interest me”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She collaged the torn-up drawings onto the colourful canvases from her gallery show. She added more paint, burlap, fragments of newspaper and bits of discarded paintings by her husband, Jackson Pollock. The resulting works, unveiled at an exhibit in 1955, were inventive and evoked the chaos of nature. They marked the beginning of a process which Krasner would often use: the dismantling of old work to make something new.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Lee Krasner: Living Colour”, a retrospective of the artist’s work at the Barbican Centre—and the first major show of her work in Europe in more than 50 years—explores these cycles of destruction and regeneration. It traces her development from art student in New York to prominent abstract expressionist, moving deftly through periods in her painting such as her “Little Drawings” (small canvases packed with colour, texture and hieroglyph-like forms) and what a friend called her “Night Journeys” (massive explosive paintings in umber made in the wake of Pollock’s death). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exhibition demonstrates Krasner’s great skill as a colourist, and how much of her work is rooted in nature. Two of her early self-portraits, created as a student, featured plants. After her father’s death Krasner struggled to paint until she moved out to Springs, Long Island, in 1945 and started observing the outside world. Among the flowers and leaves and birds, a creative impulse began to come through, realised on vibrant, small canvases thick with textured paint and in two marvellous mosaic tables made out of wagon wheels, studded with bits of glass, coins, keys and plastics. The visitor can glimpse her startling creativity, her adeptness with bits and pieces, and the interplay between order and chaos, all of which would feature in her later paintings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her range is impressive, too. Krasner could do the monumental canvases for which abstract expressionists are best known. For example, in deft strokes of red and white “Another Storm” (1963) evokes the movement of butterflies. She could also work with smaller forms. A side-room is devoted largely to Krasner’s watercolours, calligraphic works of bright hues that are also explorations of negative space. These intimate works are as arresting as the large canvases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a cliché to say that Krasner “lived in Jackson’s Pollock’s shadow”—a phrase which appeared in her obituary in the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; in 1984 and has been repeated over and over in reviews of the current show, 35 years later. It is also not really true: the bulk of Krasner’s major artworks were created before her 11-year marriage, or after Pollock’s death. She was respected by critics in the 1950s and 1960s, and internationally recognised in her lifetime (though it took longer for her to earn that acclaim than for many of the men she worked alongside; a documentary shown at the end of the exhibit highlights both the force of her personality and the institutional misogyny she faced). “Lee Krasner: Living Colour” is a celebration of her creative life, and one which does not require constant references to her marriage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, the visitor emerges from this exhibition wondering whether she was a better painter than her spouse; she was certainly a more inventive one. In 1974 she rediscovered drawings that she had made while a student of Hans Hofmann, an influential painter, and promptly cut them up. Hofmann was known to be strict, sometimes tearing up his students’ drawings, so the deliberate act of slicing with scissors provided a kind of childish delight. But the resulting works were revelatory: 11 canvases arranged with angular slices of her former self. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The past, for Krasner, wasn’t something to preserve or revere—it was something that ran through the present, something to play with in paint. “All my work keeps going like a pendulum; it seems to swing back to something I was involved with earlier, or it moves between horizontality and verticality, circularity or a composite of them,” she said. “For me, I suppose that change is the only constant.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Lee Krasner: Living Colour” continues at the Barbican Centre in London until September 1st&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 02:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The race to become Britain’s next PM]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/17/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HERESA MAY&lt;/small&gt; stepped down as leader of the Conservative Party on June 7th, but she will remain as prime minister until her successor is chosen. The first round of voting took place on June 13th; Boris Johnson topped the ballot of Tory MPs, with Jeremy Hunt a distant second and Michael Gove third. Three candidates, Andrea Leadsom, Mark Harper and Esther McVey, failed to get enough votes to go through to the next round and Matt Hancock pulled out on June 14th. The remaining six candidates will go through to the second round of voting, which is scheduled for June 18th. After further votes MPs will then send two names to party members, who will make the final choice. The result of their vote will be announced before Parliament rises for summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Betfair Exchange, a gambling website, has been tracking punters’ predictions on the next Tory leader. According to the wisdom of the betting crowd, a handful of candidates stand out. But there is only one clear frontrunner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anne McElvoy, host of &lt;i&gt;The Economist asks&lt;/i&gt;, spoke to Jeremy Hunt and Rory Stewart about their leadership plans: &lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-whocanleadbritainthroughbrexit-&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.betfair.com/exchange/plus/politics&quot;&gt;Betfair Exchange&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 20:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“It’s been an astonishing weekend”—Hong Kong’s shocking U-turn]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/17/its-been-an-astonishing-weekend-hong-kongs-shocking-u-turn]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_blm501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-17T11:23:08Z&quot;&gt;Jun 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALLS FOR the resignation of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/china/2019/06/15/hong-kongs-leader-backs-down-over-controversial-extradition-bill&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carrie Lam&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the territory’s leader, are intensifying. Hong Kongers may have put a recent freedom-crimping bill on ice, but more challenges to their independence await. We speak to the mother of a child &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.1843magazine.com/features/the-curse-of-genius&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;genius&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; who reveals the private agony of being an exceedingly clever kid. And a new podcast in &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/06/06/latin-is-dead-yet-it-also-lives-on&quot;&gt;Latin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; gets our columnist thinking about language evolution and resurrection. Runtime: 23 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/lamtotheslaughter-hongkong-sshockingu-turn&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 18:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>