<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Why Margrethe Vestager ticks all the boxes]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/charlemagnes-notebook/2019/05/28/why-margrethe-vestager-ticks-all-the-boxes]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-28T14:11:00Z&quot;&gt;May 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Editor’s note: This piece has been updated following the European Parliament elections on May 23rd-26th. &lt;/b&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPEAN POLITICS is turning more febrile after voters in elections for the European Parliament broke the old duopoly of the two main political “families”: the centre-right European People’s Party (EPP) and old centre-left Socialists and Democrats (S&amp;amp;D).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two “big tent” groups, which have dominated the parliament since direct elections were introduced in 1979, were the biggest losers as European politics fragments. By the latest count, the two groups between them lost 87 seats in the 751-seat parliament. That, in turn, is re-opening the debate about who should run the European Commission, the powerful bureaucratic machine at the heart of the European Union, which acts as an executive, a civil service and a market regulator. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The president of the commission is nominated by national leaders, with approval from the parliament. Leaders will meet in Brussels tonight to begin discussing who should fill this and a host of senior EU jobs, among them the president of the European Council (representing leaders) and the president of the European Central Bank (ECB).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the last European elections in 2014, the parliament tried to institutionalise the idea of the Spitzenkandidat, whereby leaders would be compelled to choose the “leading candidate” for commission president selected by the parliament on the basis of who can command a majority. Under a gentleman&amp;#x27;s agreement in 2014, the S&amp;amp;D made way for Jean-Claude Juncker of the EPP, whose group was the largest. The leaders acquiesced despite misgivings by Britain and Hungary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The EPP insists that, as the largest parliamentary group (which still counts 180 seats), it should have the right again to nominate its candidate—in this case Manfred Weber, the German who leads the EPP’s parliamentary group. But foisting him on leaders will be harder this time around. To begin with, Mr Weber has no executive experience, unlike Mr Juncker, a veteran prime minister of Luxembourg. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, Emmanuel Macron, the French president, is determined to halt Mr Weber and the whole Spitzenkadidat process. To do so, he is enlisting the support Pedro Sánchez, António Costa and Mark Rutte, the prime ministers of Spain, Portugal and the Netherlands respectively. Angela Merkel, the German chancellor who secured the job for Mr Juncker last time around, nominally supports Mr Weber. But she is less dominant than she used to be, and will probably not back Mr Weber at any cost; some think she is more interested in placing a hawk at the head of the ECB.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But perhaps the biggest problem for Mr Weber is that the EPP’s cosy deals with the S&amp;amp;D (the two groups share the presidency of the parliament on a rotating basis) can no longer be easily imposed on others. The S&amp;amp;D backs Frans Timmermans, a former Dutch foreign minister serving as first vice-president of the commission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Alliance of Liberals and Democrats for Europe (ALDE), which gained 42 seats for a total of 109, also refuses to endorse Mr Weber. The Greens, who also made big gains, are critical as well. And various Eurosceptic nationalist and populist groups, notably the European Alliance of People and Nations, led by Matteo Salvini, Italy’s right-wing deputy prime minister, are determined to break the mould of European politics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Mr Weber is blocked, who else might become the commission’s president? Some are pushing for an alternative EPP figure, Michel Barnier, a former French foreign minister who ably held the 27 European states united in the negotiations with Britain over Brexit. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the case for Margrethe Vestager, the powerful competition commissioner, is growing. She ticks many of the boxes needed for a successful candidate: she can get things done, she is acceptable to the centre-right EPP and the S&amp;amp;D. More important, is championed by the Liberals and Greens, whose votes will be needed for a majority. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Vestager has served as education, interior and economy minister of Denmark, despite belonging to a small social liberal party. As a commissioner since 2014 she has applied both a liberal sense of consumer rights and an interventionist commitment to defending the little guy to the task of regulating technology giants. She has taken on tax dodgers, infringers of personal privacy and market distorters. Thrusting machos from Silicon Valley have turned up in her office berating her and come off the worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The EU in 2019 faces an array of security and economic threats. It needs a powerful, efficient leader with experience of the commission and a sense of how the world is changing. It needs a leader who can stand up for Europe and initiate legislation defending its citizens. It needs someone acceptable to left and right, north and south. Many candidates will put their names forward. Ms Vestager ticks a lot of boxes. Europe would be foolish to overlook her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 21:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Fragmentation is the main trend”—Europe&#x27;s elections]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/28/fragmentation-is-the-main-trend-europes-elections]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_blm501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-28T11:30:17Z&quot;&gt;May 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPE&amp;#x27;S VOTERS have shown they are not happy with traditional political parties. But even as the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/27/the-conservatives-and-labour-take-a-bashing-in-britains-european-election&quot;&gt;Brexit Party&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; surged in Britain, populists across the continent found elections to the European Parliament tougher than expected. And despite being &amp;quot;asset-light&amp;quot;, some &lt;strong&gt;tech companies need &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/11/how-real-estate-barons-have-ridden-the-tech-boom&quot;&gt;property&lt;/a&gt; to keep expanding&lt;/strong&gt;. That’s good news for the right real-estate investment funds. Also, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/25/big-agribusiness-wants-to-make-quinoa-more-mainstream&quot;&gt;quinoa&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; is the grain getting a new lease of life. Runtime: 20 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/continentalbreakfast-europeanelections&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 20:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why managers should listen to shareholders]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/27/why-managers-should-listen-to-shareholders]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_blp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-27T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 27th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ARTHUR BALFOUR was a British prime minister who did not think much of his party members. “I’d rather take advice from my valet than from the Conservative Party conference,” he said. Corporate executives, particularly in America, seem to take a similar attitude towards their shareholders, believing that, like children, they should be seen but definitely not heard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maybe managers should get their fingers out of their ears and start listening to their investors. That is the conclusion of a recent paper* by Clifford Holderness of the Carroll School of Management at Boston College.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In America and a few other countries, boards can issue additional shares without shareholder approval. In some countries, shareholders must approve issuance above a certain threshold. And in yet others, investors must agree before any new stock can be created. So what happens to a company’s share price when new shares are issued? Mr Holderness performed a meta-analysis of more than 100 studies of stock reactions around the world. He found that, when shareholders approved issuance in advance, the price tended to rise by an average of 2%. But when managers issued stock without shareholder approval, the share price declined by an average of 2%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The simplest explanation for this differential lies in the agent-principal conflict between executives and investors. As Mr Holderness writes, if agency conflicts did not exist, “shareholder voting on equity issuance should not matter.” However, managers may want to issue shares to fund expansion of the company, allowing them to control more assets and demand a higher salary. Investors, meanwhile, may worry about the impact of such expansion on long-term returns and dislike the dilution of their control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another sign of agent-principal conflicts are shares that are privately placed with selected investors or used to pay for takeovers. In Australia, any offering of more than 15% of the equity must be subject to shareholder approval; in America, the threshold is 20%. In both countries, there is a clustering of share issuance just below the limit; managers go out of their way to avoid asking for approval. In April Occidental Petroleum promised $10bn worth of preferred shares to Berkshire Hathaway, Warren Buffett’s conglomerate, should the oil company’s bid for Anadarko, a rival, succeed. This injection helped it avoid asking shareholders to authorise the Anadarko deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This disdain for shareholders’ views contradicts the ethos of American capitalism. The system works, it is usually argued, because companies respond to shareholder pressure and because broad share ownership gives everyone, including workers, a stake in the American dream. One of the reasons for the success of the private-equity model is that investors enjoy greater scrutiny over what managers do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But when it comes to public companies, shareholders tend to be treated like an awkward uncle at a family gathering. Their only rights are to sell their shares or to vote against the reappointment of directors. In any other field, this would be extraordinary. Imagine you appointed a letting agent to look after your house and they decided to spend lots of your money on gold taps and chandeliers. When you complain, they respond that you are only entitled to sell the house, or fire them at the end of their contract.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Managers have long grumbled that shareholders want to interfere too much. A new complaint is that socially conscious investors may insist that firms concentrate on non-financial factors, like treating workers better or cutting emissions. This concern seems ill-founded. For example, research** shows that companies voted the “best to work for” produce superior subsequent long-term returns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More generally, the majority of metastudies have found that companies with better ESG (environmental, social and governance) records improved their financial performance. Mr Holderness’s work puts the tin lid on the argument that managers should ignore investors. When it comes to shareholders, managers should remember the words of Diogenes: “We have two ears and one tongue so that we would listen more and talk less.”&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* “Equity issuances and agency costs: The telling story of shareholder approval around the world”, &lt;em&gt;Journal of Financial Economics&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;** “Employee Satisfaction, Labor Market Flexibility, and Stock Returns Around the World”, by Alex Edmans, Lucius Li and Chendi Zhang, European Corporate Governance Institute Working Paper 433&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 17:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The world ahead: food for thought]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/27/the-world-ahead-food-for-thought]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/the_world_ahead_podcast_banner_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-27T18:30:25Z&quot;&gt;May 27th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AFTER THE successful &lt;strong&gt;stockmarket flotation of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/01/can-the-veggie-burger-company-change-eating-habits-before-it-goes-bust&quot;&gt;Beyond Meat&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, maker of the Beyond Burger, we assess the potential impact of meat substitutes on &lt;strong&gt;global meat consumption&lt;/strong&gt;. Also, is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/china/2019/05/04/space-themed-tourism-is-taking-off-in-china&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;space tourism&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; about to take off? And what can be done to preserve &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/02/21/the-surprising-revival-of-the-hawaiian-language&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;indigenous languages&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; for future generations. Tom Standage hosts. Runtime: 22 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theworldahead/theworldahead-foodforthought&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 07:40:30 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fiat Chrysler seeks a merger with Renault]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/27/fiat-chrysler-seeks-a-merger-with-renault]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_blp905_facebook.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-27T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 27th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE RISE of the SUV over the past decade demonstrates that carmakers have done an excellent job of persuading customers that bigger is better. Renault and Fiat Chrysler Automobiles (whose chairman, John Elkann, sits on the board of &lt;em&gt;The Economist’&lt;/em&gt;s parent company) are hoping to convince investors that the same is true of carmakers themselves. On May 27th the Italian-American FCA confirmed rumours that it was seeking a merger with its French counterpart, itself part of a close alliance with Japan’s Nissan and Mitsubishi. If a deal goes ahead it will create an automotive colossus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Together, the two companies currently sell nearly 9m cars a year for €170bn ($190bn), generating an operating profit of around €10bn. That alone would put the combined firm in third place behind only Toyota and Volkswagen (VW), each of which produces around 10m cars annually. Add in Renault’s alliance partners, however, and the new group’s combined total of 15m cars would leave everyone else in the dust.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The putative deal can be seen as the legacy of two fallen giants of carmaking. Sergio Marchionne, FCA’s storied boss who died last year, had called for consolidation of the mass market, where slender profits are partly the result of duplicated investment in similar technologies such as engines that do little to differentiate brands. FCA has long displayed a “for sale” sign on its windscreen. The architect of the Renault-Nissan-Mitsubishi alliance, Carlos Ghosn, had his plans for world domination stymied by his arrest and detention in Japan on charges of financial wrongdoing at Nissan (he denies the charges). Mr Ghosn had previously invited FCA to join the alliance, to no avail. Both Marchionne and Mr Ghosn would no doubt have coveted the driver’s seat of the merged firm. Neither Mike Manley, FCA’s newish chief executive, nor Thierry Bolloré, his counterpart at Renault, seems to possess their predecessors’ rampant egos that may have prevented a deal in the past.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The combination of the two firms looks good on paper. The scale that Marchionne talked about and Mr Ghosn built through his Franco-Japanese alliance was a sensible reaction to the challenges of the industry. It helps firms ride out economic downturns and spread investments in electric vehicles (EVs), self-driving cars and mobility services (such as ride-hailing and car-sharing beloved of younger car users) across more vehicles. FCA estimates that joint development of engines, EVs and platforms on which all cars are built will save €5bn a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two firms also plug gaps in each other’s businesses both geographically and in terms of products. FCA’s strength and profits come from America and Renault’s from Europe. The French firm’s cheap models and EV know-how will complement FCA’s pick-ups and premium brands such as Jeep, Alfa Romeo and Maserati.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Can the tie-up defy the patchy history of automotive megadeals? The list of failures is long: Daimler and Chrysler, BMW and Rover, GM and Fiat, anything to do with Ford. Both FCA and Renault-Nissan-Mitsubishi have succeeded in part thanks to those exceptional former bosses, and partly because they avoided full-blown integration. FCA has flourished because Fiat and Chrysler have remained largely apart. So have component parts of Renault-Nissan-Mitsubishi, a looser structure which falls short of a full merger but whose pace of cost savings has been sluggish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;FCA makes it clear that its deal is with Renault but also that it sees “significant expected benefits to all parties from the expanded partnership”. That partnership is looking creaky in the aftermath of Mr Ghosn’s arrest, which he claims was orchestrated by Nissan in order to prevent his plans for a full merger. Nissan denies this. Nissan may also be reluctant to continue collaborating with Renault once it merges with FCA, which competes with the Japanese firm in America&amp;#x27;s lucrative pick-up market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Running an alliance that makes 15m cars would also be hard. Mr Ghosn claimed, with some justification, that he alone had the skills to run an unwieldy entity that churned out 10m cars a year. After Marchionne’s death such boasts rang even truer. The difficulties of VW, with its garage-ful of brands, suggest that it does take a special talent. The deal, to be structured as a 50-50 partnership in proportion to existing stakes in either firm, would hand the largest single stake to Exor, the investment vehicle of Fiat’s founding Agnelli family which controls FCA through a 29% stake. The French state, which owns 15% of Renault, will apparently give up its double voting rights and accept a board made up mainly of independent directors (FCA has promised that no factories will close, in France or elsewhere).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Renault’s board, which was due to meet on May 27th, still has to sign off on the deal. So do competition authorities in Europe and America. And if scale at the top of the industry moves from 10m to 15m cars a year, will others seek to replicate it? Ford and VW are in a partnership that some say could tighten. PSA, which makes Peugeots and Citroëns, is open to offers. China’s government is perpetually rumoured to be planning a merger of its biggest state-run firms. Messrs Ghosn and Marchionne may be out of the running, but their dream rides on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 02:40:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Increasing access to abortions may have reduced America’s crime rate]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/27/increasing-access-to-abortions-may-have-reduced-americas-crime-rate]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_woc138.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-27T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 27th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ANTI-ABORTION POLICIES are on the rise in America. Influenced mainly by objections from religious conservatives, legislators in states such as Georgia, Ohio and Alabama have passed new laws limiting the practice. In some instances, the new regulations go so far as to ban abortions even in cases of rape or incest—a measure supported by just 11% of voters, according to Morning Consult, a pollster. Restricting access to abortions means that more parents who don’t want to raise children would be forced to do so. Recent research suggests this could reverse decades of progress made on curbing crime in America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a paper published in 2001, the economists John Donahue and Steven Levitt credited the legalisation of abortion across America with much of the subsequent reduction in crime in the country. They argued that violent crime in states where abortion had been banned before 1973 was 15-25% rarer in 1997 than it would have been had abortion remained illegal. The study was politically explosive, and widely criticised. Many sceptical scholars sought to poke holes in its methods, including one group who discovered an “inadvertent but serious computer programming error” (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2005/12/01/oops-onomics&quot;&gt;see article&lt;/a&gt;) underlying its findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly two decades later, Messrs Donahue and Levitt have returned to the subject, and present new evidence that bolsters their original claim. In a new working paper circulated by the National Bureau of Economic Research, they attribute a whopping 45 percentage points of the total 50% decline in crime since 1990 to legal abortion. Their primary evidence is that crime fell much faster in states where more abortions were performed than it did in those where the procedure was rarer. In the early 1990s violent crime was about 50% more common in states with relatively high abortion levels than it was in those where abortion was infrequent. By 2014, crime rates in the two groups of states had converged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors argue that this statistical association reflects an underlying causal relationship. Armed with a cache of annual state-level data on abortions, crime rates and other factors—including economic conditions, welfare payments, access to firearms and alcohol consumption—they seek to isolate the impact of abortion on violent crime, after controlling for other variables that also affect crime rates. With all other factors held constant, they find that an increase in the abortion rate of 100 per 100,000 births leads to a 10-20% reduction in crime. Past studies have also shown that children born to women who wanted an abortion but did not receive one were much more likely to become criminals and had poorer life prospects than those who were born to parents ready and willing to raise them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 23:40:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Conservatives and Labour take a bashing in Britain’s European election]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/27/the-conservatives-and-labour-take-a-bashing-in-britains-european-election]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_blp904.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-27T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 27th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE ONLY fair conclusion from the European election in Britain is that the country is still split down the middle over Brexit. On a total turnout of around 37%, slightly higher than in 2014, Nigel Farage’s new Brexit Party was the biggest winner, taking some 32% of the vote and 28 seats. Adding in the remnant UK Independence Party took the two clearest pro-Brexit parties to a vote share of 35%. Mr Farage immediately claimed that voters were telling politicians that they wanted Brexit to happen without a deal on October 31st, the current departure date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet if strong Leavers had a good night, so did strong Remainers. The Liberal Democrats got 20% of the vote, giving them 15 seats, and the Green Party 12% of the vote and seven seats. Adding in the new Change UK party, which had a bad night, and the Scottish and Welsh nationalists takes the combined score of pro-Remain and pro-second-referendum parties to almost 40%, well ahead of the two pro-no-deal parties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The biggest losers in the election were the Conservatives and Labour. The combined vote share of what are traditionally known as the two main parties fell to just 23%, down from 82% in the 2017 general election and less than half their share in the previous European one. The Tories had a truly shocking night. Their vote collapsed to just 9% and they won only three seats. Clearly many Tory voters, disappointed that Brexit has not happened yet, so necessitating this election, deserted to back Mr Farage’s Brexit Party (while many Tory Remainers fled to the Liberal Democrats).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Labour did only a little better, with 14% of the vote and ten seats. The party suffered from what voters saw as its ambiguous position on Brexit, with insufficient clarity over whether it wants a second referendum or which side it would support if there were one. Its leader, Jeremy Corbyn, promised to reflect on the result and hinted more strongly than before that he might come round more explicitly to supporting another Brexit referendum, though not all his advisers agree.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bigger question is what impact this election will have on the contest to succeed Theresa May as Tory leader and prime minister, which will formally get under way on June 10th. Some Conservative MPs were quick to conclude that the party must now embrace a no-deal Brexit, so as to fend off Mr Farage. His strong showing should thus boost the leadership hopes of the frontrunner, Boris Johnson, who has promised that Brexit will happen on October 31st with or without a deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet other Tories remain fearful of the consequences of crashing out of the European Union without a deal in October. They say there is no sign that Brussels will agree to make any big concessions to an incoming pro-Brexit prime minister, which might mean that it will be necessary to ask for a further extension of the Brexit deadline. Rory Stewart, another leadership candidate, has already said that he would not serve under Mr Johnson if the latter embraced no-deal. Other Tories think the same.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So if a new Tory leader seeks to outdo Mr Farage by backing a no-deal Brexit, he or she may be unable to secure a parliamentary majority. And that brings the country back where it started: still sharply divided over Brexit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 19:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Populists fall short of expectations in the European elections]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/charlemagnes-notebook/2019/05/26/populists-fall-short-of-expectations-in-the-european-elections]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_blp903.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-26T22:26:45Z&quot;&gt;May 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THAT right-wing populism has gained ground in Europe in recent years is a well-established fact. A glance at the continent&amp;#x27;s recent electoral history shows that much: the Lega dominates Italy’s politics, Marine Le Pen made it to the run-off of the French presidential election in 2017, Law and Justice (PiS) runs Poland and elsewhere smaller parties from Alternative for Germany to the Danish People’s Party and Vox in Spain are shaping their countries’ politics. All of which is a far cry from the settled European party landscape of 15 or 20 years ago. But that much is known. The question now is: in what direction is European politics moving and at what pace?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This evening’s result in the European elections provides some answers to that, and caveat the more excitable commentaries about the rise of nationalists in Europe. Turnout is up for the first time ever, and at 51% higher than in any European election since 1994. And yes, the right-populists have done well again. The Lega is first in Italy, Ms Le Pen’s National Rally has narrowly beaten Emmanuel Macron to first place in France, PiS came first in Poland despite running against a mostly unified opposition ticket. But it is also clear that the mighty, breakneck populist surge of a couple of years ago—with Britain voting to leave the EU, populists topping polls all over the continent and a cataclysmic nationalist takeover threatening—is over. Nationalists are now consolidating their gains and settling into a much broader pattern: that of fragmentation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consider the numbers. Ms Le Pen’s result is down on 2014, the previous European election. So is the Austrian Freedom Party and, more drastically, the Danish People’s Party and the Party for Freedom in the Netherlands. It is true that some of the latter’s support has switched to Forum for Democracy, a rival right-populist outfit. But this too underperformed expectations and the overall seat-share of Dutch Eurosceptics has halved. Alternative for Germany also disappointed its boosters: on 10.8% it only modestly increased its support on 2014 and did less well than in the 2017 Bundestag election. The Lega has made big gains, but it too seems to have done worse than was generally expected and its wins only just make up for losses elsewhere. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall the three Eurosceptic or hard-right groups in the European Parliament have, according to the parliament’s own projection, increased their seat share from 21% to 23%. Hardly a surge and oddly static after five years that have seen Europe face a migration crisis, the Brexit vote, terror attacks and the wholesale fragmentation of the continent’s politics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of that fragmentation there was much more evidence. The Green group is projected to swell in size from 52 seats to 70 seats, thanks especially to the German Green party’s 21% showing (taking second place and overtaking the doughty Social Democrats to become the largest party on the German left). The centrist Alliance of Liberals and Democrats for Europe will grow from 69 to a projected 101 seats, with Mr Macron’s Renaissance joining and immediately becoming its largest member. Meanwhile the two big losers are the big-tent party families that have together run Europe as an informal “grand coalition”: the centre-right European People’s Party (EPP) and the centre-left Socialists and Democrats (S&amp;amp;D). Their joint tally falls from 401 seats (54%) to a projected 325 seats (43%).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This fact will shape the next European Parliament. For one thing, the EPP and S&amp;amp;D have lost their majority. Expect more ad hoc coalitions around case-by-case issues. And where a “grand coalition” of the centre is needed—on the upcoming approval of a new European Commission president, for example—it will have to be much broader than before and draw in liberals and even greens. The old two-party establishment has become at least a three-and-a-half-party establishment. And it is looking much less established, in any case. European politics is churning, splitting and recombining in new ways and directions. The long-term rise of the right-wing populists is part of that but not, in this election, a particularly new or dynamic one. Tonight’s crucial trend is not a populist surge but the revelation of the full scale of Europe’s political fragmentation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 07:18:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The case for Margrethe Vestager]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/charlemagnes-notebook/2019/05/25/the-case-for-margrethe-vestager]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-25T20:09:25Z&quot;&gt;May 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPEAN POLITICS is a febrile place. The old centre-right European People’s Party (EPP) and the old centre-left Party of European Socialists (PES) have long dominated the continent’s politics but are now ceding their dominance. Tomorrow’s European election results will probably show that the two are the big losers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Who should replace them? Matteo Salvini, Italy’s far-right leader, will marshal a nationalist right-wing party. Emmanuel Macron, France’s president, will try to found a liberal pro-European force. Neither will succeed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mainstream national leaders will want a figure who can get things done, who is acceptable to the centre-right European People’s Party; to the centre-left Party of European Socialists and possibly to liberal and green camps. They will look for someone who crosses old ideological boundaries and who can make Europe relevant at a time when the continent is declining in global significance. They will stumble upon Margrethe Vestager.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Vestager has served as education, interior and economy minister of Denmark despite belonging to a tiny left-liberal party. As European Commissioner since 2014 she has applied both a liberal sense of consumer rights and a centre-left commitment to defending the little guy to the task of regulating technology giants. She has taken on tax dodgers, infringers of personal privacy and market distorters and defeated them all. Thrusting machos from Silicon Valley have turned up in her office, berated her and come off the worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The EU in 2019 faces an array of security and economic threats. It needs a powerful, efficient leader with experience of the Commission and a sense of how the world is changing. It needs a leader who can stand up for Europe and initiate legislation defending its citizens. It needs someone acceptable to left and right, north and south. Many candidates will put their names forward. Ms Vestager ticks all the boxes. Europe would be foolish to overlook her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 05:40:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Onward Christian soldiers]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/05/25/onward-christian-soldiers]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_BLP508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-25T20:30:00Z&quot;&gt;May 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IF ALL THE people involved were civilians, there would be nothing especially controversial about a popular website, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://prayatlunch.us/&quot;&gt;PLUS&lt;/a&gt;, which invites American Christians to “pray at lunchtime for the United States”. But the site’s main author, John Teichert, describes himself as an “active duty brigadier-general who has served in the United States Air Force” since 1994.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For critics like Mikey Weinstein, president of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.militaryreligiousfreedom.org/&quot;&gt;Military Religious Freedom Foundation&lt;/a&gt; (MRFF), which campaigns for church-state separation in the armed forces, this sort of thing epitomises an ever-escalating trend. In the era of Donald Trump, they allege, fundamentalist Christians in uniform have felt freer than ever to test the boundaries set by the constitution and take advantage of their rank when disseminating their own reading of their faith and of American history. The MRFF is not alone in this complaint: last year, at least two other secularist groups formally protested to the Pentagon over the fact that service personnel were being bamboozled into attending religious ceremonies, compromising their own religious freedom.    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In several ways, the PLUS website is carefully crafted. It offers the disclaimer that “the views presented are those of the author and do not necessarily represent the views of the Department of Defence or its components.” The reference to lunch suggests that people are not being asked to give up professional time. The author’s surname is not given, although it is an open secret. The Pentagon has defended the website as a legitimate use of spare time by the officer. On the other hand, as commander of fighter-aircraft testing at Edwards Air Force Base, a giant facility in California, the brigadier-general enjoys huge personal authority and charisma. The MRFF says it is continuing to complain about his site, despite repeated rebuffs from the Pentagon, at the urging of at least 40 service personnel, including believing Christians who say they feel intimidated by the knowledge that one of their commanders is propagating one particular version of the faith.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Weinstein describes this version as “dominionist” Christianity, the idea that earthly institutions should be harnessed to spread the Christian cause. This often goes hand in hand with a particular interpretation of America’s earliest years, which insists that the founding fathers planned to establish a Christian nation, not a religiously neutral one. (Secularist historians disagree.) The PLUS website urges followers to pray for America &amp;quot;to return to its biblical foundation&amp;quot;. It also advocates prayers for &amp;quot;Bible-preaching churches, pastors and missionaries&amp;quot;, in language often used by non-conformist Christians to differentiate themselves from, say, Catholics who stress the authority of the church as opposed to the Bible alone. Further supplications are proposed for the unborn and for Israel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In years past, Mr Weinstein says, this way of thinking was especially prevalent in the Air Force, but now he says he observes it in all branches of the American services. He finds it widespread in elite special-forces units, such as the Navy Seals. “The closer you get to the tip of the spear, the more dominionist thinking there is.”  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As he uses the term, dominionist Christians should be distinguished carefully from evangelicals, although the two categories do overlap. Many evangelical Christians fully respect the principle of church-state separation and correspondingly keep their faith and its propagation within boundaries that are designed to respect the freedom of others. Among the 60,000 or so supporters of the MRFF, there are many evangelicals, according to Mr Weinstein. Some turn to the MRFF because they feel bullied over religious matters by commanders or chaplains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About 3,000 chaplains serve the American forces. The overwhelming majority are Protestant, and only a handful cater to minority faiths such as Judaism, Hinduism and Islam. Within the Protestant contingent, a vocal subset make no secret of the fact that they regard chaplaincy as an opportunity for missionary work, rather than for catering to those who already profess their faith.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As in many areas of American life, managing religious affairs in the armed forces will always involve a careful equilibrium between two principles enshrined in the constitution’s First Amendment: the free exercise of faith, and a bar on the state establishment of any particular religion. In that spirit, an official instruction to Air Force officers tells them to:  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;…balance constitutional protections, for their own free exercise of religion, including individual expressions of religious beliefs, and the constitutional prohibition against governmental establishment of religion…They must ensure their words and actions cannot reasonably be construed to be official endorsing or disapproving of, or extending preferential treatment for any faith, belief, or absence of belief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;This seems to imply that officers should never use their professional time, their work e-mail accounts or the authority of their rank to spread one particular idea about religion. But in practice this principle is widely violated, complains Mr Weinstein, himself a retired Air Force officer.         &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As one example he offers, a recent legal determination by the Pentagon, winkled out by the MRFF, lays down what officers can say at change-of-command ceremonies or personal promotion celebrations. In rather surreal language, it says that in the former kind of ritual, commanders may “briefly thank a Supreme Being (either generally, such as Providence, that Almighty Being, our Lord, or the Supreme Author of All Good; or specifically, such as Allah, Brahman, Christ, Ganesh, God, Yahweh, or even Beelzebub)”. A celebrant may also be invited to offer a prayer to one of these beings.    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Weinstein and his supporters believe that these concessions to expressions of faith by commanders are mistaken. The promotion ceremony, while regarded as an individual milestone, is nonetheless conducted in uniform, he observes.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, whatever the successes chalked up by the perceived dominionists, there are some countervailing trends in the armed forces. One is the increasing acceptance of LGBT service personnel and same-sex relationships. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2015 it was announced that the armed forces&amp;#x27; equal-opportunity policies applied to gays and lesbians. Two years ago a married lesbian woman, Kristin Goodwin, was named as commandant of cadets at the US Air Force Academy. Religious conservatives grumbled that to have got so far, she could not have been honest about her sexual orientation during her early career. (In fact, the “don’t ask, don’t tell” policy, which military authorities applied in relation to sexuality between 1994 and 2011, would have spared her any difficult questions.)  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last month it was announced that Brigadier-General Goodwin had been removed from her post, pending the investigation of a complaint about which no details have been disclosed. There is no suggestion whatever that her sexual orientation was the basis of that complaint, but her removal was announced prominently on religious conservative websites. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As America prepares for Memorial Day commemorations of its war dead on May 27th, it is fair to say that battles over religion and culture are raging deep inside the armed forces, as in so many other arenas. And for what it may be worth, Brigadier-General Teichert has added Mr Weinstein to the list of people in need of those lunch-time prayers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 03:40:43 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>