<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[The world is a long way from meeting its gender-equality target]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/05/the-world-is-a-long-way-from-meeting-its-gender-equality-target]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_wom998.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-05T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“THIS IS a man’s world,” sang James Brown in the spring of 1966. The adage still holds true today. In 2015 the United Nations General Assembly approved the Sustainable Development Goals (SDGs), a collection of targets for social progress to be achieved by 2030. The goals closest to being met are those for hunger and nutrition, water and sanitation, and health and education. In contrast, one of the objectives that the world is farthest from meeting concerns gender equality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent report from Equal Measures 2030, an initiative co-sponsored by the Gates Foundation, ranks 129 countries on a scale from zero to 100 on 15 of the 17 SDGs, taking measures on 51 issues including health, gender-based violence and climate change. Data are drawn from UN agencies, the World Bank, NGOs, think-tanks and Gallup, a polling firm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On gender equality, the index shows that no country exceeds the 90-point threshold to be considered “excellent”, though Denmark, the top performer, comes close with a score of 89.3. It is closely followed by nearby Finland, Sweden, Norway and the Netherlands. Unsurprisingly, fragile and conflict-ridden states, such as Niger, Yemen and the Republic of Congo lag far behind. Chad, the lowest-ranked country on the list, scores just 33.4 points. The global average score of 65.7 is “poor”, according to the index’s scoring system. Just 8% of the world’s population of girls and women live in countries that received a “good” rating of 80-89 points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc111.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc111.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc111.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc111.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc111.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc111.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc111.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc111.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc111.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc111.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall, countries’ scores on the index seem to track national income levels. Notable exceptions are South Korea, Switzerland and the United States, which all have lower gender-equality scores than might be expected considering their wealth. In the United States, for example, this is caused by poor performance on indicators related to poverty and women’s participation in the economy. At the other end of the scale is Rwanda, which does better than its national income level might suggest. One of the reasons for this is the high proportion of female members of parliament. Women make up 61% of its lower house, the highest percentage in the world. But this also demonstrates the limits of statistical targets: even though a far higher share of the legislature is female in Rwanda than in Denmark (where the proportion is just 37%), its parliament is little more than a rubber-stamp.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 06:40:40 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The long-term decline in bond yields enters a new phase]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/05/the-long-term-decline-in-bond-yields-enters-a-new-phase]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_FNC198_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-05T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AT THE END of 1989, an American in London received a call from a friend back home. The caller had watched the fall of the Berlin Wall and the toppling of Nicolae Ceausescu in Romania with growing dismay. He was at the end of a four-year course in Russian Studies at an elite university with hefty tuition fees. He had learned all the Kremlinology a would-be cold warrior could need—but not that the cold war might suddenly end. “I just took a $60,000 bath,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This story comes to mind not so much because of fears of a new cold war, this time with China, but because of the bond market’s recent response to such fears. Long-term interest rates have tumbled almost as swiftly as communism fell in Europe. The yield on a ten-year Treasury bond has plunged from 2.5% to 2.1% in the past month. Ten-year Bund yields have turned negative again and have reached a new all-time low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What happens to long-term interest rates in large part reflects what is expected to happen to short-term rates. The bond market’s Kremlinologists expect the Federal Reserve to cut them soon. Other central banks will seek to keep money easy. One consequence is that the secular decline in real interest rates is unlikely to reverse soon (see chart). The implications are far-reaching: the whole edifice of asset prices is founded on a low-rate regime. But what if eventually it were to end abruptly?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is hard to be truly confident about the future path of real interest rates. The reasons for their decades-long decline are not well understood or agreed upon. One school stresses an increased desire for saving. Demographic change is part of this story. As a large chunk of the rich world’s population approaches the end of their working lives, they seek to set aside more of their income for retirement. The integration of high-saving China into the world economy is another strut. In this view, long-term interest rates had to fall simply to clear the saturated global market for savings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another school says that low bond yields are a distortion caused by the policies pursued by central banks in the rich world. They have kept short-term interest rates close to (or in some cases below) zero for much of the past decade. They have also spent trillions of dollars buying government bonds with the explicit goal of driving down long-term interest rates. In their defence, central bankers say they set interest rates to keep the economy purring. If they had pressed down too hard on the monetary pedal, the result ought to be a burst of rising prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the absence of rising inflation it seems reasonable to expect that the era of low interest rates will last. If yields on the safest government bonds remain low, the expected returns on other assets—the earnings yield on equities, say, or the rental yield on property—should stay in line. The result would be that all assets will continue to look expensive relative to their long-run averages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As logical as this seems, it is nevertheless disquieting. At some stage the influences that have pushed down yields will attenuate, even if this is not soon. Long-term interest rates will surely rise again. It is reasonable to believe that this will not be sudden. Demographic change happens slowly. So perhaps asset prices will adjust slowly to the new reality, whenever it dawns. But it is quite hard to imagine a world in which real interest rates grind upwards and asset-holders avoid taking a capital loss, says Shamik Dhar of BNY Mellon, a fund-management group. The uncertainty about the timing of even a gradual adjustment creates headaches, for instance for someone hoping to own a home. Buy at the wrong time, and you end up with a house that slowly loses value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And what if real interest rates rise a lot more quickly than they fell? Well, they might. China is already a spent force in the global savings glut: its current-account surplus has dwindled to next to nothing. Baby-boomers moving into retirement might step up their spending. If rich countries turn once again to fiscal policy as a tool for ginning up their economies, there are plenty of asset-heavy projects (airports, roads, fibre-optic networks) to soak up savings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kremlinologists look for signs of shifting authority, for who’s up and who’s down. But when everyone is focused on who will be the next boss, they may all miss signs that the regime itself is cracking. For now, financial-market Kremlinologists are preoccupied with which assets to hold and which to avoid. But at some point capital will become scarcer. Somebody may find that they have taken an expensive bath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 06:40:39 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mo Salah’s goals help to tackle Islamophobia in Liverpool]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/05/mo-salahs-goals-help-to-tackle-islamophobia-in-liverpool]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_brp504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-05T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“IF HE SCORES another few then I’ll be Muslim too,” chant Liverpool fans whenever Mohamed Salah, an Egyptian striker, finds the net. Since arriving in June 2017, he has done so with record-breaking frequency. On June 1st he scored his 71st goal in 104 appearances, to inspire the Reds to victory in the Champions League, Europe’s most prestigious competition. As usual, he celebrated by kneeling in prayer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is unlikely that Mr Salah—whom another chant describes as a “gift from Allah”—has converted many fans to Islam. But a working paper by political scientists at Stanford University has found signs that his popularity might have helped to tackle anti-Muslim sentiment on Merseyside. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cleanest evidence came from a Facebook experiment on 8,000 British Liverpool fans. The academics gave each respondent a survey containing footballing facts and questions; a third of surveys also included a slide describing Mr Salah’s commitment to praying. Then all users were asked about their attitudes to Muslims. Of those who saw the slide about Mr Salah’s faith, 23% thought Islam was compatible with British values, compared with 18% of the other fans. Although most Liverpool supporters may know about Mr Salah’s faith anyway, the experiment showed that a reminder could alter their opinions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The academics also hunted for signs of broader changes in Islamophobic sentiment in Liverpool since Mr Salah was signed. First they looked at hate crimes, in which the perpetrator is motivated by race, religion or another type of identity. Of 23 English regions analysed, almost all saw a rise in the number of such crimes in the ten months after Mr Salah’s arrival, part of a long-term trend that the Home Office puts down to better recording by the police. Merseyside, by contrast, reported a slight fall. The researchers built statistical models to predict monthly rates of various types of offences in Liverpool, and found that hate crimes had been 19% less common than expected, a gap that did not exist for any other illegal activity, suggesting that any “Salah effect” was limited to religious tolerance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then the researchers turned to Twitter. They identified British followers of Manchester United, Manchester City, Chelsea, Arsenal, Liverpool and Everton (a Merseyside rival), and analysed 44,000 tweets that mentioned Muslims, Arabs or mosques. In the 14 months after Mr Salah’s transfer, 7.6% of Islam-related tweets by Liverpool fans had negative sentiments, about the same as the 7.3% during the previous three years. But the figure for Everton jumped from 18.6% to 21.3%; for the other teams it rose from 7.1% to 10.9%. Online Islamophobia in Liverpool seems to have been kept in check at a time when it was rising elsewhere. (The researchers found no sign that the broader increase was caused by jealous fans abusing Mr Salah.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most parts of the country, including Merseyside, saw a spike in anti-Muslim sentiment in the summer of 2017, after terrorist attacks in London and Manchester. If Mr Salah has played even a small part in reining in Liverpool fans’ prejudice since then, that is an achievement as remarkable as leading the club to European glory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 05:40:17 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The race to become Britain’s next PM]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/05/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-05T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HERESA MAY&lt;/small&gt; has announced that she will step down as leader of the Conservative Party on June 7th. She will remain as prime minister until her successor is chosen. Nominations for the Tory leadership will close in the week beginning June 10th, followed by several rounds of voting among MPs, a process that will last until the end of the month. The MPs will then send two names to party members who will make the final choice. The result of their vote will be announced before parliament rises for summer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Betfair Exchange, a gambling website, has been tracking punters’ predictions on the next Tory leader. According to the wisdom of the betting crowd, a handful of candidates stand out. But there is only one clear frontrunner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adrian Wooldridge, our political editor, assesses the chances of the leading Conservative politicians hoping to take the top job in this short film &lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ychDrZ2QzlE&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Source: Betfair Exchange&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 02:39:55 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Using sponges to census the ocean]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/06/05/using-sponges-to-census-the-ocean]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_stp002_facebook.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-05T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;STUDYING THE health of ecosystems on dry land—a habitat that biologists share with the organisms they are looking at—is challenging enough. Studying marine ecosystems is far harder. Even discovering which species are there, let alone in what quantities, can be tricky. But an insight by Stefano Mariani of the University of Salford, in Britain, may make things easier. As he describes in Current Biology, he thinks that sponges growing on the sea floor may offer a short cut to such information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One way of sampling marine life is to sample the seawater itself, looking for DNA shed by creatures as they go about their lives. This is known to work in principal, but in practice it means running huge amounts of water through filters, to extract things like shed skin and blood cells for analysis. That is awkward, meaning sampling tends to be patchy. And attempts to automate the process using drones are proving pricey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sponges, however, are natural filters. Indeed, they make their livings that way, sucking in thousands of litres of water a day and running it through intricate systems of channels that trap particles of organic matter, which they then digest. Taking samples from sponges, and checking the DNA therein, might thus, Dr Mariani reasoned, be an effective way to assess the diversity of species in the region surrounding a particular sponge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To test this idea in principle he and his colleagues removed some pieces from sponges collected originally for other research purposes. Five of these had come from Antarctica and four from the Mediterranean. Analysis revealed, in the Antarctic samples, the presence of animals including chinstrap penguins, Weddell seals and Perknaster aurantiacus, a type of starfish. In the Mediterranean samples there were rock gobies, horse mackerel and sardines. The quality of the DNA was not always sufficient to make a precise identification all the way down to the level of “species”, but, overall, the researchers recognised genetic material from at least 31 different groups of animal—meaning that was the minimum number of species represented.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clearly, this is but a fraction of the total likely to have been present in the sponges home areas, and the data also give little idea of the size of those populations. To do all that would mean looking at a lot more sponges. Equally clearly though, Dr Mariani’s method does work in principle. Refining it and making it more sensitive is now a matter of detail. Since sponges cost nothing to manufacture, deploy or maintain, and also regenerate when they have pieces removed from them, they may thus turn out to be an ideal way of monitoring what is going on, unseen, in Davy Jones’s biological locker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 02:39:55 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fusing the future—a power struggle]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/05/fusing-the-future-a-power-struggle]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/babbage_gradient_map_80__1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-05T17:15:47Z&quot;&gt;Jun 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN THIS week’s Babbage, Alok Jha, our science correspondent, investigates a &lt;strong&gt;technology that could solve all of the world’s energy problems in a stroke—&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/05/04/fusion-power-is-attracting-private-sector-interest&quot;&gt;nuclear fusion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. From Iter, the world&amp;#x27;s largest collaborative fusion experiment, to private start-ups, he talks to the organisations racing to be first to create fusion power. Could the long-promised dream of nuclear fusion—to provide clean, limitless, carbon-free energy—finally be about to come true? Runtime: 20 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistbabbage/babbage-fusingthefuture&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 01:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Africa writer]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/05/were-hiring-a-journalist-to-write-about-africa]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20180224_wop001_9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-05T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WE ARE looking for a new journalist to strengthen our coverage of sub-Saharan Africa. The job will be based somewhere in Africa—exactly where is open for negotiation with the successful candidate. It will involve a lot of travel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applicants should send an original unpublished article of up to 600 words on an African topic suitable for publication in &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;, a CV and a cover letter to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.commailto:africawriter@economist.com&quot;&gt;africawriter@economist.com&lt;/a&gt;. The deadline for applications is July 19th 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The article is the most important part of the application. We will read it blind (ie, without looking at your name or where you are from). If what you write is not exceptionally good, we will not look at your CV. This is to ensure that the process is as unbiased and meritocratic as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyone is welcome to apply, regardless of citizenship, ethnic origin, sex, religious beliefs, disability, sexual orientation or age. Previous experience as a journalist is desirable but not essential. What we most want is original thinking, good analytical skills and, above all, good writing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 01:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America’s vision for the Indo-Pacific gets a lukewarm reception]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/05/asian-countries-fear-china-but-many-wont-side-with-america]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_asp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-05T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHAT DO YOU buy the Asian defence minister who has everything? How about a “beautiful” photo-book of North Korean ships illegally transferring oil at sea? Patrick Shanahan, America’s acting defence secretary, presented the collection of grainy aerial shots to his Chinese counterpart, General Wei Fenghe, at the Shangri-La Dialogue, an annual gathering of military bigwigs in Singapore from May 31st to June 2nd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was an emollient gesture in fractious times. When Banyan asked Mr Shanahan what he planned to say to General Wei in private, the answer was not a tirade about Huawei or the South China Sea. Instead Mr Shanahan said he was “excited” to explore areas of co-operation. North Korean sanctions-busting—which often occurs in Chinese waters—was top of the list. Such collaboration would show that America and China could “compete in a constructive way”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On June 1st the Pentagon published its plans for that competition in an Indo-Pacific strategy. At its heart was the idea of a “free and open Indo-Pacific” (FOIP), a nebulous concept conceived by Japan and enthusiastically taken up by the Trump administration. In essence, FOIP is a rules-based rejoinder to China’s vision of spheres of influence, gunboat diplomacy and murky loans. “No one nation can or should dominate the Indo-Pacific,” said the Pentagon in its report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shanahan’s notion of responsible competition—in contrast to the no-holds-barred clash of civilisations favoured by some of his head-banging colleagues—is laudable. It is also savvy. Asian states are likelier to sign up to FOIP if they are persuaded that America is not spoiling for a fight. But on both counts—stabilising the relationship with China, while rallying partners to push back against it—America has an uphill task.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start with the olive branches. General Wei did not so much ignore them as snap them into pieces. “Arise, all those who do not want be enslaved,” he thundered in his speech on June 2nd, quoting China’s national anthem. “Let us build the new Great Wall with our flesh and blood.” He warned that China’s army was “not afraid of sacrifice” and that “we make no promise to renounce the use of force” against Taiwan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One might think that such bluster would send Asians rushing to sign up to FOIP and into America’s arms. In some cases, it has. Narendra Modi will deepen defence ties with America in his second term. Japan is beefing up its armed forces and sending its navy into the South China Sea. Officials from America, Australia, India and Japan—the “Quad”—now confer routinely, most recently on May 31st.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All pay lip service to the idea that the Association of South-East Asian Nations (ASEAN), a club of ten mostly smaller powers, should be at the core of FOIP. The problem is that not all in ASEAN are sold on the idea. For one thing, many are unconvinced that America will truly stick around, as the costs of any war with China grow over time. So why risk China’s ire? “The Chinese coast guard is bigger than Malaysia’s warships,” lamented Malaysia’s defence minister.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shanahan did his best to assuage these concerns. He pointed out that the Indo-Pacific was America’s “priority theatre”, with four times as many American forces as any other American military command. America’s freedom of navigation operations in the South China Sea were also growing more routine: unusually, there were two in May alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But muscle is only half of it. The larger issue is that Donald Trump’s unpredictably incendiary foreign policy sits uneasily with the principles of FOIP. Tensions with Iran are pulling America’s attention back to the Middle East. The compulsive resort to tariffs undercuts a rules-based trading order. Mr Trump’s lack of interest in human rights hardly furthers freedom. And to many in Asia, America’s war on Huawei or its sanctions against buyers of Russian arms or Iranian oil look an awful lot like China’s “toolkit of coercion”, as Mr Shanahan put it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is unfair. An Asian order sculpted by China would be more capricious and suffocating than anything Mr Trump could devise. General Wei’s brazen defence of the Tiananmen Square massacre—he called it a “correct policy” that gave China the stability to grow richer—was a reminder of the ideological stakes. Australia, India and Japan are on board. Singapore and Vietnam’s sympathies are clear. But most ASEAN countries hate the idea of taking sides, despite widespread misgivings about China’s intentions. Mr Shanahan reckons they will eventually come round. “I think they’re building up their confidence,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 01:39:55 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Fusing the future]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/05/fusing-the-future]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/babbage_gradient_map_80__1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-05T17:15:47Z&quot;&gt;Jun 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN THIS week’s Babbage, Alok Jha, our science correspondent, investigates a &lt;strong&gt;technology that could solve all of the world’s energy problems in a stroke—&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/05/04/fusion-power-is-attracting-private-sector-interest&quot;&gt;nuclear fusion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. From Iter, the world&amp;#x27;s largest collaborative fusion experiment, to private start-ups, he talks to the organisations racing to be first to create fusion power. Could the long-promised dream of nuclear fusion—to provide clean, limitless, carbon-free energy—finally be about to come true? Runtime: 20 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistbabbage/babbage-fusingthefuture&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Africa writer]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/05/africa-writer]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20180224_wop001_9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-05T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WE ARE looking for a new journalist to strengthen our coverage of sub-Saharan Africa. The job will be based somewhere in Africa—exactly where is open for negotiation with the successful candidate. It will involve a lot of travel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Applicants should send an original unpublished article of up to 600 words on an African topic suitable for publication in &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;, a CV and a cover letter to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.commailto:africawriter@economist.com&quot;&gt;africawriter@economist.com&lt;/a&gt;. The deadline for applications is July 19th 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The article is the most important part of the application. We will read it blind (ie, without looking at your name or where you are from). If what you write is not exceptionally good, we will not look at your CV. This is to ensure that the process is as unbiased and meritocratic as possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyone is welcome to apply, regardless of citizenship, ethnic origin, sex, religious beliefs, disability, sexual orientation or age. Previous experience as a journalist is desirable but not essential. What we most want is original thinking, good analytical skills and, above all, good writing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 00:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>