<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[A rebellion against Nicolás Maduro appears to have been foiled]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/05/01/a-rebellion-against-nicolas-maduro-appears-to-have-been-foiled]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_amp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-01T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ONE DAY after the opposition announced its final push to oust Nicolás Maduro, Venezuela’s strongman was determined to show he was back in control. He duly adopted the method his regime knows best: rapid, forceful repression of protests. The early signs are that he is succeeding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On April 30th Juan Guaidó, recognised by most Western and Latin American democracies as the country’s interim president, had appeared before the walls of La Carlota airbase with a group of military defectors to announce “Operation Liberty”. He promised to mobilise the “biggest march in Venezuelan history” to prise apart the cracks in the regime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But when pro-opposition protesters approached the base again on May 1st they were dispersed by a rain of teargas canisters the moment they began aiming stones at the conscripts inside. Similarly, a demonstration in the working-class district of El Paraiso had barely started before the National Guard started firing teargas and plastic bullets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We can&amp;#x27;t put up with this anymore,” said Maria Isabel Salas, 58, a housewife, who joined the protests despite admitting her fear. “This government is no use for anything. I want them to know that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Wednesday’s protest began, Mr Guaidó told supporters that the end is “just around the corner”. He said that in the coming days a programme of “staggered strikes” would begin, leading up to a national strike at an unspecified date. But there was no sign of any more rebel soldiers joining his side. And Leopoldo López, an opposition leader who had dramatically slipped away from his house arrest to appear next to Mr Guaidó, did not resurface. He was sheltering in the Spanish embassy. About two dozen rebel national guardsmen soldiers are believed to be in the Brazilian embassy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Maduro has vowed to pursue all of those behind the uprising. “This will not go unpunished,” he said. “I have chosen three prosecutors...who will interrogate all people involved. They will launch criminal prosecutions for the serious crimes that have been committed against the constitution, the rule of law and the right to peace.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Maduro, who started his second term in January after winning a sham election, has plunged the country into economic misery. But despite the discontent, and occasional defection of groups of soldiers, the regime has so far managed to keep the loyalty of most of the army. The faltering uprising confirmed just how hard Mr Guaidó will find it to win over commanders, even though he has offered soldiers who switch sides amnesty. Many benefit from the regime’s cronyism, and some are too deeply implicated in criminal activities to qualify for amnesty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking before the demonstration began, John Bolton, America’s National Security adviser, claimed that the uprising, planned over many months, had not gone as intended. He said that Maikel Moreno, the head of Venezuela’s supreme court, which has up till now acted as a regime puppet, was expected to declare Mr Maduro’s national constituent assembly illegitimate. This would have given legal cover to Vladimir Padrino, the defence minister, and the high command, to throw their support behind Mr Guaidó and the opposition-controlled national assembly. “For reasons that are still not clear, that didn’t go forward yesterday,” Mr Bolton said. He blamed Russian and Cuban interference for dissuading Mr Maduro from fleeing to Cuba.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another explanation, based on Venezuelan military sources and reported in &lt;em&gt;El Confidencial&lt;/em&gt;, a Spanish digital newspaper, is that this plan was due to be put into effect on May 2nd and that Mr Guaidó and Mr López jumped the gun, prompting the high command to back off. It is not the first time that the opposition has seemingly overplayed its hand. Some sections of it have long believed that pressure from the streets is sufficient to overthrow Mr Maduro. So far, it has not been. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The uprising did not leave the regime unshaken. It took Mr Maduro a day to appear in public. And General Manuel Figuera, who was sacked as head of SEBIN, the intelligence service, because of his apparent support for the uprising, seemed to confirm Mr Bolton’s accounts of regime disloyalty. A letter written to Mr Maduro and attributed to General Figuera said: “I discovered that many people you trust are negotiating behind your back.” Whether the dictator can still trust General Padrino, Mr Moreno and the others after they were supposedly outed by Mr Bolton must now be open to doubt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the biggest blow struck on Tuesday was to the momentum of the opposition. More than three months after Mr Guaidó proclaimed himself interim president, with the backing of the national assembly as well as of the United States and over 50 other countries, the regime has not collapsed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The longer the stand-off continues, the more problematic the strategy of President Donald Trump’s administration becomes. On May 1st, America’s Secretary of State, Mike Pompeo, told broadcasters that American military action is possible in Venezuela. But that would be a bad idea. It would feed into the regime’s claims that America is trying to take over the country in order to quash the socialist revolution ushered in by Mr Maduro’s predecessor, Hugo Chávez. And support for America among ordinary Venezuelans may anyway be on the wane. Though the regimes of Mr Maduro and Chávez brought about Venezuela’s economic collapse, American sanctions on Venezuelan oil, which came into effect fully this week, will aggravate the country’s humanitarian crisis. Unless the stand-off is resolved soon, there is a risk that any transitional government, if and when it happens, will inherit a pauperised state.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is not in doubt is the determination of the Trump administration to get rid of Mr Maduro’s regime. Having joined this battle, it is one the administration cannot afford to lose. Mr Maduro could be gone tomorrow, or he could still be there at Christmas. In that case the administration would face a choice: either make good on Mr Trump’s threats of military action, which enjoy no support in Latin America nor among the Democrats, or hold its nose and negotiate directly with him the terms of his departure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 06:05:45 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gavin Williamson is sacked as defence secretary for leaking Britain’s Huawei plans]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/01/gavin-williamson-is-sacked-as-defence-secretary-for-leaking-britains-huawei-plans]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_brp003.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;LEAKS IN WESTMINSTER are common. Leaks from meetings of the National Security Council (NSC), which include cabinet ministers, generals and an array of spooks, are not. When details of Theresa May’s decision to allow Huawei, a Chinese telecoms group, to build next-generation infrastructure in Britain appeared in the &lt;em&gt;Daily Telegraph&lt;/em&gt; on April 24th, an inquiry was duly launched. It took barely a week to find its man. The supposed mole? Gavin Williamson, the defence secretary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite his fervent protestations of innocence, Mrs May sacked Mr Williamson on May 1st. Her letter to him was brutal. There was “compelling” evidence that he had leaked details of the meeting. Mr Williamson’s denials were ignored—no other “credible” story existed, the prime minister said. Mr Williamson has been replaced by Penny Mordaunt, previously the secretary for international development, who also attended the fateful meeting but managed to keep her mouth shut. She in turn is replaced by the ambitious Rory Stewart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mrs May has now lost ten cabinet members in less than three years in office. Mr Williamson was an uninspired defence secretary and tabloid figure of fun, who once said Russia should “go away and shut up”. But as a former chief whip he provided the prime minister with an insight into the unhappy mood of the party. Yet once the inquiry had fingered him, his fate was inevitable. Mrs May, who spent six years as home secretary, is a securocrat to her core.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The subject matter of the leak was sensitive. America has for months been lobbying its allies to freeze Huawei out of their 5G telecoms networks, arguing that China could use the firm’s gear for spying or sabotage. It has had only mixed success. Australia banned Huawei outright. New Zealand turned down a request from a local firm to use Huawei’s gear. But Germany has pushed back, as has the European Union. Britain’s decision to give Huawei a limited role makes it the most prominent refusenik. Its signals-intelligence agency, GCHQ, works hand-in-glove with its American counterpart, the National Security Agency, and similar organisations in Australia, New Zealand and Canada, as part of the Five Eyes spying alliance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America has said it may cut back intelligence sharing with countries that ignore its warnings. That is probably bluster: if nothing else, Britain’s geographical location makes it too useful to simply abandon (many transatlantic internet cables come ashore in Britain). Instead, the Americans may hope that by keeping up the pressure they may persuade a future government to reverse the decision. The NSC was split on whether to allow Huawei in. Mrs May ignored its more hawkish members and gave the green light. But she is unlikely to be prime minister for much longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several likely candidates for her job, including Ms Mordaunt, Jeremy Hunt, the foreign secretary, and Sajid Javid, the home secretary, were among those who voted no—as did Mr Williamson. Unlike the rest of this small cast, Mr Williamson now has little chance of having another say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 05:07:24 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Britain is rejecting an ever greater share of freedom-of-information requests]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/01/britain-is-rejecting-an-ever-greater-share-of-freedom-of-information-requests]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_woc944.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“OPENNESS IS fundamental to the political health of a modern state”. So began the White Paper that led to the passing of the Freedom of Information Act in Britain in 2000. Its aim was to create a transparent executive accessible to the public. Two decades later after its adoption, however, the law is failing to deliver.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Freedom-of-information requests (FOIs) can be made for material held by government departments or other agencies. Open-government advocates’ excitement about the White Paper were tempered as the law came into being with several exemptions, notably a clause giving ministers the right to veto a disclosure. Other reasons for denying requests include cost, time limits and security considerations. Even so, governments have over time tried to close the window of transparency even tighter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2006 more than 60% of FOI requests were answered. That figure has fallen steadily to 42% in 2018, according to figures released on May 1st.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_WOC832.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190504_WOC832.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190504_WOC832.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190504_WOC832.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190504_WOC832.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190504_WOC832.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190504_WOC832.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190504_WOC832.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190504_WOC832.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190504_WOC832.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;There are significant differences across departments. The Wales Office responded fully to 72% of requests (it had to deal with only 140). In contrast, the Department for Work and Pensions dealt with more than 4,000 FOIs, answering half of them. The worst departments may feel they have more pressing concerns at the moment. The Brexit department received 431 requests in 2018, but answered only a quarter. The Department for International Trade answered just 27%. The Foreign Office did even worse. No department has improved on a decade ago, and many are doing much worse.&lt;p&gt;Non-ministerial offices such as OFSTED and the Serious Fraud Office can be equally unco-operative: they answered just 16% and 28% of requests respectively. Agencies like the Crown Prosecution Service or the Charity Commission have a poor response rate, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There have been some important successes for FOIs. The MPs’ expenses scandal in 2009 was brought to light because of FOI and led to prison terms for some politicians. But the trend towards more closed government is unmistakable&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 04:07:06 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can the veggie-burger company change eating habits before it goes bust?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/01/can-the-veggie-burger-company-change-eating-habits-before-it-goes-bust]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_wbp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT IS LESS ubiquitous than Airbnb and less hubristic than Uber. But Beyond Meat, which goes public on May 2nd, shares with those firms—and with many other tech outfits expected to list this year—a Californian address and a grand, disruptive ambition. In one sense, Beyond Meat is the boldest of the lot. Changing the way people book accommodation and cars seems trifling next to changing what they eat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond Meat makes what it calls “plant-based meat products”, and what most people call veggie burgers and veggie sausages. Unlike some rival products, which are merely hamburger-shaped, Beyond Meat’s patties resemble the real thing. Throw one in a hot frying pan and it will turn from pink to brown while sizzling. Social media are full of tales of committed meat-eaters unable to distinguish it from the real thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They are the firm’s target market. Only about 5% of Americans describe themselves as vegetarians, and it is not clear why they would want to eat something that closely resembles animal flesh. Carve a slice off the gigantic meat trade, though, and you might have a good business. Look at what has happened to milk, says Beyond Meat’s prospectus. Non-dairy versions made from almonds, soya and other things are now one-eighth the size of the dairy milk market in America. Non-flesh meat could grab a similar share of the meat market, or perhaps an even larger one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A powerful environmental case can be made for the stuff, argues Beyond Meat’s founder and boss, Ethan Brown. The livestock industry is a planetary thug. It is thought to account for about 15% of greenhouse-gas emissions, if you count the forests that are felled to create fields for growing animal feed, the methane in cow farts and the fuel that is burned moving everything around. Farm animals hog enormous amounts of land and pollute the water.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet Beyond Meat might stick in investors’ gullets, for several reasons. First, the company has yet to make a profit. Second, it is not the only company trying to cut into the meat business. Another Californian outfit, Impossible Foods, sells its plant-based products through Burger King, among others. Several start-ups are trying to grow meat in vats. They could all end up trying to eat each others’ lunches, or cutting into the sales of venerable outfits like Quorn. It was possible to order veggie burgers at Burger King before the Impossible Whopper came along.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Third, it is not obvious that more people are hungry for alternatives to meat. According to the US Department of Agriculture, the average American is eating more beef, pork and chicken than a couple of years ago. Britain’s Family Food survey shows a rise in meat consumption between 2015 and 2016-17 (the most recent period for which data exists). The parallel with non-dairy milk seems dubious. Many people sip soya milk not because they disapprove of dairy products or want to save the planet, but because they are lactose intolerant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, the meat industry has seen the challengers coming. In several American states, and in France, legislators have written laws reserving the word “meat” for animal products. In Nebraska, the effort has been led by a state senator with the wonderful name of Carol Blood. This is historically illiterate: “meat” has for centuries meant not just animal flesh but solid food in general, hence “sweetmeats” and Mercutio’s description of an egg as “full of meat” in “Romeo and Juliet”. But the livestock lobby is powerful. Polluting industries tend to be that way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 04:07:05 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A middling biopic of J.R.R. Tolkien]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/01/a-middling-biopic-of-jrr-tolkien]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_BKP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-01T17:58:29Z&quot;&gt;May 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;LAST WEEK J.R.R. Tolkien’s estate announced that it did not “authorise, or participate in the making of” a new biopic of the author. This statement may have more to do with the estate’s tight grip on its lucrative intellectual property—an authorised “Lord of the Rings” prequel is in production by Amazon—than with any objection to the way in which “Tolkien” portrays its subject. The first English-language film to be directed by Dome Karukoski, a Finnish film-maker, its account of John Ronald Reuel’s childhood and young adulthood is as respectful as his relatives could have possibly wished—and a little more respectful than the viewer might have wanted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As in most artists’ biopics, all sorts of themes and images from the aspiring novelist’s best-known work are there to be spotted in his formative years. Skipping past his early childhood in Africa, “Tolkien” begins its narrative as Ronald (Harry Gilby) is living with his brother and his widowed mother in Sarehole: a rural idyll which, it seems, will be the model for the Shire of his fiction. The family then moves to industrial Birmingham, and its dark satanic mills resemble the orcs’ forges in Peter Jackson’s film adaptations of “The Lord of the Rings”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the boys’ myth-recounting mother dies, Ronald (played in his teens and beyond by Nicholas Hoult) goes to the upper-crust King Edward’s School, where a group of like-minded friends teach him about fellowship. Then it is off to Oxford, and then to the first world war, where he has visions of dragons and knights amid the mud and mustard gas. He treks through the trenches with the help of a faithful sergeant named Sam (the viewer is supposed to believe that this is where the character of Sam Gamgee came from). Along the way, Ronald has an on-off romance with another orphan, Edith (Lily Collins), who encourages him to tell stories, instead of just making up languages. The narrative finishes exactly where you would expect, with Ronald dipping a nib in an inkpot and, in that instantly recognisable font, penning the opening sentence of “The Hobbit”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As authors’ lives go, Tolkien’s was eventful, and the connections between his biography and work aren’t as tenuous as they are in so many biopics. The problem is that Ronald himself is presented as such a goody-goody. He loses his Oxford scholarship after a wild night out, but only because he took the rap for the friends who led him astray. Earlier, when he makes a hash of his Oxford entrance exam, his failure is a direct result of his having taken Edith to her favourite Wagner opera the night before. “You were seen coming out of Edith’s room at midnight,” growls the priest (Colm Meaney) who is his legal guardian. “We were talking,” protests Ronald—and knowing him, he probably was. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether or not the real Tolkien was as innocent as his screen self, he comes across as an insipid hero. Mr Hoult plays him with pained sensitivity, but he is so mild-mannered that his most reckless act of rebellion is to look on quietly as Edith throws a sugar cube onto a nearby lady’s hat. If he has any anger or resentment about the deaths of his parents, his subsequent internment in a snobby school, or his part in a conflict that claimed the lives of several friends, he is far too polite to let it show.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rather than emphasising the multiple bereavements, the traumas of war, and even the pain of his separation from Edith, David Gleeson and Stephen Beresford’s screenplay concentrates on Ronald’s inspiring chats with his chums, the so-called Tea Club and Barrovian Society. This is a disappointingly safe tack to take, but if you view “Tolkien” as a wholesome children’s film, it makes a lot more sense. “Tolkien” offers teenage and pre-teen audiences an intelligent, well-appointed guide to the author and his world, while celebrating a youthful enthusiasm for literature, music, friendship and love—and there is nothing wrong with that. Older viewers, though, may wish that the film had included something—anything—that was dark, challenging or scandalous enough to upset the author’s estate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Tolkien” is released in Britain on May 3rd and in America on May 10th&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 02:06:31 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Zero-carbon Britain: how fast can it happen?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/01/zero-carbon-britain-how-fast-can-it-happen]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/bg_twitter_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-01T16:45:18Z&quot;&gt;May 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;This week a government advisory committee releases its anticipated recommendations for Britain to become a carbon-free economy. But will ministers take meaningful action? Also, the controversial subject of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/04/27/screening-for-lung-cancer-is-a-controversial-idea&quot;&gt;lung cancer screening&lt;/a&gt;, and David Spiegelhalter discusses ‘The Art of Statistics’. Kenneth Cukier hosts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistbabbage/babbage-netzerobritain&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 01:07:02 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump is not the first president to fight subpoenas]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/01/donald-trump-is-not-the-first-president-to-fight-subpoenas]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_usp506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 1924, a Senate committee investigating the Teapot Dome bribery scandal issued a subpoena to Mal Daugherty, a bank president and brother of Harry Daugherty, who would soon resign as attorney-general. When Mal failed to appear, the Senate dispatched its deputy sergeant-at-arms to Ohio to arrest him. Daugherty challenged his arrest, arguing that the Senate had exceeded its authority. The Supreme Court disagreed. Not only can Congress compel testimony essential to “a legislative function”; “it is to be presumed” that congressional investigations are intended “to aid [Congress] in legislating,” and “it is not a valid objection to such investigation that it might disclose wrongdoing or crime by a public officer.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump has sued two banks to stop them complying with House subpoenas, and asked a federal court to block another to an accounting firm used by the Trump Organisation. He has vowed to fight one subpoena issued to Don McGahn, a former White House counsel, and has ordered an official who oversaw White House security clearances not to comply with another. More subpoenas may soon follow, most likely to compel testimony from William Barr, Mr Trump’s attorney-general, who may skip a planned appearance before the House Judiciary Committee because he dislikes the questioning format, and to obtain Mr Trump’s tax returns, which he has refused to turn over to the Ways and Means Committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Congressional subpoenas are not all-powerful. Various presidents have fought them for different reasons. The usual levers brought to bear against private citizens who ignore subpoenas—fines and imprisonment—are harder to use against executive-branch officials. And congressional oversight, says Andrew Wright, an associate counsel to Barack Obama who is now a partner with K&amp;amp;L Gates, a law firm, “is a quasi-political, quasi-legal process” that usually resists quick resolution. This does not mean that Mr Trump—who said on April 24th that “we’re fighting all the subpoenas” because the House Democrats issuing them “aren’t, like, impartial people”—can simply ignore them, merely that this fight will probably have a political rather than a legal resolution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Congress can charge people who ignore subpoenas with contempt, which requires a majority vote in a single chamber. Enforcing that charge is trickier. The days of apprehension by the sergeant-at-arms followed by detention are over; that power has not been used since 1935, when a Hoover administration official was held at the Willard hotel. Contempt of Congress has been a federal crime since 1857, but Mr Barr is unlikely to approve prosecuting either his boss or anyone who was following his boss’s orders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That leaves civil contempt as a possible legal avenue. Congress can ask a federal court to compel obedience to a subpoena. This can take a while. In October 2011 Eric Holder, Barack Obama’s attorney-general, received a congressional subpoena. Mr Obama tried to block it by declaring executive privilege in June 2012. A court rejected Mr Obama’s blanket claim of privilege, but not until January 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current standoff may finish faster, for two reasons. First, many of the justiciability concerns that took courts time to work through during the Obama and Bush administrations have been resolved. And second, as Stephen Vladeck, a law professor at the University of Texas, explains, Mr Trump’s statement of blanket refusal “suggests that case-specific objections are post-hoc rationalisations”, which courts may be inclined to swiftly reject.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But legal battles still take some time to adjudicate. That may annoy Democrats but suit Mr Trump perfectly. His supporters prize his pugnacity, and he prefers table-pounding defiance to the intricacies of legal compromise. Also, political salience fades over time; he may reckon that if he loses in court, the public will have moved on to the next outrage. And congressional subpoenas expire when the current Congress does, making a successful play for time a victory, of sorts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:06:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[From Caracas: “Rattled rebel soldiers began firing in the air”]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/01/from-caracas-rattled-rebel-soldiers-began-firing-in-the-air]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/theintelligence_overlay2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-01T11:20:37Z&quot;&gt;May 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUAN GUAIDÓ, the opposition figure widely viewed as the legitimate leader of Venezuela, has made a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/04/30/juan-guaido-makes-a-dramatic-attempt-to-oust-venezuelas-regime&quot;&gt;dramatic attempt&lt;/a&gt; to seize power from President Nicolás Maduro. But the effort appears to have stalled; how did it go wrong? We also look more widely at coups around the world, why they succeed or fail, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/23/how-to-predict-a-coup&quot;&gt;how to predict them&lt;/a&gt;. And a dramatic embassy raid reveals why it’s so tough to be a North Korean &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/27/campaigning-against-the-north-korean-regime-is-a-thankless-task&quot;&gt;dissident&lt;/a&gt;. Runtime: 22min.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/putschcomestoshove-venezuela&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 23:06:31 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Does the Civil Rights Act protect gay and transgender workers?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/04/30/does-the-civil-rights-act-protect-gay-and-transgender-workers]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_USP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-30T06:07:45Z&quot;&gt;Apr 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SINCE 2015, same-sex couples have had a constitutional right to marry—yet Americans still enjoy no federal protection from workplace discrimination on the basis of their sexual orientation or transgender identity. In some two dozen states that do not have their own civil-rights umbrella for LGBT people, a gay employee can return to the office from his honeymoon and be fired. Transgender people, too, have no recourse in these states when their bosses fire or demote them for presenting themselves as their preferred gender. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In recent years, a push for greater equality has had some success at the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission and in several federal appeals courts which have pointed to protection against employment discrimination for LGBT in the Civil Rights Act of 1964. Meanwhile, the Trump administration and other courts are sticking to less expansive readings of that law. After months of discussion in private conference, on April 22nd the Supreme Court agreed to resolve the split. Late in 2019, the justices will take up gay rights for the first time since Justice Anthony Kennedy—author of the same-sex marriage decision and a trio of rulings forging a path to it—left the bench last June. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the cases come up for argument, the main quandary will concern how to interpret three words Congress wrote over a half-century ago: “because of sex”. Title VII of the Civil Rights Act bars employers from discriminating against a worker “because of such individual’s race, colour, religion, sex, or national origin”. The question is whether skipping over a gay worker for a promotion or firing her on the basis of her sexual orientation amounts to discrimination “because of sex”—and whether similar treatment of trans people fits that bill.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two of the cases—&lt;em&gt;Altitude Express, Inc. v Zarda &lt;/em&gt;and&lt;em&gt; Bostock v Clayton County, Georgia&lt;/em&gt;—involve gay men. Donald Zarda, a sky-diving instructor, and Gerald Bostock, a child-advocate employee, both say their sexual orientation (and in Mr Bostock’s case, his participation in a gay softball league) cost them their jobs. Mr Zarda died in a jumping accident in Switzerland before the litigation began but won a posthumous &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.glad.org/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/zarda-second-circuit-opinion-2-26-18.pdf&quot;&gt;victory&lt;/a&gt; at the Second Circuit Court of Appeals in 2018. Judge Robert Katzmann found that discriminating on the basis of sexual orientation is “a subset of sex discrimination” since it is rooted in stereotypes about “how persons of a certain sex can or should be”. To sack “a man because he is attracted to men is a decision motivated, at least in part, by sex”. By contrast, the Eleventh Circuit Court of Appeals curtly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.scotusblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/17-1618-opinion-below.pdf&quot;&gt;rejected&lt;/a&gt; Mr Bostock’s claim, finding it foreclosed by a 1979 precedent which concluded that “[d]ischarge for homosexuality is not prohibited by Title VII”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;R.G. &amp;amp; G.R. Harris Funeral Homes Inc. v Equal Employment Opportunity Commission,&lt;/em&gt; the third case, poses two slightly different questions about a transgender woman, Aimee Stephens, who lost her job at a funeral home when she told her boss she would no longer dress or present herself as Anthony. The Supreme Court will ask whether dismissing employees based on their “status as transgender” violates Title VII. It will also consider whether discriminating based on “sex stereotyping” violates the law. The issues are connected but analytically distinguishable: it could conceivably be acceptable to fire someone for being transgender as long as the reason is not linked to any particular behaviour or practice. The violation of Ms Stephens’s civil rights could be traced to the boss’s refusal to let her wear a dress to work and present herself as a woman, not to a general policy of disdain for transgender employees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This distinction may sound fine, but the Sixth Circuit Court of Appeals based its &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.opn.ca6.uscourts.gov/opinions.pdf/18a0045p-06.pdf&quot;&gt;ruling&lt;/a&gt; in favour of Ms Stephens squarely on the sex-stereotyping claim. In urging the justices not to hear the appeal, Ms Stephens &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/DocketPDF/18/18-107/67903/20181024150403351_18-107%20RGGR%20Harris%20Funeral%20Homes%20v%20EEOC%20Brief%20in%20Opposition.pdf&quot;&gt;argued&lt;/a&gt; the case was a poor vehicle for considering whether Title VII bars discrimination according to gender identity. The funeral home fired Ms Stephens’s, her lawyers wrote, “because her appearance and behaviour failed to conform to its sex stereotypes”. That type of discrimination “requires no determination of whether discrimination based on transgender status itself constitutes sex discrimination under Title VII”. Instead, it is universally acknowledged by all appeals courts to be barred by &lt;em&gt;Price Waterhouse v Hopkins,&lt;/em&gt; a 1989 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.oyez.org/cases/1988/87-1167&quot;&gt;decision&lt;/a&gt; in which the Supreme Court read Title VII to preclude employers from disfavouring female workers based on “stereotypical notions about women&amp;#x27;s proper deportment”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main strike against the plaintiffs in these three cases is obvious: none of the lawmakers in Congress in 1964 believed they were barring LGBT discrimination when they included “sex” among the prohibited bases of differential treatment in the workplace. But that is not the end of the story, even—perhaps especially—for conservative justices who purport to be textualists. More than two decades ago, Justice Antonin Scalia &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.oyez.org/cases/1997/96-568&quot;&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt; a unanimous majority opinion in &lt;em&gt;Oncale v Sundowner Offshore Services, Inc&lt;/em&gt; vindicating another claim that never crossed the minds of the mid-century legislators: a male employee’s right not to be harassed at work. Sexual harassment of men may not have been among the evils members of Congress thought they were combating when they drafted the Civil Rights Act, but the workplace harm is “reasonably comparable” to others Congress was thinking of. What should matter for a textualist are the words in the statute, not the motivations of its authors. “It is ultimately the provisions of our laws rather than the principal concerns of our legislators”, Mr Scalia wrote, “by which we are governed”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 22:06:26 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A bid to grab power in Venezuela, and more from our daily podcast]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/01/a-bid-to-grab-power-in-venezuela-and-more-from-our-daily-podcast]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/theintelligence_twitter_6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-01T11:20:37Z&quot;&gt;May 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUAN GUAIDÓ, the opposition figure widely viewed as the legitimate leader of Venezuela, has made a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/04/30/juan-guaido-makes-a-dramatic-attempt-to-oust-venezuelas-regime&quot;&gt;dramatic attempt&lt;/a&gt; to seize power from President Nicolás Maduro. But the effort appears to have stalled; how did it go wrong? We also look more widely at coups around the world, why they succeed or fail, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/23/how-to-predict-a-coup&quot;&gt;how to predict them&lt;/a&gt;. And a dramatic embassy raid reveals why it’s so tough to be a North Korean &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/27/campaigning-against-the-north-korean-regime-is-a-thankless-task&quot;&gt;dissident&lt;/a&gt;. Runtime: 22min.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/putschcomestoshove-venezuela&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 20:07:00 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>