<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Two new documentaries survey ecological battlegrounds]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/07/02/two-new-documentaries-survey-ecological-battlegrounds]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BKP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-02T14:55:08Z&quot;&gt;Jul 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE FOCAL points of landscape art changed in the 1970s and 1980s. Where painters and photographers from Caspar David Friedrich to Ansel Adams had homed in on awe-inspiring, untouched vistas with mountains, valleys and lakes, a new generation of artists focused instead on grey car parks, nuclear-test sites and the vast swathes of land being cleared for suburban development. “Landscape is no longer an aesthetic refuge,” Rebecca Solnit, a writer, historian and activist, observed in 1990, “but a battleground.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That idea is dramatised in two new documentaries about mankind’s despoliation of the planet: “Earth”, directed by Nicolas Geyrhalter, and “Anthropocene: The Human Epoch” by Edward Burtynsky, Jennifer Baichwal and Nicholas de Pencier. Both films use drones to range across the globe and capture scenes of environmental degradation, including thousands of poached elephant tusks confiscated by the Kenyan government, the startlingly colourful waterways of the Atacama desert (polluted in the production of lithium), and the gleaming white caverns of the Carrara marble mine in Italy. In “Anthropocene” these devastated landscapes (pictured top and below)—shot in bold colours and majestic wide angles—have a strange and almost improper beauty. “Earth”, meanwhile, favours an approach which is both more subtle and more powerful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BKP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190706_BKP505.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190706_BKP505.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190706_BKP505.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190706_BKP505.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190706_BKP505.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190706_BKP505.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190706_BKP505.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190706_BKP505.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190706_BKP505.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Anthropocene” is an anthology of misery, filmed by three different directors but strung together by an overarching voiceover which provides context and factual information in each new scene. By contrast, “Earth” does away with voiceover and mixes drone footage with other perspectives. The viewer is shown a giant earth-moving machine from high above, hacking away at a mountain in Hungary, followed by the man who operates it—the camera follows close behind as he walks the hundreds of metres up the vast metal contraption to his cabin. Later, enjoying a lunchtime sandwich, the worker talks of his alarm at the rapidly shrinking glaciers in the region where he goes on holiday every year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Geyrhalter anchors “Earth” (pictured below) in interviews with labourers in the mining trade (something of a departure for a director who has often preferred an observational mode). An American foreman engaged in levelling a range in California expresses unease about the speed with which he and his team can destroy vast, ancient lands in a matter of months: “Do I want to tear the hills down? No!” Yet he sees no other option given the demands of the market. A worker employed at a mine in Spain, a site once exploited by the ancient Romans, muses on the rise and fall of empires, and how they always sow the seeds of their own destruction. These unexpectedly lyrical conversations make the point that climate change is as much a tale of the absurdities of human psychology, and the contradictions that it can tolerate, as it is about rainforests, oil deposits, eco-systems and emissions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190706_BKP503_0.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;These films imply that more effort should be made to probe the underlying motivations for ecological damage, be they economic, psychological or political. Neither film offers easy solutions. The spectacular approach of “Anthropocene” is unsatisfying: after surveying the various battlegrounds from high above, the viewer has no better understanding of the causes of the war, let alone how to end it. Climate devastation is portrayed almost as a catastrophe visited upon Earth by malevolent outside forces. “Earth” imparts a slim measure of hope: if environmental ruin is a human phenomenon, then it is also within humans’ power to stop it. Persuading them to care about it in the first place, however, remains a surprisingly difficult artistic challenge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Earth” is screening in Britain now. “Anthropocene: The Human Epoch” will be released in America in September&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 23:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[British Jews trace Iberian heritage to retain EU citizenship]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/07/02/british-jews-trace-iberian-heritage-to-retain-eu-citizenship]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BRP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ELLA RACHAMIM can remember the moment she discovered Britain had voted to leave the European Union as if it were yesterday. Rather than turn off the television and go to sleep, the disappointed Remain-voter picked up her laptop and navigated to the website of the Portuguese government. The research begun that night has led Dr Rachamim, a paediatrician from London, to the brink of receiving a Portuguese passport. Her only connection to the country, and her sole qualification for citizenship, is that her ancestors were expelled from it during a bout of anti-Semitism half a millennium ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A year before the Brexit referendum of 2016, Portugal and Spain passed laws which offered Sephardic Jews—those whose families once lived on the Iberian peninsula—a path to citizenship. Each country intended the gesture to act as recompense for the forcible exile of Jews in the 1490s, in one of the first acts of the Spanish Inquisition. But the two countries have unwittingly offered a lifeline for Remainers anxious to retain EU citizenship after Britain leaves the bloc. “I really want to be European, I want my kids to be European,” says Dr Rachamim. To guarantee her three children’s ability to live and work across the continent, she has sought Spanish passports for them, on top of her own application to Portugal. The cost will run to more than £10,000 ($12,650).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She is not alone. A friend and fellow Sephardic Jew, Fran Leigh, has also embarked on the expensive process. “I wanted to prove to my child that freedom of movement is the most precious thing we can have as human beings,” she says. Campus, an Israeli firm which has been helping to manage applications by Sephardim, says the majority of its British clients are Remainers. “It comes in waves,” says Eylon Kasif, a company spokesman. “Every time Theresa May did a speech about the Brexit.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far at least 420 British Jews have been granted Portuguese passports under the new law; a handful more have obtained passports from Spain (whose rules are stricter, at least for adults). The process requires applicants to demonstrate ancestry dating back to at least the mid-18th century, when Sephardim arrived in England. David Mendoza, a genealogist, says this is fairly straightforward, as the tight-knit community’s synagogue kept excellent records. Nobody knows for sure how many of Britain’s 280,000 or so Jews have Sephardic heritage; Mr Mendoza estimates that the number is in the tens of thousands. He has helped about 200 people research their ancestry in order to claim Spanish or Portuguese citizenship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among their reasons for wanting to secure an EU passport before Brexit, some Sephardim cite concerns about rising anti-Semitism. Dr Rachamim believes the referendum unleashed racism that had been simmering under the surface. “Even though the Holocaust didn’t directly affect my family, I always felt there was this thread of fear that it would happen again,” she says. Britain’s equality watchdog is investigating whether the opposition Labour Party illegally discriminated against Jews. Jewish leaders recently condemned the party’s “disgraceful step backwards in its half-baked ‘fight’ against anti-Semitism,” after it readmitted (and later re-suspended) Chris Williamson, an MP accused of showing prejudice towards Jews.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Portuguese Jewish groups advertise what they say is a friendlier environment in their country. The Jewish Community in Porto claims there is “no anti-Semitism in the city”, making it perhaps the “best safe haven for Jews in Europe.” Mr Mendoza, a ninth-generation Londoner, is wary of such language, noting that it could even inadvertently reinforce anti-Semitic tropes which cast Jews as rootless wanderers. “My family unpacked their bags over 300 years ago. It sounds a little bit hysterical to me, to be honest,” he says. Most Sephardim claiming citizenship in Iberia come from countries such as Turkey or Venezuela, where political conflict is of a different order to that in Britain. “The whole world is very strange at the moment,” he concedes. “But for Jews, England has been since the times of Cromwell a good place to live.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 23:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“A nasty kind of confrontational mood”—Hong Kong’s protests boil over]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/07/02/a-nasty-kind-of-confrontational-mood-hong-kongs-protests-boil-over]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_blm502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-02T11:33:55Z&quot;&gt;Jul 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PROTESTORS ARE in a defiant mood—a hard core of them has smashed up &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/30/hong-kong-protesters-storm-the-legislative-council&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hong Kong’s Legislative Council&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/a&gt; But demonstrations aren’t going to make the territory any more &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/china/2019/06/29/xi-jinping-sees-protests-in-hong-kong-as-a-threat-to-the-party&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;free.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; The state-owned investment vehicles known as &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/15/gulf-states-are-becoming-more-adventurous-investors&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;sovereign-wealth funds&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; are usually cautious; those of the Gulf region are proving much more adventurous and less transparent. And, a look at the future of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/06/15/what-happens-to-those-who-die-poor-or-unclaimed-in-nyc&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New York’s island of the dead.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/902fff00-95e9-4f30-9b22-fd9912738936&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 21:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hong Kong protesters storm the legislative council]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/30/hong-kong-protesters-storm-the-legislative-council]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_CNP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-30T16:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE DAY began with an official celebration of the return of Hong Kong to China on July 1st. It ended in the ransacking of a government building and tear gas. The televised chaos, including scenes of protesters violently smashing their way into and trashing the Legislative Council building, where some displayed the British and colonial-era flags, represent the latest test for Carrie Lam, the chief executive of Hong Kong, and for Xi Jinping, her ultimate boss in Beijing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A wave of massive protests in recent weeks has left them searching for how best to respond to the demands of citizens of Hong Kong, who fear that their freedoms are being whittled away under Chinese rule. Opposition has been galvanised, in particular, by a bill that would make it possible for people accused of crimes in mainland China to be sent there to face trial. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On June 15th Ms Lam had tried to appease protesters by postponing consideration of the bill. But protesters have called for it to be withdrawn entirely. Many have also called on Ms Lam to resign. In response Hong Kong leaders have tried thus far a mixture of patience, contrition and hard-nosed police tactics. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The day started with a new note of contrition from Ms Lam. The ceremony marking the 22nd anniversary of the handover was held at Hong Kong’s exhibition centre, where dignitaries watched a broadcast of the raising of the Chinese flag. In her remarks Ms Lam departed from the usual convention of opining on the progress of the city under Chinese rule, promising instead that her government would listen to the demands of the people and be more open. Meanwhile, on the streets outside, protesters were facing off with police. The contrast was stark. Television stations were using split screens to juxtapose the pomp of the ceremony with the running street battles outside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At around 2pm thousands of protesters left Victoria Park as part of a police-sanctioned march through the city. This was the third huge peaceful march to take place in under a month. Whereas the others had ended at Tamar Park, home to Hong Kong’s central government offices and Legislative Council (which is known as Legco), this time organisers asked the crowds to continue westward past the government buildings. Most obeyed. But several thousand protesters, most of them younger, veered right to help form a swelling crowd around Legco.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many wore masks to protect themselves from tear gas (and facial recognition technology). Some donned goggles to guard against pepper spray and helmets to protect from truncheons. Human supply chains passed along umbrellas, rolls of cling-film, cable-ties, pairs of scissors and bottles of water to the front line. Protesters uprooted metal fences from surrounding streets and dragged heavy bollards and bins to barricade the streets. Like all of the protests which have shaken the city in the past month, there was no obvious leader. Communications were shouted or conveyed by hand signals. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After being criticised for using excessive force, including rubber bullets, on protesters on June 12th, Hong Kong’s police force had become more passive. By the early evening protesters had smashed large glass doors and gained access to an atrium at Legco. Metal gates inside might have stopped them there, but within hours protestors had breached that defence as well. They swiftly made their way to the council chamber, a circular room where the city’s 70 lawmakers convene. Some smashed fittings and sprayed anti-government and pro-democracy graffiti on the walls while others read out their demands, which included universal suffrage for Hong Kong. Many regard the Hong Kong government as a puppet of central-government leaders in Beijing.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In this leaderless movement, decisions are made collectively on the hoof, or by emotional fiat of the moment. &lt;em&gt;Apple Daily&lt;/em&gt;, a newspaper, reported that one man inside the chamber was offering protesters the choice of whether to stay or leave. Police said that they would arrest anyone who had gone inside the building. Shortly after midnight police in riot gear cleared the streets near Legco with tear gas. Protesters withdrew from the chamber before police pushed their way in.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Some commentators were incredulous that security services had allowed Legco to be stormed in the first place. But others mused that the violence and chaos played into the hands of the authorities.The protesters&amp;#x27; display of Hong Kong’s old colonial flag in the chamber was a symbolic rebuke of the handover 22 years ago. That sort of provocation could help the government and pro-Beijing media cast protesters in a negative light. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On July 2nd Ms Lam held a 4am press conference in which she took a more defiant stance than in her handover speech, condemning the storming of Legco and declaring that authorities would &amp;quot;pursue any illegal acts&amp;quot; by protesters. But she also said she was willing to listen to the concerns voiced in the protests. O&lt;span&gt;rganisers say that more than &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;500,000&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; people participated&lt;/span&gt; in the protest march on July 1st. However authorities respond to the ransacking of Legco by several hundred protesters, they still must contend with millions of others in Hong Kong who have taken to the streets in recent weeks to register their dismay with the direction of their city under Chinese rule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 09:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hong Kong protesters storm the legislative council]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/07/01/hong-kong-protesters-storm-the-legislative-council]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_CNP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE DAY began with an official celebration of the return of Hong Kong to China on July 1st. It ended in the ransacking of a government building and tear gas. The televised chaos, including scenes of protesters violently smashing their way into and trashing the Legislative Council building, where some displayed the British and colonial-era flags, represent the latest test for Carrie Lam, the chief executive of Hong Kong, and for Xi Jinping, her ultimate boss in Beijing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A wave of massive protests in recent weeks has left them searching for how best to respond to the demands of citizens of Hong Kong, who fear that their freedoms are being whittled away under Chinese rule. Opposition has been galvanised, in particular, by a bill that would make it possible for people accused of crimes in mainland China to be sent there to face trial. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On June 15th Ms Lam had tried to appease protesters by postponing consideration of the bill. But protesters have called for it to be withdrawn entirely. Many have also called on Ms Lam to resign. In response Hong Kong leaders have tried thus far a mixture of patience, contrition and hard-nosed police tactics. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The day started with a new note of contrition from Ms Lam. The ceremony marking the 22nd anniversary of the handover was held at Hong Kong’s exhibition centre, where dignitaries watched a broadcast of the raising of the Chinese flag. In her remarks Ms Lam departed from the usual convention of opining on the progress of the city under Chinese rule, promising instead that her government would listen to the demands of the people and be more open. Meanwhile, on the streets outside, protesters were facing off with police. The contrast was stark. Television stations were using split screens to juxtapose the pomp of the ceremony with the running street battles outside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At around 2pm thousands of protesters left Victoria Park as part of a police-sanctioned march through the city. This was the third huge peaceful march to take place in under a month. Whereas the others had ended at Tamar Park, home to Hong Kong’s central government offices and Legislative Council (which is known as Legco), this time organisers asked the crowds to continue westward past the government buildings. Most obeyed. But several thousand protesters, most of them younger, veered right to help form a swelling crowd around Legco.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many wore masks to protect themselves from tear gas (and facial recognition technology). Some donned goggles to guard against pepper spray and helmets to protect from truncheons. Human supply chains passed along umbrellas, rolls of cling-film, cable-ties, pairs of scissors and bottles of water to the front line. Protesters uprooted metal fences from surrounding streets and dragged heavy bollards and bins to barricade the streets. Like all of the protests which have shaken the city in the past month, there was no obvious leader. Communications were shouted or conveyed by hand signals. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;After being criticised for using excessive force, including rubber bullets, on protesters on June 12th, Hong Kong’s police force had become more passive. By the early evening protesters had smashed large glass doors and gained access to an atrium at Legco. Metal gates inside might have stopped them there, but within hours protestors had breached that defence as well. They swiftly made their way to the council chamber, a circular room where the city’s 70 lawmakers convene. Some smashed fittings and sprayed anti-government and pro-democracy graffiti on the walls while others read out their demands, which included universal suffrage for Hong Kong. Many regard the Hong Kong government as a puppet of central-government leaders in Beijing.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;In this leaderless movement, decisions are made collectively on the hoof, or by emotional fiat of the moment. &lt;em&gt;Apple Daily&lt;/em&gt;, a newspaper, reported that one man inside the chamber was offering protesters the choice of whether to stay or leave. Police said that they would arrest anyone who had gone inside the building. Shortly after midnight police in riot gear cleared the streets near Legco with tear gas. Protesters withdrew from the chamber before police pushed their way in.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Some commentators were incredulous that security services had allowed Legco to be stormed in the first place. But others mused that the violence and chaos played into the hands of the authorities.The protesters&amp;#x27; display of Hong Kong’s old colonial flag in the chamber was a symbolic rebuke of the handover 22 years ago. That sort of provocation could help the government and pro-Beijing media cast protesters in a negative light. Organisers says more than a half-million people participated in the protest march. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;It is unclear how Ms Lam, or Mr Xi, will greet the new day on July 2nd. But however they respond to the storming of Legco by several hundred protesters, they still must contend with millions of others in Hong Kong who have taken to the streets in recent weeks to register their dismay with the direction of their city under Chinese rule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 05:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[In Turkey, demography is a brake on Islamisation]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/07/01/in-turkey-demography-is-a-brake-on-islamisation]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BLP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-01T18:18:16Z&quot;&gt;Jul 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TURKEY’S PRESIDENT, Recep Tayyip Erdogan, makes no secret of his desire to raise what he calls a “pious generation”. Since his Justice and Development (AK) party became Turkey’s dominant force in 2002, elevating Islam’s public role in this constitutionally secular republic has been more than a slogan; it has found expression in many government policies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During his sixteen years in power, Mr Erdogan has presided over the construction of thousands of new mosques and Islamic vocational schools, known as imam hatips. The number of students at such institutions has increased more than fivefold since 2012, to an estimated 1.4m in a country of about 80m. The budget of the religious directorate, the agency responsible for the conduct of sermons in the country’s mosques, has grown by leaps and bounds, overtaking several ministries in the process. The government has quietly cultivated relations with a number of Islamic movements and brotherhoods, helping them accumulate considerable power and wealth. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But curiously these policies do not seem to have had the desired result. Turks do not appear to be any more devout than they were a decade ago, scores of Islamic schools remain empty, and the brotherhoods seem increasingly out of step with a rapidly changing society. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to a study by KONDA, a local polling company, between 2008 and 2018 the share of Turks who define themselves as religious dipped from 55% to 51%. The number of women who wear the Islamic headscarf barely budged, from 52% a decade ago to 53%, and the share of those who fast regularly decreased from 77% to 65%. Meanwhile, the number of atheists has risen from 1% to 3%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In spite of the money the government has poured into imam hatip schools, which combine a standard education with hours of study of Islam, supply continues to outstrip demand. At the high-school level, imam hatips filled only 52% of available places last year, compared with 95% for regular schools. Such schools are also much less successful than others. Imam hatip students are at least twice as unlikely to enrol in a university as students at regular or private schools. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arguably the biggest brake on political Islam’s attempts to reshape Turkish society has been demography, says Bekir Agirdir, the head of KONDA. The pace of migration from the countryside to the city in Turkey has been relentless. To some extent, that has made Turkey’s urban spaces more religious and conservative in atmosphere; but over time many of the new city-dwellers tend to develop a more à la carte approach to religion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the last couple of decades the percentage of Turks living in urban areas has shot up from 64% to 75%, according to the World Bank. The population of Istanbul has been expanding by an average of more than 300,000 people per year. “Urbanisation has created its own value system, as well as a big number of grey areas,” says Mr Agirdir. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many young people born into religious families are searching for an Islam compatible with modern urban life and middle-class status, he says. To make ends meet, wives and daughters who would have been confined to the home in villages and small towns go out in pursuit of work. Unmarried conservative couples attend pop concerts and embrace in public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, the religious brotherhoods, whatever their relationship with the government, have struggled to connect with young Muslims. What is more, all brotherhoods were cast under a shadow when members of the best-known one, led by the exiled preacher Fethullah Gulen, participated in a violent coup in July 2016. Tens of thousands of alleged and actual Gulen supporters, most of whom played no role in the coup, have been thrown into jail. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For at least a part of the Islamic bourgeoisie, the line separating conservative and secular lifestyles is becoming increasingly blurred, says Etyen Mahcupyan, an adviser to a former AK prime minister. This implies a more selective approach to Islam and a more limited role for the brotherhoods. “Twenty years ago, a youngster who wanted to be religious would have looked for a guide and tried to do what he was told,” he says. “But now that youngster wants to redefine Islam for himself, and no guide can do that.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 03:40:34 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Japan resumes commercial whale hunting after more than 30 years]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/07/01/japan-resumes-commercial-whale-hunting-after-more-than-30-years]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_WOC71l.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SHOULD WHALES be hunted for profit? Japan is one of a handful of countries that says yes. In December the country announced it was leaving the International Whaling Commission (IWC)—its first withdrawal from an international body since the second world war—and would no longer abide by a global moratorium imposed by the IWC in 1986. Today Japanese whaling vessels set sail to hunt whales commercially for the first time in more than three decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Environmentalists and whale enthusiasts may despair, but some believe Japan’s decision may in fact be a face-saving admission that its long, expensive campaign to reverse the IWC’s moratorium is over. As Patrick Ramage of the International Fund for Animal Welfare, a conservation charity, recently told the Associated Press, “what we are seeing is the beginning of the end of Japanese whaling.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a start, Japan will no longer send ships on “scientific” whaling expeditions to the Antarctic, a practice criticised internationally as commercial whaling in disguise. Future hunts will be restricted to Japanese waters, and within the country’s exclusive economic zone. To prevent overhunting, commercial fishermen will be subject to a quota, currently set at 227 whales through the end of the year (in 2015 Japan reported taking 520 whales).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such quotas may be unnecessary. In the mid-1960s, Japanese fishermen hauled in nearly 25,000 whales (see chart). Since then the country’s whaling industry has shrunk to just a handful of small companies employing barely 300 people. Most Japanese, outside a handful of coastal towns, have lost their appetite for whale. Annual demand for whale meat has plummeted from 200,000 to 5,000 tonnes (equivalent to roughly 40 grams per person). Much of that piles up unsold in supermarket freezers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 02:40:01 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Education gives Kenyan prisoners hope of redemption and release]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/07/01/education-gives-kenyan-prisoners-hope-of-redemption-and-release]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_MAP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A SENIOR POLICEMAN in Kenya was recently sentenced to death for torturing and killing a prisoner who had been brought into a police station near Nairobi, Kenya’s capital, for drunkenly brawling with his wife. The policeman had thrashed him with a metal pipe, dunked his head in a drum of water and then, after the man had died, claimed he had been beaten by another prisoner, who was initially charged with the murder. Bribes were offered to other prisoners to incriminate their fellow inmate. But the judge rejected the story and sentenced the cop to death.&lt;br/&gt;The police usually enjoy impunity, especially when they kill suspected criminals, which they often do, sometimes by shooting them in the back of the head after nabbing them. More striking, in this case, was that, a mere four days after he was sentenced, the errant policeman was sitting in the front row of a class of 15 prisoners in Kamiti maximum-security jail outside Nairobi. Clad in the blue and white pyjama suit worn by convicts, he had already started a course in law under the auspices of London University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Through the African Prisons Project (APP), a British-backed NGO, about 65 Kenyan prisoners, almost all of them lifers or on death row, are taking classes in law, their papers sent back and forth between London and Nairobi, Kenya’s capital. The scheme was started by a British lawyer, Alexander McLean, in neighbouring Uganda 12 years ago. In Kamiti prisoners and warders often attend class together, sometimes helping each other with homework or jointly solving legal conundrums. “We’ve had so many success stories,” says George Dianga, the officer in charge of Kamiti. “APP has greatly improved the inmates’ capacity to make appeals. Now judges really do listen.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The APP has even helped change the law itself. One of its star students, Wilson Kinyua, who was set free in February after 19 years behind bars, had argued before the Supreme Court that the death penalty violated the constitution, which forbids cruel or inhumane punishment. In fact, no death sentence has been carried out in Kenya since 1987; thousands have had their sentences commuted to life imprisonment under presidential decrees. But the death penalty is still on the statute book. Thanks, however, to the constitutional challenge lodged by Mr Kinyua and his friends, the Supreme Court now accepts that death sentences should no longer be mandatory for murder (the recent case of the policeman was considered exceptionally heinous).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The law in Kenya is still heavily tilted against the poor, who are afforded no legal aid in their defence, except for capital crimes, unless a lawyer can be found who acts pro bono. Travesties of justice are frequent. Until the recent Supreme Court ruling, judges had little leeway to be lenient since various crimes carried mandatory sentences. Robbery with violence, for instance, used to carry a mandatory sentence of death, albeit often commuted to life. But life usually meant life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of the women prisoners serving life or facing a death sentence in the maximum security jail in Langata, on the other side of Nairobi from Kamiti, murdered their husbands or partners. Yet their standard claim that they suffered violent domestic abuse carried little extenuating weight when judges sentenced them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So a key facet of the APP has been to teach prisoners how to launch appeals and to argue for them in court. The prisoners pursuing London University courses stress that their aim is to help fellow inmates who were unable, for lack of education or money, effectively to defend themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the APP is sensitive to the charge of paternalistic interference in Kenya’s judicial system, the Kenyan government and especially its prison service have been happy to co-operate with it. The APP has sought to improve both prison conditions and the justice system itself. One effect has been to reduce the number of prisoners, nearly half of whom are on remand. Another is to warm relations between prisoners and their guards. And another is to lessen reoffending: according to the APP, none of its graduates, once freed, has slipped up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Above all, it has given prisoners hope. “APP has inspired us,” says William, a death-row prisoner who, after ten years inside, has both a poetic and lawyerly turn of phrase. “It has turned people from being unreasonable into being reasonable. Inasmuch our bodies are in prison, our minds are free. And we have minds that can move mountains.” Even the APP’s latest death-row student, the cop who tortured and murdered a prisoner, can hope for eventual redemption. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Jul 2019 02:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The singular genius of Pauline Kael]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/07/01/the-singular-genius-of-pauline-kael]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BKP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-01T15:38:39Z&quot;&gt;Jul 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PAULINE KAEL, the legendary film critic for the &lt;em&gt;New Yorker&lt;/em&gt;, would have turned 100 last month (she died in 2001). As part of the centenary celebrations an admiring and buoyant documentary, “What She Said: The Art of Pauline Kael”, was shown at the Edinburgh International Film Festival. The film makes it clear that Kael (pictured left) was the most influential critic in the history of the medium. And that she always will be: no other film writer can ever have the same impact she had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Partly this is because she was the funniest, the most combative, the most erudite and the most enthusiastic writer in the business (and that is the kind of hyperbole she enjoyed using herself). She expunged “term-paper pomposity” from her reviews, distancing herself from aloof “gentleman critics” by balancing her encyclopedic film knowledge with proudly subjective opinions, autobiographical tidbits, dirty jokes and remarks she overheard from other patrons in the cinema. Although her acidic wit was compared to Dorothy Parker’s, she saw herself as an outsider in New York and in the &lt;em&gt;New Yorker&lt;/em&gt;. A California rancher’s daughter, she was accused by a colleague of “trampling through the pages of the magazine with cowboy boots covered with dung”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Partly, though, Kael’s pre-eminence was a matter of timing. She was old enough to remember seeing silent movies with her parents in the 1920s, and yet she didn’t join the staff of the &lt;em&gt;New Yorker&lt;/em&gt; until 1968, when she was nearly 50. Prior to that, she had lurched from magazine to magazine, struggling to make a living. The problem was that she despised Hollywood’s big-budget crowd-pleasers, panning the likes of “The Sound of Music” as being overblown and sentimental. “American movies have never been more contemptible,” she declared in 1967, a stance that did not endear her to her editors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But 1967 was also the year when Arthur Penn’s controversially bloody “Bonnie and Clyde” was released. Most critics loathed or ignore it, but Kael was infatuated, and her 9,000-word defence of the outlaw biopic earned her a position at the &lt;em&gt;New Yorker&lt;/em&gt;. Suddenly, a generation of American film-makers was experimenting with the iconoclastic “New Wave” techniques of Europe’s auteurs—and Kael loved them. In particular, she loved the sex, the violence and the exploding heads she saw in the work of Francis Ford Coppola, Brian De Palma, Martin Scorsese and Robert Altman. There was none of that in “The Sound of Music”. And so it came about that a middle-aged single mother became a best-selling pundit by championing America’s youngest, hippest male directors. She made their careers, and they made hers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“What She Said” may not be particularly iconoclastic, but it is a lively, exhaustively researched, and stunningly well edited tribute to an uncompromising talent. Written and directed by Rob Garver, the documentary compiles excerpts from Kael’s journalism (read by Sarah Jessica Parker), hundreds of film clips and snippets of interviews with figures such as Camille Paglia, Paul Schrader, Quentin Tarantino, David O Russell and others. John Boorman, an English film-maker, recalls that when Kael was at her formidable peak, directors felt as if they were “under surveillance”. Ridley Scott is still angry about her dismissal of “Blade Runner” in 1982. On a chat show in 1973 Jerry Lewis, “The King of Comedy”, said that Kael was a “dirty old broad” who “never said a good word about me.” “But she’s probably the most qualified critic in the world”, he added.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just think about that: a film star praising a film critic on television and assuming that the audience would know who he was talking about. It would never happen now. In the modern, fragmented, cultural landscape, cinephiles no longer queue up to buy magazines which run 9,000-word essays by their favourite critics—they harvest opinions from countless blogs, tweets and podcasts instead. In the unlikely event that a 21st-century reviewer could write as scintillatingly as Kael did, and that she had a movement as inspiring as the American New Wave to write about, most people would still have no idea who she was or what she said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 23:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Wanted: a new writer to cover British economics]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/07/01/wanted-a-new-writer-to-cover-british-economics]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/articles/20180224_wop001_9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; is looking to hire a staff writer to cover British economics. Journalistic experience is not necessary: the last few people to do this job had not been journalists before they arrived at the paper. The ability to write clearly and entertainingly is, however, crucial. So is the ability to spot intriguing patterns in data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We test for these things mostly by asking for a sample article, which applicants should send, with a CV to: britaineconomicsjob@economist.com. Please write up to 700 words. Your article could be on some aspect of British macro- or microeconomics, or on political economy. Four recent examples follow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The job is based in London, but the successful candidate need not be British. We welcome applications from people of all backgrounds. The deadline is August 4th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Example articles:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2017/09/02/sterlings-depreciation-has-not-led-to-an-export-boom&quot;&gt;Sterling’s depreciation has not led to an export boom&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/06/four-years-after-its-steelworks-shut-redcar-is-recovering&quot;&gt;Four years after its steelworks shut, Redcar is recovering&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/03/07/why-british-housebuilders-are-making-such-juicy-profits&quot;&gt;Why British housebuilders are making such juicy profits&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2017/10/28/higher-interest-rates-could-hit-britains-vulnerable-economy&quot;&gt;Higher interest rates could hit Britain’s vulnerable economy&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 23:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>