<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[How America’s urban-rural divide shapes elections]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/03/how-americas-urban-rural-divide-shapes-elections]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_USP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-03T18:30:03Z&quot;&gt;Jun 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN NINE OF America’s 13 congressional elections between 1994 and 2018, the Republican Party won a greater share of seats than votes. In 2012, Democrats failed to garner a majority of seats while winning a broad popular vote victory. Even in the 2018 mid-terms, which were described as a “wave” election, &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; predicted that the Democrats had to win the popular vote in the House of Representatives by 5-6 percentage points to obtain a bare majority of seats. In the Senate, the situation is worse because of the way states magnify the pro-rural bias of America’s electoral institutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liberal activists and social scientists alike have blamed the Republican Party’s manipulation of the electoral system for much of this. But Democrats are battling a deeper structural problem than partisan gerrymandering. Jonathan Rodden, a political scientist at Stanford University, has written a book that explores the party’s real challenge: political polarisation has become inextricably linked with economic geography and population density. The electoral system magnifies the voices of the poor, sparsely populated and conservative countryside at the expense of voters in densely populated cities who tend to be richer, racially diverse, and liberal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In “Why Cities Lose: The Deep Roots of the Urban-Rural Political Divide”, Mr Rodden goes back to the 1870s and the origins of the labour movement. The Socialist Party in Reading, Pennsylvania takes on a microcosmic significance: it represented the interests of local manufacturing workers, but failed to win elections that required the input of the rural residents. The socialists were left with no political representation above the city level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So city-dwelling labourers began to find a home in the Democratic Party, which increasingly took on pro-labour views. Party bosses like Al Smith, the Democrats’ 1928 nominee for president, cut deals with local labour leaders to persuade them to join. While the Democratic Party still garnered a majority of its votes from rural areas in the north, the union between Democrats and urban labourers was born. Mr Rodden writes that in 1916, “a doubling of population density was associated with a 7 percent decrease in Democratic voting. By 1940, a doubling of population density was associated with a 5 percent increase”. The story in the South, where there was little organised labour, was quite different: Democrats’ prospects were kept afloat by predominantly rural segregationists, while business-owning Republican won elections in the cities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When, in the late 20th century, the parties’ realignment became complete, the causes were primarily ideological. Presidential elections in the 1950s had been characterised by the Democrats and Republicans taking opposing views on economic policy but they differed little on social issues. Lyndon Johnson’s signing of the Civil Rights Act of 1964 was a notable moment in this realignment, breaking the Democrats’ hold on the South and catalysing the cultural shifts that produced the modern Republican Party. Through the remainder of the century, the diverse constituencies that made up urban areas—the poor, union members, immigrants and minorities, educated elites and young progressives—gravitated toward the Democrats while Republicans enjoyed increasing vote share among the farmers, the rural poor and ultra-wealthy business owners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The result of this history was an electoral system that pitted city-dwellers against the exurban and rural population—with the cities losing. This is where Mr Rodden’s talent with statistics is most evident. He recounts that in Pennsylvania in 2012, Democratic candidates for Congress won 51% of the votes state-wide but came away with majorities in only 28% of the districts. This “strikingly counter-majoritarian result” was not just a product of pro-Republican partisan gerrymandering, argues Mr Rodden. After running a computer programme that generates 400 separate, equally populous congressional maps for the state, Mr Rodden finds that even “party-blind” plans disadvantage Democrats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That year was no hiccup. In all but one presidential election since 1952, the mean congressional district in Pennsylvania was much more Democratic than the median one—a testament to Democrats’ inefficient geographic distribution. This was true as recently as 2018—and not just in Pennsylvania, but nationwide. In last year’s mid-term elections, a majority of voters in Michigan, Wisconsin, Pennsylvania and North Carolina all cast ballots for Democratic candidates for state houses, but the party won a minority of seats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Rodden points out that the 2018 elections introduced another issue for the Democrats: whether or not they will move further left. Increasing liberalism within the party threatens the support of key suburban moderates who act as a barrier to further geographical disadvantage. The nomination of a socially moderate candidate for 2020 could help with that. And yet, opposition to President Donald Trump drove up Democratic margins in key suburban swing districts last year. If the president remains unpopular, Mr Rodden suggests, Democrats could win &amp;quot;narrow victories in districts where comfortable Republican victories had been the norm&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Rodden weighs a few longer-term solutions, among them electoral systems used elsewhere in the world. America might, for example, adopt a system of proportional representation. Allocating parties’ legislative seats in proportion to the votes they won would eliminate the geographic disadvantage the Democrats face. But this would require the repeal of a law from 1967, which a Republican-controlled Senate would be almost certain to block.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demographic change is perhaps most likely bring the greatest change in the Democrats’ favour. In the coming years, non-whites and today’s young voters will become increasingly large shares of the electorate. If Democrats run up big margins with these groups, a number of closely-contested states are likely to turn bluer. But winning congressional districts could be hard, and state legislatures harder still, as urban areas with increasing populations would still have to be cracked into several districts to ensure equal populations among them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the medium-term, Democrats’ best hope of rebalancing the electoral scale lies in converting suburban moderates to their cause and turning out non-voters. Both helped the Democrats overcome a big structural disadvantage in the 2018 mid-terms. But presidential politics are different. And there will still be the small states to magnify the voices of conservative, rural voters, hurting the Democrats’ chances of controlling the Senate. As Mr Rodden writes, &amp;quot;if neither reform nor demographic change is sufficient to diminish urban-rural polarisation, the United States must find ways to function as a divided society.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Why Cities Lose: The Deep Roots of the Urban-Rural Political Divide&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;By Jonathan Rodden. Basic Books; 336 pages; $18.99&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 04:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sudan’s generals turns their guns against protesters]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/03/sudans-generals-turns-their-guns-against-protesters]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_map502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-03T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHERE JUST weeks ago the scent of freedom was in the air there is now the smell of smoke and cordite. The sounds of jubilant song have given way to those of automatic gunfire and the screams of the dying. In the early hours of June 3rd Sudan’s armed forces moved against pro-democracy protesters who had been holding a sit-in since April outside the army’s headquarters in Khartoum, the capital of Sudan. They shot and killed at least 13 civilians (and possibly many more). All that remains of the carnival of democracy that had sprouted there are burnt tents and rubbish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the worst violence since demonstrations toppled Sudan’s brutal dictator, Omar al-Bashir, in early April. The Sudanese Professionals Association (SPA), which has spearheaded the uprising since it began last December, called it a “bloody massacre” and announced a campaign of “total civil disobedience” to topple the junta that took power in Mr Bashir’s place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trouble had been brewing for some weeks amid a fraught stand-off between protesters and the generals over who would control the country’s transition to democracy. Negotiators for both sides had agreed on some issues, such as the establishment of a civilian-led parliament and cabinet, and a three-year transition before elections. Such was the optimism that on May 15th leaders of the protest movement announced that they would have a deal signed with the generals within 24 hours. But this was premature because they had not reached agreement on the most contentious issue of all: who would be in charge of the sovereign council, the highest decision-making body that would oversee the move towards democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On May 16th, less than 24 hours after the supposed breakthrough, the TMC’s leader, Abdel Fattah al-Burhan, halted the talks and accused the protesters of undermining them by blocking roads in the capital. He claimed “armed infiltrators” had fired on soldiers. The opposition responded on May 28th by declaring a two-day strike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the attack on June 3rd, trust between the two sides has all but evaporated. Protesters say that all the country’s previous transitions were led by the armed forces and that the generals are determined to control this one, too. People in the opposition accuse Muhammad Hamdan Dagalo (who is widely known as Hemedti), the powerful deputy head of the TMC, of foul play. They say that the paramilitary unit he heads, the Rapid Support Forces (RSF), carried out the lethal attack against the sit-in, as well as earlier killings of protesters. Observers, including some foreign diplomats, think that Mr Dagalo wants to become president and that he may undermine any transition that excludes him from power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But he is not the only one with an incentive to act as a spoiler. Mr Bashir kept himself in power for 30 years by playing armed factions against one another and by allowing them to earn illicit incomes. Many in the TMC may lose out if Sudan moves towards democracy and establishes the rule of law. Many of them also fear justice for atrocities committed by government forces and its militias during Sudan’s long civil wars in Darfur and what is now South Sudan. “This is a game with huge stakes,” says Harry Verhoeven, the author of a book on Sudan. “Why would those who have guns give them up voluntarily?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest violence means there is even less hope for compromise. On one side are the generals, who have won the support of powerful autocratic countries in the region including Egypt, Saudi Arabia and the United Arab Emirates. Emboldened, they are no longer bothering to disguise their reluctance to cede power to civilians. “The negotiations were never serious from the beginning,” says Rashid Abdi, an independent expert on Sudan based in Nairobi. “The army was just playing for time.” On the other side are the demonstrators, who are angry at the betrayal of their democratic revolution. “This is not going to stop,” says Reem Abbas, a Sudanese journalist in Khartoum. “The protests are going to continue.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 04:40:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Chernobyl” is on track to become the highest-rated TV series ever]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/03/chernobyl-is-on-track-to-become-the-highest-rated-tv-series-ever]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_woc177.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-03T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AT TWENTY-THREE minutes past one in the morning of April 26th 1986, a safety test at a nuclear reactor in Soviet Ukraine went catastrophically wrong. The resulting steam explosion at the plant near the city of Pripyat, 70 miles north of Kiev, spewed out so much radiation that much of the surrounding area will be uninhabitable for 20,000 years. Harmful isotopes were carried by the winds as far as Ireland within a week. According to some accounts, first responders who were exposed to large doses of radiation suffered agonising deaths. These events, as well as the political intrigue of the Soviet government’s actions, are the subject of HBO’s historical drama series, “Chernobyl”. With one episode to go (the finale will air in America on June 3rd) it is the highest-rated television series of all time, according to crowd-sourced reviews on IMDb, a film and television rating site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reviewers have given the first four episodes of “Chernobyl” stellar ratings. A weighted average calculated by &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; (according to how recently each episode ran and the number of reviews) accords it 9.6 points out of 10. By the same measure, other leading shows—including comparable historical drama series such as “The Crown” and “The People v. O. J. Simpson” (now called “American Crime Story”)—lag behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is more, each episode of “Chernobyl” has been rated by users at 9.5 or higher, an impressive streak. According to &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s analysis of 517 episodes of popular television dramas, the likelihood that any show would produce four consecutive episodes that each score a 9.5 or above is roughly 0.4%. Apart from “Chernobyl”, only the final four episodes of “Breaking Bad”—previously the highest-rated show—have accomplished this feat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of this is even more impressive given its subject matter. Documentaries typically struggle to gain as much attention as action and fantasy shows such as “Game of Thrones”, and the same is true of historical dramas. Even series about well-known subjects, such as Queen Elizabeth II or the trial of O.J. Simpson, earn user ratings that are typically below those of the most popular shows. In comparison, “Chernobyl” scores better than the greats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The show has also caused a massive spike in interest about the actual disaster. Web traffic to the entry for the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chernobyl_disaster&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Chernobyl nuclear disaster&lt;/a&gt; on Wikipedia, an online encyclopedia, has increased 56-fold since the start of the year. Interest in a comparable nuclear disaster at Japan’s Fukushima Daiichi power plant in 2011 has also increased, though by a more modest 21 times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The final episode of “Chernobyl” already has a preliminary rating of 10 out of 10 among IMDb’s apparently clairvoyant reviewers. Though the episode’s rating might fall below perfect after tonight’s airing, the show looks poised to be not only the most-liked historical drama series of all time, but also, as rated by IMDb reviewers, the best television series in history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:41:05 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Liberty, democracy and the art of Martin Puryear]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/03/liberty-democracy-and-the-art-of-martin-puryear]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_BKP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-03T14:13:59Z&quot;&gt;Jun 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AT THE opening of the American pavilion at the Venice Biennale Lewis Eisenberg, America’s ambassador to Italy, stepped up to the microphone. He congratulated Martin Puryear and remarked that the title of his exhibition—“Liberty/ Libertà”— made him think of Ronald Reagan, who had often spoken of freedom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps he had yet to see the exhibition. The American president’s tenure was defined by the cold war and the crumbling of the Soviet Union; Mr Puryear’s focus for five decades has been black Americans’ historic struggle for human and civil rights. When chosen to represent the United States in Venice, he said he would do so “as both an artist and a citizen”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The son of a school teacher and a postal worker, Mr Puryear grew up in Washington, D.C., and his exceptional sculpting skills, most notably with wood, seem to date from his childhood. When he became interested in music, he made a guitar; later, an interest in archery inspired handmade bows and arrows. At university he switched from a degree in biology to one in art, specialising in painting. Later, as a member of the Peace Corp in Sierra Leone, watching African craftsmen at work encouraged him to return to 3D forms. But he studied print-making in Sweden before finally returning home in 1969 to study sculpture at Yale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He won acclaim with his first solo show at the Corcoran Gallery in D.C. in 1977, went on to take the grand prize at the São Paulo Biennial in 1989 and earned the National Medal of the Arts in 2012. In 2007 a retrospective of his work at the Museum of Modern Art in New York travelled to Washington, San Francisco and Fort Worth. But in recent years the 78-year-old African-American artist has probably become best known for “Big Bling”, an ambiguous monumental form topped with a gold-leaf shackle, installed in New York’s Madison Square Park in 2016. Here, as elsewhere, Mr Puryear imbues an abstract form with feeling and figurative references.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Ladder for Booker T. Washington”, made in 1996—a star piece of the touring retrospective and now on show at the Museum of Modern Art in Fort Worth—has a similar effect. An 11-metre ladder made of ash, it snakes tentatively upwards, so narrow at the top that its poles almost touch. The artist had set out to explore scale and perceptions of distance, but once the sculpture was finished it evoked for him “the gradual, often illusory, notion of progress that Washington [a civil-society leader] encouraged blacks to adopt in the 19th century against an overwhelming set of obstacles”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Mr Puryear’s work an everyday object such as a ladder can remind the viewer, unexpectedly, of history. In Venice the neoclassical American pavilion comes with historical baggage of its own: built in 1930, the edifice was inspired by Monticello, the house Thomas Jefferson designed for himself in Virginia. Some artists choose to ignore the architecture, but Mr Puryear engages forcefully with it, creating a work specifically for its central rotunda. A two-metre-high white fluted column, with a shackled stake driven into its top, the piece (pictured above) is a memorial for Sally Hemings, an African-American slave owned by Jefferson. The country’s third president was also the father of her children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In front of the pavilion Mr Puryear has placed a structure much like a rood screen, with lacy decorations that flow into a black hole at the top. Step around the back and you find that the piece, entitled “Swallowed Sun”, in fact has an ugly black tail. “Is it about the darkness of a solar eclipse—or a blackout when values are in jeopardy?” asked Brooke Kamin Rapaport, the curator of the pavilion, as the artist looked on, saying nothing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inside the building another commonplace object—headgear—invites the viewer, on the one hand, to celebrate revolutionary struggle, and on the other to contemplate violence. “Big Phrygian”, a smooth red mound of painted cedarwood with a flipped-over peak, evokes the &lt;em&gt;bonnet rouge&lt;/em&gt; worn by revolutionaries in France and later by enslaved blacks in the Caribbean as they rose up against the French (the work might send the viewer trawling Wikipedia to find out more about Trajan’s war against the Dacians, and to grasp how the cap’s symbolism evolved). “Tabernacle” (pictured top), the show’s closer, is shaped like a forage cap worn by both Union and Confederate infantry during the American civil war. The visitor peers in through the hat’s crown to see themselves reflected in a mirrored cannonball nestling in the barrel of a mortar—thus becoming part of the artist’s meditation on gun violence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Puryear has produced one of the most subtle and powerful shows of the Venice Biennale. With eight expertly crafted works he demonstrates both his skill as a sculptor and the originality of his thinking. He once remarked that his work is “more tactile and sensate than strictly cerebral”, but to the onlooker the balance seems fairly even. What impresses is his fusion of the two.       &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Venice Biennale continues until November 24th&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 21:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“She&#x27;s going to stick to her guns on Huawei. She&#x27;s got nothing to lose”—Theresa May and Donald Trump meet]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/03/shes-going-to-stick-to-her-guns-on-huawei-shes-got-nothing-to-lose-theresa-may-and-donald-trump-meet]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_opm501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-03T11:11:51Z&quot;&gt;Jun 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PRESIDENT DONALD Trump&lt;/strong&gt; kicks off his &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/02/donald-trumps-state-visit-to-britain&quot;&gt;state visit to Britain&lt;/a&gt; with some opening shots at London&amp;#x27;s mayor Sadiq Khan. But larger issues will take centre stage. Amid &lt;strong&gt;Brexit, a leadership contest and simmering security tensions, we discuss the strains on the “special relationship”.&lt;/strong&gt; We consider how regulators and tech giants can tackle the wilds of the internet to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/25/how-to-make-social-media-safe-for-children&quot;&gt;make browsing safe for children&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. And, &lt;strong&gt;a Ramadan &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/05/30/a-saudi-tv-series-hints-at-the-change-that-is-afoot&quot;&gt;drama in Saudi Arabia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; reveals how the crown prince wants his kingdom to be perceived. Runtime: 22 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/getpompedup-trump-sbritishvisit&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A Muslim appeal for Saudi Arabia to show mercy]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/06/02/a-muslim-appeal-for-saudi-arabia-to-show-mercy]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_blp902.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-02T18:40:14Z&quot;&gt;Jun 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;With all world religions, there are strains between the ancient heartland and the periphery. A Catholic campus in the American Mid-West feels different from the cloisters of the Vatican; the Buddhism embraced by Californian beach-goers lacks the rigour of a monastery in Thailand or Tibet. But in Islam, tensions of this kind, and the way they are resolved, can literally be a matter of life or death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least 80 respected scholars and teachers of the Muslim faith, from many countries but mostly Anglophone ones, have lent their names to a plea to the Saudi authorities. It urges the kingdom to spare the lives of three well-known figures in the world of Islam. The trio have been incarcerated on “terrorism” charges since 2017. They had refused to back the kingdom’s diplomatic and economic blockade of neighbouring Qatar, at a time when this was  becoming a litmus-test of loyalty and securing the support of prominent and mildly independent-minded imams seemed to have become a high priority for the regime. Prosecutors want the death penalty, and unconfirmed reports indicate they might be dispatched when the holy month of Ramadan ends on June 4th. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Best-known of the three is Salman al-Ouda, a religious teacher who has built up a global audience (with about 14m Twitter followers), having first gained prominence in the 1990s when he challenged the kingdom’s alliance with America against Saddam Hussein’s Iraq. In 1999 he emerged from a five-year jail term as a defender of the regime and an advocate of Sunni-Shia dialogue. For a while he was able to teach and act freely; in 2006 he attracted a big, enthusiastic audience in London.  Also facing execution are Awad al-Qarni, a preacher, academic and author, and Ali al-Omari, a popular broadcaster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what sort of people have been courageous enough to raise their voices in support of the trio, in defiance of the huge influence that Saudi Arabia and its austere brand of Sunni Islam can exercise in almost every corner of the Muslim world? For any mosque, institute or faculty that hopes one day to gain Saudi funding, backing such a document comes at a price. And in other Middle Eastern countries such as Jordan, Bahrain and Egypt, criticism of Saudi policies can end in prosecution or worse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The answer to that question provides a revealing snapshot of the state of global Islam. Virtually none of the signatories is based in a Muslim country. Yet among those who enjoy the freedom of the Western world, the theological range is remarkably broad. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To explain this, it helps to understand the categories into which Sunni Islam’s main exponents fall. There are those who follow the Muslim Brotherhood, a movement that aspires, usually peacefully, to shift both society and its governance in an Islamic direction. Then there are traditionalists, those less concerned with politics but who see Islam’s accumulated body of law and teaching as the only cure for the “bad theology” which inspires terrorism. A third category are Salafis who prefer to go back to the basic axioms of faith and life laid down by Muhammad and his immediate successors; some Salafis are aligned with the Saudi regime, others are a bit more liberal, and some are ruthless jihadists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among the people now appealing for the lives of the incarcerated trio, there are plenty of Brotherhood-minded scholars. One would expect that, given the poisonous standoff between the Saudis and the perceived Brotherhood stronghold of Qatar, the country which the trio had impertinently refused to condemn. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But more surprisingly, the appeal was initiated by traditionalist scholars, a camp which enjoys the respect of Western governments because of its eloquent critique of terrorism. The traditionalists don’t often intervene directly in earthly affairs, particularly when it comes to Saudi Arabia; this is a rare exception.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The document’s prime movers include Faraz Rabbani, a popular Muslim teacher of south Asian origin who studied for a long time in Jordan and Syria before settling in Canada. That is a classic traditionalist profile. Also on the list are some liberal Salafis, a couple of non-Muslims who are respected scholars of Islam and at least one Shia Muslim. Given the rifts within the Muslim world--especially since the Arab Spring, which triggered murderous feuds between Brothers, Salafis and traditionalists--it is quite impressive to see such a diverse list of names on a single piece of paper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the other hand, there are some striking gaps. Some of the most prominent figures in Western-based Islam are absent from the list, although their students and mentees do appear, possibly with their mentors’ discreet permission. (Lecturers from one of the West’s leading seminaries, Zaytuna College in California, are on the list but its founder, Hamza Yusuf, is not.) British signatories include Sulaiman Gani, a south London imam who forced ex-prime minister David Cameron to apologise for calling him extremist. But the leaders of Britain’s biggest mosques are noticeably missing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever the exact line-up, the appeal enjoys the approval of Mr al-Ouda’s American-based son, Abdullah, an academic scholar now based at Georgetown University. He believes the document carries real moral power, exactly because it challenges the Saudis’ claimed monopoly on Muslim wisdom. “The Saudi government is always concerned about its Islamic authority, they want to tell the West that they alone have the legitimate authority to speak about Islam.” It was in that spirit, he noted, that the kingdom in recent days hosted a conference with the paradoxically-chosen topic of “moderate Islam”, organised by the Saudi-backed Muslim World League.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jonathan Brown, an American signatory and convert to Islam who is a professor at Georgetown, said he hoped the appeal would lay bare the counter-productiveness of Saudi Arabia’s current policy. For as long as they were at liberty, the independent but broadly loyal views of teachers like Mr al-Qarni and Mr al-Ouda were a kind of advertisement for the kingdom’s fractionally loosening atmosphere. Capital punishment would have the opposite effect. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It remains hard to predict whether the executions will take place; there has been no official verdict yet. But events could unfold quickly.  If they do happen, the diverse luminaries of Western-based Islam will come together not in polite supplication but in quiet horror. (Western governments, to judge by their reaction to some recent executions, including that of 37 “spy suspects” and protesters in April, will express disapproval but not too loudly.) Meanwhile the gap between centre and the periphery will yawn wider than ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 03:40:01 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Charity begins at work]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/02/charity-begins-at-work]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190601_wbp504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE REPORT was devastating. The working environment at the organisation was described as “toxic”, there was widespread bullying of staff, a bunker mentality among senior management and 39% of employees developed mental or physical health issues as a result of their work. An investment bank or a technology firm in Silicon Valley? No. This was Amnesty International, a human-rights charity. Five managers have just left the organisation following the report’s findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Workplaces create their own hierarchies regardless of whether the aim of the operation is to help people or make money. Two female partners at KPMG, an accountancy group, recently left out of concern at the behaviour of a male colleague. Coming from a family of teachers, Bartleby can attest that school staff rooms are beset by bitter rivalries. Universities are famous for their internecine disputes, as captured in the adage that “academic politics are so vicious precisely because the stakes are so small.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Amnesty, the problem was not with staff motivation. The report, by the KonTerra group, a consultancy, makes clear that many employees regarded their job as a “vocation or life cause” that provided them with “a compelling sense of purpose and meaning”. But that commitment proved to be a double-edged sword.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, in the eyes of workers, managers believed the importance of the NGO’s work was so great that they did not need to listen to staff concerns. Employees, the higher-ups seemed to conclude, “should be grateful for being able to work at Amnesty”. Second, workers found it difficult to set healthy boundaries on their hours (or their tolerance of a toxic climate) owing to a deeply held belief in their mission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One cause of stress was a process called the Global Transition Programme (GTP) which moved the staff away from headquarters and closer to the abuses they covered. Workers felt that their views about these transfers were not seriously considered and that the implementation of the programme was rushed. As a result, employees found their work patterns disrupted, even as some moved to high-risk locations. Concerns came to a head when Gaëtan Mootoo, a long-term employee, committed suicide, leaving a note blaming work pressures. Another staff member committed suicide shortly afterwards, although inquries found no evidence that the death was work-related. The tragic incidents led to the commissioning of the report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what went wrong? On the surface, Amnesty seemed to offer services to help employees cope with stress. Staff were eligible for five counselling sessions, and an external reporting service for whistle-blowing had been created. Programmes were developed to train leaders and to help staff support their colleagues. But these efforts were described as “ad hoc, reactive and piecemeal”. In a survey 85% of employees said they had not been given enough guidance to support the well-being of their colleagues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The problem clearly came from the top. If senior management is not committed to a caring atmosphere, no amount of discussion groups or special programmes will make things better. &lt;br/&gt;A certain amount of stress at work is inevitable. Most organisations are hierarchical. Deadlines are a part of life, as is uncertainty over whether individual projects are going to succeed. But workers who are stressed and fearful are unlikely to stay in their jobs or be productive in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many managers derive a lot of their status from their oversight role. That is, in part, why organisations create such roles: they can reward high-achieving employees with a title, as well as with extra money. But power is seductive. Peter Cappelli, a scholar of human resources at the Wharton School in Philadelphia, says that toxicity arises when “the boss acts like a dictator and actively punishes people who articulate different views or express disagreement.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Amy Edmondson of Harvard Business School explained in her book, “The Fearless Organisation”, the ideal is to create an atmosphere of “psychological safety” where workers can speak their minds. Managers need to learn the art of “respectful inquiry”, where they ask employees questions and listen intently to the answers. The bosses at Amnesty may have listened to the political dissidents whose causes they were championing. But they clearly weren’t listening to their staff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 01:40:16 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The leader of Germany&#x27;s Social Democrats resigns]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/02/the-leader-of-germanys-social-democrats-resigns]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A PALL of uncertainty hangs over German politics after Andrea Nahles resigned as leader of the Social Democratic Party (SPD), the junior coalition partner, on June 2nd. Ms Nahles, an SPD veteran who has served in previous governments, will step down from both the party chairmanship and the presidency of its parliamentary caucus. She also said she would leave the Bundestag, without naming a date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Nahles’s departure, long forecast in some SPD circles, was hastened by a week of grim news for the party. On May 26th the SPD sank to a dismal 15.8% in the European elections, down by 11.5 percentage points on its 2014 result, and lost the city-state of Bremen for the first time in seven decades. A recent poll put it at just 12%, less than half the score of the surging Greens. As rumour swirled and party barons plotted, Ms Nahles sought to flush out her internal enemies by putting her leadership of its parliamentary group up for early election. But although no candidates emerged to challenge her, the continued disquiet convinced Ms Nahles that, as she said this morning, she “no longer had the support required to carry out her duties”. Something had to give.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Nahles’s resignation reignites questions over the future of Germany’s “grand” coalition, which unites the SPD with Angela Merkel’s centre-right Christian Democratic Union and its Bavarian sister party, the Christian Social Union. This awkward marriage has been on the rocks from almost the moment it was established, in March 2018. A string of political missteps and poor election results has only strengthened the hand of those in the SPD base who always believed the party would decline further in government and needed a spell in opposition. This afternoon both Mrs Merkel and Annegret Kramp-Karrenbauer, the CDU leader, urged the SPD to find a successor for Ms Nahles quickly. They said their party remained committed to the coalition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The SPD’s woes will hardly end with Ms Nahles’s defenestration. The party’s quarrelsome bench is thin on potential replacements. Beyond a parade of ex-leaders who continue to offer views, solicited or otherwise, Olaf Scholz, the vice-chancellor and finance minister, is the only SPD figure with a national profile, and he has plenty of foes himself. More difficult state elections lie ahead, in Germany’s east. The Greens continue to eat into the party’s voter base. And at the end of the year, a half-time review clause in the coalition agreement provides the SPD’s coalition sceptics with a formal platform to agitate for departure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The case against leaving nonetheless remains strong. The SPD is enjoying some policy success in government, in areas such as arms-exports and immigration. Triggering an election - the likely consequence of walking out - would probably wipe out large swathes of its representation in the Bundestag. Under the gaffe-prone Ms Kramp-Karrenbauer the CDU looks more vulnerable than it has for years. Yet the implicit promise of rejoining the CDU/CSU was that the SPD could renew itself in government. That has patently not held. Now the question is whether Germany’s coalition can.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 01:40:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s state visit to Britain]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/02/donald-trumps-state-visit-to-britain]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190601_brp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even before arriving in London on June 3rd for a three-day state visit, President Donald Trump stirred controversy, weighing in with views on potential successors to Theresa May as prime minister. The visit itself will be an extravaganza of protests and pomp. It will also be a test of how “special” the relationship between America and Britain can remain in the face of serious strains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The president is coming at a febrile time in British politics. Mrs May is about to step down as Conservative party leader, and once Mr Trump leaves she will trigger the formal start of the race between at least a dozen candidates to replace her. Like the Tories, the Labour Party took a pounding in the recent European elections; it is also beset by allegations of anti-Semitism. The country’s divisions over Brexit look deeper than ever. In such circumstances a typical visiting head of state would strive to rise above it all with tact and diplomacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not Mr Trump. On his previous working trip to Britain as president last July he embarrassed Mrs May with an interview in the Sun newspaper in which he criticised her position on Brexit and praised Boris Johnson, who had just resigned as foreign secretary. True to form, this time Mr Trump told the Sun shortly before his arrival that Mr Johnson, now front-runner in the race to be prime minister, would be “excellent” as leader. Once again he criticised Britain’s negotiating strategy for Brexit: “the UK allowed the European Union to have all the cards.”&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;As last time, too, protesters will be out in force, probably again with a giant inflatable of a baby Trump in a nappy. A few prominent figures are flagging their opposition to the visit—peevishly, critics say—by turning down their invitation to attend a state dinner on Monday. They include the Liberal Democrats’ leader, Vince Cable, and Labour’s Jeremy Corbyn, who object to Britain rolling out the red carpet for a “misogynist and racist”. The Speaker of the House of Commons, John Bercow, is also staying away—and did not invite the president to address Parliament (something Barack Obama, Bill Clinton and Ronald Reagan did).&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Despite the sense of déjà vu, this visit is a bigger deal than last year’s, in two respects. First, tensions are simmering between the two countries over issues that go to the core of their relationship. One is Iran. America has pulled out of the nuclear accord with Iran and is ratcheting up sanctions against it. Now it is twisting European allies’ arms over their efforts to enable trade to flow with the help of a new payments system called Instex. The Treasury last month warned the Europeans that efforts to circumvent sanctions could have “severe consequences, including a loss of access to the US financial system”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America is also warning its close ally about its possible use of 5G technology from Huawei, a Chinese telecoms giant with a well-established presence in the country. Last month Mike Pompeo, America’s secretary of state, warned that relying on Chinese 5G kit might put intelligence-sharing at risk. “What can Her Majesty’s government do to make sure sensitive technologies don’t become open doors for Beijing’s spymasters?” he said in a speech in London last month. “Insufficient security will impede the United States’ ability to share certain information with trusted networks.” British diplomats have long tended to downplay talk of the special relationship with America—except when it comes to security. Any erosion of trust on intelligence-sharing would be deeply damaging.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump will no doubt make his views clear on these issues, but he will also be determined to wallow in the pageantry of a state visit. That is the second reason why this time is different: such things are grand occasions. He is bringing not just the First Lady but all his four adult children to meet the Queen.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;So there will be warmth amid the wariness. The visit will culminate in events to mark the 75th anniversary of the D-Day landings, a reminder of what Britain and America can achieve when they stand shoulder to shoulder. Mr Trump likes the fact that Britain is one of a handful of NATO allies that meets the target of spending 2% of GDP on defence. Jeremy Hunt, the foreign secretary and another would-be prime minister, has said he favours a decisive increase in defence spending (“I think that’s great,” Mr Trump told the Sun). And with his characteristic modesty Mr Trump professes to love Britain: “I don’t imagine any other US president was closer to your great land.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 17:41:25 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Does Santa Claus speak Danish, English or Russian?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/06/01/does-santa-claus-speak-danish-english-or-russian]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190601_amp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;THERE ARE three reasons why Thomas Nast, the 19th-century American illustrator who created the twinkly grandfather image of Santa Claus, decided to place his workshop at the North Pole. The location was cold enough for the reindeer that pulled his sleigh; it was sufficiently remote so that curious children could not contemplate a visit; and it lay in neutral territory, allowing Santa to be an international goodwill ambassador. The last will not be true for much longer. Three states—Russia, Denmark and Canada—are claiming that the seabed and subsoil at the top of the world are part of their countries’ extended continental shelf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;The claims come under the 1982 UN Convention on the Law of the Sea, an international treaty that all the states with Arctic coastlines, except the United States, have ratified (the US says it will abide by it). The treaty states that the first 12 nautical miles from a country’s shore are territorial waters, meaning the country has exclusive rights above and below the waters, and to the airspace. Countries can also claim up to 200 nautical miles from shore as an exclusive economic zone, giving them rights to marine life in the waters and minerals on or under the seabed. This zone can be further extended if the country can prove, using a wide range of scientific evidence, that the seabed is an extension of the country’s continental shelf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Russia, Denmark (on behalf of Greenland), and now Canada on May 23&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;rd&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt; have duly filed lengthy reports with the Commission on the Limits of the Continental Shelf, a body set up under the treaty to study the scientific evidence gathered with much blood, sweat and frozen tears. Although the polar ice cap is shrinking because of global warming, large parts of the ocean remain ice-bound for most of the year. To peer at the seafloor, scientists used icebreakers (although even a nuclear-powered one could not penetrate an area north of Greenland), and set up perilous, temporary camps on drifting ice floes. Colleagues on shore did a deep dive into history, trying to establish what was happening in the Arctic before and after dinosaurs roamed the earth. How underwater ridges and mountains formed millions of years ago can help determine which land mass they should be connected to today.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;The commission decides whether the science backing a claim is robust. Russia was told to do more work on its 2001 submission, which it refiled in 2015. But the body does not resolve disputes. Countries must negotiate an agreement on overlapping claims. And there are many. The Arctic is the smallest ocean, about 14m square kilometres; it accounts for just 4.3% of the world’s total water surface compared with 46.6% for the Pacific Ocean. The bit that does not fall within some country’s exclusive economic zone is only 2.8m square kilometres. Within that area, Russia is claiming 1.2m square kilometres, Denmark almost 1m and Canada 1.2m. All three claim large parts of the 1,800km-long Lomonosov ridge, which divides the Arctic Ocean into two main basins; and all three claim the geographic North Pole.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Anywhere else on Earth this would look like a recipe for armed conflict. A steady drumbeat of stories about the militarisation of the region creating to a new cold war in the Arctic lend support to that idea. Russia has been forthright about its ambitions. It made a big deal of planting a titanium Russian flag on the seabed at the North Pole in 2007. Yet armed conflict over rival claims is unlikely for two reasons. First, relations between countries and communities in the Arctic, although strained since the Ukraine crisis of 2014, remain cordial for the most part.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;The template for co-operation was set in 1996 when the eight countries with Arctic coastlines set up an inter-governmental forum called the Arctic Council, where they and indigenous peoples could co-operate on matters affecting the region. The sharp remarks made by Mike Pompeo, the American secretary of state, on the fringes of last month’s meeting of Arctic Council ministers in Finland were a break from this trend. (He criticised, among other things, Russia’s and Canada’s claims to control sea routes in the High North.) More in keeping with it was the presence of Russian lawmakers at a meeting in May of Arctic parliamentarians in Ottawa, even though Chrystia Freeland, Canada’s foreign minister, is banned from visiting Russia because of her strong denunciation of its actions in the Ukraine.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Co-operation is most evident in the scientific domain. To collect its data, Canada conducted joint surveys with Denmark, Sweden and the United States, with which it has an overlapping claim in the western Arctic. The scientists who posed for a photo at the North Pole in 2016 displayed the flags of 14 countries. Russia, Denmark and Canada could have blocked the commission from studying a rival’s claim, but each gave the required permissions and have remained in close contact throughout. Harold Brekke, a former commissioner from Norway, was cited as a special advisor on all three submissions.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;The prospect of a resource war looks equally flimsy. The US Geological Survey made headlines in 2008 when it estimated that the Arctic region contained 30% of the world’s undiscovered gas and 13% of its undiscovered oil. But most of the known or suspected reserves are within the 200-mile limit of national exclusive economic zones. Those found further out would be uneconomic to exploit because of the hostile environment and the distance to the ports and pipelines connecting the north to markets farther south. Commercial fishing in the high seas of the Arctic is already banned under an agreement signed in 2017 by the eight Arctic states plus China, Japan, South Korea and the European Union. As Andreas Osthagen, of the Fridtjof Nansens Institute in Norway, told the High North News, “there is very little to fight over’’.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Laying claim to the North Pole appears to be more a matter of prestige than economic potential. A hefty backlog at the commission means the matter will not be settled soon. Canada estimates it will be another decade before its submission is dealt with. The three countries have made their respective cases and now face what may seem like an interminable wait—a bit like children feel while waiting for Santa Claus at Christmas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 02 Jun 2019 01:40:46 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>