<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Military spending around the world is booming]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/international/2019/04/28/military-spending-around-the-world-is-booming]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_BLP511.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-28T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE WORLD is arming itself to the teeth. That is the conclusion of a new report published on April 29th by the Stockholm International Peace Research Institute (SIPRI), a think-tank. Global military spending last year rose to $1.8trn, says SIPRI—the highest level in real terms since reliable records began in 1988, during the cold war, and 76% higher than in 1998, when the world was enjoying its “peace dividend”. Military spending as a share of global GDP has fallen in recent years, but that offers little reassurance in a world of rising geopolitical tension.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The spending boom is driven, above all, by the contest between America and China for primacy in Asia. Start with America. In 2018 it raised its already-gargantuan defence budget for the first time in seven years, ending an era of belt-tightening imposed by Congress. The boost reflected the Trump administration’s embrace of what it calls “great power competition” with Russia and China—requiring fancier, pricier weapons—in place of the inconclusive guerilla wars it had fought since 2001.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America’s military heft has no equal. Its outlay of $649bn (in 2017 dollars) was almost as large as the next eight countries combined, by SIPRI’s reckoning. Even that did not satiate the Pentagon’s appetite. It got $716bn this year (in current dollars, as counted by the Department of Defence) and hopes for a staggering $750bn in 2020—an annual increase larger than the defence budgets of almost all of its NATO allies. That includes nearly $10bn for cyber operations, a 10% year-on-year boost; over $14bn for space, a 15% jump; and the biggest budget request for shipbuilding in two decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_WOC807.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190504_WOC807.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190504_WOC807.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190504_WOC807.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190504_WOC807.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190504_WOC807.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190504_WOC807.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190504_WOC807.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190504_WOC807.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190504_WOC807.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;China is far behind. It spends somewhere between a quarter and two-fifths of what America does (the precise amount is unclear, say experts, because Chinese spending is so opaque). Nor is its military expenditure growing at a 10% clip, as it did on average in the years between 2000 and 2016. But it has risen relentlessly for a quarter-century, completely changing the balance of power in Asia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Between 2009 and 2018, America’s defence spending fell by 17% in real terms whereas China’s grew by 83%—accelerating under President Xi Jinping and outpacing every other big power. “No one has ever presided over anywhere close to this level of Chinese military development in Chinese history before Xi,” notes Andrew Erickson, a professor at the US Naval War College. Its navy has been a particular beneficiary. Between 2014 and 2018, China launched naval vessels with a total tonnage exceeding that of the entire Indian or French navies, notes IISS, another think-tank. Even so, the country’s defence spending is still smaller as a proportion of GDP than that of any other top-five country: 1.9% to America&amp;#x27;s 3.2%. That means it has room to grow, should the geopolitical mood darken.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Military reforms that Mr Xi introduced in 2015, including a slimming down of the army and reorganisation of the command structure along American lines, are also likely to have given China more bang for its yuan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In response, China’s regional rivals have opened their purses, too. India now outspends every European country. South Korea’s annual increase in 2018 was the highest since 2005. And Japanese spending is set to surge in the next five years, with new offensive weapons breaking old pacifist taboos. All in all, Asian military spending makes up 28% of the world’s total, up from 9% in 1988.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Europeans, having hollowed out their armed forces after the cold war, are getting their act together. In 2018 NATO’s European allies raised military spending by 4.2% in real terms, according to IISS. Poland, which is particularly anxious about next-door Russia, boosted spending by 8.9%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were European spending to be lumped together, the continent would be the world’s second-largest military power, outspending Russia fourfold. In practice, Europe’s hodge-podge of duplicated, mismatched equipment (Europeans use 17 types of tanks to America’s one) and continued dependence on America in key areas—such as moving troops and refueling warplanes—mean that its armed forces are far less than the sum of their parts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet not everywhere is piling up arms. Military spending in Africa shrank for a fourth consecutive year in 2018, by 8.4%, driven by big falls in Angola, Algeria and Sudan, says SIPRI. Protests in the latter two countries, with armies under pressure to hand over power to civilians, might cause bloated military budgets to be squeezed further.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Middle East also seems to be cooling off after years of frenzied arms-buying. Though SIPRI lacks data for Qatar and the United Arab Emirates (UAE), two of the biggest customers for Western arms companies, and for war-torn Yemen and Syria, spending in the rest of the region fell by 1.9% in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That trend seems likely to continue. Saudi Arabia, the region’s biggest fish, which sets aside a huge 8.8% of GDP for defence, will slash its military spending by 9.1% this year. Iran, its rival, plans even bigger cuts of its own—though the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps (IRGC), which has done most of the recent fighting in places like Syria, got a hefty raise, as did the intelligence ministry, which has been bumping off dissidents abroad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most interesting contraction is, however, in Russia. “Can they count?” President Vladimir Putin asked of his Western rivals in February. “I&amp;#x27;m sure they can. Let them count the speed and the range of the weapons systems we are developing”. But despite the theatrical flaunting of new missiles, and NATO’s impressive rearmament to the west, SIPRI calculates that Russia’s defence budget actually shrank by 3.5% in 2018—putting it outside the top five for the first time in over a decade. This may be the result of a weakening rouble. But Russia’s long military spending spree seems to be drawing to a close. That is a sobering thought for Mr Putin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 08:05:43 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Ebola outbreak in Congo is getting worse]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/04/28/the-ebola-outbreak-in-congo-is-getting-worse]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_blp903.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-28T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE GREATEST fear of most health workers battling Ebola is catching the deadly virus, which makes people gush blood from every orifice. But to Dr Richard Valery Mouzoko Kiboung, an epidemiologist from Cameroon working with the World Health Organisation (WHO), violence was also a pressing worry. Dr Mouzoko was stationed in Butembo, a city in the east of the Democratic Republic of Congo and the centre of an Ebola outbreak that was detected nine months ago. The area around it is in effect a war zone, home to over 100 militias. Locals misunderstand and distrust health workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On April 19th gunmen burst into a meeting of the local Ebola response team that he led. The attackers took everyone’s phone, then started shooting. Two people were wounded. Dr Mouzoko was killed. Hours later a group of people armed with machetes tried to set fire to an Ebola treatment centre at a hospital in nearby Katwa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The violence is part of a trend. In February and March several clinics were attacked, leading Médecins Sans Frontières, a medical charity, to pull its staff from the area around Butembo. A car carrying experts from the WHO was ambushed and damaged by men with sticks. Machete-wielding attackers slashed the head of a health worker responsible for safely burying Ebola victims, so that their corpses do not infect new victims. Congo “is as complex and as volatile an environment as I&amp;#x27;ve seen,” says Mike Ryan, who directs the WHO’s health-emergency programme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_MAM908.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190427_MAM908.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190427_MAM908.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190427_MAM908.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190427_MAM908.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190427_MAM908.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190427_MAM908.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190427_MAM908.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190427_MAM908.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190427_MAM908.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The WHO and other responders appeared to be getting a handle on the outbreak in January, but the violence has set their efforts back. The virus has infected nearly 1,400 people and killed nearly 900. In April the WHO said there was a very high risk that Ebola would spread, including to neighbouring countries such as Uganda, Rwanda and Burundi. Those countries have been asked to start vaccinating health workers and watch out for the virus. The WHO says that more work is also needed in mapping the movement of people, such as workers and refugees, across borders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tedros Adhanom Ghebreyesus, the head of the WHO, says it is becoming difficult to persuade his staff to go into the field. He is visiting Butembo to try to calm his workers and analyse the situation. He is now expecting a rise in the number of cases of Ebola. “Whenever there is an attack it slows down the response, and the number of cases immediately increases as the virus gets the advantage and continues unabated,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Locals, whose basic needs have long been neglected, resent the massive deployment of resources just to fight the virus. Earlier efforts by the police and armed forces to compel people to take preventative measures alienated the local population. Some even imagine that the government is using Ebola to exterminate the Nandes, the biggest ethnic group in the region, or that the emergency was manufactured to keep people from voting in elections last year. The idea that Ebola does not actually exist has been spread by some groups for political advantage, says Dr Tedros, who described it as “playing with fire”. Though he says local leaders have agreed to deliver the same message about the dangers of Ebola.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The WHO has thus far declined to declare the outbreak a public-health emergency of international concern, its loudest alarm bell. The means of controlling Ebola are well understood from previous outbreaks. These include quickly and safely burying victims, tracing the contacts of those infected and vaccinating people in affected areas. Dr Tedros says he has agreed to increase vaccination coverage as soon as possible. There is also discussion of using a different type of vaccine that could be administered to many more people than the one currently in use. But it is almost impossible to do any of this unless health workers can be kept safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 06:08:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling with style]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/04/28/struggling-with-style]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_WBP503_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-28T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;SUMMER’S ARRIVAL in the northern hemisphere brings the arrival of a dilemma that plagues every office worker. What does a casual dress code mean in practice? The happy medium between looking like Kim Kardashian or Hagrid the giant is hard to pin down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;Goldman Sachs has just implemented a “flexible dress code” although the executive memo noted gnomically that “casual dress is not appropriate every day”. Besuited corporate clients might not take kindly to investment-banking advice delivered by someone wearing a tank top and ripped jeans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It makes sense that banking would be one of the last bastions to fall to the advance of casual workwear. You want the people who look after our money to appear sober and respectable. For similar reasons, bank headquarters have deliberately been built in a grandiose style to emphasise the institution’s financial solidity and historical roots. Depositors might hesitate about handing over their savings to people working under a railway arch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For men, the move to casual dress seems entirely positive. Few people will mourn the demise of the tie, a functionally useless garment that constricted male necks for a century. The tie’s origins date back to the 17th century when mercenaries hired by Louis XIII of France wore a form of cravat. The modern version of the tie emerged in the 1920s and was popularised by Britain’s Edward VIII who, when not flirting with the Nazis, developed the Windsor knot. It became standard office wear for the next six decades. In the 1990s ties started to go out of fashion because technology titans and hedge fund managers refused to wear them—and were rich enough to ignore social convention. As a prank, Mark Zuckerberg, the Facebook founder, once turned up at a meeting with a venture capitalist in his pyjamas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The jacket, by contrast, is a much more useful garment, replete with pockets to house wallets, spectacle cases and travel passes (or, these days, mobile phones). So the default work garb for men, when meeting clients, is jacket, open-necked shirt and dark trousers (denim excluded).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On days without meetings, men can slob out in t-shirts (though not too garish) and jeans, and no one will think the worse of them. Arriving in shorts or without socks is another matter entirely. But dressing in the morning is a quick-and-easy process. Steve Jobs was famous for wearing the same outfit—black turtleneck, jeans and sneakers—every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what works well for men does not apply as easily to women. Karl Stefanovic, an Australian TV presenter, wore the same blue suit every day for a year and no one noticed. By contrast, his female co-presenters received constant comment on their appearance. Even the Duchess of Cambridge (Kate Middleton) gets snarky comments when she wears the same clothes twice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women’s workwear seems to have become less formal over time. A survey by Euromonitor found that sales of women’s suits fell by 77% in America between 2007 and 2016. But many women worry that they will be judged as unprofessional (unlike their male colleagues) if their clothes are deemed to be too scruffy, or too revealing. It can also be tough choosing clothes that are suitable for both inside and outside conditions. Air-conditioning systems in offices are often designed to suit the male metabolic rate, which can cope with colder temperatures than the female body. The result may be that women have to bring an extra layer to wear within the office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for formal meetings, although men have abandoned the tie, many women feel obliged to wear high heels. These give many women a sense of empowerment and femininity (not to mention extra height). But in health terms, heels can seem like the Western equivalent of the ancient Chinese practice of foot-binding: bad for women’s feet, ankles and backs and designed to limit their mobility. Britain’s Parliament held a debate after a woman was sent home from her job as a receptionist for refusing to wear high heels (it was inconclusive).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Companies understandably want workers who deal with the public to look respectable. No one should be expected to turn up at the office as if dressed for a wedding. Nor should workers wear clothes that wouldn’t be appropriate if visiting a prudish grandmother or a child’s teacher. The most important item to bring to work is a dose of sartorial common sense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 04:08:10 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Holy Fire at Easter features new lanterns for Ukraine]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/04/28/the-holy-fire-at-easter-features-new-lanterns-for-ukraine]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_blp902.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-28T14:16:37Z&quot;&gt;Apr 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHEN SEVEN weeks of ascetic abnegation culminate in a joyful Easter celebration, Orthodox Christians are supposed to be in amity with one another, and at peace with the world. That is more a statement of the obvious. Since a calendar reform of the 1920s, Christians of the east have been divided over when to celebrate say, Christmas; but virtually all, whether in Muscovite cathedrals or tiny Balkan villages, mark Easter on the same date (often, as this year, different from the western one) and in broadly the same style.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a style that stresses inclusivity. The service features a famous sermon by Archbishop John Chrysostom (c349-407) which invites everybody to the Easter feast, whether they have fasted rigorously or only a little or not at all: “The table is lavishly laden, let all enjoy it sumptuously!” Elsewhere in the prayers, there are exhortations like: “Let us embrace one another! Let us say…even to those who hate us, may all be pardoned in the light of the Resurrection!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Against this warm and forgiving background, people were watching closely for any slight mending of a split within the Orthodox world which has been described by one of the protagonists, the Patriarchate of Moscow, as the bitterest inter-Orthodox division for many centuries. It concerns the proclamation in January of an independent Ukrainian church, with the blessing of the Istanbul-based Patriarch of Constantinople, who traditionally enjoys “primacy of honour” in world Orthodoxy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a thundering retaliation for what it called encroachment on its canonical territory, the Moscow Patriarchate severed relations with the Istanbul-based hierarch, Bartholomew I, and told its flock not to receive the sacraments (supremely sacred church rites) in places under his authority.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In recent weeks and over Easter, there have been signs of things getting just a little bit easier, or at least of people learning to live with deep disagreement. A change at the top may help. The politician who spearheaded the creation of the Orthodox Church of Ukraine (OCU), Petro Poroshenko, lost last weekend’s presidential elections to a comic actor, Volodymyr Zelensky.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Muscovite hierarchy apparently sees this as an opportunity for a fresh start. Patriarch Kirill sent the new head of state a warm letter of congratulation and his Easter message contained no vituperation over Ukraine. As a practising Orthodox Christian, Mr Poroshenko had been passionately involved in church affairs and staked his unsuccessful election campaign on a slogan of “army, language and faith”. Mr Zelensky, who is Jewish, has less obvious interest in inter-Orthodox disputes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those disputes rumble on. Muscovites complain that parishes loyal to Kirill are being taken over improperly by Ukrainian nationalists. The OCU retorts that any transfers are voluntary. Whatever the circumstances, about 500 congregations have switched allegiance from the Patriarchate of Moscow to the OCU; that probably leaves around 11,000 communities in Muscovite hands, against nearly 8,000 for the OCU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In any case, the church which Mr Poroshenko helped to found was proud to celebrate its first Easter since receiving the Tomos, a document issued in Istanbul that certifies its independence. Perhaps a little crestfallen, the former president stood near the front as Metropolitan Epifaniy, the 40-year-old primate of the new church, led the Resurrection chants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was also the first year in which the independent Ukrainian church participated in one of the most spectacular Easter rituals that bind the Orthodox world together. As soon as the “Holy Fire” symbolising the Resurrection is kindled in the Church of the Holy Sepulchre in Jerusalem, usually on Saturday afternoon, the flames (or rather lanterns kindled from the flame) are swiftly transported to Orthodox communities near and far. Palestinian Christians drum the fire through their streets, while planes whisk flickering lamps to places like Greece, Cyprus, Russia—and, as of 2019, Ukraine. It was brought to Saint Michael’s Cathedral in Kiev by a group of 30 volunteers, including some war veterans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Istanbul, meanwhile, Patriarch Bartholomew solemnly prayed for all the other leaders of Orthodox churches, including Moscow’s Kirill and Kiev’s Epifaniy, as he led the four-hour overnight service. Mr Zelensky was reported to have headed to Turkey for a short holiday but he was not to be seen at the Patriarchate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other ways, though, he seems to have entered the paschal spirit. He had upset the leaders of the new Ukrainian church by waggishly comparing their beloved Tomos, or certificate of religious freedom, with a thermos, which in Slavic languages as well as English refers to a humdrum device for keeping drinks at a stable temperature. But over the weekend, leaders of the OCU said the new President had apologised for his joke and they had warmly forgiven him; they wished him well with his presidency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 02:06:46 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Who will win “Game of Thrones”?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/04/28/who-will-win-game-of-thrones]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_WOC556.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-28T14:52:55Z&quot;&gt;Apr 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This article contains plot details of season eight of “Game of Thrones”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“WHEN YOU play the game of thrones, you win or you die. There is no middle ground.” Cersei Lannister’s binary prediction, made eight years and 62 episodes ago during the first season of TV drama “Game of Thrones”, is looking prescient. With just four episodes left, a major battle looks set to wipe out many of the show’s remaining characters. And not all survivors would have much chance of taking a seat upon the Iron Throne as the ruler of Westeros when the final season ends, according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://markets.predictwise.com/entertainment/game-of-thrones&quot;&gt;bookmakers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early front-runner Bran Stark, no stranger to falling, has plummeted from favour with bettors, while his sister Sansa’s chances have nearly doubled over the past two episodes. A new “battle of the bastards” is taking place between Gendry and Jon Snow in third and fourth place, even as the latter’s true heritage starts to cause problems with his beloved aunt. And as is fitting for a show with a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/prospero/2017/07/24/what-is-the-moral-compass-of-game-of-thrones&quot;&gt;meandering moral compass&lt;/a&gt;, the two players who most want to win, Cersei and Daenerys Targaryen, have little hope, at least if the wisdom of crowds is to be believed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;More on “Game of Thrones”:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.1843magazine.com/culture/the-daily/game-of-loans&quot;&gt;The economics of “Game of Thrones&lt;/a&gt;”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.1843magazine.com/culture/the-daily/how-to-win-the-game-of-thrones&quot;&gt;How to win the “Game of Thrones”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/prospero/2016/06/27/women-rule-westeros-how-strange&quot;&gt;Women rule Westeros. How strange&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 00:06:49 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Holy Fire features new lanterns for Ukraine]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/04/28/the-holy-fire-features-new-lanterns-for-ukraine]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_blp902.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-28T14:16:37Z&quot;&gt;Apr 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHEN SEVEN weeks of ascetic abnegation culminate in a joyful Easter celebration, Orthodox Christians are supposed to be in amity with one another, and at peace with the world. That is more a statement of the obvious. Since a calendar reform of the 1920s, Christians of the east have been divided over when to celebrate say, Christmas; but virtually all, whether in Muscovite cathedrals or tiny Balkan villages, mark Easter on the same date (often, as this year, different from the western one) and in broadly the same style.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a style that stresses inclusivity. The service features a famous sermon by Archbishop John Chrysostom (c349-407) which invites everybody to the Easter feast, whether they have fasted rigorously or only a little or not at all: “The table is lavishly laden, let all enjoy it sumptuously!” Elsewhere in the prayers, there are exhortations like: “Let us embrace one another! Let us say…even to those who hate us, may all be pardoned in the light of the Resurrection!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Against this warm and forgiving background, people were watching closely for any slight mending of a split within the Orthodox world which has been described by one of the protagonists, the Patriarchate of Moscow, as the bitterest inter-Orthodox division for many centuries. It concerns the proclamation in January of an independent Ukrainian church, with the blessing of the Istanbul-based Patriarch of Constantinople, who traditionally enjoys “primacy of honour” in world Orthodoxy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a thundering retaliation for what it called encroachment on its canonical territory, the Moscow Patriarchate severed relations with the Istanbul-based hierarch, Bartholomew I, and told its flock not to receive the sacraments (supremely sacred church rites) in places under his authority.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In recent weeks and over Easter, there have been signs of things getting just a little bit easier, or at least of people learning to live with deep disagreement. A change at the top may help. The politician who spearheaded the creation of the Orthodox Church of Ukraine (OCU), Petro Poroshenko, lost last weekend’s presidential elections to a comic actor, Volodymyr Zelensky.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Muscovite hierarchy apparently sees this as an opportunity for a fresh start. Patriarch Kirill sent the new head of state a warm letter of congratulation and his Easter message contained no vituperation over Ukraine. As a practising Orthodox Christian, Mr Poroshenko had been passionately involved in church affairs and staked his unsuccessful election campaign on a slogan of “army, language and faith”. Mr Zelensky, who is Jewish, has less obvious interest in inter-Orthodox disputes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those disputes rumble on. Muscovites complain that parishes loyal to Kirill are being taken over improperly by Ukrainian nationalists. The OCU retorts that any transfers are voluntary. Whatever the circumstances, about 500 congregations have switched allegiance from the Patriarchate of Moscow to the OCU; that probably leaves around 11,000 communities in Muscovite hands, against nearly 8,000 for the OCU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In any case, the church which Mr Poroshenko helped to found was proud to celebrate its first Easter since receiving the Tomos, a document issued in Istanbul that certifies its independence. Perhaps a little crestfallen, the former president stood near the front as Metropolitan Epifaniy, the 40-year-old primate of the new church, led the Resurrection chants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was also the first year in which the independent Ukrainian church participated in one of the most spectacular Easter rituals that bind the Orthodox world together. As soon as the “Holy Fire” symbolising the Resurrection is kindled in the Church of the Holy Sepulchre in Jerusalem, usually on Saturday afternoon, the flames (or rather lanterns kindled from the flame) are swiftly transported to Orthodox communities near and far. Palestinian Christians drum the fire through their streets, while planes whisk flickering lamps to places like Greece, Cyprus, Russia—and, as of 2019, Ukraine. It was brought to Saint Michael’s Cathedral in Kiev by a group of 30 volunteers, including some war veterans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Istanbul, meanwhile, Patriarch Bartholomew solemnly prayed for all the other leaders of Orthodox churches, including Moscow’s Kirill and Kiev’s Epifaniy, as he led the four-hour overnight service. Mr Zelensky was reported to have headed to Turkey for a short holiday but he was not to be seen at the Patriarchate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other ways, though, he seems to have entered the paschal spirit. He had upset the leaders of the new Ukrainian church by waggishly comparing their beloved Tomos, or certificate of religious freedom, with a thermos, which in Slavic languages as well as English refers to a humdrum device for keeping drinks at a stable temperature. But over the weekend, leaders of the OCU said the new President had apologised for his joke and they had warmly forgiven him; they wished him well with his presidency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2019 23:07:20 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America’s strong growth this year surprises economists]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/04/26/americas-strong-growth-this-year-surprises-economists]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_USP511.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-26T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THIS YEAR America’s economy did not get the freshest of starts. A government shutdown, a wobbly stockmarket and concerns that the Federal Reserve would tighten monetary policy too quickly made for a dim outlook for 2019. With the effects of fiscal stimulus fading, and momentum in the global economy ebbing, most expected America’s economic growth to decelerate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So GDP figures for the first quarter, published on April 26th, were a pleasant surprise. Economists surveyed by the &lt;em&gt;Wall Street Journal&lt;/em&gt; had been expecting annualised real growth for the quarter of 2.5%. Instead they were treated to a figure of 3.2%. Needless to say, President Donald Trump was pleased, tweeting that the figure was “far above expectations or projections”, and (of course) adding “MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The president got an impressive number to hurl at his critics, who had doubted that his economic plans would generate sustained rapid growth. The headline figure also seemed to defy fears of a looming downturn. Markets predict an interest-rate cut this year. But an economy growing at such a healthy clip seems, at face value, unlikely to need such support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dig a little deeper, though, and the details are less rosy. Around one percentage point of that 3.2% was because of falling imports and rising exports, a volatile component of GDP. Another 0.7 percentage points came from changes in inventories, which could unwind later in the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some other components of GDP looked soft. Consumer spending, an engine of growth through most of last year, grew by just 1.2% on an annualised basis, or less than half its rate in the fourth quarter of 2018. It was pulled down by an 18% decline in spending on cars and car parts. Investment data also looked a little soggy, with the exception of investment in intellectual property.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of this weakness should reverse in the second quarter of 2019. The government shutdown probably did crimp performance, but is now over. And though retail sales went through a soft patch around the turn of the year, they seem to be picking up. And the GDP figures come with a standard caveat: they are preliminary estimates, which will be revised at least twice in the coming months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps more consequential than the eye-catching growth figure was unexpectedly weak inflation, which could suggest an underlying weakness in demand. Annualised quarterly growth in prices, as measured by personal-consumption expenditures, was just 0.6%, or 1.3% when excluding (volatile) energy and food. This sting in the tail is probably why government bond yields, which rose on news of the cheering GDP figure, then fell sharply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monetary policymakers at the Fed are due to meet next week, and some may conclude from today’s release that they raised interest rates too aggressively in 2018, and are therefore to blame for disappointing domestic demand. The weakness of inflation certainly suggests that monetary policy has not been too loose. A more constructive conclusion might be that the Fed was right to shift to a more doveish stance in the past few months, and that low inflation leaves it well placed to apply more stimulus if necessary. Official projections at its last meeting suggested that interest rates would not rise again this year. With inflation still quiescent, there seems no reason that would change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 05:12:24 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America’s strong economic growth this year surprises economists]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/04/26/americas-strong-economic-growth-this-year-surprises-economists]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_USP511.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-26T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THIS YEAR America’s economy did not get the freshest of starts. A government shutdown, a wobbly stockmarket and concerns that the Federal Reserve would tighten monetary policy too quickly made for a dim outlook for 2019. With the effects of fiscal stimulus fading, and momentum in the global economy ebbing, most expected America’s economic growth to decelerate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So GDP figures for the first quarter, published on April 26th, were a pleasant surprise. Economists surveyed by the &lt;em&gt;Wall Street Journal&lt;/em&gt; had been expecting annualised real growth for the quarter of 2.5%. Instead they were treated to a figure of 3.2%. Needless to say, President Donald Trump was pleased, tweeting that the figure was “far above expectations or projections”, and (of course) adding “MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The president got an impressive number to hurl at his critics, who had doubted that his economic plans would generate sustained rapid growth. The headline figure also seemed to defy fears of a looming downturn. Markets predict an interest-rate cut this year. But an economy growing at such a healthy clip seems, at face value, unlikely to need such support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dig a little deeper, though, and the details are less rosy. Around one percentage point of that 3.2% was because of falling imports and rising exports, a volatile component of GDP. Another 0.7 percentage points came from changes in inventories, which could unwind later in the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some other components of GDP looked soft. Consumer spending, an engine of growth through most of last year, grew by just 1.2% on an annualised basis, or less than half its rate in the fourth quarter of 2018. It was pulled down by an 18% decline in spending on cars and car parts. Investment data also looked a little soggy, with the exception of investment in intellectual property.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of this weakness should reverse in the second quarter of 2019. The government shutdown probably did crimp performance, but is now over. And though retail sales went through a soft patch around the turn of the year, they seem to be picking up. And the GDP figures come with a standard caveat: they are preliminary estimates, which will be revised at least twice in the coming months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps more consequential than the eye-catching growth figure was unexpectedly weak inflation, which could suggest an underlying weakness in demand. Annualised quarterly growth in prices, as measured by personal-consumption expenditures, was just 0.6%, or 1.3% when excluding (volatile) energy and food. This sting in the tail is probably why government bond yields, which rose on news of the cheering GDP figure, then fell sharply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Monetary policymakers at the Fed are due to meet next week, and some may conclude from today’s release that they raised interest rates too aggressively in 2018, and are therefore to blame for disappointing domestic demand. The weakness of inflation certainly suggests that monetary policy has not been too loose. A more constructive conclusion might be that the Fed was right to shift to a more doveish stance in the past few months, and that low inflation leaves it well placed to apply more stimulus if necessary. Official projections at its last meeting suggested that interest rates would not rise again this year. With inflation still quiescent, there seems no reason that would change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 04:11:33 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A fresh probe raises fears of systemic problems in the cryptocurrency market]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/04/26/a-fresh-probe-raises-fears-of-systemic-problems-in-the-cryptocurrency-market]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_FNP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-26T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TO CRITICS, predicting cryptocurrencies’ value is like flipping a coin. Volatility is so high, they say, that a buyer might as well place a wager at a casino. Others see a more direct cause for daily price movements of virtual money: changes in the supply of tokens. And when the company that makes those tokens is suspected of fraud, the casino itself trembles.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Rumours have long swirled about the bona fides of Tether, a four-year-old cryptocurrency with more than $2.8bn in circulation, and of Bitfinex, the exchange on which it is traded. On April 25th New York’s attorney-general, Letitia James, accused both of a cover-up intended to hide a $850m loss in client and corporate funds. Tether slid just 1.4% against the dollar on the news, but according to CoinMarketCap.com, a website, virtual currencies at large suffered more, with some $10bn wiped off their collective value within an hour of the attorney-general’s statement. Bitcoin, the most famous, fell from $5,499 for a single Bitcoin to a low of $4,953, before paring back some of the losses (though it remains choppy).&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The shockwave is caused by Tether’s unique status. Its issuer, also called Tether, is the “central bank of the crypto world,” says David Gerard of Attack of the 50 Foot Blockchain, a website that tracks the sector. Many cryptocurrency exchanges struggle to obtain bank accounts, because the market’s opacity makes it hard to keep tabs on flows of funds or to detect money-laundering. That makes lenders nervous. For those exchanges, Tether acts as a dollar substitute. Like fiat, as cryptocurrency buffs call government-issued money, it is pegged to hard currency, which is meant to insulate it from the worst of the volatility experienced by its anchorless peers. Traders use it as a common currency. Unhindered by regulation and the slowness of bank clearing, Tether flows quickly and easily between exchanges.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;It is not the only “stablecoin”, as cryptocurrencies designed to hold a steady price are called. But it is vastly dominant, representing 96% of daily trading volumes in that category. Some 80% of cryptocurrency trades ostensibly made in dollars are in fact executed in Tether. The currency’s wide acceptance is its strength—and a worry for everyone else. “For years, people have treated Tether as the biggest systemic risk in cryptocurrency,” says Mr Gerard. “Tether supplies most of the liquidity.” To justify its peg, Tether has repeatedly said that every coin issued is backed by a real dollar in a real bank account. But the company has provided no audit of these hard-currency holdings. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The allegations will provide doubters some relief—and more reasons to worry. Because Bitfinex was having trouble getting accounts at banks, the exchange operator used a Panamanian firm, Crypto Capital, as an intermediary to wire dollars to traders, Ms James says. She claims that last year Bitfinex entrusted over $1bn to Crypto Capital, “without any written contract or assurance”. When $850m of that went missing, Bitfinex sought to cover up the problem through “a series of conflicted corporate transactions”—giving itself access to up to $900m from a Tether account which the currency issuer had told investors “backed the tether virtual currency 1-to-1”. (Tether and Bitfinex share the same managers and owners).&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;In other words, the attorney-general concluded that the stash of cash supposed to back Tether did exist—but that it could easily be used for other purposes without customers knowing. Bitfinex has issued a statement saying that the attorney-general’s “court filings were written in bad faith and are riddled with false assertions”.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The accusations would have been much more severe just a few years ago. Now, however, they are likely to cause no more than “a short-term blip,” says Eric Turner of Messari, a data-provider that tracks cryptocurrencies. Some 30 stablecoins are under development, he notes, with a handful operational. Many submit to know-your-customer and money-laundering checks by national regulators. TrueUSD, another dollar-pegged stablecoin, holds collateral funds in an external trust; Eidoo, whose stablecoin is backed by gold, lets customers monitor the precious metal via webcam in the vaults where it is stored. Rivals’ “whole market proposition is that they are not Tether”, says Mr Gerard. Even as Tether fell after the allegations became public, peers such as TrueUSD and Paxos Standard jumped by about 2%, according to Messari’s index of stablecoins.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Investors will welcome more transparency. And tailwinds behind alternatives will have a positive side effect. Bitcoin prices closely track fresh issuance of Tether, which creates volatility and makes it easy to manipulate markets. The stablecoin pioneer’s fall from grace will probably make the cryptocurrency market more stable, not less.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 04:11:32 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The genetic-data dystopia we may face]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/04/26/the-genetic-data-dystopia-we-may-face]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_OPP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-26T17:14:23Z&quot;&gt;Apr 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE “SUBS” are, in effect, subhumans—people with a genetic rating at the low end of a 10-point scale. People tend to date others within their rate bracket. “Dealers” trade blood stolen from people with high ratings for those who need to dupe the tests. A commercial industry of self-help programmes exist for people to improve their rating, if only marginally. Individuals with famously high ratings are murdered by those protesting against “rate-ism”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The futuristic world depicted in “The Phlebotomist” is a disturbing one. A phlebotomist is someone who takes blood for medical tests. In the play, Bea, an ambitious woman who deals blood marries a louche fellow with a high rating, and her friendship deteriorates with Char, who has a genetic disorder and needs stolen blood. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the debut play by Ella Road, a 27-year-old British playwright and actor. It recently ended a run at the Hampstead Theatre in London, where it was nominated for an Olivier Award, Britain’s most prestigious theatrical prize. As part of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s Open Future project, we asked Ms Road about the challenges of presenting genetics on stage and how she views the technology’s benefits and risks. Following her replies is an excerpt from the play, in which Bea performs a blood test for Char. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*      *      *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_OPP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190427_OPP506.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190427_OPP506.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190427_OPP506.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190427_OPP506.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190427_OPP506.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190427_OPP506.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190427_OPP506.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190427_OPP506.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190427_OPP506.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: What spurred you to write a play about genetics?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ella Road&lt;/strong&gt;: I think my initial interest in genetics came from a place of mild existential crisis. I worked at the Natural History Museum whilst training as an actor, and spent a lot of time pondering our place in the world. After graduating I became obsessed with researching genetics and altruism, trying to reconcile my politics with a biological world (and an industry) that seemed harsh, judgmental and competitive. I ended up writing this particular play largely because of a TEDx Talk I saw about pre-symptomatic genetic testing for cancer. The “would I want to know?” question fascinated me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It wasn’t until years later though, when a guy I was seeing decided to disclose that he was a carrier of a genetic disease “in case it affected our kids”—rather prematurely, age 23 and on our third date—that I saw the potential for a story. Relationships are so reliant on what we think we know about each other, the imaginary futures we create, and our subliminal expectations about what someone might deliver. I started to wonder how the availability of self-knowledge might exacerbate an “investment and return”-view of human life—and also open up the possibility of betrayal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: The play delves deeply into the negatives of genetic technologies. What are the benefits that may appear alongside those negatives?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Road&lt;/strong&gt;: The potential benefits of genomics are huge, from the relatively clear-cut pros of pre-emptive treatment and precision medicine, to the slightly murkier areas of genetic editing, athletic selection and forensics. Being able to treat and advise patients according to individual biological predispositions saves time and therefore lives, as well as money. While genetic editing in humans is not (supposed to be) happening yet, the benefits largely come in the form of choices, such as mastectomies for BRCA mutations or lifestyle changes for those at risk of diabetes type 2 or lung cancer. Ultimately all this preparation still doesn’t negate the fact that life is unpredictable—and the healthiest individual could get knocked dead by a falling coconut—but it certainly helps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some people have also flagged the benefits of the play’s new “genetic social order” because it does away with current hierarchies, but this view wrongly assumes that genetics and health exist in isolation from race and class. Certain diseases are more prominent within particular ethnic and economic groups, and environmental factors affect epigenetics. Living in an area of poor air quality, for example, can greatly impact one’s likelihood of developing a mutation for respiratory disease. People from lower income backgrounds are also less likely to have access to, or the time to implement, the nutrition and lifestyle changes necessary to manage their particular genomic potential. So the benefits are huge, but they’re not a fix-all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: One seeming wrinkle in the play is that genetics was used to predict people’s potential diseases but not used to cure it—the other side of the coin, so to speak. Why didn’t you include that part of the technology’s promise as well?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Road&lt;/strong&gt;: I set out to explore a dramatic extreme of how this quest for knowledge might intersect with current social trends, and to generate a feeling of discomfort about certain aspects of contemporary culture, rather than to produce a balanced debate about genomics. Having said that, I do think the positive promises of the technology are implicit in the play. Characters monitor their personal “microbioms” and “fit-goals”, and discuss CRISPR Cas9 gene-editing trials for disease mutations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the play, simple gene edits are already available, but edits for complex conditions are still in trial. I also tried to situate genetic treatment within the economics of their world: the positive potential of genomics isn’t clear-cut in a struggling NHS. These days we barely have the infrastructure to treat the population for diseases they already have, let alone to pre-emptively treat every possible condition that a patient may one day develop. I imagined editing would be expensive and therefore exclusive. At the end of the day, money still talks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: Having thought through a possible future so profoundly as a playwright, please now play the role of policymaker: what might be done to avert the dangers that you foresee?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Road&lt;/strong&gt;: I think we need clear laws protecting citizens’ right to genetic confidentiality. In America the GINA Act theoretically prevents genetic discrimination, but recent cases show significant loopholes. In Britain there is a voluntary moratorium on companies demanding genetic information as part of medical checks, but it’s due for review.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In genomics as in other areas, regulations around personal data struggle to keep pace with technological advancements. And the matter of confidentiality itself is not so black and white. One could argue (and companies do) that if a client withholds important information about their health, the imbalance of knowledge leaves the company vulnerable to exploitation. As genome mapping becomes more popular and laws become more necessary, I expect we’ll come up against resistance from insurance and mortgage providers who rely on a democracy of information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: You used the emotional medium of the theatre to communicate important points about human dignity, freedom, equality and fairness in a way that is more effective than a nerdy essay. In an age of populism and growing authoritarianism, how would you make the case for democracy and liberalism so that it has impact? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Road&lt;/strong&gt;: There’s something about watching theatre that is in itself democratic; it requires the willing participation of both audience and company to create a performance community. In an increasingly atomised society, shared spaces and active experiences like this feel ever more important. Modern drama has been pretty successful in demonstrating the ills of populism and authoritarianism, but it is often limited to making us aware of the trap, rather than preventing us from falling into it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In our current climate, dramatising hope feels particularly necessary—and so perhaps we need to be a bit braver about exploring political empowerment on stage. In theatre our currency is the imagination; not only can we live out and learn from the worst-case scenarios, but we can also explore alternative realities without the fetters of realism. Maybe I need to get on and write some utopias…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*      *      *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_OPP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190427_OPP505.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190427_OPP505.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190427_OPP505.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190427_OPP505.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190427_OPP505.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190427_OPP505.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190427_OPP505.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190427_OPP505.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190427_OPP505.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A scene from “The Phlebotomist” By Ella Road&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[The play takes place in the future, when people are rated genetically on a scale of 1 to 10, and diseases can be predicted many years out. The scene involves two young women: Bea, who works as a phlebotomist (someone who draws blood for medical purposes), and an old friend, Char. The scene has been lightly edited from the original script.]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scene 2&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Phlebotomy consultation booth. Bea sits beside a screen. Char paces. She has just had a blood test.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: How long?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Couple more minutes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bea tidies away equipment.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Weird seeing you at work. Very professional.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Ha. Though, if you don’t mind I’m gonna have to...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bea pulls out a lunchbox and sits down.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Is that/?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Yep. Cheap and nutritious, why change?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Char laughs, shakes her head. Bea eats.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Sorry for taking up your... Thanks so much for doing this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Was waiting for you to ask to be honest. You’re making the right decision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: It’s not really a ’decision’.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Well you don’t technically have to/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Yeah but not disclosing just looks worse doesn’t it. Like you have something to hide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Have you looked at other firms?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: They’re all asking, all the good ones anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Well it’s amazing you’ve got this far at all isn’t it? It’s massive. That degree counts for something eh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Char shrugs. Beat.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Jesus the tension’s killing me! How do you stand this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: People normally wait outside, or come back next day. Stops it being so/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Horrendous? Sorry, sorry I’m being... I’m just feeling/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Come here. Look, whatever happens, I’m here for you OK? Whatever it is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bea checks. Still nothing.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You still seeing whats-her-face? With the hair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Who? Oh. Nah nah, that was just a bit of...you know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;She makes a face. Cackles.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nah, think I’m getting a bit sick of ’em to be honest. Might go back to men. Simpler.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Ha, don’t know about that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: How is sexy Aaron? Sweet smelling and louche?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Ha. Yeah he’s great. We’re good. We’re er, well... it looks like we might move in together actually, so...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: What?!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Yeah.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Fuckin hell Bea. That’s serious! Jeeeeeez! Well he is awwwwfully charming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[...]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The device beeps. They both look at it. Bea gives Char a look, &amp;quot;Ready?&amp;quot;. Char nods.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: No, hold on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;She takes a breath.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bea goes to the screen, clicks and sees the results load. She swallows and scrolls down. Char watches her.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Um. Char.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Don’t fuck with me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: I’m not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: What is it? Please. Bea. Bea?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: I’m so sorry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: What is it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: It’s the Huntington’s. Everything else is fine, it’s just/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Fuck! Fuck. No, fuck! Oh fuck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: I’m sorry. I’m really sorry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: God. Oh FUCK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pause.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How low is it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Two, point…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Let me see?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bea shows Char the screen. Char tries to hold herself together.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Look obviously this is just a number. We can look through the breakdown? And then I’ll book you in with a specialist to discuss what it means/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: It means I’m unemployable. I’m nothing. I can’t do anything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Your general risk for cancers and most diseases is actually really low, which is really lucky, it’s the/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Huntington’s. Incurable. Yeah, I know.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: But the overall/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: I don’t need the spiel Bea, I’m fucked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Sorry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: How long have I got?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: It’s speculative, I’m not supposed to/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Yeah but everyone does, don’t they.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: It’s just a rough /&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Please.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: I only take the blood, I don’t normally...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Char looks at her. Bea reluctantly consults the breakdown.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Er...OK...er, well your predisposition to heart disease is also quite... but the Huntington’s will kick in...soonish...so at a guess, lifestyle depending, you’re probably looking at somewhere between 8 to 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: What?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: But obviously you have to take that with a pinch of, well, there are so many variables/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: I/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Or you might get hit by a tram tomorrow! So you / Sorry/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Fuck / FUCK!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: I’ll refer you to a genetic counsellor Char, this really isn’t my/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: I have a degree. And a masters. I have worked my fucking arse off, it’s not fair!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: It’ll be alright.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: No it won’t, do you know what this means?!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: I know what Hungtington’s is, Char.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Dad stopped being able to walk/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: I know/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Feed himself, hold things/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Stop it! Look. I’m gonna book you in with a counsellor. We need to start working out the best course of action for your disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: I don’t have a disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: No, not yet, but...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pause. Bea goes to her and hugs her. Silence.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Can you delete the file please.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: What?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: The results, the file, can you delete it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: There’s no point, like you said, they’re all asking, not disclosing just looks worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Please, just/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Deleting it won’t change the result hun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: But if/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: There’s no point!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: There is! Listen. Just bear with me yeah. I mean obviously I knew there was a fifty-fifty chance I’d have it, but I never wanted to know, did I. But then criteria started appearing so I started thinking about what I could do if... I started looking at how people get around it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: What?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: If we used someone else’s blood, someone high, we could log it as me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: What?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: If we used someone else’s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: What are you asking me?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: If there’s someone high you’ve tested, we could, could we test that again in/stead&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Sshh! I could lose my job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: I’ve thought this through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Is that why you wanted me to do this? You said you needed moral support.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: I did, I do. But I also thought if/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: It’s illegal Char. It’s fraud. I can’t! I’d lose my job. It’s a good job, I can’t.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Are you enjoying this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: What?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Having the upper hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Don’t be stupid.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: I can pay you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: What?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: I can/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: No.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Dad left me a bit of/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Shut up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: I/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: I don’t want money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Well, you do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: I’m fine, thank / you&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Really?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: What are you doing?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: I know you’re struggling.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Excuse me?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: You’re still paying off your mum’s loans right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: I’m managing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Porridge for lunch, and you could do with a new pair of/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: You’re blowing my mind right now, Char.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Don’t fuck with me Bea, you used to take food from our fridge.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Don’t bring that shit up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Sorry. Sorry, I didn’t mean. I’m just... I really need this. I’ll do anything, honestly. Please.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Look, I know how you/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: No you don’t! You’re not low rate!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: No, but/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: And Aaron, I bet he’s high too, right? What is he?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: Well he’s...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: What is he? Some poor low rater? A little Charity case? No, what is he?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: You know you can’t get into bar training unless you’re/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: So what is he?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: 8.9, but/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: Wow/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: But we don’t care about ratings, we just met.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Char&lt;/strong&gt;: But you’ve both got good blood. Exactly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pause.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the next few years I’m going to begin the slow process of falling apart. I’ll disintegrate. I need this job so I don’t spend my last few years lying in a pool of my own/&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bea&lt;/strong&gt;: OK! OK. OK.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Long pause.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I tested a 7.7 woman this morning. Propensity for diabetes, something else minor. Nothing scary. Is that about right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Char hugs her hard.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Give me a minute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bea exits.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;___________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excerpted from “The Phlebotomist.” Copyright © 2018 by Ella Road. Used with permission of Oberon Books. All rights reserved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2019 03:11:36 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>