<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Medical marijuana is not the way out of America’s opioid crisis]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/24/medical-marijuana-is-not-the-way-out-of-americas-opioid-crisis]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_USP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-24T18:58:34Z&quot;&gt;Jun 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WEEDMAPS, an app that allows cannabis users to find sellers and review their wares, advertises its services through “Weedfacts”—marijuana-promoting factoids on bus stops and billboards in Washington, DC, where recreational use has been decriminalised. The signs proclaim that the legalisation of cannabis improves property values and decreases teenage use and crime. Harmless advertising perhaps. But some of its signs also allege that cannabis helps protect against opioid addiction, which is killing nearly 50,000 Americans a year. “Cannabis has been shown to reduce opioid deaths 25%”, says one poster. If that claim seems too good to be true, that is probably because it is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea that cannabis legalisation—for both medical and recreational purposes—could seriously make a dent in America’s opioid crisis is common. This month, the state health commissioner of New York issued emergency regulations allowing anyone with an opioid addiction to obtain medical marijuana, calling it “a critical step in combating the deadly opioid epidemic affecting people across the state”. Illinois has introduced a similar programme. Yet the evidence behind the theory that legalising marijuana can help combat opioid addiction is thin. And the consequences of bad policy could be severe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The chief evidence for the theory is a paper published in the &lt;em&gt;Journal of the American Medical Association (JAMA)&lt;/em&gt;. Analysing the relationship between opioid overdose deaths and medical marijuana laws from 1999 to 2010, the authors found a strong negative association between the two. “States with medical cannabis laws had a 24.8% lower mean annual opioid overdose mortality rate compared with states without medical cannabis laws,” they wrote. They took pains to describe this as correlational and not causal. But their findings were not interpreted so carefully by cannabis advocates and some policymakers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent paper by Chelsea Shover, an epidemiologist and a postdoctoral fellow at Stanford University, showed that this was a mistake. By simply extending the study period up to 2017—the time period during which the opioid crisis accelerated—she shows that the association between opioid deaths and medical marijuana legalisation flipped from strongly negative to strongly positive. Rather than the 25 percentage-point reduction in the opioid overdose mortality rate cited by cannabis promoters, the study shows a 23 percentage-point increase between 1999 and 2017. “One way to interpret that would be causally: To say that cannabis was saving people then, and is killing people now. But we don’t believe that,” says Ms Shover. “That’s one reason why it’s fraught to make policy decisions based on this data.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flawed interpretations of the original paper fell afoul of what statisticians call the ecological fallacy, when an inference is made about an individual based on statistical data for a group. Poorer states may be more likely to vote for Republicans, but that does not mean that poorer people are more likely to vote for the party, for example. There are very few individual-level studies, either observational or clinical, that would allow researchers to support the claim that access to marijuana limits addiction to opioids or successfully treats those recovering from addictions. The only individual-level analysis to date, a nationally representative observation study of 57,000 Americans, found that medical cannabis users were more likely to misuse prescription painkillers. This does not mean that marijuana-decriminalisation laws worsen opioid addiction—only that a lot more research is needed before policymakers make up their minds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is danger in haste. Opioid addiction is a chronic disorder characterised by repeated relapses. It is exceptionally hard to kick. People who receive medically-assisted treatment—generally methadone, buprenorphine or naltrexone—are much less likely to relapse than those who try mere abstention. But only one in five Americans with an opioid use disorder—the medical term for addiction—are currently receiving treatment. If people were to errantly substitute cannabis for one of the proven treatments, it could cause greater rates of relapse and more overdose deaths. “The suggestion that patients should self-substitute a drug (ie, cannabis) that has not been subjected to a single clinical trial for opioid addiction is irresponsible,” wrote Keith Humphreys and Richard Saitz, two experts on addiction in&lt;em&gt; JAMA&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This does not mean that decriminalising marijuana is a bad idea. Cannabis is probably not the panacea advocates claim, but it does not have the deleterious effects of other banned drugs like heroin or cocaine. There is solid evidence for the medical benefits of CBD, a non-psychoactive cannabis compound, for some forms of epilepsy. And enough patients report that cannabis relieves their pain for such claims to be taken seriously. But combating a crisis as urgent and widespread as the opioid epidemic requires responses that are proven to be effective. These include drastically increasing medically-assisted treatment, increasing the distribution of naloxone (which reverses fatal overdoses), and reducing the prescription of pain killers. Until these responses are prioritised, it is hard to justify turning to speculative—and possibly spurious—options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 04:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Missouri’s only abortion clinic loses its licence]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/24/missouris-only-abortion-clinic-loses-its-licence]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_woc953.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-24T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 2009 George Tiller, an American doctor and abortion provider, was shot and killed while attending church in Wichita, Kansas. The gunman, an activist with a history of mental illness, testified that he had to kill Dr Tiller or else “babies were going to die”. Today the battle over abortion in America is fought less with guns and explosives than with laws hammered out in the country’s statehouses. This year Alabama, Ohio and Georgia passed laws to restrict access to abortions. Some of them in effect ban the procedure even in cases of rape or incest. Last Friday state officials in Missouri chose not to renew the licence of a Planned Parenthood clinic in St Louis. If a judge in the state’s Circuit Court allows the decision to stand, the clinic will no longer be allowed to perform abortions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It would be a momentous decision. If the St. Louis clinic shuts down, Missouri would become the only state in the country without a legal abortion-providing facility for the first time since the Supreme Court legalised the procedure in 1973. Even if the clinic is allowed to continue providing abortions, it will face a slew of new restrictions. These include a ban on abortions after the eighth week of a pregnancy—an unusually early date. On average, states allow women to have abortions until the 21st week of pregnancy, according to Advancing New Standards in Reproductive Health (ANSIRH), a research group at the University of California, San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Access to abortions in the “show-me” state is already limited. According to an analysis of ANSIRH’s data by &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;, Missourians live an average of 80 km (50 miles) from the nearest abortion facility, whether it be there or in another state. This pales in comparison with the hundreds of miles travelled by abortion-seekers in Wyoming or North Dakota. When measured in terms of women of childbearing age per facility, however, abortion clinics are scarcer in Missouri than in any other state. According to ANSIRH, five other states—Kentucky, Mississippi, West Virginia, South Dakota and North Dakota—have just one abortion facility. But whereas each of their facilities serves an average of 486,000 reproductive-age women, Missouri’s serves a whopping 1,365,000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 04:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The world ahead: In the sharenthood]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/24/the-world-ahead-in-the-sharenthood]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/the_world_ahead_podcast_banner_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-24T16:30:40Z&quot;&gt;Jun 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHAT IF America decided to pull out of &lt;strong&gt;NATO&lt;/strong&gt;? And &lt;strong&gt;a trip to 2029&lt;/strong&gt; to report on a landmark case in which parents are required to pay damages for sharing images of their children online, and refusing to take them down when the children grow up. Tom Standage hosts. Runtime: 22 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistallaudio/2bd5a534-895b-4b2d-9c6e-509fa47beb80&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 01:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Women’s football is flourishing, on the pitch and off it]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/06/24/womens-football-is-flourishing-on-the-pitch-and-off-it]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_BLP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-24T15:31:04Z&quot;&gt;Jun 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NOT ALL that long ago, female football players struggled to find a pitch they could play on—let alone someone willing to pay them. Between 1921 and 1971 the Football Association (FA), which governs the sport in England, prohibited women from using the grounds of professional men’s teams, claiming that the sport was “quite unsuitable for females and ought not to be encouraged”. (Perhaps the men in suits had been irked by the enormous crowds, sometimes exceeding 50,000, that had flocked to women’s games during the first world war.) A similar ban in Germany was lifted in 1970. In 1972 the United States passed Title IX, a law that banned organisations that receive funds from the federal government from discriminating on the basis of sex. This forced universities to spend as much on women’s sport as on men’s, and kicked off the long rise of women’s football in the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fast forward nearly 50 years, and women’s football seems on the verge of going mainstream. Television records have been tumbling at this summer’s World Cup in France. Nearly 10m viewers in the host country tuned into the opening match against South Korea, accounting for almost half of all French people watching TV at the time. Some 6m Britons saw England beat Scotland 2-1. A similar number of Germans enjoyed &lt;em&gt;Die Nationalelf&lt;/em&gt;’s 1-0 victory over Spain. The winning squad, regardless of which country they come from, will become national treasures at home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The unprecedented popularity of this World Cup reflects two encouraging trends. First, the quality of play in the women’s game has improved drastically, especially since the last tournament. Second, money is starting to flow into women’s teams, making professional careers more viable. The two patterns are linked, and reinforce each other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rising standard of women’s football is obvious to long-time spectators. Until fairly recently female players received far less coaching than male ones did. No longer. This tournament has been notable for some superb team moves and remarkable goalkeeping (an aspect of the women’s game that some male viewers used to criticise). However, actually quantifying improvements in footballing skill is hard. Goals are a flawed measure. A good pub side can find the net as often as Barcelona does, and the rarity of scoring at any level means that an outlier can skew the sample. Just ask Thailand, who conceded 13 goals against the United States in their opening game of the World Cup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc299.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc299.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc299.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc299.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc299.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc299.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc299.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc299.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc299.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc299.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;A much better metric is the number of passes that occur in an average game, a figure that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://statsbomb.com/2019/02/an-overview-of-pass-heights-in-the-premier-league-english-football-league-and-scottish-premiership&quot;&gt;decreases as you move down through divisions&lt;/a&gt; (see chart). A typical Premier League fixture includes more than 900 passes, falling to around 650 for contests in the fourth tier of English men’s football. The most compelling explanation is that high-quality games involve teams who are good at retaining possession, and low-quality ones feature those who spend most of the time hoofing the ball in the air and tackling each other. Figures provided to &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; by Opta, a sports data firm, show that the average game at this women’s World Cup has featured 825 passes, up from 750 at the last tournament in 2015. (The knockout matches, which will probably include even more passes, are yet to come.) That 10% increase exceeds the rise in any major men’s competition over the same period (see chart).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This increasingly artful rendition of the beautiful game has caught the eye of some forward-thinking sponsors. Historically, rights to a women’s football team or tournament have been bundled as part of a broader package with the men’s equivalent. “Commercial partners and broadcasters have tended to primarily focus on, and value, men’s clubs or competitions, with the women’s game not valued on its stand-alone merits,” says Izzy Wray of Deloitte, a consultancy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, in November 2017 UEFA, which governs football in Europe, unbundled the region’s rights to the women’s competitions. “This opened up a pathway for brands with a specific interest to enter the market, having been previously shut off,” says Ms Wray. Given the saturation of the market around men’s football, with plenty of industries—generally bookmakers and brewers—incessantly targeting the same audience, the opportunities in women’s football are considerable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 60% of women’s football teams in major leagues around the world now have front-of-shirt sponsors that are different to those for the men’s equivalent at the same club, according to Deloitte. That figure could approach 100% by the next World Cup, the company reckons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kelly Simmons, the FA’s director of the professional women’s game, says that these new, multi-million pound sponsorship deals have been transformative. Visa is now spending as much promoting the women’s World Cup as it did on the men’s competition. “It might not pay back in terms of ROI immediately, but we’ve invested for the long term,” acknowledges Stephen Day, its European sponsorship director. The total amount of prize money on offer at the tournament has soared to $30m, twice as much as last time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Female-focused brands have been especially eager to get involved. Avon, a beauty and cosmetics company, became the first such firm to sponsor a women’s professional football club, after agreeing to an exclusive deal with Liverpool Ladies FC. Boots, a pharmacist, has finalised partnerships with the national teams of England, Scotland, Northern Ireland, the Republic of Ireland and Wales.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc300.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc300.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc300.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc300.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc300.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc300.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc300.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc300.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc300.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/game-theory/20190629_woc300.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This growth in funding has allowed European leagues to flourish, so that America is no longer the promised land for aspiring youngsters (as it was for the two teen-aged girls in “Bend It Like Beckham”, a British film from 2002). The number of professional and semi-professional female players in Europe almost doubled to 3,600 between 2013 and 2017 (see chart), the latest year for which data are available. Manchester United launched a women’s team in 2018, making it one of the last big clubs to do so—a decision no doubt motivated by how much Manchester City has invested in their ladies’ side. In 2017 Norway’s football association announced that it would become the first to pay the men’s and women’s international teams the same amount.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A game of two halves&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;But although some of the headline figures are impressive, they mask a murkier financial picture overall. Around the world, the average wage for a female professional footballer is around $7,000 a year. Even in the English Women’s Super League (WSL), one of the wealthier competitions, the average annual salary in 2017 was around £27,000 ($34,400), barely one-hundredth of the £2.6m that the average Premier League player took home. Some 58% of WSL players have considered quitting for financial reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Norway’s deal for equal pay, meanwhile, was largely a public-relations stunt. International fees make up only a tiny fraction of most players’ earnings, and the 6m kroner ($710,000) annual sum will be split among the entire female squad. The women’s team had instead asked for an increase to their marketing budget, a request that was denied. Embarrassingly for the association, Ada Hegerberg, a striker who last year became the first ever recipient of the women’s Ballon d’Or, a prize for the world’s best player, has boycotted the national side since 2017. She claims that the officials have a fundamental lack of respect for the women’s game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may take at least another decade before pursuing a career in football becomes a genuinely lucrative option for most women, rather than a sacrifice for the love of the sport. Even then, higher salaries at the elite levels will not necessarily fix all the problems in the women’s game, says Ted Knutson, co-founder of Statsbomb, a football statistics firm that has recently made access to women’s data free: the challenge is “more about equalising support at the grassroots and investment in the future”. That applies not only to players, but also to staff on the touchline. At a recent conference aimed at professional coaches, your correspondent made up half of the female contingent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nonetheless, the day when women’s football becomes regular, worldwide, mass entertainment—a day that might have come much sooner, had the FA allowed the teams from the first world war to continue drawing large crowds—is fast approaching. Most countries are broadcasting the World Cup on free-to-air channels in prime-time slots. The last 16 of the tournament features teams from six continents. In April, Argentina got its first ever professional women’s club. Who would bet against the country that raised Diego Maradona and Lionel Messi producing a worldwide superstar in women’s football?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 01:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Capuchin monkeys have been using stone tools for around 3,000 years]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/06/24/capuchin-monkeys-have-been-using-stone-tools-for-around-3000-years]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_stp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-24T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ONE OF THE most famous edits in cinematic history comes early in “2001: A Space Odyssey”. A primitive hominid hurls a bone club into the air, and a match cut to a spacecraft instantaneously tells the millennia-long story of human ingenuity. Tools maketh man. Human beings conquered the planet by using tools to appropriate materials from the natural world, in order to achieve previously impossible tasks. But there was never a human monopoly on tool use, as a new paper in &lt;em&gt;Nature Ecology &amp;amp; Evolution&lt;/em&gt; shows. A team led by Tiago Falótico of the University of São Paulo, in Brazil, and Tomos Proffitt of University College, London has demonstrated that a species of monkey called the wild bearded capuchin has been employing stone tools for perhaps 3,000 years, and that their use of the technology has changed over the course of time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Capuchins, chimpanzees and sea otters, among others, are known to use rocks to crack open, respectively, nuts and shellfish. And an earlier dig by Dr Falótico found evidence that, in capuchins, this habit goes back at least 600 years. Though some may question whether bashing a nut with a rock truly qualifies as “tool use”, capuchins (as the picture shows) use both hammerstones and anvils—quite a high level of sophistication.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They also demonstrate sophistication in the wielding of their tools, because not damaging the soft kernel of a nut while breaking the shell takes skill. Cracking open a cashew, the favourite for this treatment, requires the tool-wielder to employ a single, practised motion. First, it brings the hammerstone down two-handed for a glancing blow on the nut’s far side. It then rolls the stone towards itself, over the nut. Youngsters take around eight years of mimicking their parents to get the knack of all this. And although the stones used are not actually modified for the task, monkeys are assiduous in searching for and selecting those of the perfect shape. (They do, however, lack the insight to keep such stones for future use.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dr Falótico and Dr Proffitt returned to the site of the previous excavation—a part of Serra da Capivara National Park in the Brazilian Amazon. They dug into an area of 67 square metres, to which the monkeys bring stones from a nearby stream bed. The site’s capuchins use quartzite cobbles as hammerstones, and tree limbs and loose stones as anvils.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By excavating 1,699 stones, pebbles and flakes, and working out the age of 122 hammerstones from the radiocarbon dates of charcoal buried alongside them, the team split the site’s history into four phases. Capuchins first swung a rock in the area somewhere between 3,000 and 2,400 years ago—the beginning of a period the researchers call Phase IV. This is the oldest known instance of non-ape tool use. Phase IV hammerstones are light and have many impact marks. This suggests they were used mainly on seeds (possibly from cassavas) smaller than the cashews which today’s monkeys pound, meaning hammerstone and anvil often came into contact with one another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Phase III, between 640 and 565 years ago, featured transitional behaviours that led to Phase II, from about 257 years ago, when hammerstones were heavier and are associated with many large anvils, suggesting a food source bigger and harder than cashews (the hard-shelled Jatoba fruit is a possibility). More recently, in Phase I (from 27 years ago), cashew residue on stones suggests the monkeys were moving towards their present-day focus on cashews. What Dr Falótico and Dr Proffitt do not yet know is whether the variation they observe is a result of different groups of capuchins, with different habits, occupying the site at different times—or, alternatively, whether a single lineage of the animals has changed its nutritional culture over the years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until the original dig that the pair conducted, chimps were the only species other than human beings for which an archaeological record of tool use had been found. (In 2007 researchers found chimpanzee-modified stones that were 4,300 years old.) There is no reason, though, not to expect the finding of further, and perhaps older, sites in future. Moreover, studying how capuchins and chimps have used tools may give an inkling of how the process happened in people. One thing Dr Falótico and Dr Proffitt have noticed is that some of the sharp flakes that fly off when hammer meets anvil look identical to Stone Age blades made by human beings. Capuchins have not yet—so far as is known—thought to use such flakes as knives. But perhaps their own “2001” moment awaits them in the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 00:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Late Night Feelings”, Mark Ronson’s new album, is a delight]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/24/late-night-feelings-mark-ronsons-new-album-is-a-delight]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_BKP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-24T13:17:24Z&quot;&gt;Jun 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE FIRST single from “Late Night Feelings”, Mark Ronson’s new album, was released back in November. “Nothing Breaks Like a Heart”, a terrific, Dolly Parton-esque track featuring Miley Cyrus, was an instant hit, and has scored nearly 250m plays on Spotify to date. A number of interviews followed in which Mr Ronson talked about the album: with the BBC in November, the &lt;em&gt;Sunday Times&lt;/em&gt; in December, the &lt;em&gt;Guardian&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Interview&lt;/em&gt; magazine in February. One of the themes of those pieces was his discontent with a world in which artists were forced by their paymasters to churn out hits of diminishing quality, making records to appeal to algorithms rather than to satisfy their own artistic urges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seemed an odd thing to say as “Nothing Breaks Like a Heart” racked up the streams. Then the four subsequent singles did not come close to matching that success—the second most popular, “Find U Again”, has 225m fewer streams on Spotify—and “Late Night Feelings” did not appear. The official line from the Ronson camp is that the album was always scheduled for June, and that it wasn’t announced until April. Yet all those interviews talked about the album in some depth, and the interviewers had clearly heard it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Ronson became a superstar in 2015 with the release of “Uptown Funk”, a catchy funk-pop song featuring Bruno Mars, and one of the best-selling singles of all time. It turned Mr Ronson into the kind of artist on whom major record labels rely to generate revenue, and to prove to other artists that they know how to sell music by the truckload. Labels want their superstars to carry on being superstars: if someone makes them a great deal of money making party hits, they tend to want more of the same. So while the official line is that “Late Night Feelings” was always meant to be coming out now, it wouldn’t be a huge surprise if at some point in the future Sony reveals that it had wanted more obvious hits on one of their marquee albums for 2019, and had offered Mr Ronson more time to make them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Luckily “Late Night Feelings” is worth the wait. It is both very old-fashioned and very modern. Mr Ronson has said that it is an album of “sad bangers”—meaning songs both heartbroken and catchy—which happens to be one of pop’s more notable trends (Robyn, the current critical darling, is a queen of the sad banger). It is also a notion that is at the heart of some of the very best pop music of the 1970s: ABBA, especially, and huge tranches of disco (see “I Will Survive”).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It might seem a curious move for Mr Ronson, who is best known for party music: “Valerie”, with Amy Winehouse, from 2007; the all-conquering “Uptown Funk”; “Electricity”, the single he and his friend Diplo made in 2018 with the singer Dua Lipa. The one word you wouldn’t have used to describe Mr Ronson’s past work is “personal”, but this time it is inspired by his own despair after the breakdown of his marriage (even if he is just one of scores of writers on each track, and as ever, it is guests—Lykke Li, Camila Cabello, King Princess, Yebba, Alicia Keys, Ms Cyrus, Angel Olsen, Diana Gordon, Ilsey—doing the singing).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, this is a rather lovely album. In theory putting a number of very good writers, musicians and singers together on one record will produce something worthwhile, but in reality that is not always the case. Mr Ronson, though, has a gift for synthesising the contributions of others into something coherent, and he clearly sticks with people he trusts. “Late Night Feelings” features members of the Dap-Kings, a soul group which played on Winehouse’s “Back to Black” (produced by Mr Ronson), Kevin Parker of Tame Impala, and the Parisian production duo The Picard Brothers. Between them, they’ve made a gorgeous, lush, melodic record, the kind that—and this is meant as praise—you can imagine popping up in bar scenes and montages in decent romantic comedies for years to come.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shame is that “Late Night Feelings” deserved all those big interviews this month, to give it the biggest push. Its big hit single should have come out two weeks before release, rather than seven months before, to maximise momentum. It is a terrific album—even if it doesn’t include another “Uptown Funk”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 20:40:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“It&#x27;s frankly sent us all a bit crazy”—how Brexit divided Britons]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/24/its-frankly-sent-us-all-a-bit-crazy-how-brexit-divided-britons]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_blm520.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-24T09:48:54Z&quot;&gt;Jun 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EXACTLY THREE years after the referendum result, it’s clear: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/briefing/2019/06/20/how-brexit-made-britain-a-country-of-remainers-and-leavers&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brexit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; has driven Britain a bit batty. We look into the grand societal divides that the vote exposed. In &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/22/a-re-election-in-istanbul-tests-president-erdogans-power&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Istanbul&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a repeat mayoral election reaches the same result: the ruling party lost. President Recep Tayyip Erdogan no longer seems so invincible. And, in Kenya, an “Uber for ambulances” saves time and lives. Runtime: 22 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/dc2ac083-d9e5-41de-9a6c-ad98c204e180&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 20:40:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How Americans became workaholics]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/23/how-americans-became-workaholics]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_wbd001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-23T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMERICANS LIKE to work hard whereas Europeans prefer a more leisurely life. That is the widely held perception of the continental divide in business culture. But it has not always been the case; 40 years ago, there was precious little difference between the two.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his new book, “Spending Time: The Most Valuable Resource”, Daniel Hamermesh, an economist, examines how work and leisure patterns in America differ from those in the rest of the developed world. In the first half of the 20th century the American working week fell sharply from nearly 60 hours to around 40. By 1979 the average worker in America put in around 38.2 hours a week, similar to the number in Europe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is where the figures started to diverge. For a while, the American workweek got longer, reaching 39.4 hours in 2000, before falling back to 38.6 in 2016. The main difference, however, is holidays. In the 1980s Europeans began to take more annual leave but Americans did not. Over the year as a whole, Americans average 34 hours a week, six more than the French and eight more than the Germans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What explains this gap? Some point to cultural reasons but, as Mr Hamermesh points out, it is hard to see why American culture suddenly diverged from that of the rest of the world in the last 40 years. Others point to lower taxes, which raise the value of putting in the extra hour. Yet American taxes were lower than European rates back in the 1960s, when working hours were similar. Another potential explanation is a decline in trade union membership has weakened American workers’ bargaining power—except that unionisation rates in France and America are not far apart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A more plausible reason is policy. There is no legal requirement to offer paid vacations in America, whereas France mandates a minimum of 25 days, and Germany, 24. Famously, France also limits the working week to 35 hours. Mr Hamermesh finds similar examples in Asia. In the 1980s and 1990s, Japan passed laws reducing the standard working week from 48 hours to 40. Beyond that, workers were entitled to overtime pay. A similar process occurred in South Korea between 2004 and 2008. Employers responded by cutting hours; workers earned less as a result but surveys found they were happier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In America, by contrast, champions of workers’ rights have recently focused on raising the minimum wage (so far to little avail at the federal level, though some states have enacted more generous wage floors). Wage gains have certainly skewed toward the better-off. The median American worker makes about $20 an hour while the worker at the 95th percentile makes $62. That is a ratio of 3.1. Back in 1979, the ratio was 2.2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These higher wages do seem to have had an incentive effect. High-paid employees work 8-9 more hours a week than the lowest-paid. In part, this may reflect the low earnings of part-time workers, who have grown as a share of the workforce. Either way, the gap has widened since the late 1970s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But don’t shed too many tears for the wealthy. They may work more hours, but the poor often work more inconvenient ones. It is a myth to say that well-paid workers put in more hours at the weekends or at night, Mr Hamermesh says. It is cleaners and food delivery people who work when it is dark, not bankers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what is going on? John Maynard Keynes dreamed that his grandchildren would be working only 15 hours a week. But the decline in hours which the economist predicted slowed after the 1970s. This may hint that 35-40 hours is close to the most efficient working period. Any more and workers become too stressed; any less and companies lose too much production. But it is also a sign that Keynes was wrong to think that society would place a high value on extra leisure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the developed world most workers have more than enough to feed themselves and their families. But they still want &amp;quot;positional&amp;quot; goods—homes in a good location, holidays in sun-drenched resorts and possessions that demonstrate their social status. Prices of these goods will be pushed higher, driving status-seeking employees to work more hours to earn them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So whatever labour-saving gadgets Silicon Valley dreams up, future generations will probably still have to put in a long shift. But Americans could enjoy a bit more holiday. Those who feel the same ought to ask their politicians why Europeans should get more rest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 20:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The opposition’s new star deals Turkey’s president a stinging blow]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/24/the-oppositions-new-star-deals-turkeys-president-a-stinging-blow]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_blp903.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-24T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THIS TIME around, there was no room for doubt. In late March Ekrem Imamoglu had won the Istanbul mayoral election by a fraction of a percentage point. On June 23rd he won the re-run by a landslide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Imamoglu’s victory in the rerun was the best showing for any opposition politician in decades, and Turkey’s biggest city celebrated in style. Street parties erupted in some neighbourhoods. “Sunny days will come,” sang a crowd of young people by the Bosphorus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given the scale of Mr Imamoglu’s success, there was no room for the antics that Turkey’s president, Recep Tayyip Erdogan, pulled last time to deny the new mayor his first victory. Then, after Mr Imamoglu prevailed by just 13,000 votes, Mr Erdogan and his ruling Justice and Development (AK) party challenged the outcome, accused the opposition of stealing the vote and leaned heavily on the country’s election board to order a repeat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The move turned out to be one of the worst gambits of Mr Erdogan’s career. In the new election, Mr Imamoglu received a solid 54% of the vote to 45% for AK’s candidate, Binali Yildirim, a former prime minister—a margin of over 800,000. Turnout reached 85%, boosted by thousands of Istanbul residents who cancelled or interrupted their holidays to be home on election day. Mr Yildrim conceded in front of the cameras as soon as the first results were made public. In a written statement, Mr Erdogan congratulated the new mayor shortly thereafter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Imamoglu forged a coalition that included his secular Republican People’s Party (CHP), Kurdish voters, a breakaway nationalist group and some Islamists. But he has also earned the sympathy and the votes of a growing number of disenchanted ruling-party supporters. A street vendor in one conservative Istanbul neighborhood said he was so appalled by the re-run decision that he chose to stop voting AK. “What they did to Imamoglu was an injustice,” he said. “There’s been too much corruption,” another former AK voter said. “They made too many mistakes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Imamoglu’s success should be a lesson for his party, says Fehmi Koru, a newspaper columnist. By running a relentlessly positive campaign and refusing to play by the rules of Turkey’s identity politics, he was able to make inroads with conservative voters, something the CHP has not managed for decades. Assuming that Mr Imamoglu can reshape the party in his own image, it might finally broaden its reach. The CHP has long been unable to attract more than 25% or so of the electorate. Mr Imamoglu may soon shine on the national stage, says Mr Koru, though he needs to prove he can run Istanbul. Success in Turkey’s largest city as mayor was exactly how Mr Erdogan himself rose to prominence in the 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now, however, Mr Erdogan remains in charge of the country. Turkey’s leader enjoys sweeping executive powers, which he can use to undermine Mr Imamoglu. He also retains the support of the Nationalist Movement Party (MHP), which gives him control of the parliament. At least in theory, Mr Erdogan does not have to face another election for four years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the ground beneath his feet is starting to shake. Emboldened by Mr Imamoglu’s success, some estranged AK politicians, already poised to launch a rival conservative party, might do so sooner rather than later. The economy, which clawed its way out of recession a few months ago, faces the risk of another downturn later this year. Possible American sanctions over Mr Erdogan’s purchase of a Russian missile-defence system would compound the damage severely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The opposition at last has the wind at its back, with an inspiring new leader. Together with Istanbul, the CHP and its allies now control municipalities that account for roughly 70% of Turkey’s economy, says Sinan Ulgen of Carnegie Europe, a think-tank. “They now have the means to fund their political activities, and to eliminate AK’s network of patronage,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Imamoglu, meanwhile, has the country’s attention, a mandate to shake up his own party and a chance to heal a divided society. “The era of partisanship is over,” he said in a victory speech in front of a crowd of elated supporters. “The era of rights, law and justice is here.” Elsewhere, the same words might sound bland. In today’s Turkey, as Mr Erdogan knows, they are nothing short of revolutionary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 18:40:01 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The American exception]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/23/the-american-exception]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_wbd001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-23T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMERICANS LIKE to work hard whereas Europeans prefer a more leisurely life. That is the widely held perception of the continental divide in business culture. But it has not always been the case; 40 years ago, there was precious little difference between the two.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his new book, “Spending Time: The Most Valuable Resource”, Daniel Hamermesh, an economist, examines how work and leisure patterns in America differ from those in the rest of the developed world. In the first half of the 20th century the American working week fell sharply from nearly 60 hours to around 40. By 1979 the average worker in America put in around 38.2 hours a week, similar to the number in Europe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is where the figures started to diverge. For a while, the American workweek got longer, reaching 39.4 hours in 2000, before falling back to 38.6 in 2016. The main difference, however, is holidays. In the 1980s Europeans began to take more annual leave but Americans did not. Over the year as a whole, Americans average 34 hours a week, six more than the French and eight more than the Germans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What explains this gap? Some point to cultural reasons but, as Mr Hamermesh points out, it is hard to see why American culture suddenly diverged from that of the rest of the world in the last 40 years. Others point to lower taxes, which raise the value of putting in the extra hour. Yet American taxes were lower than European rates back in the 1960s, when working hours were similar. Another potential explanation is a decline in trade union membership has weakened American workers’ bargaining power—except that unionisation rates in France and America are not far apart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A more plausible reason is policy. There is no legal requirement to offer paid vacations in America, whereas France mandates a minimum of 25 days, and Germany, 24. Famously, France also limits the working week to 35 hours. Mr Hamermesh finds similar examples in Asia. In the 1980s and 1990s, Japan passed laws reducing the standard working week from 48 hours to 40. Beyond that, workers were entitled to overtime pay. A similar process occurred in South Korea between 2004 and 2008. Employers responded by cutting hours; workers earned less as a result but surveys found they were happier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In America, by contrast, champions of workers’ rights have recently focused on raising the minimum wage (so far to little avail at the federal level, though some states have enacted more generous wage floors). Wage gains have certainly skewed toward the better-off. The median American worker makes about $20 an hour while the worker at the 95th percentile makes $62. That is a ratio of 3.1. Back in 1979, the ratio was 2.2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These higher wages do seem to have had an incentive effect. High-paid employees work 8-9 more hours a week than the lowest-paid. In part, this may reflect the low earnings of part-time workers, who have grown as a share of the workforce. Either way, the gap has widened since the late 1970s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But don’t shed too may tears for the wealthy. They may work more hours, but the poor often work more inconvenient ones. It is a myth to say that well-paid workers put in more hours at the weekends or at night, Mr Hamermesh says. It is cleaners and food delivery people who work when it is dark, not bankers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what is going on? John Maynard Keynes dreamed that his grandchildren would be working only 15 hours a week. But the decline in hours which the economist predicted slowed after the 1970s. This may hint that 35-40 hours is close to the most efficient working period. Any more and workers become too stressed; any less and companies lose too much production. But it is also a sign that Keynes was wrong to think that society would place a high value on extra leisure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the developed world most workers have more than enough to feed themselves and their families. But they still want &amp;quot;positional&amp;quot; goods—homes in a good location, holidays in sun-drenched resorts and possessions that demonstrate their social status. Prices of these goods will be pushed higher, driving status-seeking employees to work more hours to earn them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So whatever labour-saving gadgets Silicon Valley dreams up, future generations will probably still have to put in a long shift. But Americans could enjoy a bit more holiday. Those who feel the same ought to ask their politicians why Europeans should get more rest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 20:17:05 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>