<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump is not the first president to fight subpoenas]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/01/donald-trump-is-not-the-first-president-to-fight-subpoenas]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_usp506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 1924, a Senate committee investigating the Teapot Dome bribery scandal issued a subpoena to Mal Daugherty, a bank president and brother of Harry Daugherty, who would soon resign as attorney-general. When Mal failed to appear, the Senate dispatched its deputy sergeant-at-arms to Ohio to arrest him. Daugherty challenged his arrest, arguing that the Senate had exceeded its authority. The Supreme Court disagreed. Not only can Congress compel testimony essential to “a legislative function”; “it is to be presumed” that congressional investigations are intended “to aid [Congress] in legislating,” and “it is not a valid objection to such investigation that it might disclose wrongdoing or crime by a public officer.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump has sued two banks to stop them complying with House subpoenas, and asked a federal court to block another to an accounting firm used by the Trump Organisation. He has vowed to fight one subpoena issued to Don McGahn, a former White House counsel, and has ordered an official who oversaw White House security clearances not to comply with another. More subpoenas may soon follow, most likely to compel testimony from William Barr, Mr Trump’s attorney-general, who may skip a planned appearance before the House Judiciary Committee because he dislikes the questioning format, and to obtain Mr Trump’s tax returns, which he has refused to turn over to the Ways and Means Committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Congressional subpoenas are not all-powerful. Various presidents have fought them for different reasons. The usual levers brought to bear against private citizens who ignore subpoenas—fines and imprisonment—are harder to use against executive-branch officials. And congressional oversight, says Andrew Wright, an associate counsel to Barack Obama who is now a partner with K&amp;amp;L Gates, a law firm, “is a quasi-political, quasi-legal process” that usually resists quick resolution. This does not mean that Mr Trump—who said on April 24th that “we’re fighting all the subpoenas” because the House Democrats issuing them “aren’t, like, impartial people”—can simply ignore them, merely that this fight will probably have a political rather than a legal resolution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Congress can charge people who ignore subpoenas with contempt, which requires a majority vote in a single chamber. Enforcing that charge is trickier. The days of apprehension by the sergeant-at-arms followed by detention are over; that power has not been used since 1935, when a Hoover administration official was held at the Willard hotel. Contempt of Congress has been a federal crime since 1857, but Mr Barr is unlikely to approve prosecuting either his boss or anyone who was following his boss’s orders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That leaves civil contempt as a possible legal avenue. Congress can ask a federal court to compel obedience to a subpoena. This can take a while. In October 2011 Eric Holder, Barack Obama’s attorney-general, received a congressional subpoena. Mr Obama tried to block it by declaring executive privilege in June 2012. A court rejected Mr Obama’s blanket claim of privilege, but not until January 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current standoff may finish faster, for two reasons. First, many of the justiciability concerns that took courts time to work through during the Obama and Bush administrations have been resolved. And second, as Stephen Vladeck, a law professor at the University of Texas, explains, Mr Trump’s statement of blanket refusal “suggests that case-specific objections are post-hoc rationalisations”, which courts may be inclined to swiftly reject.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But legal battles still take some time to adjudicate. That may annoy Democrats but suit Mr Trump perfectly. His supporters prize his pugnacity, and he prefers table-pounding defiance to the intricacies of legal compromise. Also, political salience fades over time; he may reckon that if he loses in court, the public will have moved on to the next outrage. And congressional subpoenas expire when the current Congress does, making a successful play for time a victory, of sorts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 00:06:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[From Caracas: “Rattled rebel soldiers began firing in the air”]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/01/from-caracas-rattled-rebel-soldiers-began-firing-in-the-air]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/theintelligence_overlay2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-01T11:20:37Z&quot;&gt;May 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUAN GUAIDÓ, the opposition figure widely viewed as the legitimate leader of Venezuela, has made a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/04/30/juan-guaido-makes-a-dramatic-attempt-to-oust-venezuelas-regime&quot;&gt;dramatic attempt&lt;/a&gt; to seize power from President Nicolás Maduro. But the effort appears to have stalled; how did it go wrong? We also look more widely at coups around the world, why they succeed or fail, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/23/how-to-predict-a-coup&quot;&gt;how to predict them&lt;/a&gt;. And a dramatic embassy raid reveals why it’s so tough to be a North Korean &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/27/campaigning-against-the-north-korean-regime-is-a-thankless-task&quot;&gt;dissident&lt;/a&gt;. Runtime: 22min.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/putschcomestoshove-venezuela&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 23:06:31 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Does the Civil Rights Act protect gay and transgender workers?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/04/30/does-the-civil-rights-act-protect-gay-and-transgender-workers]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_USP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-30T06:07:45Z&quot;&gt;Apr 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SINCE 2015, same-sex couples have had a constitutional right to marry—yet Americans still enjoy no federal protection from workplace discrimination on the basis of their sexual orientation or transgender identity. In some two dozen states that do not have their own civil-rights umbrella for LGBT people, a gay employee can return to the office from his honeymoon and be fired. Transgender people, too, have no recourse in these states when their bosses fire or demote them for presenting themselves as their preferred gender. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In recent years, a push for greater equality has had some success at the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission and in several federal appeals courts which have pointed to protection against employment discrimination for LGBT in the Civil Rights Act of 1964. Meanwhile, the Trump administration and other courts are sticking to less expansive readings of that law. After months of discussion in private conference, on April 22nd the Supreme Court agreed to resolve the split. Late in 2019, the justices will take up gay rights for the first time since Justice Anthony Kennedy—author of the same-sex marriage decision and a trio of rulings forging a path to it—left the bench last June. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the cases come up for argument, the main quandary will concern how to interpret three words Congress wrote over a half-century ago: “because of sex”. Title VII of the Civil Rights Act bars employers from discriminating against a worker “because of such individual’s race, colour, religion, sex, or national origin”. The question is whether skipping over a gay worker for a promotion or firing her on the basis of her sexual orientation amounts to discrimination “because of sex”—and whether similar treatment of trans people fits that bill.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two of the cases—&lt;em&gt;Altitude Express, Inc. v Zarda &lt;/em&gt;and&lt;em&gt; Bostock v Clayton County, Georgia&lt;/em&gt;—involve gay men. Donald Zarda, a sky-diving instructor, and Gerald Bostock, a child-advocate employee, both say their sexual orientation (and in Mr Bostock’s case, his participation in a gay softball league) cost them their jobs. Mr Zarda died in a jumping accident in Switzerland before the litigation began but won a posthumous &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.glad.org/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/zarda-second-circuit-opinion-2-26-18.pdf&quot;&gt;victory&lt;/a&gt; at the Second Circuit Court of Appeals in 2018. Judge Robert Katzmann found that discriminating on the basis of sexual orientation is “a subset of sex discrimination” since it is rooted in stereotypes about “how persons of a certain sex can or should be”. To sack “a man because he is attracted to men is a decision motivated, at least in part, by sex”. By contrast, the Eleventh Circuit Court of Appeals curtly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.scotusblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/17-1618-opinion-below.pdf&quot;&gt;rejected&lt;/a&gt; Mr Bostock’s claim, finding it foreclosed by a 1979 precedent which concluded that “[d]ischarge for homosexuality is not prohibited by Title VII”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;R.G. &amp;amp; G.R. Harris Funeral Homes Inc. v Equal Employment Opportunity Commission,&lt;/em&gt; the third case, poses two slightly different questions about a transgender woman, Aimee Stephens, who lost her job at a funeral home when she told her boss she would no longer dress or present herself as Anthony. The Supreme Court will ask whether dismissing employees based on their “status as transgender” violates Title VII. It will also consider whether discriminating based on “sex stereotyping” violates the law. The issues are connected but analytically distinguishable: it could conceivably be acceptable to fire someone for being transgender as long as the reason is not linked to any particular behaviour or practice. The violation of Ms Stephens’s civil rights could be traced to the boss’s refusal to let her wear a dress to work and present herself as a woman, not to a general policy of disdain for transgender employees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This distinction may sound fine, but the Sixth Circuit Court of Appeals based its &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.opn.ca6.uscourts.gov/opinions.pdf/18a0045p-06.pdf&quot;&gt;ruling&lt;/a&gt; in favour of Ms Stephens squarely on the sex-stereotyping claim. In urging the justices not to hear the appeal, Ms Stephens &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/DocketPDF/18/18-107/67903/20181024150403351_18-107%20RGGR%20Harris%20Funeral%20Homes%20v%20EEOC%20Brief%20in%20Opposition.pdf&quot;&gt;argued&lt;/a&gt; the case was a poor vehicle for considering whether Title VII bars discrimination according to gender identity. The funeral home fired Ms Stephens’s, her lawyers wrote, “because her appearance and behaviour failed to conform to its sex stereotypes”. That type of discrimination “requires no determination of whether discrimination based on transgender status itself constitutes sex discrimination under Title VII”. Instead, it is universally acknowledged by all appeals courts to be barred by &lt;em&gt;Price Waterhouse v Hopkins,&lt;/em&gt; a 1989 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.oyez.org/cases/1988/87-1167&quot;&gt;decision&lt;/a&gt; in which the Supreme Court read Title VII to preclude employers from disfavouring female workers based on “stereotypical notions about women&amp;#x27;s proper deportment”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main strike against the plaintiffs in these three cases is obvious: none of the lawmakers in Congress in 1964 believed they were barring LGBT discrimination when they included “sex” among the prohibited bases of differential treatment in the workplace. But that is not the end of the story, even—perhaps especially—for conservative justices who purport to be textualists. More than two decades ago, Justice Antonin Scalia &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.oyez.org/cases/1997/96-568&quot;&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt; a unanimous majority opinion in &lt;em&gt;Oncale v Sundowner Offshore Services, Inc&lt;/em&gt; vindicating another claim that never crossed the minds of the mid-century legislators: a male employee’s right not to be harassed at work. Sexual harassment of men may not have been among the evils members of Congress thought they were combating when they drafted the Civil Rights Act, but the workplace harm is “reasonably comparable” to others Congress was thinking of. What should matter for a textualist are the words in the statute, not the motivations of its authors. “It is ultimately the provisions of our laws rather than the principal concerns of our legislators”, Mr Scalia wrote, “by which we are governed”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 22:06:26 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A bid to grab power in Venezuela, and more from our daily podcast]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/01/a-bid-to-grab-power-in-venezuela-and-more-from-our-daily-podcast]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/theintelligence_twitter_6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-01T11:20:37Z&quot;&gt;May 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUAN GUAIDÓ, the opposition figure widely viewed as the legitimate leader of Venezuela, has made a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/04/30/juan-guaido-makes-a-dramatic-attempt-to-oust-venezuelas-regime&quot;&gt;dramatic attempt&lt;/a&gt; to seize power from President Nicolás Maduro. But the effort appears to have stalled; how did it go wrong? We also look more widely at coups around the world, why they succeed or fail, and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/23/how-to-predict-a-coup&quot;&gt;how to predict them&lt;/a&gt;. And a dramatic embassy raid reveals why it’s so tough to be a North Korean &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/27/campaigning-against-the-north-korean-regime-is-a-thankless-task&quot;&gt;dissident&lt;/a&gt;. Runtime: 22min.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/putschcomestoshove-venezuela&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 20:07:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Juan Guaidó makes a dramatic attempt to oust Venezuela’s regime]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/04/30/juan-guaido-makes-a-dramatic-attempt-to-oust-venezuelas-regime]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_AMP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-30T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUAN GUAIDÓ, recognised by most Western and Latin American democracies as Venezuela’s interim president, seems to have decided it was now or never to claim real power. In the early morning of April 30th he stood outside the La Carlota air-force base in Caracas, the capital, to proclaim that Operación Libertad, or Operation Liberty, the final push to free Venezuela from the dictatorial regime of Nicolás Maduro, had begun.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;A few signs suggested that Mr Guaidó, who is supported by millions of Venezuelans suffering from regime-inflicted hunger and other hardships, might have the sort of backing needed to remove it. A video showed him surrounded by a small group of soldiers wearing blue armbands, signalling support for his movement. Some armoured cars were parked behind them.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;More important, Mr Guaidó was joined by Leopoldo López, once the country’s most popular opposition leader, who had been jailed in 2014 and later placed under house arrest. He said he had been freed by agents from SEBIN, Venezuela’s intelligence service, who had been keeping him under guard. That suggests that his jailers, at least, had switched sides. Videos appeared of small groups of armed men joining protesters against the regime. Mr Guaidó declared that “brave soldiers...have followed our call.”&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;But for Mr Guaidó to wrest power from Mr Maduro, troops will have to defect in large numbers, and that is likely to happen only if their commanders do, too. Rumours of high-level defections circulated throughout the morning. Questions revolved around Manuel Figuera, the general in charge of SEBIN, who has not been heard from. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;In the afternoon the United States’ national-security adviser, John Bolton, suggested that more high-level defections were expected. He asserted that &amp;quot;key figures in the regime” had been “talking to the opposition over these last three months” and called on them to “make good on their commitments to achieve the peaceful transfer of power from the Maduro clique” to Mr Guaidó. Among those prepared to defect, he asserted, were the defence minister, Vladimir Padrino López, the supreme court’s chief justice, Maikel Moreno, and the commander of the presidential guard, Iván Rafael Hernández Dala.” All of them “agreed that Maduro had to go,” Mr Bolton claimed. He told them to “act this afternoon or this evening to help bring other military forces” to Mr Guaidó’s side. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Whether these regime stalwarts had indeed agreed to dump Mr Maduro is unclear. Certainly, the United States has long wanted them to. By, in effect, declaring them to be disloyal to the regime, Mr Bolton may be hoping to force them to take action against it. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Before his intervention, most of the people popularly thought to be high-level rebels appeared to have confirmed their loyalty to the regime. José Ornellas, the chief of the armed forces, whom unsubstantiated reports said was the leader of the rebellion, tweeted his backing for Mr Maduro. So did Mr Padrino López. Some informed observers think the rising went off at half-cock: it had been planned for another day, with the support of senior officers, but was brought forward because the regime was about to arrest Mr Guaidó and the coup plotters then backed down. Mr Bolton asserted that the Cubans, who spy on the Venezuelan armed forces and feed the intelligence to Mr Maduro, “played a very significant role in propping Maduro up today, possibly with help from the Russians”.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The most senior officer known to have joined the rebellion seems to be a lieutenant-colonel of the National Guard charged with guarding the opposition-controlled national assembly. The protesters around Mr Guaidó failed to enter the La Carlota base. They were fended off by rounds of teargas. The repression appeared to turn brutal. Images on social media showed a National Guard armoured car running over demonstrators. By late morning Diosdado Cabello, perhaps the regime’s second-most-powerful figure, was declaring that “the traitors to the country have once again been defeated”.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;For now, it looks as if Mr Guaidó is left with the tactic of mobilising opposition on the streets, until now his main way of putting pressure on the regime. He has called for the largest demonstration in Venezuela’s history to take place on May 1st. Radicals are urging Mr Guaidó to head directly towards the presidential palace. Others warn that may be a futile gesture: routes to the palace are easily blocked by loyalist security forces.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;In short, events in Venezuela remain unpredictable. It is still too soon for the regime to declare victory. It is unclear what effect, if any, Mr Bolton’s claim to be outing top regime officials will have. Mr Maduro himself has not appeared in public. The march may well be yet another reminder to exasperated citizens that whereas Mr Guaidó has the popular support, the president still has the guns. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;If so, the initiative may soon pass to the regime. Its first decision will be whether to allow Mr Guaidó, to remain free. (Mr López and his family have found refuge at the Chilean embassy.) The government has so far permitted Mr Guaidó to agitate largely unmolested, no doubt in part because the United States has warned of reprisals if he is arrested. Until the events of April 30th, the regime had tried to avoid killing people at recent protests. If they swell it may begin to repress them more forcibly.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Another possibility is that the opposition will lose heart. Mr Guaidó’s last big gambit—an attempt in February to bring in humanitarian aid from Colombia watched by the world’s media—was a failure. Another could demoralise the opposition. The United States and most Latin American countries have given Mr Guaidó full-throated support. This has been backed by American sanctions on Venezuela’s vital oil industry. President Donald Trump has now threatened a “full and complete embargo” against Cuba, blaming it for helping to keep Mr Maduro in power. But the pressure has yet to break the regime. It is not clear how many setbacks Mr Guaidó and his allies can tolerate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 17:06:21 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Xiaomi’s founder loses a 1bn yuan bet]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/01/xiaomis-founder-loses-a-1bn-yuan-bet]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_wbp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-01T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 2013 BUSINESS folk gathered at a gala in Beijing to honour Chinese “Economic Figures of the Year” were treated to an unexpected twist. One of the winners, Lei Jun, ventured that in five years the sales of Xiaomi, the smartphone-maker he founded in 2010, would surpass those of Gree, a state-owned manufacturer of air-conditioners. To make things interesting, Dong Mingzhu, Gree’s chairwoman with whom he shared the award, bet him 1bn yuan ($148m today) that her company’s turnover would remain ahead. Mr Lei accepted. From March 19th, when Xiaomi posted revenues of 175bn yuan in 2018, corporate China awaited the figure from Gree. On April 28th the verdict was in: it made 200bn yuan. Mr Lei was out of the money. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bet looked bold for Mr Lei in 2013. Xiaomi was then making a quarter of Gree’s 120bn yuan in annual sales. “Apple of the East”, as it was dubbed, represented a new sort of Chinese company: market-driven and spunky, not state-led and stodgy; online instead of bricks and mortar; digital rather than mechanical engineering. By mid-2018 Xiaomi’s revenue neared 90% of Gree’s. When it floated on the Hong Kong stock exchange last July it was valued at $54bn. It has become the fourth-most-valuable Chinese brand, according to BrandZ, a consultancy; Gree is 29th. Ms Dong herself suggested that the wager was meaningless given how different Gree and Xiaomi were.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In reality, the companies are not that dissimilar—and growing less so as China’s economy modernises. Both have boomed thanks to swelling Chinese disposable incomes. The fiercely independent Ms Dong has repeated publicly that her firm must fight for customers just as private ones like Xiaomi do. In April Gree’s largest shareholder, a regulator overseeing state-owned enterprises, said it would sell most of its 18% stake. To build an ecosystem of devices controlled by his mobile phones, Mr Lei relies on closeness to China’s manufacturing heartland, Gree’s home. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They face similar challenges, too. The competition in their core markets is stiff. Xiaomi’s margins from low-cost phones are wafer-thin. Gree has lost share of Chinese air-con sales to rivals such as Haier or Midea, which are introducing more high-tech models. Xiaomi and Gree have both taken a punt on diversifying beyond their original business models. Gree is selling more online. Xiaomi opens more physical stores. To keep up with rapidly changing consumer tastes, Gree has moved into smart home appliances, as well as low-emission vehicles and chip design—areas in which Xiaomi does business, too. Ms Dong now makes smartphones. Mr Lei has a line of air-conditioners. Whether or not he makes good on it—gambling is outlawed on the mainland—the bet highlights the changing face of China Inc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 16:06:43 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Juan Guaidó makes another dramatic attempt to oust Venezuela’s regime]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/04/30/juan-guaido-makes-another-dramatic-attempt-to-oust-venezuelas-regime]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_AMP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-30T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUAN GUAIDÓ, recognised by most Western and Latin American democracies as Venezuela’s interim president, seems to have decided it was now or never to claim real power. In the early morning of April 30th he stood outside the La Carlota air-force base in Caracas, the capital, to proclaim that Operación Libertad, or Operation Liberty, the final push to free Venezuela from the dictatorial regime of Nicolás Maduro, had begun.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;A few signs suggested that Mr Guaidó, who is supported by millions of Venezuelans suffering from regime-inflicted hunger and other hardships, might have the sort of backing needed to remove it. A video showed him surrounded by a small group of soldiers wearing blue armbands, signalling support for his movement. Some armoured cars were parked behind them.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;More important, Mr Guaidó was joined by Leopoldo López, once the country’s most popular opposition leader, who had been jailed in 2014 and later placed under house arrest. He said he had been freed by agents from SEBIN, Venezuela’s intelligence service, who had been keeping him under guard. That suggests that his jailers, at least, had switched sides. Videos appeared of small groups of armed men joining protesters against the regime. Mr Guaidó declared that “brave soldiers...have followed our call.”&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;But for Mr Guaidó to wrest power from Mr Maduro, troops will have to defect in large numbers, and that is likely to happen only if their commanders do, too. Rumours of high-level defections circulated throughout the morning. Questions revolved around Manuel Figuera, the general in charge of SEBIN, who has not been heard from. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;In the afternoon the United States’ national-security adviser, John Bolton, suggested that more high-level defections were expected. He asserted that &amp;quot;key figures in the regime” had been “talking to the opposition over these last three months” and called on them to “make good on their commitments to achieve the peaceful transfer of power from the Maduro clique” to Mr Guaidó. Among those prepared to defect, he asserted, were the defence minister, Vladimir Padrino López, the supreme court’s chief justice, Maikel Moreno, and the commander of the presidential guard, Iván Rafael Hernández Dala.” All of them “agreed that Maduro had to go,” Mr Bolton claimed. He told them to “act this afternoon or this evening to help bring other military forces” to Mr Guaidó’s side. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Whether these regime stalwarts had indeed agreed to dump Mr Maduro is unclear. Certainly, the United States has long wanted them to. By, in effect, declaring them to be disloyal to the regime, Mr Bolton may be hoping to force them to take action against it. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Before his intervention, most of the people popularly thought to be high-level rebels appeared to have confirmed their loyalty to the regime. José Ornellas, the chief of the armed forces, whom unsubstantiated reports said was the leader of the rebellion, tweeted his backing for Mr Maduro. So did Mr Padrino López. Some informed observers think the rising went off at half-cock: it had been planned for another day, with the support of senior officers, but was brought forward because the regime was about to arrest Mr Guaidó and the coup plotters then backed down. Mr Bolton asserted that the Cubans, who spy on the Venezuelan armed forces and feed the intelligence to Mr Maduro, “played a very significant role in propping Maduro up today, possibly with help from the Russians”.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The most senior officer known to have joined the rebellion seems to be a lieutenant-colonel of the National Guard charged with guarding the opposition-controlled national assembly. The protesters around Mr Guaidó failed to enter the La Carlota base. They were fended off by rounds of teargas. The repression appeared to turn brutal. Images on social media showed a National Guard armoured car running over demonstrators. By late morning Diosdado Cabello, perhaps the regime’s second-most-powerful figure, was declaring that “the traitors to the country have once again been defeated”.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;For now, it looks as if Mr Guaidó is left with the tactic of mobilising opposition on the streets, until now his main way of putting pressure on the regime. He has called for the largest demonstration in Venezuela’s history to take place on May 1st. Radicals are urging Mr Guaidó to head directly towards the presidential palace. Others warn that may be a futile gesture: routes to the palace are easily blocked by loyalist security forces.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;In short, events in Venezuela remain unpredictable. It is still too soon for the regime to declare victory. It is unclear what effect, if any, Mr Bolton’s claim to be outing top regime officials will have. Mr Maduro himself has not appeared in public. The march may well be yet another reminder to exasperated citizens that whereas Mr Guaidó has the popular support, the president still has the guns. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;If so, the initiative may soon pass to the regime. Its first decision will be whether to allow Mr Guaidó, to remain free. (Mr López and his family have found refuge at the Chilean embassy.) The government has so far permitted Mr Guaidó to agitate largely unmolested, no doubt in part because the United States has warned of reprisals if he is arrested. Until the events of April 30th, the regime had tried to avoid killing people at recent protests. If they swell it may begin to repress them more forcibly.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Another possibility is that the opposition will lose heart. Mr Guaidó’s last big gambit—an attempt in February to bring in humanitarian aid from Colombia watched by the world’s media—was a failure. Another could demoralise the opposition. The United States and most Latin American countries have given Mr Guaidó full-throated support. This has been backed by American sanctions on Venezuela’s vital oil industry. President Donald Trump has now threatened a “full and complete embargo” against Cuba, blaming it for helping to keep Mr Maduro in power. But the pressure has yet to break the regime. It is not clear how many setbacks Mr Guaidó and his allies can tolerate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 07:06:38 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Juan Guaidó makes another dramatic attempt to dislodge Venezuela’s regime]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/04/30/juan-guaido-makes-another-dramatic-attempt-to-dislodge-venezuelas-regime]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_AMP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-30T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUAN GUAIDÓ, recognised by most Western and Latin American democracies as Venezuela’s interim president, seems to have decided it was now or never to claim real power. In the early morning of April 30th he stood outside the La Carlota air-force base in Caracas, the capital, to proclaim that Operación Libertad, or Operation Liberty, the final push to free Venezuela from the dictatorial regime of Nicolás Maduro, had begun.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;A few signs suggested that Mr Guaidó, who is supported by millions of Venezuelans suffering from regime-inflicted hunger and other hardships, might have the sort of backing needed to remove it. A video showed him surrounded by a small group of soldiers wearing blue armbands, signalling support for his movement. Some armoured cars were parked behind them.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;More important, Mr Guaidó was joined by Leopoldo López, once the country’s most popular opposition leader, who was jailed in 2014 and later placed under house arrest. He said he had been freed by agents from SEBIN, Venezuela’s intelligence service, who had been keeping him under guard. That suggests that his jailers, at least, had switched sides. Videos appeared of small groups of armed men joining protesters against the regime. Mr Guaidó declared that “brave soldiers...have followed our call.”&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;But for Mr Guaidó to wrest power from Mr Maduro, troops will have to defect in large numbers, and that is likely to happen only if their commanders do, too. Rumours of high-level defections circulated throughout the morning. Questions revolved around Manuel Figuera, the general in charge of SEBIN, who has not been heard from. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;In the afternoon the United States’ national-security adviser, John Bolton, suggested that more high-level defections were expected. He asserted that &amp;quot;key figures in the regime” had been “talking to the opposition over these last three months” and called on them to “make good on their commitments to achieve the peaceful transfer of power from the Maduro clique” to Mr Guaidó. Among those prepared to defect, he asserted, were the defence minister, Vladimir Padrino López, the supreme court’s chief justice, Maikel Moreno, and the commander of the presidential guard, Iván Rafael Hernández Dala.” All of them “agreed that Maduro had to go,” Mr Bolton claimed. He told them to “act this afternoon or this evening to help bring other military forces” to Mr Guaidó’s side. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Whether these regime stalwarts had indeed agreed to dump Mr Maduro is unclear. Certainly, the United States has long wanted them to. By, in effect, declaring them to be disloyal to the regime, Mr Bolton may be hoping to force them to take action against it. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Before his intervention, most of the people popularly thought to be high-level rebels appeared to have confirmed their loyalty to the regime. José Ornellas, the chief of the armed forces, whom unsubstantiated reports said was the leader of the rebellion, tweeted his backing for Mr Maduro. So did Mr Padrino López. Some informed observers think the rising went off at half-cock: it had been planned for another day, with the support of senior officers, but was brought forward because the regime was about to arrest Mr Guaidó and the coup plotters then backed down. Mr Bolton asserted that the Cubans, who spy on the Venezuelan armed forces and feed the intelligence to Mr Maduro, “played a very significant role in propping Maduro up today, possibly with help from the Russians”.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The most senior officer known to have joined the rebellion seems to be a lieutenant-colonel of the National Guard charged with guarding the opposition-controlled national assembly. The protesters around Mr Guaidó failed to enter the La Carlota base. They were fended off by rounds of teargas. The repression appeared to turn brutal. Images on social media showed a National Guard armoured car running over demonstrators. By late morning Diosdado Cabello, perhaps the regime’s second-most-powerful figure, was declaring that “the traitors to the country have once again been defeated”.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;For now, it looks as if Mr Guaidó is left with the tactic of mobilising opposition on the streets, until now his main way of putting pressure on the regime. He has called for the largest demonstration in Venezuela’s history to take place on May 1st. Radicals are urging Mr Guaidó to head directly towards the presidential palace. Others warn that may be a futile gesture: routes to the palace are easily blocked by loyalist security forces.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;In short, events in Venezuela remain unpredictable. It is still too soon for the regime to declare victory. It is unclear what effect, if any, Mr Bolton’s claim to be outing top regime officials will have. Mr Maduro himself has not appeared in public. The march may well be yet another reminder to exasperated citizens that whereas Mr Guaidó has the popular support, the president still has the guns. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;If so, the initiative may soon pass to the regime. Its first decision will be whether to allow Mr Guaidó, to remain free. (Mr López and his family have found refuge at the Chilean embassy.) The government has so far permitted Mr Guaidó to agitate largely unmolested, no doubt in part because the United States has warned of reprisals if he is arrested. Until the events of April 30th, the regime had tried to avoid killing people at recent protests. If they swell it may begin to repress them more forcibly.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Another possibility is that the opposition will lose heart. Mr Guaidó’s last big gambit—an attempt in February to bring in humanitarian aid from Colombia watched by the world’s media—was a failure. Another could demoralise the opposition. The United States and most Latin American countries have given Mr Guaidó full-throated support. This has been backed by American sanctions on Venezuela’s vital oil industry. But the pressure has yet to break the government. It is not clear how many setbacks Mr Guaidó and his allies can tolerate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 06:07:47 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can employees be fired because they are gay or transgender?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/04/30/can-employees-be-fired-because-they-are-gay-or-transgender]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_USP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-30T10:07:45Z&quot;&gt;Apr 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SINCE 2015, same-sex couples have had a constitutional right to marry—yet Americans still enjoy no federal protection from workplace discrimination on the basis of their sexual orientation or transgender identity. In some two dozen states that do not have their own civil-rights umbrella for LGBT people, a gay employee can return to the office from his honeymoon and be fired. Transgender people, too, have no recourse in these states when their bosses fire or demote them for presenting themselves as their preferred gender. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In recent years, a push for greater equality has had some success at the Equal Employment Opportunity Commission and in several federal appeals courts which have pointed to protection against employment discrimination for LGBT in the Civil Rights Act of 1964. Meanwhile, the Trump administration and other courts are sticking to less expansive readings of that law. After months of discussion in private conference, on April 22nd the Supreme Court agreed to resolve the split. Late in 2019, the justices will take up gay rights for the first time since Justice Anthony Kennedy—author of the same-sex marriage decision and a trio of rulings forging a path to it—left the bench last June. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the cases come up for argument, the main quandary will concern how to interpret three words Congress wrote over a half-century ago: “because of sex”. Title VII of the Civil Rights Act bars employers from discriminating against a worker “because of such individual’s race, colour, religion, sex, or national origin”. The question is whether skipping over a gay worker for a promotion or firing her on the basis of her sexual orientation amounts to discrimination “because of sex”—and whether similar treatment of trans people fits that bill.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two of the cases—&lt;em&gt;Altitude Express, Inc. v Zarda &lt;/em&gt;and&lt;em&gt; Bostock v Clayton County, Georgia&lt;/em&gt;—involve gay men. Donald Zarda, a sky-diving instructor, and Gerald Bostock, a child-advocate employee, both say their sexual orientation (and in Mr Bostock’s case, his participation in a gay softball league) cost them their jobs. Mr Zarda died in a jumping accident in Switzerland before the litigation began but won a posthumous &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.glad.org/wp-content/uploads/2017/06/zarda-second-circuit-opinion-2-26-18.pdf&quot;&gt;victory&lt;/a&gt; at the Second Circuit Court of Appeals in 2018. Judge Robert Katzmann found that discriminating on the basis of sexual orientation is “a subset of sex discrimination” since it is rooted in stereotypes about “how persons of a certain sex can or should be”. To sack “a man because he is attracted to men is a decision motivated, at least in part, by sex”. By contrast, the Eleventh Circuit Court of Appeals curtly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.scotusblog.com/wp-content/uploads/2018/06/17-1618-opinion-below.pdf&quot;&gt;rejected&lt;/a&gt; Mr Bostock’s claim, finding it foreclosed by a 1979 precedent which concluded that “[d]ischarge for homosexuality is not prohibited by Title VII”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;R.G. &amp;amp; G.R. Harris Funeral Homes Inc. v Equal Employment Opportunity Commission,&lt;/em&gt; the third case, poses two slightly different questions about a transgender woman, Aimee Stephens, who lost her job at a funeral home when she told her boss she would no longer dress or present herself as Anthony. The Supreme Court will ask whether dismissing employees based on their “status as transgender” violates Title VII. It will also consider whether discriminating based on “sex stereotyping” violates the law. The issues are connected but analytically distinguishable: it could conceivably be acceptable to fire someone for being transgender as long as the reason is not linked to any particular behaviour or practice. The violation of Ms Stephens’s civil rights could be traced to the boss’s refusal to let her wear a dress to work and present herself as a woman, not to a general policy of disdain for transgender employees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This distinction may sound fine, but the Sixth Circuit Court of Appeals based its &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.opn.ca6.uscourts.gov/opinions.pdf/18a0045p-06.pdf&quot;&gt;ruling&lt;/a&gt; in favour of Ms Stephens squarely on the sex-stereotyping claim. In urging the justices not to hear the appeal, Ms Stephens &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/DocketPDF/18/18-107/67903/20181024150403351_18-107%20RGGR%20Harris%20Funeral%20Homes%20v%20EEOC%20Brief%20in%20Opposition.pdf&quot;&gt;argued&lt;/a&gt; the case was a poor vehicle for considering whether Title VII bars discrimination according to gender identity. The funeral home fired Ms Stephens’s, her lawyers wrote, “because her appearance and behaviour failed to conform to its sex stereotypes”. That type of discrimination “requires no determination of whether discrimination based on transgender status itself constitutes sex discrimination under Title VII”. Instead, it is universally acknowledged by all appeals courts to be barred by &lt;em&gt;Price Waterhouse v Hopkins,&lt;/em&gt; a 1989 &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.oyez.org/cases/1988/87-1167&quot;&gt;decision&lt;/a&gt; in which the Supreme Court read Title VII to preclude employers from disfavouring female workers based on “stereotypical notions about women&amp;#x27;s proper deportment”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main strike against the plaintiffs in these three cases is obvious: none of the lawmakers in Congress in 1964 believed they were barring LGBT discrimination when they included “sex” among the prohibited bases of differential treatment in the workplace. But that is not the end of the story, even—perhaps especially—for conservative justices who purport to be textualists. More than two decades ago, Justice Antonin Scalia &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.oyez.org/cases/1997/96-568&quot;&gt;wrote&lt;/a&gt; a unanimous majority opinion in &lt;em&gt;Oncale v Sundowner Offshore Services, Inc&lt;/em&gt; vindicating another claim that never crossed the minds of the mid-century legislators: a male employee’s right not to be harassed at work. Sexual harassment of men may not have been among the evils members of Congress thought they were combating when they drafted the Civil Rights Act, but the workplace harm is “reasonably comparable” to others Congress was thinking of. What should matter for a textualist are the words in the statute, not the motivations of its authors. “It is ultimately the provisions of our laws rather than the principal concerns of our legislators”, Mr Scalia wrote, “by which we are governed”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 04:06:33 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Britain’s super-rich are Corbyn-proofing their finances]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/04/30/britains-super-rich-are-corbyn-proofing-their-finances]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_blp904.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-30T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JEREMY CORBYN may have it in for tax havens, but they are not all cursing the Labour leader right now. Well-heeled types worried about the prospect of a Corbyn-led government have been buying property on Guernsey with a view to relocating to the island, attracted by its flat 20% income-tax rate and lack of capital-gains or inheritance taxes. Demand for homes there has been buoyant this year, and Jo Stoddart of Locate Guernsey, an investment-promotion agency, says queasiness over Mr Corbyn is one of the main reasons (along with Brexit and personal security). Matt Brouard, a Guernsey estate agent, says some British expats are moving to the island rather than returning to the mainland after stints working overseas, partly because of Corbyn-induced uncertainty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The opposition leader makes no secret of his disdain for the rich. The real divide in Britain, he said recently, is not over Brexit but “between the many, who do the work, create the wealth and pay their taxes, and the few, who set the rules, reap the rewards and dodge their taxes.” The super-rich, he has warned, are “on borrowed time”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Small wonder, then, that plutocrats are seeking advisers’ counsel—and increasingly taking action—to keep their incomes, mansions and pensions out of Labour’s clutches. “How to Corbyn-proof your Wealth”, an event held in London in February by a club for elite investors, sold out quickly. A recent, eight-page special section on the topic in the &lt;em&gt;Mail on Sunday&lt;/em&gt; screamed that Corbynomics threatens to wreak economic havoc that could “rival that heaped upon the poor people of Venezuela”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Betting sites offer odds as short as 3/1 on Mr Corbyn becoming the next prime minister (he is jostling with Boris Johnson, a leading Tory, for top spot). If that happened, says the chief executive of a FTSE 100 company, the rich would “take all the money offshore, wait for the economy to crash, and come back and get richer.” There would be “a major crash in the pound and [firms] will all start losing jobs.” Private-client advisers have warned of Britain’s multi-millionaires moving up to £1trn ($1.3trn) out of the country. But the “mass affluent”, those with liquid assets in the hundreds of thousands, also have cause to fret.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such fears have fluctuated in line with recent political turmoil. Wealth advisers interviewed for this article agreed that clients worry more about Mr Corbyn than Brexit—though the two are linked, as some fear a disorderly Brexit precisely because it could usher in a Labour government. When clients of Saunderson House, a wealth manager, were asked last October what was the biggest threat to their finances, the top answer, mentioned by 42%, was a change of government. The number would almost certainly be higher now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The worries fall into three main categories. The first concerns existing tax and pension arrangements. Labour is likely to target pension tax relief for high earners. On income tax, it has promised to reintroduce the 50% rate on earnings over £123,000 (rather than £150,000), and add a 45% rate that kicks in at £80,000. It is likely to reverse cuts to capital-gains tax made by the Tories. And it is expected to tighten the inheritance-tax regime, possibly by reducing or removing allowances for those giving to discretionary trusts, passing on property or handing gifts to relatives. To cap it all, Labour’s manifesto pledges to impose VAT on private-school fees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second area is brand new taxes. Labour hopes to raise almost £5bn a year from a new financial-transactions levy. This would cream 0.2% off every transaction executed by financial firms. Some hedge funds are reportedly considering moving management overseas in response. The bigger worry is the possibility of a general “wealth tax” on assets, perhaps focused on high-value homes, to help fund social care. In 2012 John McDonnell, who has since become shadow chancellor, backed a proposal for a one-off, 20% wealth tax to help reduce government debt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The third category—and the biggest bogeyman—is the spectre of capital controls, measures to restrict the flow of capital in and out of the country, in the event of severe economic turbulence. Labour has repeatedly denied it would consider such a draconian measure, last seen in Britain in the late 1970s. Even Mr Corbyn’s harshest critics see it as a long shot. Nevertheless, contingency plans are being put in place. A year ago, says Mr Tait, it would have seemed “ludicrous” to be mulling measures to protect against capital controls. Yet clients raised the issue in “around half” of the meetings he attended in the run-up to Easter. As an “insurance policy”, some have arranged for custody of their investment accounts (used to buy and sell securities) to be moved to the Channel Islands or Switzerland. Changing the jurisdiction in which accounts are booked in this way is all about “asset access” and has nothing to do with tax, says Mr Tait.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a possible property-based wealth tax in mind, some rich folk are accelerating the transfer of homes to children. “They might have done this anyway when the kids were in their 20s. Now they’re doing it in their teens,” says one adviser, who has “dozens” of clients who have opted to speed up handovers. Some are also using up tax-free pension allowances, or vesting tax-free cash, earlier than required, for fear of such benefits evaporating under Labour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A smaller number are exploring taking themselves offshore. Rather than emigrating now, the majority of these Jeremiahs are looking to buy foreign residence permits to hold alongside their British passports, in order to be well placed to hop abroad if things turn nasty at home. Advisers say they are looking not only at obvious places like Monaco and the Channel Islands but also at EU countries that have become friendlier to rich foreigners, such as Portugal (where a “golden visa” can be bought for €500,000, or $561,000) and Italy (where, since 2017, income from abroad can be taxed at a flat €100,000).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among those who may be tempted to up sticks are resident “non-doms”: foreigners who live in Britain but declare their domicile as elsewhere to avoid tax on their non-British income. The Tories took away some of their privileges in 2016, after a media outcry over their cushy deal, but the non-doms still get fairly generous treatment for up to 15 years. The threat of a Corbyn government, though, is leading some who were wavering after the changes in 2016 to go elsewhere. Another wealth adviser has Swedish and French non-dom clients who are returning home. “Sweden and France, those well-known tax havens!” he guffaws.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were Britain’s 90,000 or so non-doms to leave, many Corbynistas might say good riddance. Indeed, some Labour advisers believe that a falling-out with the super-rich would go down well with the public. Mr Corbyn has long accused them of using Britain to dodge tax and contributing little to the economy. But non-doms contributed a not-so-paltry £9.4bn in tax—equivalent to a third of the transport budget—in the year to April 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr McDonnell’s team dismisses the bleating from Belgravia as alarmist. Fears over a wealth tax are as misplaced as those concerning capital controls, aides say. Yes, income tax will rise, but to nowhere near the stomach-churning rates of the 1970s. Mr McDonnell may have an avowedly Marxist past, but he has been on a charm offensive in the City, meeting moneymen to assure them he has nothing shocking up the sleeves of his branch-manager suit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, when it comes to squeezing the rich there is not as much clear blue water between the two main parties as the Tories would have voters believe. As well as turning the screws on non-doms, the current lot have cut high earners’ tax-free pension allowances and are mulling an inheritance-tax grab. The chancellor, Philip Hammond, has warned of the need for higher taxes to fund an ageing population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, tone matters, and there is a difference between measured tax increases, served up apologetically, and what looks to some like anti-capitalist blood-lust. Mr Corbyn has said he is “coming for” the rich. Some of Labour’s plans suggest a taste for confiscation. It wants to nationalise several industries, including water, for which it is considering basing compensation for investors on “book” value—currently a third of the industry’s market value—or even less. A plan to snatch 10% of shares in big British firms and give them to workers and the state has nauseated many business leaders. “The rich are prepared for higher taxes,” says Bobby Vedral of MacroEagle, a political and economic intelligence firm, “but not for expropriation.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Vedral caused a ruckus in 2017 when he predicted a Britain led by Mr Corbyn would be like “Cuba without the sun”. That is unfair—but increasing numbers of the moneyed seem unwilling to take any chances. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2019 04:06:32 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>