<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[The future of genetic engineering]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/24/the-future-of-genetic-engineering]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/babbage_11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-24T15:16:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;KENNETH CUKIER takes a look at what it means to be human. He speaks to leading scientists, doctors and philosophers to ask if ethics and regulations are able to keep up with the technology of genetic engineering. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistbabbage/babbage-thegeneticrevolution&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id508376907?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/0BCUrdrOb3tvfIwazeLBUH&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWVjb25vbWlzdGJhYmJhZ2U&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=142124&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Economist-Babbage-p401958/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 22:38:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A troubling death in Northern Ireland, and more from our daily podcast]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/24/a-troubling-death-in-northern-ireland-and-more-from-our-daily-podcast]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/the_intelligence_60.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-24T11:18:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A YOUNG journalist will be buried today, after being accidentally shot by dissident republicans in Belfast. Her murder is a worrying reminder of decades of violence that fraught Brexit negotiations may be rekindling. We take a look at the push to get more young people into work in South Africa. And, why are more American politicians speaking several languages? Runtime: 21 min.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/troubling-adeathinnorthernireland&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 19:06:42 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lyra McKee’s killing sparks revulsion with the “New IRA”]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/04/24/lyra-mckees-killing-sparks-revulsion-with-the-new-ira]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/articles/20190427_brp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-24T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;THE SHOT that killed Lyra McKee, one of Northern Ireland’s most promising young journalists, was fired by a youth urged on by embittered ancients still convinced that Irish republicanism can prevail only through the barrel of a gun. Leaders of the so-called New IRA, which has admitted responsibility for the murder, persuaded the unidentified killer that mainstream republicans had betrayed their followers by swapping violence for politics. Yet in so doing, they have gravely damaged their cause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The killing of Ms McKee, hit by a stray bullet as she watched rioting in Derry/Londonderry on April 18th, has caused shock waves. Her funeral in Belfast today is due to be attended by the heads of the British and Irish governments, as well as a host of local politicians. That she died on the eve of the anniversary of the Good Friday Agreement, which brought an end to three decades of sectarian Troubles in 1998, has only underlined what is at stake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one expects a return to violence of the scale seen in the Troubles, whatever Brexit or any other development may bring. By the time it disbanded in 1998 the IRA had killed more than 1,700 people. Dissident republicans, who never accepted the peace and who now exist as a number of unco-ordinated splinters, have since then killed fewer than 100. This is enough for the security services to rate their threat as “severe”. But the “micro-groups”, as Sinn Fein, the main republican party, dismisses them, lack the experience or skills to maintain an effective and sustained campaign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their incompetence nonetheless makes them dangerous in other ways. This has recently been illustrated twice in Derry, with Ms McKee’s killing and, in January, the detonation of a car bomb in a busy street following a warning of only 30 minutes. The device could easily have caused civilian deaths or injuries. Dissident republicans also claimed responsibility for a number of parcel bombs posted to British addresses last month. The riot that Ms McKee was observing was sparked by police raids which gave the dissidents an excuse to blood young men in the arts of street warfare. The presence in the city of a TV camera crew may have given them an extra incentive to bring out a few guns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So-called loyalist paramilitary groups represent a different sort of threat, still roaming the backstreets of Belfast but these days less interested in sectarian violence than everyday gangsterism. Since the end of the Troubles they have devoted themselves to lining their pockets through drug-dealing, loan-sharking and extortion in Protestant ghettoes. In January an east-Belfast man who had fallen foul of a loyalist organisation was murdered by a five-man gang who stabbed him in the back 11 times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Attacks like this, as well as occasional beatings, bricks through windows, and so on, continue. But over the years the pattern has been that acts of terrorism which result in the death of civilians cause widespread revulsion and lead to a dip in terrorist activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms McKee’s killers have issued an apology, even if they have shown little sense of real remorse. But they do appear shaken, for they are well aware that deaths like hers are bad for their cause. The Derry offices of Saoradh, a political party supported by the New IRA, were smeared with red handprints by protesters. “Not in our name” was painted beneath a local republican mural. Police said that by the end of the Easter weekend over 140 people had come forward to offer information on the killing—a “sea change” in a city that has historically been reluctant to pass on information regarding republicans of any stripe. Many Derry doors which were once opened to dissidents may now be shut in their faces. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 19:06:41 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Global jihadists increasingly turn against religious targets]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/23/global-jihadists-increasingly-turn-against-religious-targets]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/articles/000_1fv0ez.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-23T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TWO DECADES ago al-Qaeda made its name by mounting a succession of bombings against America across the world. These included the American embassies in Kenya and Tanzania in 1998; an American destroyer moored in Yemen in 2000; and, most bloodily of all, the attacks of September 11th 2001 on American soil. Though Osama bin Laden, the group’s founder, had long railed against “Jews and Crusaders”, so giving a religious sectarian dimension to his global jihad, his central target was clear: “kill the Americans and their allies”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twenty years on, jihadists have changed their focus, particularly under the new generation of extremists affiliated with Islamic State (IS). The Easter Sunday bombing of three churches as well as hotels in Sri Lanka—claimed by IS, albeit without clear proof—constituted the largest co-ordinated terrorist attacks in Asia in recent times, taking the lives of more than 300 people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/articles/20190427_woc937_20190423_1746_59.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/articles/20190427_woc937_20190423_1746_59.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/articles/20190427_woc937_20190423_1746_59.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/articles/20190427_woc937_20190423_1746_59.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/articles/20190427_woc937_20190423_1746_59.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/articles/20190427_woc937_20190423_1746_59.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/articles/20190427_woc937_20190423_1746_59.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/articles/20190427_woc937_20190423_1746_59.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/articles/20190427_woc937_20190423_1746_59.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/articles/20190427_woc937_20190423_1746_59.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This reflects a broader trend in terrorism directed against religious targets. The number of people killed in attacks on mosques, churches and the like has increased sharply in the past decade—and faster than attacks on other targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to an analysis by &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; of data on worldwide terrorism compiled by the University of Maryland, there were 620 deaths in 240 attacks on religious targets in the five years between 2000 and 2004. That number has since risen sharply, to more than 4,000 deaths in 1,400 incidents between 2013 and 2017 ( the five most recent years for which data are available.) Two-thirds of these recent deaths have taken place in just four countries: Pakistan, Nigeria, Afghanistan and Egypt. These numbers exclude terrorist incidents in Iraq and Syria, where the civil wars distort global figures&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why is this so? One reason may be the baleful influence of IS which, in its formative years as al-Qaeda in Iraq (AQI), deliberately aimed to kill Shias, the country’s largest group, with the aim of polarising the population and driving Sunni Muslims into its arms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It took up that strategy so vigorously that it alarmed al-Qaeda’s leadership. In 2005 Ayman al-Zawahiri, then Mr bin Laden’s deputy and now al-Qaeda’s leader, warned AQI that it was alienating people: “the sectarian and chauvinistic factor”, he said, “is secondary in importance to outside aggression”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;AQI paid no attention. In 2014, rebranded as Islamic State (IS), it swept through large parts of Iraq and Syria using untrammelled violence and persecution of opposing sects. It also encouraged its acolytes around the world to conduct freelance attacks—something that al-Qaeda, with its more rigid hierarchy, was more reluctant to do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pattern of attacks reflected IS’s preference for theatrical assaults on a wider range of targets. To be sure, IS’s European followers have not stopped attacking transport hubs and concert-goers, much as al-Qaeda did a decade ago. But its devotees have also picked out religious sites, notably in the Middle East and Asia. In part they have been incited by IS propaganda, which claims Islam will defeat Christianity and take over Rome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;IS’s Egyptian branch is responsible for an onslaught of bombings against the country’s Coptic Christian minority (as well as Sufi Muslims). Its devotees in the Gulf have attacked Shia mosques. IS has also been linked to church bombings in Indonesia last year and in the Philippines in January.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Terrorism of course is meant to shock and terrorise. Its power is thus heightened when holy places are singled out and innocent worshippers and clerics slaughtered,” says Bruce Hoffman of Georgetown University. “IS understands the outsized impact of attacking such targets.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a sense, IS’s tactics mark a return to the jihadists’ war against the “near enemy”, in which jihadists often treated minorities as supporters of local dictators. Coptic churches were attacked in the 1980s; monks were beheaded in Algeria in the 1990s. “You can mobilise against others if you can declare them apostates,” says Raffaello Pantucci, of the Royal United Services Institute, a defence think-tank in London. “Once you have done that it’s easy to slaughter them en masse.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Al-Qaeda itself has not been averse to acts against religious targets, such as the bombing of a synagogue in Djerba, in Tunisia, in 2002. Yet even al-Qaeda’s leadership is still committed to the war against the “far enemy”, ie, America and the West, and finds IS’s overt sectarianism too much to stomach. According to Paul Cruickshank, editor of CTC Sentinel, a journal focused on terrorism, a month ago al-Qaeda’s leadership instructed followers to shun attacks on places of worship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Islamic State’s spectacular—though brief—seizure of territory and the creation of a “caliphate” in 2014 gave it worldwide cachet among extremists, who absorbed its nihilistic message and unshackled choice of targets. As the caliphate has collapsed, nearly a fifth of the 40,000-plus foreign fighters who had flocked to Iraq and Syria from more than 80 countries, have headed home—bringing with them contacts, expertise and sectarian fervour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest bombings suggest that religious sites in all countries, even those with little history of anti-Christian attacks such as Sri Lanka, have become fair game for jihadists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Picture: AFP)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 06:15:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China’s maritime ambitions are becoming more evident]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/china/2019/04/23/chinas-maritime-ambitions-are-becoming-more-evident]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/articles/20190427_cnp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-23T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS MILITARY PAGEANTS go, multinational parades of warships deliver quite a complex message. Over a dozen countries—ranging from friends to overt rivals—sent naval vessels to the eastern Chinese city of Qingdao on April 23rd. There they steamed past a destroyer carrying China’s commander-in-chief, President Xi Jinping, in honour of the 70th anniversary of the founding of the People’s Liberation Army Navy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paint gleaming and brass fittings buffed to a hospital shine, there were frigates from near-allies such as Russia, and destroyers from almost-foes like India. Their mission was friendship and diplomacy. But these were heavily armed peace envoys, warily visiting a China whose emergence as an ocean-going nation is shaking Asia, and may one day change the world. Visitors involved in territorial disputes with China, including Japan and Vietnam, sent ships bristling with advanced weaponry. America sent no ships at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China sent mixed messages, too. As celebrations began, the visitors were hailed by Mr Xi as a sort of floating United Nations. A peace-loving China yearned to work with foreign navies to secure international sea-lanes and safeguard the ocean’s riches, Mr Xi declared. On state television presenters noted that, as a mainstay of anti-piracy patrols in the Gulf of Aden since 2008, the Chinese navy had escorted more than 6,600 ships, from China and other countries, through bandit-infested waters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then came the bit which many Chinese viewers probably preferred: shots of their newest warships, dwarfing foreign visitors. Here came a Chinese ballistic missile submarine—nuclear-powered and designed for destroying enemy cities, not arresting Somali pirates. It glided past the destroyer carrying Mr Xi, who boarded wearing a dark Mao suit befitting his other jobs as the Communist Party’s general secretary and chairman of the Central Military Commission. “Comrades, greetings!” barked Mr Xi over a radio. “Chairman, greetings!” came the submariners’ shouted reply. On state television, presenters compared China’s newest destroyer, the 10,000-tonne Type 055, to the most powerful of America’s. Screens filled with archive footage of jets roaring from the deck of the Liaoning, China’s first aircraft carrier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On shore in the handsome, fog-shrouded port city of Qingdao, bilingual posters celebrating the naval anniversary offered variations on Mr Xi’s favourite diplomatic slogans, such as: “The Ocean connects us all, a community with a shared future.” Others, in Chinese, hailed the navy’s role as a political force, under the direct control of Mr Xi as the party’s chief. A banner outside Qingdao’s naval museum suggested that Mr Xi’s peace of mind was the ultimate test of naval modernisation. “Obey Chairman Xi’s commands. Answer to Chairman Xi. Let Chairman Xi be reassured,” it read.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cui Junkai, a 19-year-old student, had travelled from the city of Chengdu, hundreds of kilometres inland, for the fleet review. The parade-eve found Mr Cui in Qingdao’s naval museum, inspecting a wooden torpedo-boat from the years when China’s navy was a merely a “brown-water” one, tasked with launching guerrilla attacks in muddy coastal waters. A mighty navy offers China a double benefit, Mr Cui said. “It not only defends the nation, but demonstrates our power to the outside world.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Behind the teenager, rusty patrol boats bobbed at the museum quayside, recalling the decades when China boasted a “green-water navy”, capable of intimidating smaller neighbours but powerless when American battle-groups steamed by. That navy was a defensive force tasked with warding off sea-borne threats, not with projecting power over far horizons. In 1990 China’s then-president, Jiang Zemin, urged the navy to be “the motherland’s great wall at sea”. The next Communist leader, Hu Jintao, signalled a change in 2012 when he called for China to become a “great maritime power”. The navy saw its budgets soar and its fleet quality transformed. Today China has the region’s largest navy with over 300 ships, of which as many as 78 will be submarines, according to a Pentagon report to Congress in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese scholars have pored over the theories of Alfred Thayer Mahan, an American navy captain and 19th-century writer on “sea power” as a source of global strength resting on three pillars: commerce, naval firepower and access to far-flung bases. Mahan was a prescient man. On April 19th Chinese state television reported on China’s first naval base abroad, which opened in Djibouti last year. The report included a revealing on-camera prediction from the base’s political commissar: that support for far-flung missions would increasingly depend on such facilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Change of PLAN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Such talk alarms military chiefs in America and other countries. Their anxiety in turn worries Hu Bo, a leading maritime strategist at Peking University. For as China’s navy rises it has more than one goal, he says. First, to become a blue-water navy capable of providing security worldwide, which may perhaps involve opening a few more bases, for instance around the northern Indian Ocean. China’s other goal is “near-sea control”, Mr Hu says, meaning the capability to contain any threat in the western Pacific and northern Indian oceans—just as America and Russia currently enjoy comparative advantages close to home. That does not mean that China can or will evict all American ships from the South China Sea or other nearby waters, Mr Hu insists. In a generation’s time he can imagine a more restrained America and a more confident China reaching a new balance of power in those near seas, after a period of competition. The dangerous period is the next five or ten years, he says. “China’s capability is growing fast, but the United States is not ready to grant China status matching that power.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A balance must be reached, though. After millennia as an agrarian, continental power, China is a maritime nation, bound to the seas by strategic and commercial interests. Few foreigners would recognise the Chinese naval ensign today. That will change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:17:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Critics of Francis embrace the other “pope”, Benedict XVI]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/04/22/critics-of-francis-embrace-the-other-pope-benedict-xvi]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/000_1ft5f3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-22T14:57:40Z&quot;&gt;Apr 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;AS WAS CLEARLY observed on April 21st by excited pilgrims as well as television-watchers across the world, only one white-robed prelate appeared on a balcony overlooking Saint Peter’s Square to deliver the traditional Easter message. Pope Francis (pictured) duly chided rich countries over the arms race, called for peace in the greater Middle East and Africa, and lamented the victims of terror in Sri Lanka. The power of such occasions depends both on modern technology and on a centuries-old tradition, which holds that the task of representing Jesus Christ as his “vicar” on earth falls to a single, uniquely legitimate office-holder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;But in the grounds of the Vatican, there are two gentlemen who use the title of pope: Francis and his predecessor, Benedict XVI, who lives nearby in a comfortable former convent. Officially, they get along well. On April 15th the current pontiff called on Benedict to offer congratulations on the eve of his 92nd birthday. But in photographs, Francis looked less genial than usual, and some wondered whether the wishes had been delivered through gritted teeth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;For several years, it has been clear that the relatively liberal, relatively inclusive style that Francis brings to the papacy is triggering a wave of theological and political opposition in many Catholic quarters. And some of that opposition is crystallising around Benedict, who styles himself “pope emeritus” and has retained some of the trappings of his old office, including the all-white garb plus a papal ring and dangling cross.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;What is not so clear is how far Benedict himself, and/or people with strong influence over him, are encouraging people to think of him as a counter-weight to Francis. But Massimo Faggioli, an Italian theologian, has likened the present situation to a “post-modern version” of a medieval schism: between 1378 and 1417, two and sometimes three clerics vied for the title of pope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Recent events have brought the contrast between the two clerics to a head. Benedict’s newly-published &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/04/12/a-former-pope-blames-the-swinging-sixties-for-clerical-crimes&quot;&gt;essay&lt;/a&gt;, blaming the surging sex-abuse crisis on the swinging sixties and “homosexual cliques” in seminaries, was his most blatant intervention since stepping down in 2013. Francis showed a very different style when, in a TV show aired on April 19&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;, he assured a gay British comedian that “only people who don’t have a heart” would fail to respect him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;For Vatican-watchers, all this simply marks one more episode in a long-term build-up of tension between the two popes, egged on by conservative critics of Francis. It was three years ago that Matteo Salvini, the anti-immigrant politician who is now Italian interior minister, sported a T-shirt with a pun in capital letters. “IL MIO PAPA E BENEDETTO” could either mean “my pope is Benedict” or “my pope is blessed”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;On the ecclesiastical front, four conservative cardinals (of whom America’s Cardinal Raymond Burke was the best-known) showed their hand in November 2016 with a letter that challenged a Vatican document which had promised more generous treatment to Catholics who divorce and remarry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;A few months later, the Benedict camp seemed to offer moral support to that challenge. At the funeral of one of the four signatories, a German prelate who is one of Benedict’s close&lt;span &gt; &lt;/span&gt;aides, Georg Gänswein, read a letter from the ex-pontiff, saying pointedly that God would not abandon the church “even if the boat [is] on the verge of capsizing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Whereas traditionalist clerics take issue with Francis over reproduction and sexuality, worldly politicians find fault with him (and see merit in his predecessor) over questions like immigration and the protection of traditional Western culture. European conservatives loved Benedict for his perceived attachment to the heritage of their continent; their American counterparts resent Francis for his anti-capitalism and his embrace of the grievances of the global South. All these impulses have come together in the increasing prominence of a right-wing Catholic think-tank located not far from Rome, the Dignitatis Humanae Institute, with which Cardinal Burke and Steve Bannon, a former adviser of President Donald Trump, are deeply involved.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;In the world of Catholic theology, as opposed to its political exploitation, there are those who insist that the Francis-Benedict rift is either exaggerated or being mischievously fanned by people who have little real concern for either cleric. Indeed, even among theologically-minded fans of Francis, some still profess admiration for Benedict “at his best” as a clear thinker and teacher. Michael Sean Winters, a Catholic writer, responded to the 6,000-word essay by calling it a mixture of flawed analysis and trivial anecdote which nonetheless contained glimmers of the “genius and beauty” which characterised the work of Benedict (formerly Cardinal Joseph Ratzinger) at its finest.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;And to right-wing Americans who loathe Francis’s aversion to capitalism and embrace of the environment, it can be pointed out that both Benedict and his predecessor John Paul II had some harsh things to say about the unrestrained market. Nor has any recent pope been a fan of America’s military policy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;On the other hand, Benedict has hardly made life easy for his successor.&lt;span &gt;  &lt;/span&gt;After his surprise retirement in March 2013, he vowed to “remain hidden to the world”. He could have retired to a monastery in his native Bavaria and never said another public word. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Instead, he gave himself scope for future interventions. He not only kept many of the paraphernalia of office but, so critics argue, seemed keen to retain its essence. Many canon lawyers say his chosen title of “pope emeritus” is a dubiously-founded provocation, and that it would have been more correct to call himself bishop emeritus of Rome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Others note that Benedict’s resignation speech, in Latin, was profoundly and perhaps deliberately ambiguous. He said that, because of his age, he no longer had strength to exercise the papal ministry (munus in Latin). But he then went on to say that the munus had aspects: one consisted of acting and speaking and the other of praying and suffering. Father Stefano Violi, a canon-law teacher, reckons that Benedict was merely surrendering the administrative duties of a pope but not the pastoral ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;For conservatives who want to present themselves as anti-Francis but loyal (perhaps more loyal than the pontiff himself) to the Catholic tradition, Benedict’s presence in the Vatican city is, at a minimum, a golden opportunity.&lt;span &gt; And Benedict seems unable to resist the temptation of offering that opportunity.&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:17:18 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Congress fails to claw back the right to wage war]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/04/23/congress-fails-to-claw-back-the-right-to-wage-war]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/articles/20190427_usp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-23T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WERE THE founding fathers to return, suggested Michael Beschloss, a historian, in last year’s “Presidents of War”, they would be “thunderstruck” to discover how the power to kick off major wars could now “rest on the whim of a President”. Presidents have “regularly told Congress to go to hell” on such matters, as Harry Truman admiringly noted of his predecessor, James Polk.&lt;br/&gt;Donald Trump is keeping up that tradition. On April 16th he wielded his veto for only the second time in his presidency to strike down a groundbreaking law that might have forced him to end America’s support for the Saudi-led war against the Houthi militia in Yemen. The fighting has caused what the UN calls the world’s worst humanitarian crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That the bill got so far, so quickly, is notable in itself. It sped through Congress–passing the Senate on 13th March and the House on 4th April—because of expedited procedures, never before used, granted by the War Powers Resolution (WPR). This act was passed in 1973 in response to Richard Nixon’s secretive expansion of the Vietnam war. &lt;br/&gt;In theory, the WPR tied presidents’ hands by requiring them first to consult Congress before sending forces abroad, and then to ask Congress for a declaration of war or a specific mandate to keep them there beyond 60 days. In practice, most presidents have either stretched or ignored the law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much of the recent stretching has occurred as a result of America’s sprawling “war on terror”. Three days after the terrorist attacks of September 11th 2001, Congress passed an Authorization for Use of Military Force (AUMF) permitting George Bush to go after those who “planned, authorized, committed or aided” the atrocity. That was clearly a reference to al-Qaeda, then holed up in Afghanistan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But by 2016 the AUMF had been used by Mr Bush and his successor, Barack Obama, 37 times to justify action in 14 countries s–“even against groups that did not exist on 9/11”, points out Christopher Anders of the American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU). Mr Obama, for instance, deployed the AUMF in defence of his war on Islamic State in Iraq and Syria even though the group angrily split from al-Qaeda long ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the WPR was gutted long before the elastic AUMF created loopholes wide enough to fly F-16s through. Most presidents after Nixon have simply ignored it, declaring its demands to be an unconstitutional infringement on their executive powers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some presidents have tried to conjure up a mandate in dubious ways. When the Kosovo war crossed the 60-day mark in 1999, Bill Clinton insisted that Congress had expressed approval by ponying up money for it—never mind that the WPR explicitly says that does not count, and that lawmakers are loth to cut off funds for troops in the line of fire.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most inventive approach has been to pretend that, contrary to appearances, there is in fact no war. In 2011 Mr Obama said he was free to bomb Libya because the action was led by NATO, did not involve “sustained fighting or active exchanges of fire” and was unlikely to escalate—and so did not meet the definition of “hostilities” envisaged by the WPR. Mr Trump has put forward much the same argument for his own entanglement in Yemen (which started under Mr Obama). Indeed had he signed the Yemen bill rather than nixing it, it is likely that his administration would have claimed its provisions did not apply to Yemen anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lawmakers are right to roll their eyes at such make-believe. After all, American commanders sit in an operations room in Riyadh next to their Saudi counterparts. American engineers service the Saudi warplanes taking off to drop bombs. Until recently American planes refuelled the Saudi bombers mid-flight. War at arms-length is still war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile the fighting has left ten million Yemenis “one step away from famine”, warned the UN’s World Food Programme. Congress, though exasperated, does not have the numbers to override Mr Trump’s veto. But it is likely to continue the fight in other ways, such as by tacking riders onto the annual National Defense Authorization Act (NDAA), which is much trickier for the president to quash. At least some of the founding fathers would have approved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 03:16:25 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China throws a revealing party for the anniversary of its navy]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/china/2019/04/23/china-throws-a-revealing-party-for-the-anniversary-of-its-navy]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/articles/20190427_cnp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-23T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS MILITARY PAGEANTS go, multinational parades of warships deliver quite a complex message. Over a dozen countries—ranging from friends to overt rivals—sent naval vessels to the eastern Chinese city of Qingdao on April 23rd. There they steamed past a destroyer carrying China’s commander-in-chief, President Xi Jinping, in honour of the 70th anniversary of the founding of the People’s Liberation Army Navy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paint gleaming and brass fittings buffed to a hospital shine, there were frigates from near-allies such as Russia, and destroyers from almost-foes like India. Their mission was friendship and diplomacy. But these were heavily armed peace envoys, warily visiting a China whose emergence as an ocean-going nation is shaking Asia, and may one day change the world. Visitors involved in territorial disputes with China, including Japan and Vietnam, sent ships bristling with advanced weaponry. America sent no ships at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China sent mixed messages, too. As celebrations began, the visitors were hailed by Mr Xi as a sort of floating United Nations. A peace-loving China yearned to work with foreign navies to secure international sea-lanes and safeguard the ocean’s riches, Mr Xi declared. On state television presenters noted that, as a mainstay of anti-piracy patrols in the Gulf of Aden since 2008, the Chinese navy had escorted more than 6,600 ships, from China and other countries, through bandit-infested waters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then came the bit which many Chinese viewers probably preferred: shots of their newest warships, dwarfing foreign visitors. Here came a Chinese ballistic missile submarine—nuclear-powered and designed for destroying enemy cities, not arresting Somali pirates. It glided past the destroyer carrying Mr Xi, who boarded wearing a dark Mao suit befitting his other jobs as the Communist Party’s general secretary and chairman of the Central Military Commission. “Comrades, greetings!” barked Mr Xi over a radio. “Chairman, greetings!” came the submariners’ shouted reply. On state television, presenters compared China’s newest destroyer, the 10,000-tonne Type 055, to the most powerful of America’s. Screens filled with archive footage of jets roaring from the deck of the Liaoning, China’s first aircraft carrier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On shore in the handsome, fog-shrouded port city of Qingdao, bilingual posters celebrating the naval anniversary offered variations on Mr Xi’s favourite diplomatic slogans, such as: “The Ocean connects us all, a community with a shared future.” Others, in Chinese, hailed the navy’s role as a political force, under the direct control of Mr Xi as the party’s chief. A banner outside Qingdao’s naval museum suggested that Mr Xi’s peace of mind was the ultimate test of naval modernisation. “Obey Chairman Xi’s commands. Answer to Chairman Xi. Let Chairman Xi be reassured,” it read.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cui Junkai, a 19-year-old student, had travelled from the city of Chengdu, hundreds of kilometres inland, for the fleet review. The parade-eve found Mr Cui in Qingdao’s naval museum, inspecting a wooden torpedo-boat from the years when China’s navy was a merely a “brown-water” one, tasked with launching guerrilla attacks in muddy coastal waters. A mighty navy offers China a double benefit, Mr Cui said. “It not only defends the nation, but demonstrates our power to the outside world.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Behind the teenager, rusty patrol boats bobbed at the museum quayside, recalling the decades when China boasted a “green-water navy”, capable of intimidating smaller neighbours but powerless when American battle-groups steamed by. That navy was a defensive force tasked with warding off sea-borne threats, not with projecting power over far horizons. In 1990 China’s then-president, Jiang Zemin, urged the navy to be “the motherland’s great wall at sea”. The next Communist leader, Hu Jintao, signalled a change in 2012 when he called for China to become a “great maritime power”. The navy saw its budgets soar and its fleet quality transformed. Today China has the region’s largest navy with over 300 ships, of which as many as 78 will be submarines, according to a Pentagon report to Congress in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese scholars have pored over the theories of Alfred Thayer Mahan, an American navy captain and 19th-century writer on “sea power” as a source of global strength resting on three pillars: commerce, naval firepower and access to far-flung bases. Mahan was a prescient man. On April 19th Chinese state television reported on China’s first naval base abroad, which opened in Djibouti last year. The report included a revealing on-camera prediction from the base’s political commissar: that support for far-flung missions would increasingly depend on such facilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Change of PLAN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Such talk alarms military chiefs in America and other countries. Their anxiety in turn worries Hu Bo, a leading maritime strategist at Peking University. For as China’s navy rises it has more than one goal, he says. First, to become a blue-water navy capable of providing security worldwide, which may perhaps involve opening a few more bases, for instance around the northern Indian Ocean. China’s other goal is “near-sea control”, Mr Hu says, meaning the capability to contain any threat in the western Pacific and northern Indian oceans—just as America and Russia currently enjoy comparative advantages close to home. That does not mean that China can or will evict all American ships from the South China Sea or other nearby waters, Mr Hu insists. In a generation’s time he can imagine a more restrained America and a more confident China reaching a new balance of power in those near seas, after a period of competition. The dangerous period is the next five or ten years, he says. “China’s capability is growing fast, but the United States is not ready to grant China status matching that power.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A balance must be reached, though. After millennia as an agrarian, continental power, China is a maritime nation, bound to the seas by strategic and commercial interests. Few foreigners would recognise the Chinese naval ensign today. That will change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 02:10:51 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why wages for the poorest Americans are on the rise]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/23/why-wages-for-the-poorest-americans-are-on-the-rise]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/money_talks_12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-23T17:50:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS THE debate about raising the minimum wage in America intensifies, it seems that wages for the lowest-paid Americans are already on the increase. And why is wage growth in Britain picking up at last? Finally, the most expensive homes are becoming a bit less expensive. Simon Long hosts.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-wagingbull&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id420929545?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/2Yvo8QxZf7WlSEsIwKjtX4&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWVjb25vbWlzdG1vbmV5dGFsa3M&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=18377&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/Business--Economics-Podcasts/The-Economist-Money-Talks-p603831/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 01:07:35 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to predict a coup]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/23/how-to-predict-a-coup]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_WOC735.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-23T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TWO AGEING PRESIDENTS, one bad and one awful, were forced from office this month: Abdelaziz Bouteflika in Algeria and Omar al-Bashir in Sudan. Mr Bouteflika had been in power since 1999; Mr Bashir, since 1989. Their hasty and unlamented departures raise a question: how easy is it to predict a coup?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One obstacle to building a good coup-predicting model is that coups are extremely rare and becoming even more so. However, as our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/international/2019/04/20/how-to-predict-when-a-despot-will-fall&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;print-edition story&lt;/a&gt; explains, social scientists now have more tools than ever before at their disposal. Perhaps the most rigorous quantitative forecast of sudden regime changes is CoupCast, published by One Earth Future, an NGO.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CoupCast finds that economic misery is linked to higher coup risk, as is extreme weather. But political factors matter more. Dictators tend to lose popularity when they stay in office for too long. Autocrats who cling to power after losing elections are particularly likely to be deposed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The strongest predictor of future instability is past instability. CoupCast rated Algeria the country most likely to experience a coup just before Mr Bouteflika&amp;#x27;s exit. As for who might be next, the leaders of Burkina Faso, Afghanistan and South Sudan should be nervous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 01:07:34 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>