<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[“Too Old To Die Young” and the problem of the unsupervised auteur]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/20/too-old-to-die-young-and-the-problem-of-the-unsupervised-auteur]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_BKP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-20T13:37:08Z&quot;&gt;Jun 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE RISE of subscription-based channels and streaming services has enabled cinema’s biggest names to develop their own television series, not as a way to make a quick buck between passion projects, but as a way to tell ever longer and richer stories. Following Paolo Sorrentino’s “The Young Pope”, Woody Allen’s “Crisis in Six Scenes” and Ava DuVernay’s “When They See Us”, the latest and most radical example is Nicolas Winding Refn’s ten-part series, “Too Old To Die Young”, released on Amazon on June 14th. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fans of the Danish director’s films, including “Pusher”, “Drive” and “Only God Forgives”, won’t be surprised to learn that he has come up with another seedy, brutal, yet coolly stylish urban crime thriller. But during its 13-hour running time, two things become clear. The first is that nothing quite like it has ever been made before. The other is that this is probably for the best. Shot by shot, “Too Old To Die Young” is startlingly beautiful. But when all those shots are strung together, the result is so stupefying as to be almost unwatchable. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Co-written by Ed Brubaker, the first episode introduces Martin (Miles Teller), a 30-year-old Los Angeles Country Sheriff, and his partner Larry (Lance Gross). They are both bad cops, but Larry is worse: a typical evening for him is spent harassing women, taking bribes and discussing whether he should murder his cokehead mistress before she can reveal their affair to his wife. It is difficult to be upset when a Mexican youth, Jesus (Augusto Aguilera), walks up to him in the street and shoots him dead. But Martin is afraid that he will be executed next, because he and Larry killed Jesus’s mother, the sister of a druglord. He needs the protection of a Nigerian gangster, Damian (Babs Olusanmokun), and to pay for that service he has to kill whomever Damian chooses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So much for the first 93-minute episode—or “Volume One” as Mr Refn calls it. The 97-minute second episode abandons Martin and heads down to Mexico, where Jesus meets Yaritza (Cristina Rodlo), a tarot-card reader who styles herself as “The High Priestess of Death”. The 76-minute third episode returns to Los Angeles, where Martin meets Viggo (John Hawkes), a retired FBI agent, and Diana (Jena Malone), a new-age therapist and victim-support officer. With Diana’s help, Viggo goes around murdering rapists, but he wants Martin to take his place as “an extermination machine eliminating all evil in the universe”. And so the series goes on, shifting from blackly comic Tarantino-esque violence to apocalyptic Lynchian surrealism—but doing so very slowly indeed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Too Old To Die Young” is relentlessly sleazy and politically dubious, but not many people will sit through it long enough for its exploitative aspects to be an issue. Wallowing in the freedom and the budget that Amazon has given him, Mr Refn lets his hard-boiled saga trudge along at such a lethargic pace that you can leave the room and make a cup of tea in the gaps between the lines of murmured dialogue. It could be argued that the blank, affectless Martin has been numbed by the shock of his partner’s death, but the other characters seem to be just as dazed and deadpan as he is. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps Mr Refn should be congratulated on conjuring up such a murky atmosphere. Expertly shot by Darius Khondji and Diego Garcia, with a synthesiser-heavy score by Cliff Martinez, “Too Old To Die Young” is set in a world sapped of energy, a purgatory where shaded lamps and neon signs furnish nothing more than faint patches of light in the gloom; so maybe it is appropriate that the characters drift around like ghosts. Perhaps, too, Mr Refn should be congratulated on challenging the audience’s expectations with an anti-thriller, an avant-garde art installation to compare with Andy Warhol’s “Sleep” and “Empire”. The decision to combine bloody-minded perversity with a torpid tempo is certainly daring. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But, for Amazon, it was a mistake to allow Mr Refn to do what he wanted for 13 hours: “Too Old To Die Young” would have been a lot more compelling if it had been 11 hours shorter. After an episode or two, viewers may feel as if they are too old to keep watching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Too Old To Die Young” is available on Amazon Prime Video now&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 21:41:17 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[To restore calm in Hong Kong, try democracy]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/20/to-restore-calm-in-hong-kong-try-democracy]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_ldp001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-20T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;T WAS PROBABLY&lt;/small&gt; the largest political protest ever staged in Hong Kong. It may have been the biggest in China’s history. Organisers reckon that about 1.9m people joined the demonstration on June 16th. Even during the unrest in Tiananmen Square three decades ago, no single protest approached that scale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The estimate may not be reliable. But there is no disputing the impact of this display of discontent, and others leading up to it. It came only a week after another demonstration of jaw-dropping size and four days after one that escalated into Hong Kong’s most violent disorder since the 1960s. The territory’s government and its overlords in Beijing could not have received a clearer message that Hong Kongers distrust their own leaders, as well as the central government’s (see China section). Protesters are demanding that Hong Kong’s chief executive, Carrie Lam, step down. Yet, even if she did, trust would still not be restored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The unrest was triggered by a proposed law that would allow the extradition of criminal suspects from Hong Kong (where the rule of law still more or less prevails) to the Chinese mainland (where those who displease the ruling party have little chance of a fair trial). The law would also let Hong Kong’s courts seize assets connected with crimes on the mainland. At a news conference on June 18th Mrs Lam apologised for her handling of the bill (but gave no indication that she would resign). Earlier, just before the latest record-breaking demonstration, she had announced that the bill would be shelved indefinitely. All this was welcome, but it is not enough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This crisis has vividly shown how disillusioned Hong Kongers have become. It was different in 2003, when hundreds of thousands of people took to the streets in protest against a proposed anti-sedition law. Then the Communist Party had reason to hope that it could defuse the problem by allowing Hong Kong to shelve the bill, and encouraging the unpopular chief executive, Tung Chee-hwa, to resign (he did so in 2005). At the time, many people in Hong Kong still thought that the party would eventually fulfil its pledge to give them more democracy. In the meantime they could grudgingly put up with the appointment system, which ensured that Mr Tung’s successor was loyal to the government in Beijing. For his first few months in office the new man, Donald Tsang, enjoyed strong public support. Some pro-democracy politicians even felt hopeful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their optimism faded as the party’s intentions became clearer. During the “Umbrella Movement” of 2014, when protesters staged weeks of sit-ins to press for free and fair elections to the post of chief executive, China’s leaders dug in their heels. They made it plain that the “universal suffrage” Hong Kong had been promised would mean only the chance to vote for someone the party considers loyal. That is why Hong Kongers are without illusion today. They see Mrs Lam, who took over in 2017, as the party’s stooge—as they will see her successor, too. Without democracy, or a credible promise of it, no leaders in the territory will be seen as legitimate, severely limiting their ability to govern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China’s leader, Xi Jinping, therefore has a stark choice. He can keep Hong Kong’s political system as it is and carry on trying to stifle the freedoms that Hong Kongers otherwise enjoy. The result would be more protests and probably more violence. Businesspeople would become more jittery, and Hong Kong’s reputation as a safe base from which to trade with the mainland would be at risk. Or Mr Xi can offer Hong Kong hope again, by setting out a timetable for real democratic reform. “We have to have the confidence that Hong Kong people can manage Hong Kong well,” goes a mantra of China’s leaders. It is time to let its people try. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Leaders&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;China’s chance&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 21:41:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cleaning up nuclear waste is an obvious task for robots]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/06/20/cleaning-up-nuclear-waste-is-an-obvious-task-for-robots]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_std001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-20T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;S&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;OME PEOPLE&lt;/small&gt; worry about robots taking work away from human beings, but there are a few jobs that even these sceptics admit most folk would not want. One is cleaning up radioactive waste, particularly when it is inside a nuclear power station—and especially if the power station in question has suffered a recent accident.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those who do handle radioactive material must first don protective suits that are inherently cumbersome and are further encumbered by the air hoses needed to allow the wearer to breathe. Even then their working hours are strictly limited, in order to avoid prolonged exposure to radiation and because operating in the suits is exhausting. Moreover, some sorts of waste are too hazardous for even the besuited to approach safely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, send in the robots? Unfortunately that is far from simple, for most robots are not up to the task. This became clear after events in 2011 at the Fukushima Daiichi nuclear power plant in Japan, which suffered a series of meltdowns after its safety systems failed following a tsunami. The site at Fukushima has turned into something of a graveyard for those robots dispatched into it to monitor radiation levels and start cleaning things up. Many got stuck, broke down or had their circuits fried by the intense radiation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Intelligence test&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stopping such things happening again is part of the work of the National Centre for Nuclear Robotics (&lt;small&gt;NCNR&lt;/small&gt;). This is a collaborative effort involving several British universities. It is led by Rustam Stolkin of the University of Birmingham, and its purpose is to improve the routine use of robotics in nuclear power stations as well as to ensure that robotic trips into irradiated areas are less likely to end up as suicide missions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One problem with the robots dispatched into the ruins of Fukushima Daiichi was that they were not particularly clever. Most were operated by someone twiddling joysticks at a safe distance. Such machines are awkward to steer and their arms are tricky to move accurately when viewed via a video screen. Dr Stolkin reckons the answer is to equip them with artificial intelligence (&lt;small&gt;AI&lt;/small&gt;), so that they can operate autonomously.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nuclear industry, though, is extremely conservative and not yet prepared to let autonomous robots loose within its facilities. So, for the time being at least, &lt;small&gt;AI&lt;/small&gt; will be used to assist human operators. For example, instead of relying on a remote human operator to manipulate all its controls, an &lt;small&gt;AI&lt;/small&gt;-equipped robot faced with a pile of different objects to move would employ a camera to understand those objects’ shapes and positions relative to one another. It could then plan how best to grasp each object and move it to, say, an appropriately designed disposal skip without it colliding with anything else in the vicinity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A human being would remain in overall control of the process via a motorised joystick that exerts forces on the operator’s hand similar to those he or she would feel by actually grasping the object. But although the operator still uses the joystick to move the robot’s arm to carry out a particular task, it is the &lt;small&gt;AI&lt;/small&gt; which takes care of the details. It makes sure the arm swings in exactly the right direction and picks things up properly. Such an arrangement has already been successfully tested at the Springfields nuclear-fuel facility in north-west England. It was used to cut up contaminated steel with a high-powered laser.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other members of &lt;small&gt;NCNR&lt;/small&gt; are examining different aspects of the problem. At the University of Bristol, Tom Scott leads a group working on means for robots to identify materials, including various sorts of plastic, from the “fingerprints” provided by the distinctive ways they scatter laser light. At Queen Mary, a college of the University of London, Kaspar Althoefe’s team is working on radiation-resilient tactile sensors for robots’ fingers. Gerhard Neumann of the University of Lincoln is developing advanced navigation systems. And to ensure robots’ circuits don’t get frazzled, Klaus McDonald-Maier at the University of Essex is developing electronics toughened against the effects of radiation, including circuits that automatically detect and correct errors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Besides helping run nuclear power stations, all this will also assist with the growing need to clean up and recycle nuclear waste—and not just because of disasters like Fukushima. Early members of the nuclear club, such as America, Britain, France and Russia, have accumulated a vast legacy of the stuff. In Britain alone, some 4.9m tonnes of contaminated nuclear material are in need of safe disposal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lot of this is found at one of the most hazardous industrial sites in Europe, Sellafield, also in north-west England. Sellafield began producing plutonium for bombs in 1947. In 1956 the world’s first commercial-sized civil nuclear power station opened there. The site went on to become a centre for reprocessing nuclear fuel. Cleaning up Sellafield’s decaying buildings and nuclear-waste storage facilities will take decades. Robots with autonomous abilities would greatly hurry that process along.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nor is it just inside buildings that robots can help. This April Dr Scott and his colleagues at Bristol completed an aerial survey of the Red Forest in the Chernobyl exclusion zone in Ukraine using robotic drones. Even 33 years after the accident at the site’s number four reactor, they found previously undetected radiation hotspots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike a neat and tidy factory, where robots can be programmed to undertake repetitive tasks without any surprises, decontaminating an old nuclear site requires the ability to operate in an unstructured environment. In some cases, operators may not even know what they might find inside a building. Devising artificial intelligence clever enough to deal with all this will be tricky. But if Dr Stolkin and his colleagues succeed, their efforts are likely to have a wider impact, stretching even into the world of jobs that people are, at the moment at least, content to do themselves.&lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Science and technology&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Cybernetic skivvies&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 21:41:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[African swine fever spreads to South-East Asia]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/20/african-swine-fever-spreads-to-south-east-asia]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_asp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-20T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HERE ARE&lt;/small&gt; few dishes that a typical Filipino, Thai or Vietnamese would not consider improved by the addition of pork. What better to stuff a squid with, or garnish a bowl of steaming noodles, or simply spit-roast and scoff? No wonder, then, that South-East Asia is home to more than 83m pigs. But the outbreak of African swine fever that has swept through China in recent months is now spreading across the region. Its governments are likely to find it no easier than China’s to contain the disease, which is harmless to humans but typically fatal to pigs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swine fever first crossed the border from China into Vietnam in February. It has gradually worked its way south, and in April spread to Cambodia (see map). Thailand fears it is next. In fact, the disease could already be there or elsewhere: experts worry that monitoring and reporting are patchy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pigs catch the disease from each other, from contaminated surfaces, from ticks and from food (slop containing infected pork or pig’s blood). There is also a risk that farmed pigs may be infected by wild ones, and vice versa. Those transporting not just live pigs, but also pork, across borders risk introducing swine fever to new areas. Meanwhile, pork prices have jumped more than 40% compared with a year ago and analysts expect overall inflation to rise in Vietnam and Cambodia as a result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Culling swine is one of the main ways officials hope to curb the disease. Vietnam has slaughtered 2.5m pigs, twice as many as China. Bans on the import of pigs and pork are another tactic. But many of the region’s pig farms are tiny, as in China. Their owners cannot afford to erect special fencing or buy commercial feed. The temptation, if they suspect their pigs are infected, is to kill or sell them quickly and quietly, to save themselves from financial ruin. Although the Vietnamese government compensates farmers who report sick pigs that are subsequently culled, the fear of slow or low payments can still put farmers off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, international co-ordination, especially between governments and companies in South-East Asia’s pork industry, has been impressive, says Wantanee Kalpravidh of the Food and Agriculture Organisation, a &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt; agency. She lauds a scheme to send Thai pork to Cambodia to meet demand at affordable prices—on carefully cleaned and monitored vehicles—to discourage the smuggling of possibly contaminated meat from Vietnam. Somkuan Choowatanapakorn of Charoen Pokphand Foods, a big Thai agribusiness that handles lots of pork, says the company has “taken steps already” to train farmers to recognise and respond to the disease’s symptoms. He adds that contingency plans for an outbreak are also in place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite such efforts, the scale of the porcine plague in China means that South-East Asia will probably struggle with it for as long as its neighbour does. A working vaccine is still a long way off. It is hard to see what can save the region’s bacon. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Asia&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Swine on the line&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 21:41:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The UN revises down its population forecasts]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/22/the-un-revises-down-its-population-forecasts]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_gdc100.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-22T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190622_GDC100_population1/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE UNITED NATIONS&lt;/small&gt; is the world’s most important watcher of human tides. Its demographers have a good record of predicting global population change, although they have made mistakes about individual countries. So it is worth paying attention when the &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt; revises its figures, as it does every few years. The latest bulletin is especially surprising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent revisions have sent the projected global population upwards. The one released on June 17th cuts it back. The &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt; now thinks the world will contain a little over 9.7bn people in 2050 and just under 10.9bn in 2100. The first figure is 37m lower than the &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt; forecast two years ago. The latter is 309m lower—almost an America’s worth of people revised away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Birth rates are falling faster than expected in some developing countries. In the late 1980s Kenya had a fertility rate of 6.5, implying a woman could expect to have that many children. Two years ago the &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt; reckoned Kenya’s fertility rate would drop to 2.1 (the point at which the population sustains itself naturally) only in the late 2070s. Because of new data, it now thinks Kenya will reach that point a decade earlier. Uganda also looks less fecund. A smaller cut to India’s fertility rate has a big effect on the global population forecasts because India has so many people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190622_GDC100population2/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt;’s population model assumes that countries with fertility rates well below two will bounce back a little. Even in countries where babies have become rare, most people continue to believe that the ideal family contains two or even three kids. But the recovery keeps failing to happen in some places, so the demographers have changed their forecasts in a second way. They now expect some countries with extremely low birth rates, such as Italy, Japan and South Korea, to stay that way for years. Korea, which has a fertility rate of just 1.1, is now expected to have 30m people in 2100—down from 51m today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190622_GDC100population3/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another change has to do with death. Most people are living longer. The biggest improvement is in east and southern Africa, where &lt;small&gt;HIV&lt;/small&gt; is being treated better. In America, however, the opioid epidemic has pushed up the death rate, especially for men. The chance of a 15-year-old boy dying by the age of 50 is now higher in America than in Bangladesh. It would be nice if the American forecast, at least, proved to be too pessimistic. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Sources: UN; Gapminder&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Graphic detail&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Missing millions&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 20:40:25 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why interest rates in Britain are likelier to fall than rise]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/20/why-interest-rates-in-britain-are-likelier-to-fall-than-rise]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_brp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-20T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;T WAS A&lt;/small&gt; turning point in Britain’s recovery from the financial crisis of 2008-09. In November 2017 the monetary policy committee (&lt;small&gt;MPC&lt;/small&gt;) of the Bank of England raised the base rate of interest from 0.25% to 0.5%, the first increase in over a decade. Nine months later came a further rise of equal size—and traders priced in another one shortly thereafter. But then the mood music changed. No further rises materialised (as we went to press on June 20th the &lt;small&gt;MPC&lt;/small&gt; was expected to leave interest rates on hold for the tenth month running). Financial markets have come to take the view that the next move in rates is more likely to be down than up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bank turned hawkish in 2017 because it feared that consumer-price inflation would settle above its 2% target. A 10% depreciation of sterling against other currencies after the Brexit referendum of 2016 made imports pricier. At the same time the unemployment rate continued to fall (see chart), forcing employers to compete harder for workers by offering them better pay. With weak productivity growth, the &lt;small&gt;MPC&lt;/small&gt; feared that employers would be forced to pass on rising wage costs to their customers. For a while these fears looked founded: inflation hit 3.1% in late 2017.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_brc271.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_brc271.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_brc271.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_brc271.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_brc271.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_brc271.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_brc271.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_brc271.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_brc271.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_brc271.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet since then inflation has fallen a lot further than the &lt;small&gt;MPC&lt;/small&gt; had believed it would. Data released on June 19th put the inflation rate in May at 2% on the nose. Companies may be doing a better job than expected at raising productivity, which allows them to absorb higher wage costs. The impact of sterling’s depreciation may also be fading faster than expected, suggested Michael Saunders, a member of the &lt;small&gt;MPC&lt;/small&gt;, in a speech on June 10th. Companies may have passed on higher import prices to consumers in one go, rather than phasing them in slowly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lower-than-expected inflation also owes something to the level of demand in the economy. A trade war between America and China is causing global economic growth to slow (the Federal Reserve and the European Central Bank are expected to cut interest rates before long). Britain’s economy, highly exposed to trade, moves in tandem with world trends. Brexit is another drag. Postponing it from March 29th to October 31st headed off the calamity of a no-deal exit, but the delay has prompted some companies to hold off on investment until the outlook is clearer. In the past year capital spending by businesses has fallen in real terms. Consumer confidence remains low. The data released so far point to zero &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; growth in the second quarter of 2019, compared with an earlier forecast by the bank of 0.2%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some members of the &lt;small&gt;MPC&lt;/small&gt;, including Mr Saunders and Andy Haldane, the bank’s chief economist, continue to insist that rate rises are around the corner. If Britain pulls off a smooth exit from the European Union by the end of October, business investment could bounce back. Another extension would prolong the uncertainty, however; and a no-deal Brexit would almost certainly force the bank to loosen monetary policy to gee up the economy, even as sterling depreciated again. The case for doveishness is strengthening. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Britain&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Hawks take flight&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 20:40:23 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Facebook wants to create a worldwide digital currency]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/20/facebook-wants-to-create-a-worldwide-digital-currency]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_wbd002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-20T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;A&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt; GLOBAL DIGITAL&lt;/small&gt; currency would make sending money across the world as easy as texting. It would do away with fees, delays and other barriers to the flow of cash. It might give those in less developed countries access to the financial system and a means to protect hard-earned wages against runaway inflation. It could trigger a wave of innovation in finance, much as the internet did in online services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That, in a nutshell, is what Facebook promised on June 18th. Within a year, the social network will launch a new currency to be known as Libra, in honour of an ancient Roman unit of mass—it is also the word for “pound” in many romance languages. Inevitably, Facebook dished out a generous helping of trendy words like crypto and blockchain. Unable to contain its appetite for Silicon Valley platitudes, Facebook claimed that its mission was to “empower billions of people”. Making money or strengthening its market power are, apparently, a sideshow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Notwithstanding the guff, the commercial potential is indeed significant—as are the potential problems. If each of Facebook’s 2.4bn users converted a slice of their savings into Libras, it could become a widely circulated currency. It could also, if broadly adopted, vest unprecedented power in the hands of its issuer. In a tacit acknowledgment that its mishandling of user data, tolerance of the spread of misinformation and other sins have devalued its stock with policymakers, users and potential partners—though not investors—Facebook wants to outsource the running of Libra to a consortium of worthies recruited from the world of finance, technology and &lt;small&gt;NGO&lt;/small&gt;s. The consequences for the global financial system could be significant (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/node/21765645&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;). So could the impact on Facebook’s business.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the project lives up to the mock-ups, buying, selling, holding, sending and receiving Libras will become a doddle. It can be done in Facebook’s Messenger app or WhatsApp, another messaging-service-cum-social-network it owns—and, later next year, in a stand-alone app.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far, so familiar. Messenger already offers payments to Americans. WhatsApp is testing a similar function in India. But these services do not cross borders, and require users to have a bank account. Fintech firms like TransferWise, which offer international transfers, take a 4-5% cut to wire $200, a third less than Western Union. But Libra will be much cheaper, and require no bank accounts: more Bitcoin than Venmo.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Except that, unlike Bitcoins and other cryptocurrencies, Libras will change hands in seconds, not minutes, for next to nothing, not a few dollars. The system should handle 1,000 transactions a second at its launch, and more later, compared with no more than seven a second for Bitcoin. The virtual coins will be bought with real money, which will top up the reserve backing the currency. This should prevent wild price swings from speculation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If it works, Libra could be a money-spinner for Facebook, albeit not directly. Notional transaction fees would not generate much revenue. But Libras should allow Facebook to charge more for online ads, by making purchases of advertised products quicker and simpler. It could furnish a new source of data to target adverts, making up for user information Facebook will forgo with the “pivot to privacy”, which Mark Zuckerberg, its boss, proclaimed in March in respect of messaging. Facebook may catch up with WeChat, a Chinese super-app which offers payments and other services, and whose foreign ambitions are on hold as the Sino-American trade war rages on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Technically and financially, Facebook could probably pull off such an ambitious undertaking on its own. But not politically. Its culture is less amoral than it was in its youth, when it aspired to “move fast and break things”—but only a bit. Chary consumers may choose not to entrust their money to a social network which has, until recently, leaked their personal data left and right. Unless users are on board, merchants may be reluctant to embrace the currency, however hassle-free.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enter the Libra consortium. The association, to be based in Geneva, will take over from Facebook before the first Libra has been spent, and manage the hard-currency reserves. Facebook has enlisted 28 other prospective founding members out of an envisaged 100, each with equal voting rights and operating a node in a decentralised system which issues coins. They include financial firms (Visa, Stripe), online services (Spotify, Uber), cryptocurrency wallets (Anchorage, Coinbase), venture capitalists (Andreessen Horowitz, Union Square Ventures) and charities (Kiva, Mercy Corps)—though, for the time being, no banks. Not a libertarian alternative to the existing financial system, in other words, but a complement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To add credibility to its promise, broken in the past, to keep social and financial data separate, Facebook has created a subsidiary, Calibra, to run Libra services within its apps. It is unlikely to face hurdles to uptake from Apple or Google. It is impossible to imagine them expelling Messenger and WhatsApp—and later other providers Facebook is inviting to the open-source project—from their app stores, as they have done with other cryptocurrency offerings, many of which were scams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To get Libra going, the consortium will pay merchants to offer discounts to customers who use the new currency, financed by a $10m one-off fee each member pays for a seat at the table. Eventually, Facebook would like anybody, not just the consortium, to be able to generate the currency, transfer it and offer services on top of its “blockchain” (crypto-speak for the database that keeps track of who owns what). At that point, Libra would turn into Bitcoin, minus the kinks and the libertarianism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Hard currency&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a project with so many moving parts, much can go wrong. Although Facebook says it has a working prototype, the technology is untested; sceptics doubt that a 100-node system, let alone a bigger one, could process thousands of transactions per second. Hackers are doubtless champing at the bit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then there are consortium dynamics. Facebook will have to prove to the other 99 Libra members that it is truly prepared to give up control. At the same time, because important decisions need a two-thirds majority, someone has to knock heads together. The history of information technology is littered with initiatives that collapsed under the weight of internal conflict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The biggest barrier may be political. Facebook has apparently consulted many regulators. The providers of digital wallets will have to comply with national rules, such as those against money-laundering. Calibra, whose integration into Messenger and WhatsApp will initially make it the dominant wallet, is bound to stoke competition concerns. These may recede as the currency grows bigger and more decentralised, only to be replaced by worries about financial stability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Libra’s success, then, is far from assured. But it could prove useful even if it flops, for it offers a blueprint for how Facebook itself could one day be governed. The Libra Association’s main task is to oversee the blockchain, ensuring, for instance, that Calibra does not enjoy privileged access to it. An equivalent Facebook Association, some observers have ventured, could be composed of representatives of users, advertisers, data-protection authorities and so on. Their job could be to oversee the “social graph”, another database, which lists all of Facebook’s users and the links between them—and to guarantee that Facebook users can post to another social network, and vice versa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Calls for a Facebook constitution along these lines have grown louder as the social network’s influence on world affairs, from election-meddling in America to genocide in Myanmar, has become apparent. Mr Zuckerberg is no stranger to such thinking. In 2009 Facebook let users vote on big changes in its privacy policies but abandoned the experiment with global democracy a few years later. Last year Mr Zuckerberg announced that Facebook wanted to set up a “content review board” of independent experts—a kind of “Supreme Court”, in his words, which would make “the final judgment call on what should be acceptable speech”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asked whether Libra could serve as a model for Facebook, David Marcus, who is in charge of the project, replies that it marks “a coming of age, the moment we recognise that there are some things that we shouldn’t control—and a radical departure from the traditional way of operating things”. Perhaps. But checks and balances would almost certainly make Facebook less profitable. It would be ironic if a new digital currency marked the beginning of the end of Facebook’s money-minting days.&lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Business&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Coin flip&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 20:40:22 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The promotion curse]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/20/the-promotion-curse]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_wbd001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-16T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;S YOUR PROMOTION&lt;/small&gt; really necessary? Many workers focus their hopes on climbing the hierarchy of their organisations. The prospect of higher pay helps explain their ambition, but so does the greater status that comes with each successive title.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This scramble can often end in disappointment. The Peter principle, developed by Laurence Peter for a book published in 1969, states that workers get promoted until they reach their level of incompetence. It makes perfect sense. If you are good at your job, you rise up the career ladder. Eventually, there will be a job you are not good at and at that point your career will stall. The logical corollary is that any senior staff members who have been in their job for an extended period are incompetent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is another problem with chasing the promotion chimera. In a recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://voxeu.org/article/promotions-and-peter-principle&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt; for Vox&lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;, an online portal, the records of almost 40,000 salespeople across 131 firms were studied by Alan Benson, Danielle Li and Kelly Shue. They found that companies have a strong tendency to promote the best sales people. Convincing others to buy goods and services is a useful skill, requiring charisma and persistence. But, as the authors point out, these are not the same capabilities as the strategic planning and administrative competence needed to lead a sales team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research then looked at what happened after these super-salespeople were promoted. Their previous sales performance was actually a negative indicator of managerial success. The sales growth of workers assigned to the star sellers was 7.5 percentage points lower than for those whose managers were previously weaker performers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scott Adams, the cartoonist, described this problem in his book, “The Dilbert Principle”. In his world, the least competent people get promoted because these are the people you don’t want to do the actual work. It is foolish to promote the best salesperson or computer programmer to a management role, since the company will then be deprived of unique skills. That is how the workers in the Dilbert cartoon strip end up being managed by the clueless “pointy-haired boss”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bartleby is not an expert at climbing the greasy pole. When he was last promoted, Iraq had yet to be invaded. In part, that is because he has observed a variant on the Peter and Dilbert principles; what might be dubbed the Bartleby curse. People get promoted until they reach a level when they stop enjoying their jobs. At this point, it is not just their competence that is affected; it is their happiness as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trick to avoiding this curse is to stick to what you like doing. If you enjoy teaching, don’t be a headmaster or college principal. If you like writing articles and columns, editing other people’s work (let alone conducting career reviews) may not give you the same degree of satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another problem with pursuing frequent promotions is that it turns you into a supplicant, endlessly in search of favourable feedback from the higher-ups. This can lead you to lose control of your work-life balance. In Charles Handy’s new book, “21 Letters On Life And Its Challenges”, the veteran management theorist recalls an epiphany when working for Royal Dutch Shell, an oil giant. “In exchange for the promise of financial security and guaranteed work, I had sold my time to complete strangers with my permission for them to use that time for their own purposes,” he writes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The higher up the ladder you go, the greater the demands are likely to be on your time. The chief executive will expect you to be available at weekends; after all, that is why you get paid the big bucks. Subordinates will also feel that they are able to ask you tricky questions whenever they arise; they don’t want to take decisions that are above their pay grade. If you are in charge of a geographical region, you may spend much of your time on planes, visiting the corporate troops. And when you are not travelling, your day will be filled with meetings. At the end of the day, you will have been extremely busy, but with a nagging feeling that you have achieved nothing of substance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So that shiny promotion may not be for everyone. Beware the curse of overwork and dissatisfaction. Some people like to devote their whole lives to their job and be at the centre of events. It is best to let them get on with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 20:40:21 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The rising cost of education and health care is less troubling than believed]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/20/the-rising-cost-of-education-and-health-care-is-less-troubling-than-believed]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_fnd000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;A&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;MONG THE&lt;/small&gt; compensations of ageing is the right to bore youngsters with stories of the prices of yesteryear. Once upon a time a ticket to the cinema cost just five quid, and a hogshead of mead but a farthing. Of course, savvier youths know how to debunk such tales. Adjust for inflation and many things are cheaper than ever. Since 1950 the real cost of new vehicles has fallen by half, that of new clothing by 75% and that of household appliances by 90%, even as quality has got better. Tumbling prices reflect decades of improvements in technology and productivity. But the effect is not economy-wide. Cars are cheaper, but car maintenance is more expensive, and costs in education and health care have risen roughly fivefold since 1950. Though no mystery, this rise is often misunderstood, with serious economic consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are as many explanations for the ballooning cost of such services as there are politicians. But as a newly published analysis argues, many common scapegoats simply cannot explain the steady, long-run rise in such prices relative to those elsewhere in the economy. In “Why are the prices so damn high?” Eric Helland of Claremont McKenna College and Alex Tabarrok of George Mason University write that quality has improved far too little to account for it. Administrative bloat is not the answer either. In America the share of all education spending that goes on administration has been roughly steady for decades. Health-care spending has risen faster than &lt;small&gt;GDP &lt;/small&gt;in rich countries, despite vast differences in the structure of their health-care systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The real culprit, the authors write, is a steady increase in the cost of labour—of teachers and doctors. That in turn reflects the relentless logic of Baumol’s cost disease, named after the late William Baumol, who first described the phenomenon. Productivity grows at different rates in different sectors. It takes far fewer people to make a car than it used to—where thousands of workers once filled plants, highly paid engineers now oversee factories full of robots—but roughly the same number of teachers to instruct a schoolful of children. Economists reckon that workers’ wages should vary with their productivity. But real pay has grown in high- and low-productivity industries alike. That, Baumol pointed out, is because teachers and engineers compete in the same labour market. As salaries for automotive engineers rise, more students study engineering and fewer become teachers, unless teachers’ pay also goes up. The cost of education has thus risen because of the rising pay needed to fill teaching posts. Other factors matter too, and can explain, for instance, why Americans pay more than Europeans for health care and higher education. But across countries, none is as important as the toll exacted by cost disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baumol’s earliest work on the subject, written with William Bowen, was published in 1965. Analyses like that of Messrs Helland and Tabarrok nonetheless feel novel, because the implications of cost disease remain so underappreciated in policy circles. For instance, the steadily rising expense of education and health care is almost universally deplored as an economic scourge, despite being caused by something indubitably good: rapid, if unevenly spread, productivity growth. Higher prices, if driven by cost disease, need not mean reduced affordability, since they reflect greater productive capacity elsewhere in the economy. The authors use an analogy: as a person’s salary increases, the cost of doing things other than work—like gardening, for example—rises, since each hour off the job means more forgone income. But that does not mean that time spent gardening has become less affordable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither do high prices necessarily need fixing. Many proposed solutions would be good for growth but would not solve the cost-disease problem. Boosting the supply of labour by increasing immigration could depress costs in both high-productivity sectors and low-productivity ones. But the price of a college education in terms of sedans would remain eye-watering. Innovation in stagnant sectors, while welcome, would shift the problem of cost disease elsewhere. A burst of productivity growth in education—because of improved online instruction, say—should contribute to a decline in the price of education per student. But because a given instructor could serve many more students than before, teachers’ potential income would rise, luring some would-be doctors away from the study of medicine and exacerbating the problem of cost disease in health care. A productivity boom in health care might shunt the cost disease to dentistry, or child care, or veterinary medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only true solution to cost disease is an economy-wide productivity slowdown—and one may be in the offing. Technological progress pushes employment into the sectors most resistant to productivity growth. Eventually, nearly everyone may have jobs that are valued for their inefficiency: as concert musicians, or artisanal cheesemakers, or members of the household staff of the very rich. If there is no high-productivity sector to lure such workers away, then the problem does not arise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A cure worse than the disease&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;These possibilities reveal the real threat from Baumol’s disease: not that work will flow toward less-productive industries, which is inevitable, but that gains from rising productivity are unevenly shared. When firms in highly productive industries crave highly credentialed workers, it is the pay of similar workers elsewhere in the economy—of doctors, say—that rises in response. That worsens inequality, as low-income workers must still pay higher prices for essential services like health care. Even so, the productivity growth that drives cost disease could make everyone better off. But governments often do too little to tax the winners and compensate the losers. And politicians who do not understand the Baumol effect sometimes cap spending on education and health. Unsurprisingly, since they misunderstand the diagnosis, the treatment they prescribe makes the ailment worse. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 20:40:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[California and Texas have different visions for America’s future]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/special-report/2019/06/22/california-and-texas-have-different-visions-for-americas-future]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190622_SRP079_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-22T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;N TEXAS AN&lt;/small&gt; unexpected enemy gets a lot of attention. In a television ad for lieutenant-governor that aired last year, Dan Patrick, the winning Republican candidate, looked sternly at the camera and warned of a grave danger. “Truth is, Democrats want to turn Texas into California,” he said. “Well, I’m not about to let that happen. What about you?” United in concern is Greg Abbott, Texas’s Republican governor. He predicts that excessive regulation could turn “the Texas dream into a California nightmare”. “Don’t California my Texas” has become a rallying cry for Republicans in the Lone Star State. You can even buy the bumper-sticker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some competitive jousting between the two is inevitable. California, with 40m inhabitants, and Texas, with 29m, are the states with the largest populations, with more than one-fifth of Americans claiming them as home. They also have the biggest economies. If they were countries, they would be the fifth- and tenth-largest in the world (see chart), with around $3trn and $1.8trn in &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt;, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Texas is the country’s largest exporter, and California claims the number-two spot. In the past 20 years nearly a third of American jobs were generated in just these two states. Combined, they account for around a quarter of American &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt;. They educate nearly a quarter of American children, so their investments in, and approach to, public education directly affects national competitiveness. Both states are booming, too. Between 2010 and 2018 two of the three fastest-growing metro areas in America were in Texas: greater Dallas and Houston each gained more than 1m people. The state has a robust oil and gas industry and has succeeded in diversifying its economy. California enjoys the many fruits of the technology boom, a rising stockmarket and some of America’s best universities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;A nation divided&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the two states matter just as much because of the opposing visions and models of government for which they stand. Indeed their rivalry is often an expression of these differences. California is the standard-bearer for progressive experimentation nationally, spearheading policies to deal with climate change, gay rights, the decriminalisation of drugs, paid family leave, inclusive immigration and more. Since Donald Trump assumed office, California has become a state of resistance, suing the federal government around 50 times. It is the country’s largest blue state, where the share of registered Republicans is at a historic low and Democrats control all three branches of government. Its model can be summed up as high taxes, high services and high regulation. California sees a strong role for government and leans heavily on its affluent residents to fund a social-safety net.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190622_SRC107.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190622_SRC107.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190622_SRC107.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190622_SRC107.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190622_SRC107.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190622_SRC107.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190622_SRC107.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190622_SRC107.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190622_SRC107.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190622_SRC107.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Texas, by contrast, has been socially conservative for decades. Although Democrats made gains in the state legislature in 2018, no Democrat has been elected to statewide office for more than 25 years. Its model is low taxes, low services and low regulation. “Govern wisely and as little as possible,” is how Sam Houston, who served as the first president of the Republic of Texas in 1836, described the state’s light-touch philosophy. Serious about avoiding government overreach, the legislature meets only every other year. In 2017 Texas ranked 49th out of 50 in spending per person, shelling out around $3,925 per citizen, 52% less than the national average and 68% less than California.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demographically, both states are already living America’s future. Their non-white populations started to outnumber their white ones long ago; California became a “majority-minority” state in 2000, Texas in 2005. Today they are both around 40% Hispanic, more than double the national share. With fast-growing, young and ethnically diverse populations, what California and Texas look like today is what the country will look like in 2050. According to Stephen Klineberg, a professor at Rice University in Houston, “states like California and Texas are where the American future is going to be worked out.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both states have vulnerabilities. “The key question for California is how much a state can take on, and with Texas it is about how little a government can continue to take on,” says Ken Miller of Claremont McKenna College. Their differences can be seen in dramatic and subtle ways. To fund its operations, California levies one of the highest income taxes in America. By contrast, Texas’s constitution forbids a state income tax. Unions are a mighty force in Californian politics and workplaces, but Texas is what is known as a “right-to-work” state, meaning that employees do not need to belong to a union, so such infrastructure is weak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Big-state big state&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;California probably has the strongest environmental regulations in the country, whereas Texas nurtures its oil and gas industry and regards nature as something to be subdued. It puts minimal restrictions on keeping exotic animals as pets, which is why there are believed to be more tigers in captivity in Texas than in the wild in India.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their leaders embody the two states’ divergent philosophies. California’s governor, Gavin Newsom, who took office in January, is a former mayor of San Francisco, best known for legalising gay marriage in 2004 and sparking a national social movement. The governor of Texas, Greg Abbott, is a staunch social conservative who formerly served as the state’s attorney-general and is proud to have sued Barack Obama’s administration 31 times over policies including health care and environmental regulations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Earlier this year Mr Newsom ordered a moratorium on the death penalty, around the same time that politicians in the Texas legislature were debating whether to start providing air-conditioning in prisons during the sweltering summer—an expensive creature comfort, in the eyes of some. Since 1976 Texas has executed more prisoners than any other American state and around five times more than second-placed Virginia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190622_SRM971.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190622_SRM971.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190622_SRM971.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190622_SRM971.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190622_SRM971.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190622_SRM971.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190622_SRM971.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190622_SRM971.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190622_SRM971.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190622_SRM971.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their independent natures can be partly explained by history. Tellingly, Texans celebrate 1836 as their founding year, when the state became independent from Mexico after an armed insurrection, not 1845, when Texas officially became an American state. At the time slaveholding Texas received an ambivalent welcome into the nation, which was worried about the balance between states that permitted slavery and those that did not. California, which had also been a part of Mexico before it joined America in 1850, never allowed slavery, which meant it was more warmly welcomed. This experience shaped its political attitudes. Its distance from Washington, &lt;small&gt;DC&lt;/small&gt;, fuelled its ability to experiment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both states used to be supportive of the other political party. Republicans won California in nearly every presidential election between 1952 and 1988, and Ronald Reagan served as governor there before he became president. The state’s politics swerved in response to its growing population of immigrants, who were troubled by Republicans’ intolerant rhetoric and policies. Texas used to be strongly Democratic and produced Lyndon B. Johnson, who became president after John F. Kennedy was assassinated in Dallas. Mr Johnson’s legacy includes launching many of the programmes that Texan politicians today scorn, including the war on poverty and federally funded health care for the poor and elderly. His commitment to social services and civil rights helped hand his state and the south to Republicans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Americans and immigrants have for decades travelled to both states to build their future unencumbered by tradition. The “Texas Triangle”, formed by the four large cities of Austin, Dallas, Houston and San Antonio, accounts for three-quarters of the state’s population, has been responsible for three-quarters of its population growth since 2010, and produces 82% of its &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Small-state big state&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The threat of Texas becoming California, as the Lone Star State’s leadership fears, is exaggerated. However, it raises the question of which pole America will turn towards—the progressive left represented by California or the right represented by Texas. “The fact that America can contain two such assertive, contrary forces as Texas and California is a testament to our political dynamism, but more and more I feel that America is being compelled to make a choice between the models these states embody,” writes Lawrence Wright in his book “God Save Texas”. “Under the Trump administration, Texas is clearly the winning archetype.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That may not hold for ever. Texas is already changing. “Outsiders think Austin is a blue bubble and the rest of Texas is tumbleweeds,” says Ann Beeson of the Centre for Public Policy Priorities, a left-leaning think-tank. “People have a huge misunderstanding of how giant, progressive and diverse our cities are.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nor should California, which frequently creates political winds that then sweep across the country, be discounted. It experienced an anti-tax backlash in the 1970s and an anti-immigrant push in the 1990s, both of which spread nationally. It legalised abortion six years before &lt;em&gt;Roe v Wade&lt;/em&gt;, the historic Supreme Court decision, in a bill signed by Reagan, then governor. “So much of what we aspire to as a country resides in California,” says Austin Beutner, a former businessman who is superintendent of Los Angeles Unified School District. “Laws go east to west. Values go west to east.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much of America’s future rides on California’s and Texas’s success. This special report will look in detail at how the states are approaching business, taxation, public education, social welfare, the environment, and policies toward immigrants. It will ask which state’s model is likely to prove more fruitful in the long term. “There are 50 labs in the United States, and you can watch the California and Texas experiment,” says Ross Perot junior, a successful Texan businessman. “That’s the American way.” &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Special report&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;A tale of two states&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 19:40:17 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>