<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[How has the LGBT movement changed in the past 50 years?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/14/how-has-the-lgbt-movement-changed-in-the-past-50-years]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_opp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-14T16:21:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ARMISTEAD MAUPIN was one of the first writers to bring gay and transsexual characters to a mainstream audience. “Tales of the city” began as a series of stories published in a San Francisco newspaper in the 1970s. In this episode of “The Economist asks” podcast, Anne McElvoy asks him about what drew him back to the setting of 28 Barbary Lane to tell a new batch of tales of queer America. Fifty years on from the Stonewall riots that sparked the LGBT civil-rights movement, Mr Maupin talks about how far there is still to go, what young gay men can never understand about his generation, and why he has finally decided to abandon his beloved San Francisco. Runtime 23 min. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-armisteadmaupin&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 23:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The race to become Britain’s next PM]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/14/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-14T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HERESA MAY&lt;/small&gt; stepped down as leader of the Conservative Party on June 7th, but she will remain as prime minister until her successor is chosen. The first round of voting took place on June 13th; Boris Johnson topped the ballot of Tory MPs, with Jeremy Hunt a distant second and Michael Gove third. Three candidates, Andrea Leadsom, Mark Harper and Esther McVey, failed to get enough votes to go through to the next round and Matt Hancock pulled out on June 14th. The remaining six candidates will go through to the second round of voting, which is scheduled for June 18th. After further votes MPs will then send two names to party members, who will make the final choice. The result of their vote will be announced before Parliament rises for summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Betfair Exchange, a gambling website, has been tracking punters’ predictions on the next Tory leader. According to the wisdom of the betting crowd, a handful of candidates stand out. But there is only one clear frontrunner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anne McElvoy, host of &lt;i&gt;The Economist asks&lt;/i&gt;, spoke to Jeremy Hunt and Rory Stewart about their leadership plans: &lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-whocanleadbritainthroughbrexit-&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.betfair.com/exchange/plus/politics&quot;&gt;Betfair Exchange&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 23:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Do you hear the people sing? Not in China]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/14/do-you-hear-the-people-sing-not-in-china]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_BKP509.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-14T12:41:46Z&quot;&gt;Jun 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BEFORE THE tear gas and the rubber bullets, there was music. At the protests in Hong Kong over the past week, people have regularly broken into song. For those gathered outside government headquarters, “Sing Hallelujah to the Lord”, a popular Christian hymn, has been a favourite. “Do You Hear The People Sing?”, a tune from “Les Misérables” and the unofficial anthem of protests in Hong Kong in 2014, has also made a reappearance. The songs are powerful, as protest music has been for centuries, channelling voices together into something moving, even beautiful. On occasion, priests have led the crowds, giving them the appearance more of a giant church choir than an angry rabble.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the surest sign of the music’s power has not been the singing in Hong Kong but its absence in mainland China. “Do You Hear The People Sing?” has been censored on QQ Music, one of the country’s most popular music streaming services. Search for the song, and three results pop up, all saying that it cannot be played for copyright reasons. Search for the full “Les Misérables” album, and there are more than ten versions of it, minus that one song. On NetEase Music, another popular streaming service, censors appear to have been a little less zealous. Individual searches for “Do You Hear The People Sing?” yield no hits, but it still appears as a track on its various “Les Misérables” albums.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The protesters in Hong Kong in 2014 were not the first to call on the song. It has featured in a series of demonstrations, including the Maidan revolution in Ukraine, which kicked off in late 2013, and union marches in Wisconsin in 2011. The appeal is obvious, given its rousing tune and lyrics: “Do you hear the people sing?/Singing the songs of angry men?/It is the music of the people/Who will not be slaves again!” That said, aficionados of “Les Misérables”, a musical based on the novel by Victor Hugo, know that the story is rather less cheering: the students who lead an anti-monarchist rebellion (a depiction of the Paris Uprising in 1832) almost all end up dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Exactly when censors started scrubbing out the song in China is unclear. Before the Hong Kong protests, they had little reason to worry about it. A musical film of “Les Misérables” was a hit in the West in 2012 but a flop in China. The main controversy about the song back then was whether the official translation was good enough. As recently as last year, authorities permitted a performance of “Les Misérables” in Shanghai. That may well have been the event that caught the censors’ attention: at the end of the show, audience members rose to their feet and belted out “Do You Hear The People Sing?” in unison. Perhaps they were just fans of the musical, but the song evidently had the ability to stir emotions in China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Censorship is rarely water-tight, and that is certainly the case for music. The Chinese government has taken a hard line against Hong Kong singers such as Denise Ho who supported the pro-democracy movement in 2014: their music is no longer available on streaming services and their concerts in the mainland have been cancelled. But on smaller streaming services such as Xiami, which is estimated to have a roughly 2% market share in China, “Do You Hear The People Sing?” is still available. What’s more, censors do not appear to have cottoned onto the fact that “Sing Hallelujah to the Lord” was the protest song of choice on the streets of Hong Kong during the past week. QQ Music offers 11 different versions of it. Chinese fans of contemporary Christian pop should listen while they can.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 21:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“A miscalculation could result in a serious military response”—the Gulf of Oman attack]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/14/a-miscalculation-could-result-in-a-serious-military-response-the-gulf-of-oman-attack]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_blm509.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-14T11:43:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMERICA HAS blamed Iran for yesterday’s tanker attacks in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/13/who-is-blowing-up-ships-in-the-gulf&quot;&gt;Gulf of Oman&lt;/a&gt;. If that’s true, Iran is playing a dangerous game that involves the whole of the region. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/05/30/mafias-run-by-rogue-police-officers-are-terrorising-rio&quot;&gt;violent militias&lt;/a&gt; that control much of Rio de Janeiro might be easy to beat if they weren’t so &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/30/jair-bolsonaro-will-not-defeat-crime-in-brazil-by-tolerating-militias&quot;&gt;well-connected&lt;/a&gt;. And, a breakaway hit reveals the racial fault lines in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/30/the-sociology-of-country-music-lyrics&quot;&gt;country music&lt;/a&gt;. Runtime: 21min.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/43503f5d-084e-4060-81f9-e34bbc3e916a&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 21:39:55 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Who is blowing up ships in the Gulf?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/13/who-is-blowing-up-ships-in-the-gulf]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_blp504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-13T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SHINZO ABE hoped this was a moment for diplomacy. His visit to Tehran this week, the first by a Japanese prime minister since the Islamic revolution in 1979, was meant to reduce tensions between America and Iran. After a meeting with Iran’s president, Hassan Rouhani, Mr Abe warned that the region could “accidentally” slip into conflict. And then, a few miles off Iran’s southern coast, came an illustration of how that might happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On June 13th two tankers in the Gulf of Oman sent distress calls after they had been damaged by large explosions. The Front Altair, flagged in the Marshall Islands and owned by Frontline, a Norwegian shipping company, was hauling a cargo of naphtha, an oil derivative, from Abu Dhabi; the Kokuka Courageous, registered in Panama and operated by the Japanese company Kokuka Sangyo, was laden with methanol. Both were bound for Asian ports. Photos from Iranian news agencies showed a fire burning on the starboard side of the Front Altair. The plume of black smoke overhead was thick enough to appear in satellite images. One-fifth of the world’s supply travels through the Strait of Hormuz, an important chokepoint for international shipping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the second time in just over a month that tankers have been damaged in the Gulf. On May 12th four ships anchored off Fujairah, a port in the United Arab Emirates (UAE), had holes blown in their hulls. A preliminary investigation suggests that they were damaged by limpet mines. The latest explosions caused far more damage, forcing crews to evacuate both ships as they were underway. It will take weeks to probe what happened, amid reports of torpedoes being used. But the explosions do not seem accidental. The president of Kokuka Sangyo said the Kokuka Courageous vessel was “attacked” twice in a three-hour period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nor is it likely that two sets of explosions, weeks apart and in the same area, were mere coincidence. Though a UAE-led investigative team did not assign blame for last month’s sabotage, it said an unnamed “state actor” carried it out. America has blamed Iran for both sets of attacks. Iran, which is a regional rival of the UAE and Saudi Arabia, both American allies, has denied responsibility and hints that the latest explosions were orchestrated by its rivals. “Suspicious doesn’t begin to describe what likely transpired,” tweeted Iran’s foreign minister, Muhammad Javad Zarif, on June 13th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iran has in the past threatened to close the Strait of Hormuz if it were ever attacked. Some will see the strikes against ships in the area as a veiled warning of its readiness to make good on its threat. Messrs Zarif and Rouhani probably understand that attacking regional shipping would be to play with fire. But they do not call all of the shots in Iran. They are stuck in an internal battle with Iran’s ruling mullahs, who are more distrustful of the West, and their Revolutionary Guards, who back local forces in Syria and Yemen that have fought against Emirati- and Saudi-backed forces. Iran has a history of irregular warfare that allows it to maintain a measure of plausible deniability. In the 1980s it fought the so-called tanker war with Iraq. The conflict ravaged international shipping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tensions in the region have been rising since last spring, when Donald Trump withdrew from the deal, signed in 2015, that loosened sanctions on Iran in exchange for limits on its nuclear programme. Mr Trump reimposed sanctions and added new ones, in effect cutting Iran off from the global economy. After a year of abiding by the agreement, a bid to win European sympathy, Iran last month said it would begin enriching uranium in excess of the prescribed limits. Mr Rouhani warned that he would abrogate other provisions unless other signatories—Britain, France, Germany, Russia, China and the European Union—helped his country bypass American sanctions, which is unlikely to happen. Critics of Mr Trump’s approach have long warned that economic distress would lead Iran to lash out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the Arab states across the Gulf, these latest explosions fit into a troubling pattern. In May, two days after the Fujairah incident, two blasts in the centre of Saudi Arabia, 700km north of the Yemeni border, damaged an oil pipeline that carries crude across the kingdom. On June 12th a rocket hit the international airport in Abha, a Saudi city 200km from the Yemeni border, injuring 26 people. Both attacks were carried out by the Houthis, a Shia militia that controls large parts of Yemen and is fighting a Saudi-led coalition there. A United Nations panel of experts has said that Iran supplied weapons to the Houthis, including drones and missiles, though the group does not always act at Iran&amp;#x27;s behest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Saudi Arabia and its allies have tried not to escalate directly a conflict that would wreak havoc on their oil exports, and thus their economies. The UAE has been particularly circumspect in its public statements about last month’s sabotage (though in private officials evince little doubt about Iran’s involvement). If there is to be a response, they would like it to come from America. Mr Trump’s hawkish national security adviser, John Bolton, has long supported regime change in Iran, and even military action against it. But the president, as ever, is erratic, toggling between fiery threats and offers of dialogue. He is reported to have given Mr Abe a message to pass to Iran’s supreme leader, Ali Khamenei (who declined to reply). “We do not believe at all that the US is seeking genuine negotiations with Iran; because genuine negotiations would never come from a person like Trump,” said Ayatollah Khamenei.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump has already bolstered America’s military presence in the region. Last month he rushed an aircraft-carrier strike group to the region. Those vessels have not transited the Strait of Hormuz, an effort to avoid further tension. They will probably step up their patrols; an American destroyer picked up some sailors from the stricken tankers (Iran says it rescued some too). The Pentagon is deploying an extra 1,500 troops to bases in Qatar, Bahrain and Iraq, and Mr Trump is invoking emergency powers to override congressional objections and sell weapons to Saudi Arabia and the UAE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All sides insist they do not want war. But even if they are sincere, good intentions go only so far. The Gulf states (and their American protector) cannot tolerate threats to shipping. Mr Abe was right to push for diplomacy between America and Iran. But his visit, and the events that overshadowed it, underscore how difficult that will be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 03:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why are the Chicago White Sox commemorating Disco Demolition Night?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/13/why-are-the-chicago-white-sox-commemorating-disco-demolition-night]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_BKP508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-13T16:26:02Z&quot;&gt;Jun 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON THURSDAY nights the Chicago White Sox give something back to baseball fans, usually T-shirts for the first 10,000 people through the gates of Guaranteed Rate Field. On July 4th the garment is a handsome navy-blue number to mark Independence Day; on July 25th they remember the legendary Sox team of 1983 with a “Miracle on 35th Street” tee. And today, June 13th, when they play the New York Yankees, they are planning to commemorate one of the strangest—and, for many people, most disgraceful—episodes in their history with a T-shirt bearing the legend: “Disco Demolition – the night records were broken.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disco Demolition Night took place on July 12th 1979 at the Sox’s old stadium, Comiskey Park. Trying to boost attendance in a season of poor crowds, the Sox invited a local DJ named Steve Dahl to provide some entertainment between the first and second games of a double-header against the Detroit Tigers. Mr Dahl, a rock DJ, had lost his slot at a radio station when it switched formats to disco, and when he got a new job he made much of his unequivocal hatred of the music. This hatred was to be the entertainment for fans. Mr Dahl invited his listeners to bring disco records to the ballpark where he would blow them up, to “end disco once and for all”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Sox had hoped for a crowd of 20,000; they got 50,000, with a further 20,000 locked out. During the first game, vinyl records began showering down on the outfield from the seats. The explosion during the break prompted a pitch invasion of several thousand people. Writing in 2014 Mr Dahl recalled it as “a joyous heat- and beer-infused celebration”, though footage shows fans tearing down the bullpen, building bonfires in the outfield and burning banners in the stands. It was described as “a riot” on local news, and it took mounted police in riot gear to clear the field. The second game was abandoned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What made Disco Demolition Night infamous was that it seemed to symbolise the rage of white, male heterosexuality against black, Latino and gay culture. Comiskey Park was situated in the white working-class neighbourhood of Bridgeport, and there had been a history of racist incidents in the area. One African-American member of the stadium staff said that fans didn’t just bring disco records, they brought records by any black artist that came to hand. In &lt;em&gt;Rolling Stone&lt;/em&gt; Dave Marsh described it as “your most paranoid fantasy about where the ethnic cleansing of the rock radio could ultimately lead”, while Nile Rodgers of Chic, a disco and funk band, compared it to Nazi book-burning. Mr Dahl continues to insist that it was just a bit of fun—simply “one of the greatest radio promotions in history”, plus an expression of rebellion against a “trendy social elite”, a choice of words that echoes today. He has maintained that he has never been remotely racist or homophobic (he did not respond to a request for comment for this article). Yet the event has come to be seen as an appalling outbreak of prejudice. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So there has been a furious reaction to the Sox’s decision to mark the event, with Mr Dahl throwing the opening pitch. “I almost couldn’t believe it, I thought it was a joke,” Marea Stamper, an activist and American DJ who works under the moniker of The Black Madonna, says. She has no truck with Mr Dahl’s defence that he was simply aggrieved about losing his job to DJs playing disco, nor that it was a celebration. “I come from the South, and this was like people burning ‘race’ records—that was white families burning the black music their kids were listening to, and a way of enforcing racial borders and social barriers, with records as an effigy.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For all the decades of writing about Disco Demolition Night, and the analyses of it as a mass act of bigotry, the Sox seemed to have been caught by surprise by the furious reaction to their plans. In response to a request for comment they sent this statement: “This year’s Disco Demolition T-Shirt giveaway was intended to recognise the anniversary of a historic off-the-field moment...We have been communicating with our community partners who have raised concerns to make it clear that the intent of this giveaway was only meant to mark the historical nature of the night 40 years later. We have reinforced that the White Sox organisation is dedicated to advocating for a safe, welcoming ballpark experience for all people and communities...We remain proud of our franchise’s longstanding record on advocating for inclusion and diversity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Stamper laughs in contempt at that. “It’s not as if they were offering context—it’s not as if there’s a display at the ballpark saying what this riot was about, or even what some people say it was about. If it’s historical, where’s the history?” She thinks it is an ill-thought-out promotional event. “Take any other book burning or destruction of art, and imagine slapping a picture of it on a shirt and giving it away!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 01:40:25 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hong Kong rattled by protests, the changing nature of war, and Australia’s nanny state]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/13/hong-kong-rattled-by-protests-the-changing-nature-of-war-and-australias-nanny-state]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-13T16:00:14Z&quot;&gt;Jun 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A SELECTION of three essential articles read aloud from the latest issue of The Economist. This week, huge demonstrations in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/13/the-rule-of-law-in-hong-kong&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hong Kong&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; have rattled the territory’s government (08:50). America’s biggest defence merger highlights the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/15/the-utc-raytheon-deal-highlights-the-changing-nature-of-war&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;changing nature of war&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (17:11). And, why Australia’s pioneering image cloaks a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/15/australias-surprising-disregard-for-free-speech&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;nanny state&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Runtime: 23 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-june13th2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 00:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The race to become Britain’s next PM]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/13/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-13T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HERESA MAY&lt;/small&gt; stepped down as leader of the Conservative Party on June 7th. She will remain as prime minister until her successor is chosen. Nominations for the Tory leadership closed on June 10th, to be followed by several rounds of voting among MPs to whittle down the ten candidates, a process that will take a week or two. The MPs will then send two names to party members who will make the final choice. The result of their vote will be announced before Parliament rises for summer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Betfair Exchange, a gambling website, has been tracking punters’ predictions on the next Tory leader. According to the wisdom of the betting crowd, a handful of candidates stand out. But there is only one clear frontrunner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Friday&amp;#x27;s edition of &lt;i&gt;The Economist asks&lt;/i&gt;, Anne McElvoy spoke to Jeremy Hunt and Rory Stewart about their leadership plans: &lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-whocanleadbritainthroughbrexit-&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adrian Wooldridge, our political editor, assesses the chances of some of the leading Conservative politicians hoping to take the top job in this short film: &lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ychDrZ2QzlE&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.betfair.com/exchange/plus/politics&quot;&gt;Betfair Exchange&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 21:40:31 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cricket’s increasing sizzle owes much to India]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/15/crickets-increasing-sizzle-owes-much-to-india]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190615_GDC500cricket1/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;C&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;RICKET MATCHES&lt;/small&gt; between India and Pakistan are always heated. Their World Cup fixture on June 16th will be particularly fierce: in February an attack by militants on Indian police in Kashmir led to tit-for-tat airstrikes. Even neutral spectators, however, eagerly await pyrotechnics on the pitch. Scoring rates in cricket have been rising for decades, but in recent years they have exploded in the sport’s newer, shorter formats. The game’s evolution into a faster-paced, more exciting spectacle has been most notable in India. The Indian Premier League (&lt;small&gt;IPL&lt;/small&gt;), founded in 2008, has become cricket’s most lucrative product by copying the franchise system of American sports and importing star foreign players in a huge country with growing &lt;small&gt;TV&lt;/small&gt; viewership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;small&gt;IPL&lt;/small&gt;’s other innovation was to adopt the T20 format, devised in England in 2003. Unlike Test matches—in which each team bats for two innings, taking up to five days—T20 gives each side one innings of 120 balls, limiting games to four hours. The rules are the same. Batsmen score as many runs as possible during an innings. Whacking the ball over the boundary rope yields four runs if it bounces on the field, and six if it does not. The fielders try to get the batsmen out by hitting the wooden wicket or catching an errant shot (among other methods of dismissal). Each side bats until either ten players are out or the fixed number of balls, or days, is used up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Test cricket batsmen often block the ball defensively, to preserve their wickets. But because it is rare for ten men to get out in just 120 balls, players in T20 try riskier shots in pursuit of faster rewards. The result makes baseball look sedate. Whereas an average night at Yankee Stadium produces two home runs, an average T20 match features 39 boundary shots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These aggressive tactics have also been adopted in one-day internationals (&lt;small&gt;ODI&lt;/small&gt;s), the format used in the World Cup, which gives each side one innings of 300 balls. Boundary rates in &lt;small&gt;ODI&lt;/small&gt;s have soared since 2003. In contrast, the long increase of run-scoring in Tests stopped just when T20 was invented. It may not be possible to hit much more than 6.4% of balls to the boundary, as batting teams did in 2000-03, while occupying the crease for five days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190615_GDC600cricket2/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Purists insist that slow-building Tests are more gripping than a flurry of sixes. But a survey of fans in 2018 found that only 69% are interested in Tests, rising to 92% for T20. Media Partners Asia, a consultancy, expects broadcasters to pay $1.4bn a year for T20 over the next four years, compared with $190m for Tests. England and Australia hope to emulate the &lt;small&gt;IPL&lt;/small&gt;’s success, using a similar template. Once a sporting imitator, India is now setting the trend. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Graphic detail&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Beyond a boundary&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 20:40:22 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pebble Beach should give shorter hitters a chance at the U.S. Open]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/06/13/pebble-beach-should-give-shorter-hitters-a-chance-at-the-us-open]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_BLP502_facebook.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-13T11:47:36Z&quot;&gt;Jun 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NOWHERE BEATS Augusta National for tradition, but by common consent America’s most beautiful golf course is Pebble Beach Golf Links. Hugging the Pacific Ocean cliffs just south of Monterey, California, the stunning property is regularly voted country’s best public course. It has also been the site of many of the sport’s most memorable moments, including Tom Watson’s famous &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DO6qIg7aInw&quot;&gt;chip from thick rough&lt;/a&gt; to beat Jack Nicklaus in the 1982 U.S. Open.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nine years after the U.S. Open was last held at Pebble, the tournament returns to its most picturesque venue on June 13th. Two players in particular will be chasing history. After &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/04/14/tiger-woods-wins-his-fifth-masters-in-a-comeback-for-the-ages&quot; data-tegid=&quot;eu045r07t49jb6jg1o3h9jr7ocrbkk3l&quot;&gt;winning the Masters&lt;/a&gt; at Augusta in April, the 43-year-old Tiger Woods is on the hunt for a 16th major trophy, which would leave him just two behind Mr Nicklaus for the all-time record. And Brooks Koepka, fresh off a victory at the PGA Championship last month, is campaigning to become the first player to win the same major in three consecutive years since &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peter_Thomson_(golfer)&quot;&gt;Peter Thomson&lt;/a&gt; managed the feat in 1954-56.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The swirling ocean winds at Pebble Beach can be nearly as frustrating for statistical modellers as they are for players. By the standards of modern major tournaments, it is a relatively short course, at just 7,075 yards for a par-71. (In contrast, last year’s U.S. Open, at Shinnecock Hills on Long Island, measured 7,445 yards and was only a par 70.) In theory, such accessible distances should yield a flock of birdies and perhaps even an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.dictionary.com/browse/aerie&quot;&gt;aerie&lt;/a&gt; of eagles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what Pebble lacks in length, it makes up for with nature and design. The omnipresent water hazard crashing alongside most of the course not only swallows up double and triple bogeys, but also forces cautious players into taking indirect lines and awkward lies. And the course’s sharp doglegs, towering trees and narrow fairways limit the use of drivers to a handful of holes. With a humped green that can send even well-placed approach shots scurrying away from the flag, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.sfgate.com/sports/kroichick/article/Pebble-Beach-s-14th-hole-is-pure-evil-3184718.php&quot;&gt;Pebble’s 14th &lt;/a&gt; is the hardest hole, relative to a typical hole of its distance and par value, measured at any major this millennium. According to EAGLE, &lt;i&gt;The Economist&lt;/i&gt;’s statistical golf-forecasting system, par-fives around 580 yards long typically took around 4.82 strokes to complete in majors in 2010, the last time the U.S. Open was held there. The unfortunate souls who had to navigate Pebble Beach’s 580-yard par-five that year averaged 5.44. (You can follow EAGLE’s predictions for the U.S. Open as they update in real time at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://eagle.economist.com&quot;&gt;eagle.economist.com&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because course organisers frequently modify holes from year to year—and adjust green conditions and hole locations once tournaments are underway—EAGLE places little weight on course-wide scoring data from the distant past. (In contrast, the relative difficulty of each hole to the course average tends to be stable over time.) As a result, the model currently expects scoring at Pebble to roughly match the level of a typical course of its length, after accounting for unusually tough holes like the 14th. That would come to an average of 72.35, 1.35 strokes above par, during the first two rounds. The best players, such as Dustin Johnson and Mr Koepka, should fare about three strokes better than that. However, the last time the U.S. Open was held at Pebble Beach, &lt;i&gt;nobody&lt;/i&gt; finished below par: Graeme McDowell lifted the trophy at one-over. Should similar carnage be expected on the course this time around?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is good reason to believe this year’s Open field may get the best of Pebble. Overall, by EAGLE’s reckoning, the average golfer in a major today is about a full stroke per round better than they were a decade ago. Since the configuration of Pebble Beach has barely changed since the 2010 Open, that suggests finishing scores for players making the cut should wind up about four strokes lower. Further evidence that Pebble can be beaten can be found in the scores from the AT&amp;amp;T Pebble Beach Pro-Am tournament, held at the course this February. Based on the skill of the players who participated in that event and the course layout—about 200 yards shorter than the U.S. Open design—EAGLE would have expected the average round score in the Pro-Am to be 72.41. The actual average was 71.57, suggesting that the course played slightly &lt;i&gt;easier&lt;/i&gt; than expected. Nonetheless, EAGLE is designed to adjust its forecasts rapidly when new data contradict its expectations. If bogeys abound and the birdies are in hiding on Thursday morning, the model’s predictions for all players’ scores will turn bearish in a hurry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pebble’s modest yardages should also open the field to a wider range of plausible contenders than longer courses do. Whereas the leaderboards on 7,500-yard courses often resemble lists of the biggest drivers, Pebble Beach rewards judgment and precision. That might enable a shorter hitter like Matt Kuchar to end his long-running major curse, or Henrik Stenson, Webb Simpson or Jim Furyk to double their hauls of major trophies. At the other extreme, players whose games depend on power, such as Bubba Watson, Gary Woodland or Tony Finau, could prove ill-suited to Pebble’s demands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nonetheless, EAGLE’s favourites for the U.S. Open are mostly familiar faces, many of whom wield potent drivers. In the model’s estimation Mr Johnson remains the world’s best player, as he has been for nearly two years, and is the front-runner, with an 8% chance of victory. Thanks to a new adjustment that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/05/20/brooks-koepka-saves-his-best-work-for-a-major-yet-again&quot; data-tegid=&quot;5t5k43g2oj11kgul4npe1lguuc8rd4eh&quot;&gt;grants credit to players who have performed better in majors than in other tournaments&lt;/a&gt;, Mr Koepka—or #MajorKoepka, as we have dubbed him on Twitter—now ranks second, at just under 7%. Fresh off a victory at the RBC Canadian Open, Rory McIlroy is the third-most-likely champion, with a 5-6% chance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just two months ago, we were &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/04/09/why-dustin-johnson-is-our-favourite-to-win-the-masters&quot; data-tegid=&quot;oqou31kstlhicqufhhnpongak12it4gr&quot;&gt;touting&lt;/a&gt; Patrick Cantlay, whom betting markets priced as a 100-to-one longshot to win the Masters, as a promising “sleeper pick”. But after finishing ninth at Augusta, third in his next two tournaments (including the PGA Championship), and winning the Memorial Tournament two weeks ago, the public has caught on to Mr Cantlay. He is EAGLE’s fifth-most-likely player to win, with a 4% shot—but now ranks even higher in betting markets, which put him fourth at a 5% probability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In what is likely to be a recurring pattern, the player EAGLE is most bullish on relative to punters is Jason Day. Starting with this year’s U.S. Open, we have modified EAGLE to consider not just players’ final scores on each hole, but also more granular measures of their skill. Although Mr Day is currently ranked just 16th in the world, and has not won a tournament in over a year, his underlying performance measures are outstanding. Among the 156 players who will tee off at Pebble, he ranks second in putting, 11th in driving distance and 17th in scrambling by EAGLE’s reckoning. The only other players in the top 20 in three categories are Mr Johnson, Mr Cantlay and Mr Kuchar. It was just 26 months ago that Mr Day, still just 31 years old, was ranked first in the world. And he has proven he can put it all together on the biggest of stages: in 2015 he shot 20 under par to win the PGA Championship, one of the best marks in modern memory. The only real weaknesses in Mr Day’s game are occasionally spotty iron play and a propensity for errant tee shots. As long as he can find himself on or around the green in regulation, this year’s Open could well prove his—ahem—Day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 20:40:21 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>