<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Curing the big sea]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/27/curing-the-big-sea]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_blm512.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-27T17:30:13Z&quot;&gt;Jun 27th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;RESEARCHERS HOPE to use disease-fighting genes found in whales to help find treatments for cancer in humans. Airliners that mix batteries and fossil fuel could dominate the skies in the future. And, are people more &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/06/22/people-are-more-honest-than-they-think-they-are&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;honest&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; than they think they are? Kenneth Cukier hosts. Runtime: 19 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistbabbage/9278e29d-99eb-40b6-b28b-f10c154435e7&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 01:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Global house-price index]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/27/global-house-price-index]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20180811_WBP202.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-27T17:40:05Z&quot;&gt;Jun 27th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;F&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;INANCIAL&lt;/small&gt; media focus most of their attention on stocks and bonds, but the world’s biggest asset class is actually residential property. With an estimated value of about $200trn, homes are collectively worth about three times as much as all publicly traded shares.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The charts above track housing-market indicators across 28 countries, in some instances going as far back as 1970. The first two metrics are price indices, one expressed in nominal terms and another adjusted for inflation. The second two measure valuation: one compares house prices with their long-run relationship with individual incomes, and the other with the historical ratio of home values to rents. If house prices climb faster than either earnings or rent payments for a long period of time, a housing bubble may be forming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;On this basis, house prices appear to be on an unsustainable path in Australia, Canada and New Zealand. Ten years ago they reached similarly dizzying heights against rents and incomes in Spain, Ireland and some American cities, only to endure a brutal collapse. Check back in three months’ time for our latest update.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 23:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Our global house-price forecasts]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/27/our-global-house-price-forecasts]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-27T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 27th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;EN YEARS&lt;/small&gt; ago a housing bust caused the deepest recession in generations. Since then, ultra-low interest rates and an increasing abundance of credit have pushed house prices back towards or beyond their pre-crisis peaks. As a result, in some markets policymakers are beginning to worry that boom could once again turn to bust. The long housing rally in Australia is coming to an abrupt end: prices there fell 8% in the year to the end of March. Appreciation has also slowed markedly in Britain, Canada and New Zealand during the past year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Could another crash lurk on the horizon? To estimate this risk, The Economist has created a statistical prediction model for house prices. It uses data on macroeconomic conditions, market fundamentals and historical home values to peer 18 months into the future. As an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/29/for-now-residential-property-prices-are-likely-to-keep-rising&quot; data-tegid=&quot;1rllrnkjn37phsjkgnlph7s5hg4jm56m&quot;&gt;article in our print edition&lt;/a&gt; this week shows, the model performs well when back-tested against the past. Although it would not have anticipated the magnitude of the extreme boom and bust of the mid-2000s, it would have foreseen a sharp reversal in the trend. For example, ahead of the financial crisis, when prices were growing at 8% a year in America, our model would have expected house-price growth to slow to just 0.3% a year 18 months later. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking ahead, the model is currently rather sanguine about the likely paths for home values across ten rich world countries, thanks to the persistence of low interest rates and ample credit. The average of its median forecasts for price growth in the year to the end of June 2020 is 2.3%. The model expects prices in Australia to level off rather than continuing to decline. Only in Italy are values more likely to fall than to rise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Sources: OECD; BIS; IMF; national statistics; &lt;i&gt;The Economist&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-js=&quot;/2019/house-price-forecast/js/bundle.js&quot; data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/house-price-forecast/css/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/house-price-forecast/css/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 23:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[For now, residential-property prices are likely to keep rising]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/29/for-now-residential-property-prices-are-likely-to-keep-rising]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Graphic detail&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;As safe as houses&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 21:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[London’s reign as the world’s capital of capital is at risk]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/29/londons-reign-as-the-worlds-capital-of-capital-is-at-risk]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190629_FNP001_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;A&lt;/span&gt; &lt;small&gt; WELL-KNOWN&lt;/small&gt; stockmarket sell signal is a company splurging on flashy new headquarters. It might then be time to go short the City of London. From the Shard, the tallest building in the European Union, the view is of a crowded skyline of fellow concept skyscrapers. There is the Gherkin, the Cheesegrater, the Walkie Talkie and, rising in their midst, 22 Bishopsgate, which will be the Square Mile’s tallest and most capacious tower. The building frenzy is even accelerating. Londoners are waiting to hear if the 1,000-foot Tulip—with a design that many contend is more phallic than floral—will be approved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of this suggests a financial centre bracing for Britain’s departure from the European Union. But as soon as Theresa May, the prime minister, made leaving the single market a “red line” after the Brexit referendum in 2016, it seemed likely that the City would be sundered from its biggest foreign market. Regulators on both sides of the Channel scrambled to ensure business continuity and financial stability. British firms were asked to draw up contingency plans, including opening hubs in the &lt;small&gt;EU27&lt;/small&gt; (the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; minus Britain). For much of the City, Brexit happened sometime last year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to New Financial, a think-tank in London, 291 big financial firms have moved some activities or people to the &lt;small&gt;EU27&lt;/small&gt;, or opened legal entities there. Many contingency plans were triggered before March 29th, when Brexit was supposed to have happened. About £1trn ($1.27trn) of the City’s assets has gone, says &lt;small&gt;EY&lt;/small&gt;, a consultancy. That compares with perhaps £16trn of bank assets and securities. To London’s &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; rivals, Brexit looks like a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity to grab business. A repatriated French banker says so many people have moved to central Paris that she often bumps into London friends. In the run-up to the extended deadline of October 31st, another wave of staff and their families will head off to new digs, offices and schools.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some financial infrastructure is moving, as are whole classes of &lt;small&gt;EU27&lt;/small&gt; business. The London Stock Exchange has moved trading in European government bonds worth £2.4bn daily to Milan, for example. Amsterdam has gained more government-bond trading as well as trading in euro-denominated repurchase agreements.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The moves do not seem hasty. Though Brexit’s final form is unclear, only the softest of departures would keep Britain in the single market. And nothing short of that would safeguard “passporting” rights for City firms. These allow financial firms in any &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; country to sell in any other and matter hugely in banking and asset management (and a bit less in insurance). In 2016, 5,476 firms based in Britain used 336,421 passports to sell in the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;. Around 8,000 firms in the European Economic Area, where much of the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;’s writ runs, used 23,535 of them to offer services in Britain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Including asset managers, insurers and so on as well as banks, Britain provides a quarter of all financial services in the &lt;small&gt;EU27&lt;/small&gt;. Scores of financial firms run their Europe, Middle East and Africa operations from London. American investment banks have as much as 90% of their European staff in London. In 2016, before the referendum, the City of London’s trajectory was better than that of New York as gravity shifted eastward to Asia, says William Wright of New Financial. “London is London as we know it, the world’s number-one or number-two financial centre, because the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; allowed it to become the financial centre of the euro zone,” says an &lt;small&gt;EU27&lt;/small&gt; official. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that status is at risk. “Before the [Brexit] debate began in 2015 it never crossed anyone’s mind that we would have to move financial services for Europe out of London,” says Bernard Mensah, president of Europe and the Middle East at Bank of America Merrill Lynch. “It was as if the British court system suddenly stopped working.” For the hundreds of small companies doing business with the &lt;small&gt;EU27&lt;/small&gt;, the removal of passporting and uncertainty over what will replace it is an existential threat, says John Liver, global head of regulation at &lt;small&gt;EY&lt;/small&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Financial services account for 6.5% of Britain’s economic output and 11% of its tax revenue. The sector and its ecosystem of lawyers, consultants, lobbyists and the like employ 2.2m people, not only in the wealthy centres of the Square Mile, Canary Wharf and Edinburgh but also in places like Cardiff and Bournemouth. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet Britain’s negotiators have treated the industry as a sideshow. The government took the view that the City is strong enough to cope, and made little effort to keep passporting, which would have meant blurring Mrs May’s red lines. Nor did it press hard for “mutual recognition”, in which the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; would accept Britain’s rules as a basis for future trading as long as they did not diverge too much. The City is likely instead to be left with “equivalence”, a piecemeal status that the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; sometimes grants to third countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About half of the City’s business is domestic, a quarter from the &lt;small&gt;EU27&lt;/small&gt; and a quarter with the rest of the world. At worst the City could lose a quarter of its business and some of its non-&lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; international activity. Few City veterans expect things to get that bad. If regulators work together, equivalence could be made to function well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the obstacles are not merely technocratic. The &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; would like to use Brexit to force much City activity to relocate to the European mainland. A row has broken out over plans from the European Securities and Markets Authority (&lt;small&gt;ESMA&lt;/small&gt;) to stop &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; investors trading stocks in London—a blatant land grab, say City folk. In May the Bank of England fulminated against “&lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; colleagues” who, it said, were scaremongering about Brexit in meetings with a foreign bank to lure it to the continent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; regulators had become concerned that London’s clout impinged on the bloc’s financial and economic sovereignty well before the Brexit referendum. In 2011 the European Central Bank (&lt;small&gt;ECB&lt;/small&gt;) tried to force British clearing houses handling huge volumes of euro-denominated financial products to move into the euro zone, only to be defeated four years later when the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; General Court said it lacked powers to make them do so. In the middle of the &lt;small&gt;ECB&lt;/small&gt;’s gambit, the decision by &lt;small&gt;LCH&lt;/small&gt;.Clearnet, Europe’s dominant, London-based clearing house, to raise margin requirements on some Italian and Spanish government bonds was seen by some in the &lt;small&gt;EU27&lt;/small&gt; as a hostile act. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Monetary sovereignty&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A paper by economists at the Bank for International Settlements underlines the City’s centrality to &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; financial operations. About half of all the €2.6trn ($3trn) of euro-area bonds bought by the &lt;small&gt;ECB&lt;/small&gt;’s asset-purchase programme came from institutions outside the euro zone. Banks in Britain were the main facilitators of bond sales. That &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; regulators have spotty control over activities core to the bloc’s banking stability becomes troubling post-Brexit, they say. “If I have one heart I rely on and it’s inside me, that’s fine,” explains Olivier Guersent, director-general of the European Commission’s unit for financial stability, financial services and capital markets union. “But if I am reliant on a mechanical heart outside me, I become shaky.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190629_FNC309.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190629_FNC309.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190629_FNC309.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190629_FNC309.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190629_FNC309.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190629_FNC309.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190629_FNC309.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190629_FNC309.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190629_FNC309.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190629_FNC309.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;“How do you manage a financial crisis if the bulk of your financial services are provided by a third country?” adds Robert Ophèle, chairman of the Autorité des marchés financiers, France’s stockmarket regulator. Suppose the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; wanted to impose a blanket ban on shorting the shares of banks, he says (some countries restricted shorts during the crisis in 2008-09). In the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;, Britain could not easily refuse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For its part, once it has left the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; Britain will no longer be able to block the forced relocation of financial activities to the euro zone. City folk fret about four areas in particular: clearing; share trading; risk management; and “delegation”, in which firms set up office in one &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; country while their funds are managed in another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Few rule out a fresh attempt to force euro-denominated clearing to relocate. In the meantime Eurex Clearing, &lt;small&gt;LCH&lt;/small&gt;’s main &lt;small&gt;EU27&lt;/small&gt; rival, is trying the carrot rather than the stick. A new revenue-sharing model has helped increase its market share in euro-denominated interest-rate swap clearing (measured in notional amount outstanding) to 15%, from under 1% at the start of 2018. “Banks have flicked a switch in our favour where they easily can,” says Erik Müller, the firm’s boss.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for share trading, in late May &lt;small&gt;ESMA&lt;/small&gt; partially backed down and said that &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; fund managers could continue to trade 14 stocks in London that trade overwhelmingly there now. But that leaves 6,186 more that, in the event of a no-deal Brexit, &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;-registered investors will be able to trade only on exchanges in the &lt;small&gt;EU27&lt;/small&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regarding delegation, in 2017 &lt;small&gt;ESMA&lt;/small&gt; published guidelines aimed at stopping European financial centres making “sweetheart” deals to lure financial firms from the City. It warned national regulators to watch out for firms that follow &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; rules and locate there but keep managing their portfolios from Britain. Stopping &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; funds from being run by City-based stockpickers would strike at the heart of the active asset-management model. Though &lt;small&gt;ESMA&lt;/small&gt; appears to have backed off for now, risk management is still in regulators’ sights. The &lt;small&gt;ECB&lt;/small&gt; sees “back-to-back” operations—doing business in the &lt;small&gt;EU27&lt;/small&gt; but shifting the risk to London using internal trades—as a ruse to minimise relocations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the referendum global banks made grids to help them decide where in the &lt;small&gt;EU27&lt;/small&gt; they might open new offices or expand their business, says a lawyer in London. Criteria such as size, tax and regulation were colour-coded red, green and amber. Then they examined the red and orange squares—and ruled everywhere out. “Frankfurt was seen as boring; Amsterdam, Luxembourg and Dublin were too small; Madrid and Milan had tax and regulation problems; and Paris was a nightmare for employment law,” says the lawyer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, London’s rivals are doing their utmost. Paris is touting its size, cultural richness, financial-markets tradition, derivatives talent and proximity to London. François Hollande, France’s president until 2017, had declared in campaigning that his “true enemy” was finance. But Emmanuel Macron is more welcoming. Labour-market reforms and the abolition of the wealth tax have helped. And dinner with him is a big lure, bankers say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Frankfurt, for its part, emphasises its banking clout—it is home to the &lt;small&gt;ECB&lt;/small&gt; and has long been Germany’s banking capital—plus regulatory and political predictability. It lies tenth in the Global Financial Centres Index (&lt;small&gt;GFCI&lt;/small&gt;), a ranking of competitiveness. That is well above Paris, at 23rd. Germany’s government has chipped in by allowing banks to hire and fire far more readily. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190629_FNP002_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190629_FNP002_0.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190629_FNP002_0.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190629_FNP002_0.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190629_FNP002_0.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190629_FNP002_0.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190629_FNP002_0.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190629_FNP002_0.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190629_FNP002_0.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190629_FNP002_0.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;To some banks Frankfurt’s refusal to make “crazy” deals is preferable to Paris’s newfound flexibility. As the head of Brexit preparations for an American investment bank tells it, French officials asked “what would you like?” and offered to change national law. The bank thought they might reverse things for someone else and went elsewhere. Though it has made strides, France has still to establish a long record as a reliable home for international finance, acknowledges a government adviser. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Staff have been mutinous about leaving London. For its way of life, Paris is the clear winner. In some of Frankfurt’s elegant suburbs the population is so elderly that “you’re the youth policy”, quips the European head of an American investment bank. All the same the German city has won the most banking business, attracting 44% of bank moves, according to New Financial. Paris has attracted a wide range of financial firms; Dublin and Luxembourg are popular with asset managers; Amsterdam is favoured by trading firms and market-infrastructure providers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Sell signals&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shifts that have happened so far are just the start, however. According to the French government adviser, banks are placing smallish bets across Europe, and are likely to reconcentrate their &lt;small&gt;EU27&lt;/small&gt; activities once the dust settles. For London, the harm could be substantial. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Warning signs are already in evidence. The number of initial public offerings in London has fallen of late, with the total value in 2018 down 23% compared with 2017. Frankfurt, by contrast, had one of its best years in terms of issue volume since the turn of the century. London kept its top spot in the &lt;small&gt;GFCI&lt;/small&gt; in March 2018 but was beaten by New York this year. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Catherine McGuinness of the City of London Corporation, the municipal body that governs the Square Mile, says that more business is moving away than is visible in banks’ announcements. She fears more will leave than are legally required to. Asian institutions in particular are flummoxed by the Brexit chaos. Nomura, a Japanese investment bank, no longer counts London as its global wholesale hub and will soon slash staff there. American investment banks, which particularly value passporting, are among the most critical of Brexit’s harm to financial services. In a decade, under even a soft Brexit, London will no longer be the financial centre it once was, Jamie Dimon, the boss of &lt;small&gt;JP&lt;/small&gt;Morgan Chase, recently said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“How much of the City’s international position relies on single-market access to the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; has not yet been tested,” says Mr Wright. Capital flows can quickly shift course if market infrastructure or regulation change. A case in point are so-called venues, where fixed income, currencies and commodities (&lt;small&gt;FICC&lt;/small&gt;) trade. &lt;small&gt;M&lt;/small&gt;i&lt;small&gt;FID&lt;/small&gt; 2, a huge piece of new European regulation, regulates venues for the first time, creating greater scope for European regulators to try to bring &lt;small&gt;FICC&lt;/small&gt; liquidity onshore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the next decade London could see business trickle away to &lt;small&gt;EU27&lt;/small&gt; capitals, New York and, increasingly, Asian financial centres. The situation is highly unpredictable, says Mr Mensah of Bank of America Merrill Lynch. “The City grew organically over a long period of time, so there is no blueprint to dismantle bits of it while avoiding unintended consequences.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the City is not a passive observer of its fate. Britain’s time zone, between New York and Asia, and common-law system are powerful advantages—as are a willingness to experiment, global approach, cultural allure and deep hiring pool. And even if it loses some of its &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;-related business, optimists think that revenues from the rest of the world will grow faster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One way to safeguard the City would be for Britain to become a rule-taker, hewing to European financial regulation. But British regulators (and especially the large insurance industry, which has less &lt;small&gt;EU27&lt;/small&gt; business) reckon it is too big and important to be lashed to the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;. Following the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt;’s more dirigiste and inflexible rule book after Brexit could hobble it relative to New York and Asian financial centres, they say. What is more, in future &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; regulators could set out to harm London deliberately. European officials know where the compromises are between British priorities and, say, French ones, says Jonathan Hill, Britain’s former &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; commissioner in charge of financial services. “They know precisely how to send Exocets into London.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hence another possibility: to embrace a buccaneering future. Brexiteer politicians’ conception of “Singapore-on-Thames”—slashing regulation, lowering capital standards and corporate taxes, and prioritising competitiveness—is often compared to the 1980s Big Bang. Though it is unclear how Britain could emulate a city state, &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; negotiators take the risk seriously. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Bank of England and the &lt;small&gt;FCA&lt;/small&gt; are pressing for a compromise. Under “stylish regulation” Britain would return to a more outcomes-based system, guided by six principles, including openness to the rest of the world, sensitivity to business models and promoting competition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for equivalence, Andrew Bailey, the &lt;small&gt;FCA&lt;/small&gt;’s chief executive, says Britain will need to see what framework the &lt;small&gt;EU27&lt;/small&gt; offers. “We are a global financial centre so we need to see if the price is worth paying.” Mr Bailey reckons that unless the &lt;small&gt;EU27&lt;/small&gt; follow Britain towards principles-based regulation, they will have little chance of developing more vibrant capital markets or bigger financial centres. And in private, officials express doubts as to whether &lt;small&gt;EU27&lt;/small&gt; countries really want outsized quantities of financial risk shifting to European capitals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such confident views are typical of the City. Yet there is more than a whiff of complacency. Passporting is not all the City is losing: also gone is its reputation for political stability and predictability. British governments of all stripes have long supported financial services. But Brexit’s toxic politics changed that. Mrs May earned a reputation for being hostile to the City. Boris Johnson, her probable successor, said “fuck business” in pursuit of a hard exit. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shadow chancellor, John McDonnell, has recently begun courting the City. But the Labour Party’s plans, which include heavy taxes on the rich, giving a tenth of big firms’ equity to workers and nationalising utilities and rail, are viewed with dread. Mr McDonnell is rumoured to be plotting retroactive capital controls and clawbacks of bankers’ compensation from the crisis—though he insists that strong economic growth under a Labour government would mean no need for capital controls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some hear echoes from history. In the 18th century Amsterdam’s financiers used to lead the world, but they lost faith in the city’s future under Napoleon and moved to London. For a financial hub facing the twin threats of an acrimonious Brexit and a hard-left government, that is a lesson worth heeding. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Finance and economics&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;City under siege&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 21:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A rare peep at the finances of Britain’s 0.01%]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/29/a-rare-peep-at-the-finances-of-britains-001]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_brd002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HEY ARE&lt;/small&gt; objects of both fascination and fury. But beyond the annual &lt;em&gt;Sunday Times&lt;/em&gt; “Rich List”, which estimates the fortunes of Britain’s wealthiest, relatively little is known about the finances of the economic elite. Official statistics, which extrapolate from surveys of the general public, are good at guessing the incomes of middling sorts. But they find it harder to get an accurate picture of those with more unusual circumstances. The very richest are particularly elusive. As well as being frustrating for nosy parkers, this makes it harder to estimate inequality, which depends on an accurate understanding of the full extent of their loot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a paper published on June 17th, Mike Brewer and Claudia Samano-Robles of Essex University paint an unusually detailed portrait of Britain’s very highest earners. Using data from the tax office up until 2015-16, they focus on the incomes of not just the top 1%—who earned a trifling £129,000 ($164,000) or more in that year—but the top 0.01%. The 5,000 or so individuals in that club each made at least £2.2m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Who are they? Nearly all live in England, the majority in London. Scotland has about 200 of them, and Wales and Northern Ireland perhaps 50 between them. Only about one in ten is a woman; one in 20 is a millennial (roughly defined as the generation born between 1981 and 1996). Financial services, by far the biggest category, employ more than a third of them. Yet roughly 15% of Britain’s super-high earners do not appear to work at all. In 2015 40% of the income of the top 0.01% was “unearned”, meaning that it came from the returns to financial investments and the like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The very rich have been getting a lot richer. Since 1995 the share of overall income accruing to the top 0.01% has roughly tripled (see chart). They had a turbulent time during the financial crisis of 2008-09, when many bankers were sacked and the value of financial investments plummeted. Yet they quickly bounced back. By 2015-16 the share of income accruing to the top 0.01% was at its second-highest level in decades. It is likely to have risen still further since then.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190629_BRC308.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190629_BRC308.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190629_BRC308.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190629_BRC308.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190629_BRC308.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190629_BRC308.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190629_BRC308.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190629_BRC308.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190629_BRC308.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190629_BRC308.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The paper is part of a recent trend among economists to improve estimates of the incomes of the rich. That work is much needed, since Britain’s two official measures of overall inequality—one from the Office for National Statistics (&lt;small&gt;ONS&lt;/small&gt;) and the other from the Department for Work and Pensions (&lt;small&gt;DWP&lt;/small&gt;)—have limited success in guessing the incomes of the well-off. Both suffer from the problem that very rich people are particularly likely to under-report their income. Some evidence finds that the very well-off are less likely to answer surveys, since they believe they are too busy to do so. They may also have earnings from a variety of sources, which can make it hard to keep track of everything that is gushing in. An &lt;small&gt;ONS&lt;/small&gt; study published in February suggests that survey data capture only about half the income of someone who has just made it into the richest 0.5%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the rich command a disproportionately large share of overall income, getting them wrong is a disproportionately big problem. Both the &lt;small&gt;ONS&lt;/small&gt; and &lt;small&gt;DWP&lt;/small&gt; suggest that, somewhat surprisingly, since the early 1990s overall income inequality (as measured by the Gini coefficient) has not changed much. Could these conclusions be skewed by a poor understanding of just how rich the richest are?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In an effort to get to the bottom of this, academic researchers have sought to combine tax data with survey data. (Wonks at the &lt;small&gt;DWP&lt;/small&gt; already do this, though their methodology is widely agreed to be flawed.) Calculations in a paper published earlier this year by Stephen Jenkins of the London School of Economics and the late Tony Atkinson, formerly of Oxford University, show a marked increase in overall inequality since the mid-1990s, in contrast to the stability shown by official statistics. Such work is at an early stage. But it suggests that a better understanding of the 0.01% may reveal that the gap between rich and poor has been widening more than many people thought. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Britain&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;How the 0.01% live&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 21:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[As America and Iran inch closer to war, new talks are needed]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/29/as-america-and-iran-inch-closer-to-war-new-talks-are-needed]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_LDD001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;F&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;OR NEARLY&lt;/small&gt; four years Iran’s path to a nuclear weapon was blocked. The deal it signed with America and other powers in 2015 limited its nuclear programme to civilian uses, such as power-generation, and subjected them to the toughest inspection regime in history. The experts agreed that Iran was complying and that its nuclear activities were contained. But then President Donald Trump ditched the nuclear deal and Iran resumed stockpiling low-enriched uranium. It is now poised to breach the 300kg cap set by the agreement. Iran may hesitate before crossing that line, but it is also threatening to increase the enrichment level of its uranium, bringing it closer to the stuff that goes into a bomb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, Iran is not about to become a nuclear-weapons power. Its breakout time is over a year. But it is once again using its nuclear programme to heap pressure on America. That adds an explosive new element to an already-volatile mix. America accuses Iran of attacking six ships in the Strait of Hormuz since May. On June 20th Iran shot down an American spy drone. America insisted the aircraft was above international waters, not Iran’s, and sent warplanes to strike back. Ten minutes before they were due to hit targets inside Iran Mr Trump called them off and contented himself with a cyber-attack instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither Mr Trump, nor America’s allies, nor Iran wants a big new war in the Middle East. Yet Mr Trump’s strategy of applying “maximum pressure” on Iran is making the prospect more likely—because each side, issuing ever-wilder threats, could end up misreading the other’s red lines. The president’s room for manoeuvre is shrinking. As Iran turns more belligerent, calls for action will grow, not least from his own party (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/briefing/2019/06/29/breaking-the-nuclear-deal-ratchets-up-the-conflict-between-iran-and-america&quot; data-tegid=&quot;1pkf8n63agbldidsdglj7gfp6afoffh7&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;). Before things escalate out of control, both sides need to begin talking. That is not as unlikely as it sounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump’s Iran strategy is based on the premise that Barack Obama gave too much away too easily when he negotiated the deal in 2015. Last year the president set out to get better terms by reneging on the agreement and reimposing the sanctions that have crippled Iran’s economy. This, his advisers argue, will force a weakened Iran to accept a new deal that lasts longer than the old one, most of which expires by 2030. They also want curbs on Iran’s missile programme and an end to its violent meddling in the region. Mike Pompeo, the secretary of state, sees recent Iranian aggression as a sign that the strategy is working.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hard-hitting sanctions brought Iran to the negotiating table in 2015, but they are unlikely to lead to the transformation Mr Trump wants. One reason is that he has discredited Hassan Rouhani, Iran’s president and a champion of the nuclear deal. Hardliners are now calling the shots. Another is that America is acting alone. In 2015, in a rare moment of international unity, it had the support of its European allies as well as Russia and China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maximum pressure comes with extra risks, to boot. The mullahs and their Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps want to prove their mettle by showing that Mr Trump’s actions have costs—for everyone. On top of the attacks on ships and drones, Iranian proxies have hit pipelines in Saudi Arabia and are suspected of having struck Iraqi bases hosting American troops. If sanctions are not lifted, Iranian officials may resort to closing the Strait of Hormuz, through which one-fifth of the world’s oil passes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hawks like John Bolton, Mr Trump’s national security adviser, retort that if Iran wants war, that is what it will get—especially if it shows signs of dashing for a nuclear bomb, which could trigger disastrous proliferation in the Middle East. But this is the riskiest calculation of all. Having pulled out of a working deal, America may not win the backing of European allies for strikes. China and Russia would vehemently oppose any action at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps sanctions or war will cause the regime to crumble. But that is hardly a strategy: Cuba has resisted sanctions for decades. More probably, a defeated Iran would heed the lesson of nuclear-armed North Korea and redouble its efforts to get a bomb. Attacking Iran’s nuclear facilities would not destroy its know-how, as even Mr Bolton admits. If, as is likely, Iran barred international inspectors, its programme would move underground, literally and figuratively, making it very hard to stop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The alternative to today’s course is talks between America and Iran. Just now that looks far-fetched. Iran’s foreign ministry says American sanctions imposed on Ayatollah Ali Khamenei, the supreme leader, and other top officials this week mark “the permanent closure of the path of diplomacy”. Mr Rouhani has suggested that the White House is “mentally handicapped”—after which Mr Trump threatened “obliteration”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But optimists will remember similar clashes between America’s president and Kim Jong Un, North Korea’s despot, before they met in Singapore and “fell in love”, as Mr Trump put it. When he is not threatening to annihilate the mullahs, Mr Trump is offering to talk without preconditions and to “make Iran great again”. He does not want the prospect of war in the Middle East looming over his re-election campaign. Likewise, in Iran the economy is shrinking, prices are rising and people are becoming fed up. Pressure is growing on Mr Khamenei to justify his intransigence. Love could yet bloom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America might coax Iran back to the table with a gesture of good faith, such as reinstating waivers that let some countries buy Iranian oil. Iran, in turn, could promise to comply with the nuclear deal again. Behind the scenes, its leaders have expressed a willingness to sign something like the old agreement with additions—such as extending parts of the deal beyond 2030. Negotiations would never be easy; the Iranians are infuriating to deal with. But that would let the president claim victory, as he did with the United States-Mexico-Canada Agreement, which his administration signed last year and which looks a lot like its predecessor, the North American Free Trade Agreement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What of a deal that also curbs Iran’s missile programme and restrains it in the region? As Mr Trump seems to realise, biting everything off in one go is unrealistic. A new deal cannot solve all the problems posed by Iran or normalise ties with America after decades of enmity. It may not even lift all America’s sanctions. Neither did the first agreement. But, if done right, a deal would put Iran’s nuclear programme back in a box, making it easier to tackle all those other problems without causing a war. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Leaders&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;How to contain Iran&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 21:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Breaking the nuclear deal ratchets up the conflict between Iran and America]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/briefing/2019/06/29/breaking-the-nuclear-deal-ratchets-up-the-conflict-between-iran-and-america]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_FBD001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE FACILITY&lt;/small&gt; 30km (19 miles) north-west of the Iranian city of Natanz looks like a humdrum industrial site. Only the anti-aircraft guns hint at what goes on eight metres (26 feet) underground. For over a decade Iranian scientists there have fed uranium hexafluoride into centrifuges that spin at twice the speed of sound so as to sift out uranium-235, the isotope capable of sustaining a chain reaction in a nuclear power plant or bomb. The “raw” uranium that goes in is 0.7% {+2}{+3}{+5}U; the stuff that comes out is 4% {+2}{+3}{+5}U.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2015, as part of the nuclear deal between Iran, the permanent-five nations on the &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt; Security Council and Germany, Iran promised that it would not enrich any uranium beyond this 4% level, nor hold stocks of more than 300kg of such low-enriched uranium (&lt;small&gt;LEU&lt;/small&gt;). But in May 2018 President Donald Trump walked away from that deal, reimposing old sanctions and adding a spate of new ones, too. America now imposes over 1,000 sanctions on Iran and parties that might trade with it. These sanctions have hurt Iran a lot: inflation is expected to reach 50% this year, and &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; to shrink by 6%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iran hopes that if it does, or threatens to do, things others would rather it did not, it might have its plight relieved. So in May it quadrupled the rate at which it was producing &lt;small&gt;LEU&lt;/small&gt;. On June 27th, according to the International Atomic Energy Agency (&lt;small&gt;IAEA&lt;/small&gt;), the &lt;small&gt;LEU&lt;/small&gt; stocks at Natanz had not quite surpassed 300kg. But in just a few days the limit could be broken.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An imminent step beyond the limits of the deal is not a cause for immediate alarm. For one thing, no amount of &lt;small&gt;LEU&lt;/small&gt; can in itself be used to make a bomb; that is typically done with uranium enriched to 90% or so. For another, the step is easily reversed. Enrichment is difficult, but dilution is a doddle.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the point when it signed the deal, Iran had amassed a much larger stockpile of &lt;small&gt;LEU&lt;/small&gt;—ten tonnes—and had many more centrifuges up and running. Its breakout time—the time it would take to produce enough fissile material for a single bomb—was a harrowing two to three months. With the stockpile and centrifuges it has working at Natanz today, the breakout time would be over a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stepping over the &lt;small&gt;LEU&lt;/small&gt; threshold is a signal that Iran is no longer willing to abide by the terms of the deal, despite encouragement to do so from the other five parties, unless it is offered new incentives. Further steps look sure to follow. Iran’s president, Hassan Rouhani, recently warned that if the deal’s other signatories did not set about easing the country’s economic pain by July 7th, the country would start enriching uranium beyond the 4% level. Another reversible move, but a more troubling one. Enrichment follows the rules of geometric growth, so uranium enriched to 20% is most of the way to 90%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other escalations might include: pulling mothballed centrifuges out of storage to increase the amount of enrichment it can do; restarting enrichment at Fordow, an even deeper-buried and thus harder-to-bomb plant. Perhaps the most ominous would be to expel the inspectors from the &lt;small&gt;IAEA&lt;/small&gt; who closely monitor Iran’s nuclear facilities, leaving the world blind to any attempts at breakout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the time being, Iran is more interested in hinting at such options than dashing nuke-wards. Measured and reversible steps lessen the backlash from European states, which have some sympathy with Iran’s predicament, and make it harder for America or Israel to justify a preventive war. But they are still provocative, and speak of a certain desperation. “When we looked at scenarios in the past, we never assumed such a long and unbelievably aggressive &lt;small&gt;US&lt;/small&gt; policy towards Iran,” says a former Pentagon official who participated in war games to understand how a conflict with Iran might play out. “Maximum pressure”, America’s term for the tightening vice of sanctions, “has left Iran as a wounded animal, up against a wall.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBM987.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBM987.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBM987.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBM987.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBM987.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBM987.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBM987.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBM987.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBM987.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBM987.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fissile brinkmanship is the most candid signal of Iran’s willingness to make its pain a concern to others, but there are more. On May 12th and June 13th several tankers were attacked off the coast of the United Arab Emirates and in the Gulf of Oman. America and some allies blamed Iran’s Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps (&lt;small&gt;IRGC&lt;/small&gt;). Rebels in Yemen, who have been armed by Iran in the past, have recently carried out several missile and drone attacks against targets in America’s ally, Saudi Arabia. And on June 20th Iran shot down a remotely piloted American spy-plane which it claimed was in its airspace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump quickly ordered an attack on the surface-to-air missile system that shot down that drone. He then called off the operation, reportedly with ten minutes to spare. He later said he had done so because he had learned that it could inflict up to 150 casualties, a death toll he described as “not proportionate” to the provocation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Deals of choice&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;What Iran wants from all this is clear: relief from sanctions. What America wants is harder to say—not least because Mr Trump and his advisers may well not agree.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A couple of weeks after America pulled out of the deal, Mike Pompeo, the secretary of state, set out a dozen demands to be made of Iran in any negotiations. They included ceasing all enrichment, withdrawing all forces under Iranian command from Syria and ending support for militant groups such as Hizbullah and Hamas. These demands go far enough beyond what Iran might conceivably comply with as to suggest that the real aim is regime change brought on by economic collapse and, if necessary, military confrontation. John Bolton, Mr Trump’s national security adviser, has called for attacks on Iran over many years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump seems less keen. Yes, he has chosen to employ hawks like Mr Pompeo and Mr Bolton. He is much closer to Iran’s regional foes, Israel and Saudi Arabia, than was Barack Obama, under whom the deal was negotiated. But on the campaign trail he largely set himself against foreign interventions. His &lt;em&gt;volte face&lt;/em&gt; over the retaliatory raid reportedly followed a conversation with Tucker Carlson, a Fox News host keen to be seen standing up for the promises of that campaign—pro-little-guy, anti-big-business, nigh-on-isolationist. And the president knows that he will soon be on the trail again. Any military outcomes short of prompt and decisive triumph would be a boon to his opponents.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hence another interpretation of maximum pressure on Iran: that it is aimed at pushing the country into negotiations. “I think they want to negotiate,” Mr Trump said on June 23rd. “And I think they want to make a deal. And my deal is nuclear.” &lt;em&gt;Pace&lt;/em&gt; Mr Pompeo’s wide-ranging demands, Mr Trump stressed there were no preconditions for talks. The plan, to the extent that such a thing exists, would seem to follow the template he used with North Korea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In that stand-off, too, Mr Trump was prepared to go to the rhetorical brink, alarming the world with talk of fire, fury and the size of his nuclear button, before taking part in a summit with Kim Jong Un, North Korea’s leader, in Singapore. “He may believe that by targeting the supreme leader [with specific sanctions] he can push him into the same dialogue as he forced ‘Little Rocket Man’,” says John Smith, a former head of the &lt;small&gt;US&lt;/small&gt; Treasury’s sanctions enforcement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Coercive diplomacy can work: indeed, it produced the deal of 2015. However William Burns, a diplomat who was involved in that effort and now heads the Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, a think-tank, points out that Mr Trump is trying the coercion without the diplomacy. Take the latest sanctions aimed at high-ranking individuals. Their first targets are Ali Khamenei, Iran’s supreme leader, and eight military commanders. The next salvo is likely to include the foreign minister, Javad Zarif. Some of America’s allies see this as making diplomacy very difficult. Iran’s foreign ministry says it means “the permanent closure of the diplomatic path”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, there are always channels. Shinzo Abe, Japan’s prime minister, recently visited Tehran bearing a message from Mr Trump. True, he is said to have left empty-handed. But the fact that Mr Khamenei, who rarely meets foreign leaders, was prepared to see him was perhaps a sign of openness. The question is what might America want him open to?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Any deal Mr Trump could countenance has to look like something tougher than the one he broke. Iran might expand the supreme leader’s apparently long-standing &lt;em&gt;fatwa&lt;/em&gt; outlawing nuclear weapons in effect turning religious law into secular law. It might also agree to tighten the &lt;small&gt;IAEA&lt;/small&gt; inspections regime—already one of the toughest in existence—and to extend the amount of time for which certain nuclear activities are prohibited.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In return, Iran would need America to rejoin the deal, provide greater sanctions relief than it did in 2015 and decline to press Iran on some or all of the wider goals Mr Pompeo set out. America might also offer the surety of a deal which, unlike the original, would be enshrined in a treaty ratified by the Senate from which no president could withdraw off his own bat. Democratic senators want the deal restored, and the Republicans who opposed it under Mr Obama might now come round.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBC949.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBC949.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBC949.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBC949.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBC949.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBC949.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBC949.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBC949.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBC949.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_FBC949.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This might be presented as “more for more”. Mr Trump could boast of a bigger, better deal—most importantly, one struck by him rather than Mr Obama. Iran could hail its success in seeing off sanctions and staring down American threats. However, such things take time and patience. Iran and America have a long record of mutual distrust (see timeline). Iranians point to America’s part in the 1953 coup against their elected prime minister and its support for Saddam Hussein in the Iran-Iraq war of the 1980s. Americans recall the embassy hostage-taking of 1979-81 and promiscuous support for terrorism, some of which has cost American lives. There is now the added problem that America broke their last agreement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though Mr Trump would surely prefer the sort of meeting in front of the world’s cameras that he had with Mr Kim, the countries’ long history of bad blood, along with the fact that Iran’s regime needs to keep various factions on board, would probably require normalisation to come about step by step—through the appointment of trusted envoys, waivers on some sanctions, confidence-building talks on Yemen, and so on. Mr Bolton would be unlikely to have any of it; he might decamp to the fields of punditry, criticising any reconciliation (though probably not on Mr Carlson’s show, where he has been denounced as a “bureaucratic tapeworm”).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;What could go wrong?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the meantime the risks of miscalculation rise. This does not mean all-out war is imminent. Iran spends just over $13bn on its armed forces each year—five times less than Saudi Arabia and about 50 times less than America. If the attack of June 20th had not been called off, Iran could not easily have escalated matters by means of a direct military response. But it might have launched further mine attacks in the Persian Gulf, or intensified the attacks against Saudi Arabia by rebels in Yemen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It might also have launched cyber-attacks of its own. “Incidents involving Iran have been among the most sophisticated, costly, and consequential attacks in the history of the internet,” noted Collin Anderson and Karim Sadjadpour, experts at the Carnegie Endowment, in a study in 2018. Marcus Willett, a former senior official at &lt;small&gt;GCHQ&lt;/small&gt;, Britain’s signals-intelligence agency, observes that Iranian cyber-operations have penetrated not only Saudi Arabia’s national oil company but also critical national infrastructure in Western states.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America could respond in kind. It has devoted considerable resources to planting malware throughout Iran’s nuclear sites, military and communication networks and power grid as part of a project called Nitro Zeus. After the air strikes of June 20th were called off, cyber-attacks on the &lt;small&gt;IRGC&lt;/small&gt; and missile forces went ahead. America also disrupted the communications of Kata’ib Hizbullah, an Iran-backed militia group in Iraq, in the days afterwards. Persistent low-level cyber-skirmishing may be becoming normal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Iranian mines, missiles or malware provoked America to launch a much bigger strike—Mr Trump has tweeted that “any attack by Iran on anything American will be met with great and overwhelming force”—its armed forces would doubtless prevail. But they might well suffer some losses along the way. The &lt;small&gt;IRG&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;C&lt;/small&gt; has honed the art of asymmetric warfare, for instance operating small, zippy boats designed to swarm around and discombobulate big American warships. Iran has also built up a formidable array of projectiles, including the largest ballistic-missile force in the Middle East and sea-skimming anti-ship missiles that can be launched from the shore or from quiet submarines hidden in the murky waters of the Persian Gulf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nor would American warplanes have a free run of Iranian skies. Iran’s air force may be dilapidated—it flies &lt;small&gt;F&lt;/small&gt;-14 fighters from the “Top Gun” era—but since 2017 it has acquired 32 batteries of Russia’s formidable &lt;small&gt;S&lt;/small&gt;-300 air-defence system. Its home-grown missiles are not bad, either. One of them took down that sophisticated high-altitude American drone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;small&gt;IRGC&lt;/small&gt;’s elite Quds Force would also be likely to draw on its region-wide network of proxy groups and allies to extend the conflict beyond its borders. Hizbullah in Lebanon has around 130,000 rockets and missiles. Predominantly Shia militia groups in Syria and Iraq could threaten thousands of American troops with guerrilla attacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Above the level of punitive strikes and regional repercussions there is little room for anything but a campaign to destroy Iranian nuclear sites or overthrow the regime. Neither is appealing. In 2012 a study by former diplomats and military officers concluded that air strikes on Iranian nuclear sites might delay Iran’s programme by just four years. Only an invasion and occupation of Iran could durably quash such efforts. That, said the study, would require about a million troops for an extended period. Even the most bellicose of Mr Trump’s advisers would blanch at that, you would hope. American voters certainly would.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regime change sounds easier than occupation; but it has not proved a very productive strategy in recent years. And if the new regime inherits a nuclear programme, even a degraded one, any relief might prove short-lived.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither side is eager for war; but Iran is definitely eager to see sanctions relaxed, and has few ways of achieving that end which do not look warlike. What is more, ratcheting down is harder than ratcheting up. And if North Korea is indeed the template, it is not a terribly encouraging one. Yes, Mr Trump and Mr Kim are again exchanging warm letters. But Mr Kim shows no sign of being willing to denuclearise in the way America wants him to, and continues to churn out fissile material for bombs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a deeper difference. With North Korea Mr Trump appeared to defuse, or at least defer, a serious crisis that predated him. With Iran, he faces an unnecessary crisis of his own making. That sad fact of authorship may make it harder for him even to appear to come out ahead.&lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Briefing&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;The narrowing gyre&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 21:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Diego Maradona” is Asif Kapadia’s best documentary to date]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/27/diego-maradona-is-asif-kapadias-best-documentary-to-date]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_BKP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-27T13:58:19Z&quot;&gt;Jun 27th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EARLY IN “Diego Maradona” there is a chaotic press conference. The celebrated Argentine playmaker has been signed by Napoli, an Italian football club, and he is being unveiled to more than 80,000 ecstatic fans at Stadio San Paolo. A journalist puts a loaded question to Corrado Ferlaino, the club’s president: how could Napoli—then one of the lowest-ranking teams in Serie A, Italy’s top league—afford the world’s most expensive player? He is insinuating that the Camorra, a mafia network, might have helped to make the transfer possible; in the film, this signposts the trouble that lies ahead for the star.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asif Kapadia, a British film-maker, focuses on Mr Maradona’s career between 1984 and 1991, spanning his time in Italy and his captaincy of Argentina at the 1986 and 1990 World Cups. As in his previous two films, “Senna” and “Amy” (which won an Oscar for Best Documentary Feature), Mr Kapadia crafts his narrative from old footage. Much of the grainy video featured in the film was shot by two jobbing camera operators hired by Jorge Cysterzpiler, Mr Maradona’s former agent, for a film about the footballer. As that movie was never made, much of the tape has never been seen before.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The director highlights his subject’s supremacy on the pitch—“The Golden Boy” guided his country to a World Cup win in 1986 and Napoli to its first Serie A title in 1987—but gives plenty of space to his antics off it, too. Mr Maradona recounts socialising with the Giuliano clan, part of the Camorra, which supplied him with protection and cocaine. Drug binges in seedy Neapolitan nightclubs would begin after matches and continue for three days, at which point Mr Maradona would begin training for the next fixture. This was his routine for years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The film’s most memorable sporting scenes are situated in their historical context. Britain had defeated Argentina in the Falklands war in 1982; had it been a match, Mr Maradona said, they would have won 20-0. When England and Argentina met in the World Cup quarter-final four years later, the atmosphere was fraught. Mr Maradona used his hand to punch the ball past Peter Shilton, England’s goalkeeper: he called it the “hand of god”. Minutes later he dribbled past six England players—including Mr Shilton—to score one of the most stunning goals in football history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp508.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp508.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp508.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp508.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp508.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp508.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp508.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp508.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp508.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Social divides in Italy, particularly between north and south, are also laid bare. Footage shows Napoli’s followers enduring execrable abuse from supporters of northern Italian teams: visiting fans hold banners which read “cholerati” (“cholera infected”)—there had been an outbreak in Naples in 1973 in which people had died—and chant that Mount Vesuvius should “wash them with fire”. As a result, Mr Maradona called on Neapolitans to support him and Argentina, rather than their native Italy, in the 1990 World Cup semi-final, played in Naples. Argentina went on to win the game on penalties, with Mr Maradona scoring from the final, crucial kick. Many Italians never forgave him, particularly for encouraging some to renege on their national side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, Mr Maradona is not a likeable hero. He is crude, teaching his young daughter to chant expletives in the manner of an extreme “Napoli ultra” fan. He makes sexist remarks, and he refuses to acknowledge a love-child for decades. But it is hard not to feel some sympathy for him. He winces in agony as he receives pain-killing injections for sciatica, a nerve condition, in order to play. Mr Maradona’s sister, Maria Rosa, recalls that he became the family breadwinner aged 15, after being signed by Argentinos Juniors, a club in Buenos Aires. He moved his parents and seven siblings into his city-centre flat from the slums. “It was a lot of responsibility for a 15-year-old,” Maria Rosa says with sadness. “He was never able to be himself after that.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Ferlaino, meanwhile, describes himself as “Maradona’s jailor”, having refused the player’s repeated requests to leave Napoli in 1989. Stuck in the city and with no means to cope with the pressures of fame, he went off the rails. All he had was the Giulianos, who in the end dumped him too. Once they had withdrawn their protection Mr Maradona soon tested positive for cocaine during a random drug test, and was banned from competing for more than a year. His career never recovered. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Diego Maradona” tells a compelling story, and it paints a vivid picture of Naples in the 1980s and its football-mad inhabitants, as well as of a troubled star. It is Mr Kapadia’s finest documentary to date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Diego Maradona” is screening in Britain now. It will be released in America in September&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 21:39:55 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“The government does nothing more than pay fighters on all sides”—the struggle for Libya]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/27/the-government-does-nothing-more-than-pay-fighters-on-all-sides-the-struggle-for-libya]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_blm511.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-27T11:45:24Z&quot;&gt;Jun 27th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;LIFE IN &lt;strong&gt;Libya’s capital&lt;/strong&gt; seems calm, even as a warlord backed by ragtag forces bids to take the city. Meanwhile the putative government can muster little political power—or electric power. We examine a miracle in &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/15/russia-and-america-both-want-moldovas-ruling-oligarch-to-go&quot;&gt;Moldova&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;: after years as a swamp of post-Soviet corruption, an anti-graft campaigner has become prime minister. And, historical data reveal the overlooked power of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/27/the-democrats-hold-their-first-presidential-primary-debate&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;primary debates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Runtime: 22 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/0ff7dc35-24b3-46e3-b041-5e2b3410e9a3&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 21:39:54 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>