<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[“America and China are spending enormous sums on defence”]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/02/america-and-china-are-spending-enormous-sums-on-defence]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/china_navy_day.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-02T10:02:01Z&quot;&gt;May 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;GOVERNMENTS THE world over are beefing up &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/international/2019/04/28/military-spending-around-the-world-is-booming&quot;&gt;defence spending&lt;/a&gt;—chief among them America’s and China’s. But some of the usual big military spenders are actually shrinking budgets. May Day protests in France took a violent turn this year, and that complicates President Macron’s efforts to calm an already protest-prone populace. And academics have been trying to determine which English-speaking country produces the most &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/30/who-are-the-biggest-bullshitters&quot;&gt;bullshit&lt;/a&gt;. Runtime: 21min.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/buythebullet-globaldefencespending&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 23:07:09 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg wants to build WeChat for the West]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/02/mark-zuckerberg-wants-to-build-wechat-for-the-west]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_wbp001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;N HIS SPARE&lt;/small&gt; time Mark Zuckerberg likes to run. In 2016 Facebook’s boss pledged to cover 365 miles (587km) that year and, ever the overachiever, completed the challenge by July. He does not practise martial arts, but his almost discomfiting poise could lead you to mistake him for a master of something like aikido. That would be appropriate, for in his professional life Mr Zuckerberg is trying to turn his opponents’ energy against them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When in early March he announced that Facebook would follow a “privacy-focused vision for social networking”, complete with encrypted messages that even the firm cannot peer into, observers interpreted this as a defensive move. Some discerned a belated response to outrage over privacy abuses on the world’s largest social network. Others saw the plan to knit together its instant-messaging services, chiefly Messenger and WhatsApp, as a way to make the company harder to break up, as some American politicians demand. Others still spied a ruse to escape liability for violent user content, now that Facebook would no longer be able to read any of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All three rationales probably played a part. Yet the firm’s “privacy pivot” is perhaps better seen as an aikido-like redirection of detractors’ momentum. Mr Zuckerberg’s speech at his firm’s annual developer conference in San Jose on April 30th suggested as much. Far from retreating, he is limbering up for a new contest—to reinvent social networking, this time around messaging. “The future is private,” he declared grandiosely. Though he might not admit it in public, he seems keen to turn Facebook into a Western version of WeChat, the Chinese messaging app whose array of mobile services, from payments to filing court paperwork, has made it ubiquitous in China—even if his recent pledge to store user information only in countries that respect the rule of law is an implicit admission that he has given up on the Chinese market, where Communist minders insist that Western firms must keep all data locally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;Older. And wiser?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook’s core business is maturing, as its boss clearly sees. Its operating margins—42%, excluding $3bn set aside to cover an expected fine by America’s Federal Trade Commission for privacy violations—remain the envy of the tech world (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/02/american-technology-firms-mixed-results&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;). In the latest quarter revenue grew by 26% compared with the previous year, exceeding $15bn. But user growth is slowing. In some rich countries, especially European ones, it is flat. The young prefer social media which are more “intimate” and “ephemeral”, like Snapchat, which pioneered “stories”, messages and pictures that disappear after 24 hours—and which Facebook aped. More than 500m users of Instagram, Messenger and WhatsApp now post stories every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Zuckerberg expects migration from the online “town square” to a digital “living room” to continue; stories may soon outnumber posts on Facebook’s newsfeed. The plan is to build it around WhatsApp, which already offers secure texting. It would let users find each other, pay digital and offline shopkeepers, or purchase a cornucopia of online services—perhaps one day using Facebook’s own currency. In time, the thinking goes, it may become as indispensable to Westerners as WeChat is in China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some elements of the new platform already exist; WhatsApp is testing a payment service in India. Others, such as new shopping features on Instagram, were launched in San Jose. All this falls short of a full-blown business plan. But the contours of Mr Zuckerberg’s vision are taking shape. The 34-year-old is proceeding more cautiously than in Facebook’s early years, when he was guided by the now infamous injunction to “move fast and break things”—but no less deliberately.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is just as well, for “platform shifts” are tricky. Microsoft did not see smartphones coming and Facebook itself almost missed the rise of mobile apps. To succeed, it must clear a number of hurdles. The first is technical. Facebook wants an Instagram user to be able to send a note directly to a friend on WhatsApp. Creating a common phone book for these services, with a combined total of 2.7bn users and different source codes, presents a knotty problem for programmers. Chris Cox, one of Mr Zuckerberg’s top lieutenants, is rumoured to have left the company in March because he did not think it could be done (this week Mr Cox attributed his departure to “artistic differences” with his boss).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second challenge is economic. WeChat could become the platform of choice on smartphones because China had no dominant app stores. Facebook must contend with incumbents such as Apple and Google. Since you can’t sell microtargeted adverts against encrypted messages your algorithms cannot see, the new platform will need a fresh way to make money. For all its ubiquity, WeChat is no cash cow (Tencent, its owner, makes most of its revenue from online games). Maintaining Facebook’s fat margins would require new revenue sources, such as charging businesses to contact users or taking a cut of any purchases, as credit-card issuers do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, there are the entwined issues of privacy and competition. Mr Zuckerberg accepts that a lot of people dismiss Facebook’s sincerity here—his recent article in the &lt;em &gt;Washington Post&lt;/em&gt;, imploring governments to regulate social media, notwithstanding. It will continue to collect plenty of data. Integrating these, and the underlying apps, could in turn enable Facebook to convert its dominance in public social networking into power over private messaging. This reminds seasoned competition regulators of Microsoft’s attempts to bundle its operating system with a web browser in the mid-1990s in a bid to control cyberspace. With the internet’s rise, the stakes today are bigger: no country wants one firm to become society’s de facto operating system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since its services cost nothing, Facebook says, it is not gouging users. It could argue that a single dominant social network is easier to police than lots of smaller ones and has greater financial and technical capacity to keep users safe from harmful content. And it would be a bulwark against WeChat, which might otherwise become a force outside China—bringing the Chinese surveillance state with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, Mr Zuckerberg’s &lt;em &gt;Washington Post&lt;/em&gt; article looks like a bid to broker a 21st-century version of the Kingsbury Commitment of 1913, when &lt;small&gt;AT&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;T&lt;/small&gt;, then America’s telephone monopoly, accepted government oversight and agreed to spin off some of its businesses in exchange for not being nationalised or broken up. The difference is that, unlike &lt;small&gt;AT&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;T&lt;/small&gt;, Facebook’s reach extends beyond America and spans a growing range of industries, from advertising to finance. It must grapple with politicians, regulators and rivals. If enough opponents gang up at once, even the most gifted aikido master may struggle to fend them off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Finance and economics&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Mark Zuckerberg’s WeChat moment&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 22:06:33 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Satellite data shed new light on North Korea’s opaque economy]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/04/satellite-data-shed-new-light-on-north-koreas-opaque-economy]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_gdc101_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;

&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190504_GDNorthKorea/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;V&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;IEWED FROM&lt;/small&gt; space at night, North Korea looks like the recently released first image of a black hole: an abyss, ringed by the brilliant glow of South Korea, China and Russia, from which nothing can escape. But the Hermit Kingdom does emit a bit of light, which orbiting satellites detect. And nocturnal luminosity is one of the few reliable sources of information about the country. It implies that North Korea’s economy is poorer, more volatile and more vulnerable to weather than formerly thought.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Night lights are a strong proxy for economic activity. A new paper by the &lt;small&gt;IMF&lt;/small&gt; finds that they explain 44% of the variation in countries’ &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; per person—as close a tie as that between a person’s height and hand size. In places where records are poor or manipulated, night lights offer an alternative measure of output. One study found that among countries with similar luminosity, autocracies reported &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; growth 15-30% higher than democracies did.&lt;/p&gt;



&lt;p&gt;Nowhere are good economic data rarer than in North Korea. The most detailed numbers come from South Korea’s central bank, which derives them from figures on production volumes of various goods. When adjusted for the cost of living in a developing Asian economy, the bank’s most recent estimate of North Korea’s annual &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; per person is enough to buy goods and services that would cost $2,500 in America.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190504_GDNorthKorea_Chart/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The picture painted by night lights, however, is even grimmer. In 2013 a group of scholars compared luminosity and &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; within rural China, obtaining an equation to estimate economic output from light. A forthcoming paper by World Data Lab, a startup, and a team of researchers applies this formula to North Korea. It yields a standard of living that would cost $1,400 a year in America, making North Korea one of the world’s ten poorest countries.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The data also suggest that the economy has been unusually volatile. In 2013-15 luminosity fell by 40%. That implies a 12% reduction in &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt;, including 19% in the capital region, Pyongyang. Since 2016, however, the country has brightened again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190504_GDNorthKorea_Pyongyang/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;International sanctions are unlikely to have produced this darkening. They were made stricter in 2016-17, just as luminosity rose. A drop in the prices of North Korean exports, like coal, may have played a part.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But the main cause was probably weather. North Korea relies on hydropower, and in 2015 it was parched by a drought. The Bank of Korea also reckons that electricity, gas and water output fell by 13% in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The economy may not have shrunk as much as the dimming suggests. Recessions caused by power cuts could disproportionately reduce lighting. Many North Koreans own solar panels, which power daytime activity not shown in night lights. And state buildings, whose illumination is a political choice, make up much of the capital’s glow. As with physics inside a black hole, no one knows what economic laws apply within North Korea’s eerie silhouette.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Nonetheless, a 40% drop in luminosity indicates a serious recession. And this year the government has admitted publicly that heatwaves, floods and drought have caused a dire food shortfall. The regime appears much better prepared to weather trade sanctions than the wrath of nature.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p data-interactive-source=&quot;&quot; &gt;Sources: World Data Lab in collaboration with the NOMIS Foundation, Vienna University of Economics and Business, and the International Institute for Applied Systems Analysis; Earth Observation Group, NOAA NCEI; “Illuminating economic growth”, by Yingyao Hu and Jiaxiong Yao, IMF working paper, April 2019&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/gd-north-korea/css/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/gd-north-korea/css/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Graphic detail&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;When the lights go out&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 21:06:20 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Xiaomi’s founder loses a billion-yuan bet]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/02/xiaomis-founder-loses-a-billion-yuan-bet]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_wbp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;N 2013 BUSINESS&lt;/small&gt; folk gathered in Beijing to honour Chinese “Economic Figures of the Year” were treated to an unexpected twist. One of the winners, Lei Jun, ventured that in five years the sales of Xiaomi, the smartphone-maker he founded in 2010, would surpass those of Gree, a manufacturer of air-conditioners with government roots. To make things interesting Dong Mingzhu, an entrepreneur and Gree’s chairwoman with whom Mr Lei had shared an award, bet him 1bn yuan ($148m today) that her company’s turnover would stay ahead. Mr Lei accepted. Since March 19th, when Xiaomi posted revenues of 175bn yuan in 2018, corporate China has awaited the figure from Gree. On April 28th the verdict was in: it made 200bn yuan. Mr Lei was out of the money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bet looked bold for Mr Lei in 2013. Xiaomi was then making a quarter of Gree’s 120bn yuan in annual sales. The “Apple of the East”, as it was dubbed, represented a new sort of Chinese company: market-driven and spunky, not state-led and stodgy; online instead of bricks and mortar; relying on digital technology rather than mechanical engineering. By mid-2018 Xiaomi’s revenue neared 90% of Gree’s (see chart). When the firm floated on the Hong Kong stock exchange last July it was valued at $54bn. It has become the fourth-most-valuable Chinese brand, according to Brand&lt;small&gt;Z&lt;/small&gt;, a consultancy; Gree is 29th. Ms Dong herself suggested that the wager was meaningless given how different Gree and Xiaomi were.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_WBC817.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190504_WBC817.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190504_WBC817.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190504_WBC817.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190504_WBC817.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190504_WBC817.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190504_WBC817.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190504_WBC817.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190504_WBC817.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190504_WBC817.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In reality, the companies are not that dissimilar—and growing less so as China’s economy modernises. Both have boomed thanks to swelling Chinese disposable incomes. The fiercely independent Ms Dong has repeated publicly that her firm must fight for customers just as private ones like Xiaomi do. In April Gree’s largest shareholder, a regulator overseeing state-owned enterprises, said it would sell most of its 18% stake. To build an ecosystem of devices controlled by his mobile phones, Mr Lei relies on closeness to China’s manufacturing heartland, Gree’s home.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They face similar challenges, too. The competition in their core markets is stiff. Xiaomi’s margins from low-cost phones are wafer-thin. Gree has lost share of Chinese air-con sales to rivals such as Haier and Midea, which are introducing more high-tech models. Xiaomi and Gree have both taken a punt on changing their original business models. Gree is selling more online. Xiaomi is opening more physical stores. To keep up with rapidly changing consumer tastes, Gree has moved into smart home appliances, as well as low-emission vehicles and chip design—areas in which Xiaomi now does business, too. Ms Dong now makes smartphones, and Mr Lei has a line of air-conditioners. Whether or not he makes good on it—gambling is outlawed on the mainland—the bet highlights the changing face of China Inc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Business&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;The billion-yuan bet&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 21:06:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump is not the first president to fight subpoenas]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/02/donald-trump-is-not-the-first-president-to-fight-subpoenas]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_usp001_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;N 1924 A&lt;/small&gt; Senate committee investigating the Teapot Dome bribery scandal issued a subpoena to Mal Daugherty, a bank president and brother of Harry Daugherty, who would soon resign as attorney-general. When Mal failed to appear the Senate dispatched its deputy sergeant-at-arms to Ohio to arrest him. Daugherty challenged his arrest, arguing that the Senate had exceeded its authority. The Supreme Court disagreed. Not only can Congress compel testimony essential to “a legislative function”; “it is to be presumed” that congressional investigations are intended “to aid [Congress] in legislating,” and “it is not a valid objection to such investigation that it might disclose wrongdoing or crime by a public officer.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump has sued two banks to stop them complying with House subpoenas (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/02/donald-trump-sues-deutsche-bank-and-capital-one&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;), and asked a federal court to block another to an accounting firm used by the Trump Organisation. He has vowed to fight one subpoena issued to Don McGahn, a former White House counsel, and has ordered an official who oversaw White House security clearances not to comply with another. More subpoenas may soon follow. The House Ways and Means Committee wants Mr Trump’s tax returns, which he has declined to turn over to them. The House Judiciary Committee may find William Barr, Mr Trump’s attorney-general, to be in contempt of Congress for ignoring a subpoena demanding the unredacted Mueller report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As that example suggests, congressional subpoenas are not all-powerful. Various presidents have fought them for different reasons. The usual levers brought to bear against private citizens who ignore subpoenas—fines and imprisonment—are harder to use against executive-branch officials. And congressional oversight, says Andrew Wright, an associate counsel to Barack Obama who is now a partner with &lt;small&gt;K&amp;amp;L&lt;/small&gt; Gates, a law firm, “is a quasi-political, quasi-legal process” that usually resists quick resolution. This does not mean that Mr Trump—who has said that “we’re fighting all the subpoenas” because the House Democrats issuing them “aren’t, like, impartial people”—can simply ignore them, merely that this fight may have a political rather than a legal resolution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Congress can charge people who ignore subpoenas with contempt, which requires a majority vote in a single chamber. Enforcing that charge is trickier. The days of apprehension by the sergeant-at-arms followed by detention are over; that power has not been used since 1935, when a Hoover administration official was held at the Willard hotel. Contempt of Congress has been a federal crime since 1857, but Mr Barr is unlikely to approve prosecuting either his boss or anyone who was following his boss’s orders, including himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That leaves civil contempt as a possible legal avenue. Congress can ask a federal court to compel obedience to a subpoena. This can take a while. In October 2011 Eric Holder, Barack Obama’s attorney-general, received a congressional subpoena. Mr Obama tried to block it by declaring executive privilege, in June 2012. A court rejected Mr Obama’s blanket claim of privilege, but not until January 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current standoff may finish faster, for two reasons. First, many of the justiciability concerns that took courts time to work through during the Obama and Bush administrations have been resolved. And second, as Stephen Vladeck, a law professor at the University of Texas, explains, Mr Trump’s statement of blanket refusal “suggests that case-specific objections are post-hoc rationalisations”, which courts may be inclined to swiftly reject.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But legal battles still take some time to adjudicate. That may annoy Democrats but suit Mr Trump perfectly. His supporters prize his pugnacity, and he prefers table-pounding defiance to the intricacies of legal compromise. Also, political salience fades over time. He may reckon that if he loses in court, the public will have moved on to the next outrage. And congressional subpoenas expire when the current Congress does, making a successful play for time a victory, of sorts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;United States&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;An oversight&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 21:06:18 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Gavin Williamson is sacked as defence secretary for leaking Britain’s Huawei plans]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/02/gavin-williamson-is-sacked-as-defence-secretary-for-leaking-britains-huawei-plans]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_brp003.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;L&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;EAKS IN WESTMINSTER&lt;/small&gt; are common. Leaks from meetings of the National Security Council &lt;small&gt;(NSC),&lt;/small&gt; which include cabinet ministers, generals and an array of spooks, are not. When details of Theresa May’s decision to allow Huawei, a Chinese telecoms group, to build next-generation infrastructure in Britain appeared in the &lt;em &gt;Daily Telegraph&lt;/em&gt; on April 24th, an inquiry was duly launched. It took barely a week to find its man. The supposed mole? Gavin Williamson, the defence secretary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite swearing his innocence (“on my children’s lives”), Mr Williamson was sacked by Mrs May on May 1st. Her letter to him was brutal. There was “compelling” evidence that he had leaked details of the meeting. No other “credible” story existed. Mr Williamson has been replaced by Penny Mordaunt, previously secretary for international development, who also attended the fateful meeting but managed to keep her mouth shut. She in turn is replaced by the ambitious Rory Stewart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mrs May has now lost ten cabinet members in less than three years in office. Mr Williamson was liked by defence chiefs for winning more money for his department, but became a tabloid figure of fun after squeaking that Russia should “go away and shut up”. As a former chief whip he gave the prime minister valuable insight into the unhappy mood of the party. Yet when the inquiry fingered him, Mrs May wasted no time. She has not revealed the evidence against him and calls the matter “closed”. But opposition parties are calling for a criminal investigation; Mr Williamson himself says the police would clear him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The subject matter of the leak was sensitive. America has for months been lobbying its allies to freeze Huawei out of their 5&lt;small&gt;G&lt;/small&gt; telecoms networks, arguing that China could use the firm’s gear for spying or sabotage. It has had only mixed success. Australia banned Huawei outright. New Zealand turned down a request from a local firm to use Huawei’s gear. But Germany has pushed back, as has the European Union. Britain’s decision to give Huawei a limited role makes it the most prominent refusenik. Its signals-intelligence agency, &lt;small&gt;GCHQ&lt;/small&gt;, works hand-in-glove with its American counterpart, the National Security Agency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America has said it may cut back intelligence-sharing with countries that ignore its warnings. That is probably bluster: if nothing else, Britain’s geographical location makes it too useful to simply abandon (many transatlantic internet cables come ashore in Britain). Instead, the Americans may hope that by keeping up the pressure they may persuade a future government to reverse the decision. The &lt;small&gt;NSC&lt;/small&gt; was split on whether to allow Huawei in. Mrs May ignored its more hawkish members and gave the green light. But she is unlikely to be prime minister for much longer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several likely candidates for her job, including Ms Mordaunt, Jeremy Hunt, the foreign secretary, and Sajid Javid, the home secretary, were among those who voted no—as did Mr Williamson. Unlike the rest of this small cast, Mr Williamson now has little chance of having another say.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Britain&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Leak, plugged&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 21:06:17 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Britain’s super-rich are Corbyn-proofing their finances]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/02/britains-super-rich-are-corbyn-proofing-their-finances]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_BRD001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;J&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;EREMY CORBYN&lt;/small&gt; may have it in for tax havens, but they are not all cursing the Labour leader. Well-heeled types worried about the prospect of a Corbyn-led government have been buying property on Guernsey with a view to moving to the island, attracted by its flat 20% income-tax rate and lack of capital-gains or inheritance taxes. Demand for homes there is buoyant, and Jo Stoddart of Locate Guernsey, an investment-promotion agency, says queasiness over Mr Corbyn is one of the main reasons.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The opposition leader makes no secret of his disdain for the rich. The real divide in Britain, he said recently, is not over Brexit but “between the many, who do the work, create the wealth and pay their taxes, and the few, who set the rules, reap the rewards and dodge their taxes.” The super-rich, he has warned, are “on borrowed time”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Small wonder, then, that plutocrats are seeking advisers’ counsel—and increasingly taking action—to keep their incomes, mansions and pensions out of Labour’s clutches. “How to Corbyn-proof your wealth”, an event held in London in February by an investors’ club, sold out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bookmakers offer odds as short as 3/1 on Mr Corbyn becoming the next prime minister. If that happened, says the chief executive of a &lt;small&gt;FTSE&lt;/small&gt; 100 company, the rich would “take all the money offshore, wait for the economy to crash, and come back and get richer.” Private-client advisers have warned of Britain’s multi-millionaires moving up to £1trn ($1.3trn) out of the country. But the “mass affluent”, those with liquid assets in the hundreds of thousands, also have cause to fret.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such fears have fluctuated in line with recent political turmoil. Wealth advisers agree that clients worry more about Mr Corbyn than Brexit—though the two are linked, as some fear a disorderly Brexit precisely because it could usher in a Labour government. Iain Tait of London &amp;amp; Capital, who advises dozens of rich families, says anxiety about Labour has reached its highest point yet in the past couple of months. When clients of Saunderson House, a wealth manager, were asked in October about the biggest threat to their finances, the most likely answer, mentioned by 42%, was a change of government. The number would almost certainly be higher now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The worries fall into three categories. The first concerns existing tax and pension arrangements. Labour is likely to target pension tax relief for high earners. On income tax, it has promised to reintroduce the 50% rate on earnings over £123,000 (rather than £150,000) and add a 45% rate that kicks in at £80,000. It is likely to reverse the Tories’ cuts to capital-gains tax. And it is expected to tighten the inheritance-tax regime, possibly by reducing or removing allowances for those giving to discretionary trusts or handing property or gifts to relatives. To cap it all, Labour promises to levy &lt;small&gt;VAT&lt;/small&gt; on private-school fees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second area is brand new taxes. Labour hopes to raise almost £5bn a year from a new financial-transactions levy. This would cream 0.2% off every transaction executed by financial firms. Some hedge funds are reportedly considering moving overseas in response. The bigger worry is the possibility of a wealth tax on assets, perhaps focused on high-value homes, to help fund social care. In 2012 John McDonnell, who has since become shadow chancellor, backed a proposal for a one-off, 20% wealth tax to help reduce government debt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The third category—and the biggest bogeyman—is the spectre of capital controls, measures to restrict the flow of capital in and out of the country, in the event of severe economic turbulence. Labour has repeatedly denied it would consider such a measure, last seen in Britain in the late 1970s. Even Mr Corbyn’s critics see it as a long shot. Nevertheless, contingency plans are being put in place. A year ago, says Mr Tait, it would have seemed “ludicrous” to be mulling measures to protect against capital controls. Yet clients raised the issue in “around half” the meetings he attended in the run-up to Easter. As an insurance policy, some have arranged for custody of their investment accounts (used to buy and sell securities) to be moved to the Channel Islands or Switzerland. Changing the jurisdiction in which accounts are booked is all about “asset access”, not tax, says Mr Tait.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a property-based wealth tax in mind, some rich folk are accelerating the transfer of homes to children. “They might have done this anyway when the kids were in their 20s. Now they’re doing it in their teens,” says one adviser, who has “dozens” of clients who have opted to speed up handovers. Some are also using up tax-free pension allowances, or vesting tax-free cash, earlier than required, for fear of such benefits evaporating under Labour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;Sunny places for gloomy people&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;A smaller number are considering moving offshore. Rather than emigrating now, most of these Jeremiahs are considering buying foreign residence permits to hold alongside their British passports, in order to be well placed to hop abroad if things turn nasty. Advisers say they are looking not only at obvious places like Monaco and the Channel Islands but also at &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; countries that have become friendlier to rich foreigners, such as Portugal (where a “golden visa” can be bought for €500,000, or $561,000) and Italy (where income from abroad can be taxed at a flat €100,000).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among those tempted to up sticks are resident “non-doms”: foreigners who live in Britain but declare their domicile as elsewhere to avoid tax on their non-British income. The Tories took away some of their privileges in 2016, but the non-doms are still handled fairly generously for up to 15 years. The threat of a Corbyn government, though, is leading some who were wavering to go elsewhere. Another wealth adviser has Swedish and French clients who are returning home. “Sweden and France, those well-known tax havens!” he guffaws.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were Britain’s 90,000 or so non-doms to leave, many Corbynistas might say good riddance. Some Labour strategists believe the public would welcome a falling-out with the super-rich. Mr Corbyn has long accused them of dodging tax and contributing little to the economy. But non-doms paid a not-so-paltry £9.4bn in tax—equivalent to a third of the transport budget—in the year to April 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr McDonnell’s team dismisses the bleating from Belgravia as alarmist. Fears over a wealth tax are as misplaced as those concerning capital controls, aides say. Yes, income tax will rise, but to nowhere near the rates of the 1970s. Mr McDonnell may have an avowedly Marxist past, but he has been on a charm offensive in the City, assuring moneymen he has nothing up the sleeves of his branch-manager suit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, when it comes to squeezing the rich there is less to separate the two main parties than the Tories admit. As well as turning the screws on non-doms, the Conservatives have cut high-earners’ tax-free pension allowances and are mulling an inheritance-tax grab. The chancellor, Philip Hammond, has warned that taxes must rise to fund an ageing population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, tone matters, and there is a difference between measured tax increases and what looks to some like anti-capitalist bloodlust. Mr Corbyn has said he is “coming for” the rich. Some of Labour’s plans suggest a taste for confiscation. The party wants to nationalise several industries, including water, for which it is considering basing compensation for investors on “book” value—currently a third of the industry’s market value—or even less. A plan to snatch 10% of shares in big British firms and give them to workers and the state has nauseated many business leaders. “The rich are prepared for higher taxes,” says Bobby Vedral of Macro Eagle, an advisory business, “but not for expropriation.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Vedral caused a ruckus in 2017 when he predicted a Britain led by Mr Corbyn would be like “Cuba without the sun”. That is unfair—but ever more of the monied seem unwilling to take any chances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Britain&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;The pips squeak again&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 21:06:16 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg wants to build WeChat for the West]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/02/mark-zuckerberg-wants-to-build-wechat-for-the-west]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_wbp001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;N HIS SPARE&lt;/small&gt; time Mark Zuckerberg likes to run. In 2016 Facebook’s boss pledged to cover 365 miles (587km) that year and, ever the overachiever, completed the challenge by July. He does not practise martial arts, but his almost discomfiting poise could lead you to mistake him for a master of something like aikido. That would be appropriate, for in his professional life Mr Zuckerberg is trying to turn his opponents’ energy against them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When in early March he announced that Facebook would follow a “privacy-focused vision for social networking”, complete with encrypted messages that even the firm cannot peer into, observers interpreted this as a defensive move. Some discerned a belated response to outrage over privacy abuses on the world’s largest social network. Others saw the plan to knit together its instant-messaging services, chiefly Messenger and WhatsApp, as a way to make the company harder to break up, as some American politicians demand. Others still spied a ruse to escape liability for violent user content, now that Facebook would no longer be able to read any of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All three rationales probably played a part. Yet the firm’s “privacy pivot” is perhaps better seen as an aikido-like redirection of detractors’ momentum. Mr Zuckerberg’s speech at his firm’s annual developer conference in San Jose on April 30th suggested as much. Far from retreating, he is limbering up for a new contest—to reinvent social networking, this time around messaging. “The future is private,” he declared grandiosely. Though he might not admit it in public, he seems keen to turn Facebook into a Western version of WeChat, the Chinese messaging app whose array of mobile services, from payments to filing court paperwork, has made it ubiquitous in China—even if his recent pledge to store user information only in countries that respect the rule of law is an implicit admission that he has given up on the Chinese market, where Communist minders insist that Western firms must keep all data locally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;Older. And wiser?&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Facebook’s core business is maturing, as its boss clearly sees. Its operating margins—42%, excluding $3bn set aside to cover an expected fine by America’s Federal Trade Commission for privacy violations—remain the envy of the tech world (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/02/american-technology-firms-mixed-results&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;). In the latest quarter revenue grew by 26% compared with the previous year, exceeding $15bn. But user growth is slowing. In some rich countries, especially European ones, it is flat. The young prefer social media which are more “intimate” and “ephemeral”, like Snapchat, which pioneered “stories”, messages and pictures that disappear after 24 hours—and which Facebook aped. More than 500m users of Instagram, Messenger and WhatsApp now post stories every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Zuckerberg expects migration from the online “town square” to a digital “living room” to continue; stories may soon outnumber posts on Facebook’s newsfeed. The plan is to build it around WhatsApp, which already offers secure texting. It would let users find each other, pay digital and offline shopkeepers, or purchase a cornucopia of online services—perhaps one day using Facebook’s own currency. In time, the thinking goes, it may become as indispensable to Westerners as WeChat is in China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some elements of the new platform already exist; WhatsApp is testing a payment service in India. Others, such as new shopping features on Instagram, were launched in San Jose. All this falls short of a full-blown business plan. But the contours of Mr Zuckerberg’s vision are taking shape. The 34-year-old is proceeding more cautiously than in Facebook’s early years, when he was guided by the now infamous injunction to “move fast and break things”—but no less deliberately.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is just as well, for “platform shifts” are tricky. Microsoft did not see smartphones coming and Facebook itself almost missed the rise of mobile apps. To succeed, it must clear a number of hurdles. The first is technical. Facebook wants an Instagram user to be able to send a note directly to a friend on WhatsApp. Creating a common phone book for these services, with a combined total of 2.7bn users and different source codes, presents a knotty problem for programmers. Chris Cox, one of Mr Zuckerberg’s top lieutenants, is rumoured to have left the company in March because he did not think it could be done (this week Mr Cox attributed his departure to “artistic differences” with his boss).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second challenge is economic. WeChat could become the platform of choice on smartphones because China had no dominant app stores. Facebook must contend with incumbents such as Apple and Google. Since you can’t sell microtargeted adverts against encrypted messages your algorithms cannot see, the new platform will need a fresh way to make money. For all its ubiquity, WeChat is no cash cow (Tencent, its owner, makes most of its revenue from online games). Maintaining Facebook’s fat margins would require new revenue sources, such as charging businesses to contact users or taking a cut of any purchases, as credit-card issuers do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, there are the entwined issues of privacy and competition. Mr Zuckerberg accepts that a lot of people dismiss Facebook’s sincerity here—his recent article in the &lt;em &gt;Washington Post&lt;/em&gt;, imploring governments to regulate social media, notwithstanding. It will continue to collect plenty of data. Integrating these, and the underlying apps, could in turn enable Facebook to convert its dominance in public social networking into power over private messaging. This reminds seasoned competition regulators of Microsoft’s attempts to bundle its operating system with a web browser in the mid-1990s in a bid to control cyberspace. With the internet’s rise, the stakes today are bigger: no country wants one firm to become society’s de facto operating system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since its services cost nothing, Facebook says, it is not gouging users. It could argue that a single dominant social network is easier to police than lots of smaller ones and has greater financial and technical capacity to keep users safe from harmful content. And it would be a bulwark against WeChat, which might otherwise become a force outside China—bringing the Chinese surveillance state with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, Mr Zuckerberg’s &lt;em &gt;Washington Post&lt;/em&gt; article looks like a bid to broker a 21st-century version of the Kingsbury Commitment of 1913, when &lt;small&gt;AT&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;T&lt;/small&gt;, then America’s telephone monopoly, accepted government oversight and agreed to spin off some of its businesses in exchange for not being nationalised or broken up. The difference is that, unlike &lt;small&gt;AT&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;/small&gt;&lt;small&gt;T&lt;/small&gt;, Facebook’s reach extends beyond America and spans a growing range of industries, from advertising to finance. It must grapple with politicians, regulators and rivals. If enough opponents gang up at once, even the most gifted aikido master may struggle to fend them off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Finance and economics&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Mark Zuckerberg’s WeChat moment&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 20:06:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Struggling with style]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/02/struggling-with-style]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_WBD001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;S&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;UMMER’S ARRIVAL&lt;/small&gt; in the northern hemisphere brings with it a dilemma that plagues every office worker. What does a casual dress code mean in practice? The happy medium between looking like Kim Kardashian or Hagrid the giant is hard to pin down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Goldman Sachs has just implemented a “flexible dress code” although the executive memo noted gnomically that “casual dress is not appropriate every day”. Besuited corporate clients might not take kindly to investment-banking advice offered by someone wearing a tank top and ripped jeans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It makes sense that banking would be one of the last bastions to fall to the advance of casual workwear. You want the people who look after your money to appear sober and respectable. For similar reasons, bank headquarters have deliberately been built in a grandiose style to emphasise the institution’s financial solidity and historical roots. Depositors might hesitate about handing over their savings to people working under a railway arch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For men, the move to casual dress seems entirely positive. Few people will mourn the demise of the tie, a functionally useless garment that constricted male necks for a century. The tie’s origins date back to the 17th century, when mercenaries hired by Louis XIII of France wore a form of cravat. The modern version of the tie emerged in the 1920s and was popularised by Britain’s Edward VIII who, when not flirting with the Nazis, developed the Windsor knot. It became standard office wear for the next six decades. In the 1990s ties started to go out of fashion because technology titans and hedge-fund managers refused to wear them—and were rich enough to ignore social convention. Once, when Mark Zuckerberg, the founder of Facebook, was to meet a venture capitalist, he turned up wearing his pyjamas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The jacket, by contrast, is a much more useful garment, replete with pockets to house wallets, spectacle cases and travel passes (or, these days, mobile phones). So the default work garb for men, when meeting clients, is jacket, open-necked shirt and dark trousers (denim excluded).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On days without meetings, men can slob out in &lt;small&gt;T&lt;/small&gt;-shirts (though not too garish) and jeans, and no one will think the worse of them. Arriving in shorts or without socks is another matter entirely. But dressing in the morning is quick and easy. Steve Jobs was famous for wearing the same outfit—black polo neck, jeans and trainers—every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what works well for men does not translate as easily to women. Karl Stefanovic, an Australian television presenter, wore the same blue suit every day for a year and no one noticed. By contrast, his female co-presenters received constant remarks on their appearance. Even the Duchess of Cambridge, Kate Middleton, gets snarky comments when she wears the same clothes twice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women’s workwear seems to have become less formal over time. A survey by Euromonitor found that sales of women’s suits fell by 77% in America between 2007 and 2016. But many women worry that they will be judged as unprofessional (unlike their male colleagues) if their clothes are deemed to be too scruffy, or too revealing. It can also be hard choosing clothes that are suitable for both indoors and out. Air-conditioning systems in offices are often designed to suit the male metabolic rate, which can cope with colder temperatures than the female body. The result may be that women have to bring an extra layer to wear in the building.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for formal meetings, while men have abandoned the tie, many women feel obliged to wear high heels. These give some women a sense of empowerment and femininity (not to mention extra height). But in health terms, heels can seem like the Western equivalent of the ancient Chinese practice of foot-binding: bad for women’s feet, ankles and backs and designed to limit their mobility. Britain’s Parliament held a debate after a woman was sent home from her job as a receptionist for refusing to wear high heels (it was inconclusive).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Companies understandably want workers who deal with the public to look respectable. Workers shouldn’t wear clothes that wouldn’t be appropriate if visiting a prudish grandmother or a child’s teacher. And yet no one should be expected to turn up at the office as if dressed for a wedding. The most important item to bring to work is a dose of sartorial common sense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 20:06:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Indonesia plans to replace one unsuitable capital with another]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/02/indonesia-plans-to-replace-one-unsuitable-capital-with-another]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_ASP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;O EXPERIENCE THE&lt;/small&gt; true Jakarta, sit in a taxi for an hour, listening to the motorbikes rev and the horns honk, only to realise that you are no closer to your destination than when you set off. Indonesia’s capital, home to 30m people, is in a constant state of gridlock. Meetings are routinely missed; businessfolk often call in from the back seat of a stationary vehicle. Some policemen have started a sideline selling motorcade escorts. Fumes from the sea of cars add to the smog. Public transport offers little respite: a new underground service, decades in the building, already feels jam-packed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The traffic is the result of decades of rapid urbanisation coupled with neglect of infrastructure. It is not the city’s only failing. There is no real centre, just a vast concrete sprawl where highways and flyovers corral skyscrapers. Parks are a rarity. So are pavements—and the few there are are crowded with makeshift restaurants, forcing pedestrians onto the heaving roads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another big problem is water. Torrential rain falls for half the year, but rivers and drainage ditches are clogged with rubbish and swimming with untreated sewage. They overflow regularly, flooding much of the city. Only a third of residents have access to municipal water, so the rest drill wells to tap groundwater. As a result, Jakarta is sinking faster than any other city in the world, even as sea levels rise. Some neighbourhoods are dropping at a rate of 25cm a year. Researchers think that almost all the city’s coastal districts could be submerged in 30 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_ASM943.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190504_ASM943.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190504_ASM943.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190504_ASM943.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190504_ASM943.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190504_ASM943.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190504_ASM943.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190504_ASM943.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190504_ASM943.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190504_ASM943.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Small wonder, then, that the president, Joko Widodo, who is known as Jokowi, wants to move the capital. On April 29th Bambang Brodjonegoro, the planning minister, announced that the government will leave the island of Java, where Jakarta sits, although it is still considering where to go. The intention, in addition to escaping (and reducing) congestion in Jakarta, is to shrink regional inequalities. Indonesia is an archipelago of 13,000 or so islands, but Java generates about 58% of &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The relocation could take ten years. It is likely to face stern resistance, not least from Indonesia’s tycoons, who do not want to see the value of their Jakarta penthouses fall. Civil servants will probably object too, because the most likely new site for the capital is something of a backwater.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Palangkaraya is a city of 260,000 in the province of Central Kalimantan, part of the Indonesian portion of Borneo. Whereas Jakarta lacks greenery, Palangkaraya has it in abundance: the city is in the middle of the jungle. There is a titchy airport; the nearest seaport is a four-hour drive away, past an orangutan reserve. Much of the surrounding terrain is soft and swampy—not ideal for building skyscrapers. And when nearby peatlands burn, a toxic haze fills the air. Government officials may be sinking and choking in their new digs, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Asia&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;An extraordinary move&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2019 20:06:56 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>