<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[EU workers think about the Brexit exit]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/bartleby/2019/04/25/eu-workers-think-about-the-brexit-exit]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_BLP508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T15:17:37Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IF YOU live in Britain, and ever turn on the TV or read a paper, it has been hard to escape from Brexit in the last three years. It has been bad enough if you are British-born. But EU citizens who are working in the UK have faced added uncertainty about their future status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gartner, a research company, has conducted weekly polls of around 300 UK-based employees to see how they have been affected. The key week was towards the end of March when the official deadline for Brexit was scheduled (it has since been postponed twice). In that week, more than half of EU workers in British experienced disgust, anger and sadness. Those feelings have subsided a little since, but are still running at about 40% of EU workers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unsurprisingly, that has led EU workers to think about moving jobs. in the week starting March 7th, only 11% of them were doing so; by the week of April 8th that proportion had jumped to 24%. The proportion of footloose British-born workers saw a more modest rise from 15% to 21%. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The polling also suggests that all this Brexit uncertainty is bad for productivity as well. In the week of March 25th, the average employee spent almost an hour of their working day thinking about Brexit, with EU citizens hitting nearly 70 minutes. Since then that proportion has dropped a bit, although EU citizens still spent 47 minutes worrying about the issue. Never has national navel-gazing proved so fruitless. As the Eagles once sang&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know what&amp;#x27;s been on your mind&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You&amp;#x27;re afraid it&amp;#x27;s all been wasted time&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 26 Apr 2019 00:07:21 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A brief cultural history of the scream]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/04/25/a-brief-cultural-history-of-the-scream]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_BKP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T15:01:48Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I WAS walking along the road with two friends – the sun was setting,” Edvard Munch wrote in his diary in 1892. “Suddenly the sky turned blood red...there was blood and tongues of fire above the blue-black fjord and the city...I sensed an infinite scream passing through nature.” The scene inspired Munch’s best-known work, currently on display at the British Museum. “The Scream” exists in four different versions, each with thick, stark lines reverberating with a sound that can never be heard. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Robert Rosenblum, an art historian, has suggested that the image was inspired by a Peruvian mummy, buried with its hands clutching its face, which was exhibited at the Exposition Universelle in Paris in 1889. “Human Misery” (1888), a painting by Paul Gauguin, also drew on this particular mummy, as did his “D&amp;#x27;ou Venons Nous / Que Sommes Nous / Où Allons Nous” (1897). The frightened face recurs in Munch’s work, too. In the painting “Dead Mother and Child” (1901) a small boy stands by his mother’s corpse, his hands covering his ears; “Inheritance” (1916) bears similar traces of “The Scream”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Munch’s “face distorted by despair” has permeated popular culture. The image inspired the GhostFace mask in “Scream”, a horror film franchise, which exaggerates the ghoulish and sinister qualities of the painting. In the poster for “Home Alone” (1990), a young Macaulay Culkin assumes a similar facial expression. In the internet age, the artwork has influenced the design of the scream emoji.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why does the act of screaming fascinate viewers and audiences? Screams are disturbing, an explosion of feeling that is not verbal yet not quite nonsense. They are primal, involuntary reflexes that represent a loss of control. There are many, often contradictory, reasons to scream: fear, shock, pain and pleasure. All can be traced through art, literature and music.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arthur Janov, a psychologist, thought that screams could uncover repressed childhood trauma. The cover of his book (“The Primal Scream”, 1970) promised that “what I heard may change the nature of psychotherapy as it is now known – an eerie scream welling up from the depths of a young man”. His approach inspired John Lennon, whose screaming can be heard on the tracks “Mother” and “Well, Well, Well” on his first solo album; Yoko Ono’s music, too, features plenty of guttural sounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_BKP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190427_BKP507.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190427_BKP507.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190427_BKP507.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190427_BKP507.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190427_BKP507.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190427_BKP507.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190427_BKP507.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190427_BKP507.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190427_BKP507.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;A scream, at the beginning of a novel, jolts the reader awake. “Gravity’s Rainbow” (1973) opens as “a screaming comes across the sky”—that of a V2 rocket about to fall on London—whereby Thomas Pynchon instantly evokes the terrors of his wartime setting. When novels end with a scream, the effect is unsettling. Francis Spufford closes “Golden Hill” with the narrator remembering “how good it was,” at a pivotal moment, “to scream”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere, shrieks are imbued with philosophical depths. In the final scene of “King Lear”, Lear repeats “howl, howl, howl, howl”; his garbled scream of agony at the death of Cordelia has been reinterpreted in myriad ways by actors over the centuries. In Tennessee Williams’s short story “Miss Coynte of Greene”, the grandmother screams “like a peacock in heat” to attract the attention of her family. Abigail and her fellows in “The Crucible” (pictured, above) screech in unison as a form of manipulation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cinema is also famous for its screams. The most important scene of “Psycho” (1960, pictured, top), for Alfred Hitchcock, was that of Janet Leigh in the shower; her scream of terror harmonises with Bernard Herrmann’s jagged score. Steven Spielberg made actors scream as part of the audition process for “Jurassic Park” (1993). When he watched the tapes back at home at night, Ariana Richards’s cry jolted Mr Spielberg’s wife awake, and she ran to check her children were safe. He cast Ms Richards immediately. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some screams become motifs. The “Wilhelm Scream”, a stock sound effect created in 1951 for the film “Distant Drums”, has been used in over 389 films and TV series since. It features in “Star Wars: A New Hope” (1977) when a Stormtrooper falls to his death after being shot by Luke Skywalker, and several times in the Indiana Jones films. The tagline of “Alien” (1979), “In Space, No One Can Hear You Scream”, established both the film’s appreciation of science—sound waves do not travel well through space—as well as the vastness and isolation of the setting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A blood-curdling scream represents an extreme of emotion; it both excites and terrifies. When Rosa Klebb, the villain of “From Russia With Love” (1957), interrogated her victims, she “would watch the eyes in the face a few inches away from hers and breathe in the screams as if they were perfume”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 23:06:46 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Deutsche Bank and Commerzbank call off merger talks]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/04/25/deutsche-bank-and-commerzbank-call-off-merger-talks]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_FNP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;A&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;FTER SIX&lt;/small&gt; weeks of rumour, a progress report was due. Deutsche Bank, Germany’s biggest bank, had promised investors an update on merger discussions with its Frankfurt neighbour, Commerzbank, on April 26th, alongside its first-quarter earnings. The update came, unplanned, a day early. On April 25th the two banks said they had called off the talks, the announcement prompted by a Reuters report that negotiations were about to fail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pair said that a deal would not justify the “additional execution risks, restructuring costs and capital requirements associated with such a large-scale integration”. Outside the two banks and the German government, Commerzbank’s biggest shareholder with a 15% stake, plenty had reached that conclusion even before the banks said in mid-March that talks were under way and embarked on weeks of negotiation. Two troubled lenders looked unlikely to make one strong one. Deutsche eked out only a tiny profit in 2018, its first for four years, while Commerzbank has made paltry returns. Deutsche’s shares have been trading at about 25% of book value, Commerzbank’s at little more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though Commerzbank has done a lot of reconstructive work since taking over Dresdner Bank during the global financial crisis, Deutsche still resembles a building site. It is still attempting to integrate Postbank, a retail business it bought in 2008-10, tried to sell and then decided to keep. It has retreated in investment banking, especially trading, to focus on corporate clients, who it still believes need a strong European alternative to Wall Street firms. Even a combined entity, after deep cuts in costs, would have found it difficult to build profitability in an overcrowded domestic market in which the co-operative and public sectors are also strong competitors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what was the logic of a merger? There was some, if never enough. It would have created Germany’s biggest retail bank by some distance, with about a fifth of deposits in a highly fragmented market. It might have forced a faster digitisation of German retail banking, including branch closures—loudly opposed by trade unions at both banks while the talks were under way. Commerzbank’s deposit base would have brought Deutsche cheaper and more stable funding. It would have tilted Deutsche faster towards serving companies—notably by bringing more business from Germany’s &lt;em &gt;Mittelstand&lt;/em&gt;, the backbone of both Commerzbank’s revenues and the national economy. Given Europe’s lack of banks with the clout of America’s giants, domestic consolidation has long been seen as a stepping stone to creating continent-wide players, with economies of scale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the government, one attraction of a merger was that Commerzbank would then be sure not to fall into the hands of one of the foreign suitors with which it has been repeatedly linked. Even in the past few weeks, reports have surfaced of interest from Italy’s UniCredit, which already owns &lt;small&gt;HVB&lt;/small&gt;, a large Munich-based lender, and from &lt;small&gt;ING&lt;/small&gt;, of the Netherlands, which already has a successful branchless retail bank in Germany.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Deutsche ruled out, such rumours are unlikely to go away. Ironically, the failed talks may, through a bid for Commerzbank, hasten a cross-border deal. Deutsche’s situation is as dismal as ever. In a preview of its first-quarter earnings with the announcement that talks had failed, it said it had made only a puny €200m ($227m) or so in net profit, with corporate and investment-banking revenues down on a year earlier. Put away the drawing board, and get back to the building site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Finance and economics&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;It’s off&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 22:06:26 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why you should never start a trade war with an autocracy]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/27/why-you-should-never-start-a-trade-war-with-an-autocracy]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_GDC411_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-27T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 27th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;

&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190427_GD411_tradewar/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;E&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;CONOMISTS OFTEN&lt;/small&gt; argue that trade wars cannot be won. Yet they will be among the few beneficiaries from America’s barrage of tariffs. For decades, rich countries’ sound trade policies denied academics cases of tit-for-tat protectionism to study. But new American taxes on many goods from China and metals from everywhere have produced the data set of their dreams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;America’s government seems unfazed by the damage its tariffs do to the economy. One study by scholars at the Federal Reserve and Princeton and Columbia Universities found that the new levies have raised costs for consumers by $1.4bn per month.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;However, Donald Trump is devoted to his voters. And his trading rivals have retaliated where it hurts. A paper by Joseph Parilla and Max Bouchet of the Brookings Institution, a think-tank, estimated that 61% of jobs affected by retaliatory tariffs are in counties that voted for Mr Trump.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Is this a coincidence? If a country’s imports from America already come from mostly Republican areas, those regions will bear the brunt of a trade war. However, a new paper by Thiemo Fetzer and Carlo Schwarz of the University of Warwick finds that America’s rivals probably did consider politics when crafting their policies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To test if recent tariffs were politically motivated, the authors needed to compare them with alternatives that were not. They devised this benchmark by creating at random 1,000 hypothetical bundles of targeted goods for each trading partner, all worth the same as the actual trade facing tariffs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The authors then compared real-world policies with these alternatives. First, they assessed the political impact of each plan, by measuring how closely its targeted areas matched Republican gains when Mr Trump was elected. Next, they estimated how much each policy would harm a retaliating bloc’s own economy, by counting the share of its imports of the chosen goods that come from America. The more a country relies on one supplier, the more switching to a less efficient source is likely to hurt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The study found that the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; prioritised minimising such damage. Its tariffs deftly protected domestic consumers, causing less disruption than 99% of alternatives. The bloc targeted Trump voters as well—its tariffs matched the election of 2016 more closely than in 87% of simulations—but not at the cost of upsetting its own citizens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In contrast, China focused on punishing Trump voters. Its tariffs tracked the election better than 99% of alternatives. They also disrupted China’s own economy more than in 99% of simulations. Even among plans including soyabeans—one of China’s main imports, grown mostly in Republican areas—China’s policy was just slightly more politically targeted than similar options, but far worse for its economy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;China’s choice of tariffs seems designed to deter escalation at any cost. Only regimes with no voters to satisfy can run that risk. The lesson is clear: if you start a trade war, fight a democracy, not an autocracy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/20190427_GD411_tradewar/fixes.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190427_GD411_tradewar/fixes.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Graphic detail&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;You get what you give&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 20:07:07 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why presidential libraries are controversial]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/04/25/why-presidential-libraries-are-controversial]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_BLP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T11:04:29Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE BUILDING of Barack Obama’s presidential library in Chicago ought to be uncontroversial. Unlike many other such libraries, it will not be maintained by American taxpayers. The Obama Foundation, a non-profit organisation founded by the 44th president, will foot the bill for maintaining the building, overseeing its exhibits and running its events. But not all Chicagoans are thrilled by what the foundation has called a new “economic engine for the city”. A local pressure group, Protect Our Parks, has taken city authorities to court for its decision to grant 20 acres of land in Jackson Park, on Chicago’s south side, on a 99-year lease costing just $10. Indignant at this relinquishing of public space, the group calls the act an “illegal land grab”. If legal matters can be sorted out, the complex will open in 2021. It will not be a presidential library in the traditional sense of housing Mr Obama’s records. Instead, the foundation has formed a partnership with the National Archives and Records Association (NARA), a government agency, which will digitise them. The building will be part museum, part community centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The libraries use exhibitions and events to chart the lives of their respective presidents. Some contain recreations of the Oval Office. They also hold archives of documents from the presidents and their staffers and, in the cases of Lyndon B. Johnson and Nixon, recordings of conversations they had in office. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Presidential records (such as books, correspondence, memos and papers) were once considered the property of the office holder. As a result, many documents were poorly looked after, lost or destroyed. In 1941 Franklin D. Roosevelt opened the first presidential library and donated his records to the state. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Presidential libraries can take two forms. In some cases, presidents and their supporters run the libraries themselves (as was the case with Richard Nixon’s until 2007). This applies mainly to the records of presidents who served before Herbert Hoover, because the NARA refuses to fund them. For more recent presidents, maintenance is usually overseen by NARA, which also looks after on-site archives. The Presidential Libraries Act of 1955 stipulated that presidents could build a library using funds they raised themselves, with ownership (and maintenance costs) subsequently transferred to the state. In 1978 the Presidential Records Act transferred ownership of all records to the public, bolstering libraries’ archival offerings by imposing a legal duty on presidents and their staff to ensure records are not thrown away. Later, Congress required presidents to provide an endowment in proportion to the size of the library, to contribute to maintenance costs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The libraries have been a source of controversy before. Benjamin Hufbauer of the University of Louisville says they are tantamount to presidential publicity centres. Johnson paid close attention to his library’s attendance figures, reportedly suggesting that opening times be extended and doughnuts served to boost numbers. Some libraries have provoked ire with their selectivity. An exhibit at the Nixon library, when still privately owned by the Richard Nixon Foundation, implied that the uproar over the burgling of the offices of the Democratic National Committee in 1972 in an effort to steal campaign secrets—an event that Nixon tried to cover up and for which he was forced to resign—was actually an effort by Democrats to overturn his victory in the 1972 election. This version of the Watergate scandal was only redressed when the library came under public ownership. However, even under NARA stewardship libraries can be problematic. The Iran-Contra scandal was one of the biggest controversies of Ronald Reagan’s presidency, resulting in a congressional investigation and the indictment of a number of senior administration officials. Yet it went unmentioned by exhibitions in his library until 2011.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The libraries do, however, have some more practical benefits. Many consider them a boon for the local economy. Indeed, that may well be the reason why, despite NARA’s refusal to fund libraries for presidents preceding Hoover, local groups and states fund the libraries themselves. In 2018, 100 years after the death of Theodore Roosevelt, North Dakota’s governor unveiled an as-yet-unconfirmed plan to commit $50m of state funds, matched by $100m in private donations, to a library dedicated to the former president. What should be expected from President Donald Trump’s library? Mr Hufbauer would comment only on Mr Trump’s taste:  “He does seem to have a fondness for gold.” As for the legacy of the 45th president, the records will have to speak for themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 20:07:05 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China tries to calm jitters about the “Belt and Road” initiative]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/china/2019/04/25/china-tries-to-calm-jitters-about-the-belt-and-road-initiative]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/articles/20190427_cnp001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;C&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HINESE ENGINEERS&lt;/small&gt; are drilling their way through the green hills of Laos, clearing a path for a railway that one day may traverse South-East Asia. Each time they complete a tunnel—at least three times in the past month—they hold a brief ceremony, waving Chinese flags for the cameras. They are celebrating not just their engineering success but also the evidence before them that the Belt and Road Initiative (&lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;), China’s global infrastructure-building scheme, is making progress. The full railway is a long way off. Work has barely begun in Thailand, the next link. But the section in Laos should be in use by 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It will be a test of what many see as a big economic danger of the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;: that it will saddle poor countries with unmanageable debts. China insists that its tens of billions of dollars in loans and investments are fostering global prosperity—a message that it is sure to repeat to foreign leaders attending the second Belt and Road Forum, which takes place from April 25th to 27th in Beijing (pictured is a floral display marking the event). But worries about the cost of the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;, a project closely linked with President Xi Jinping’s foreign policy, have become widespread. Malaysia, Pakistan and Sierra Leone are among a growing list of countries that have delayed or scrapped China-led projects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are three main concerns about the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;’s financial consequences. The most extreme is that the scheme involves what is pithily described as “debt-trap diplomacy”. In this view, China is deliberately overloading weak countries with loans; when they buckle, it seizes their assets and influences their politics. This idea has featured in speeches by some American officials, including the vice-president, Mike Pence, who see &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; as an attempt to undermine America’s global influence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the investments funded by Chinese cash are not in China, so China has limited ability to grab assets when governments default. If it pushes too hard it may merely stoke antipathy. Instead, it usually responds by reducing the amount of money that debtors have to repay. Countries with longer records of lending to poor countries often do the same: the Paris Club of creditors was formed in 1956 to devise ways of reducing defaulters’ debt loads. The Centre for Global Development, a think-tank in Washington, has counted more than 80 cases between 2000 and 2017 in which China provided relief to its debtors overseas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An oft-cited example of China’s supposedly predatory approach involves Hambantota, a Sri Lankan port which has flopped commercially. In 2017 Sri Lanka handed control of the port to a state-owned Chinese company on a 99-year lease. But Deborah Brautigam of Johns Hopkins University says that of more than 3,000 China-financed projects that she and others have tracked, Hambantota is the only one that is used in support of the debt-trap theory. It is the exception, not the rule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What it lacks in malevolence, the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; may make up in clumsiness. This is the second concern: that China is lending to vulnerable states without sufficient caution. Take a group of 37 poor countries monitored by the &lt;small&gt;IMF&lt;/small&gt;. Loans from traditional bilateral lenders, including America and Japan, have declined from 7% of the debtors’ &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; to 2% over the past decade. Loans from China, by contrast, have soared from virtually nothing to 4%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is welcome that China is supporting hard-up nations. But its enthusiasm generates foolhardiness. David Dollar of the Brookings Institution in Washington has found that Chinese development lending appears indifferent to political and economic risks. The Centre for Global Development has identified eight countries drowning in red ink that could be further swamped by &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; projects (see chart). A report in December released by Peking University ranked 94 &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; countries based on measures such as the quality of their financial regulation and their openness to trade. Pakistan came second to last. That is awkward for China: Pakistan may receive as much as $60bn in &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; loans, which would make it the biggest recipient of all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is truth to claims that &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; credit can be ruinously expensive. Consider China Eximbank’s lending to Kenya for the Nairobi-Mombasa railway. Local reports say half the $3.6bn loan was priced 3.6 percentage points above a floating market interest-rate. That is high for a poor country. It is just one of many such loans by Eximbank, which said this week that its outstanding &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;-related credit was more than 1trn yuan, or nearly $150bn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;’s success will depend on whether Chinese lenders can tighten their procedures for assessing creditworthiness while making their loans more affordable. There are some promising signs. This week’s forum in Beijing is expected to stress the need for &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; debt to be sustainable. In the case of the railway in Laos, caution is already evident. The project involves $6bn of Chinese lending, which is about one-third of the &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; of Laos. So a joint venture has been created. It draws 70% of its capital from China and 30% from Laos. To fund its portion, Laos took a $465m loan from Eximbank. The loan was generous, according to local reports: it matures in 35 years at a 2.3% annual interest rate, well below the commercial price of such debt. Laos has five years before it has to begin making repayments. That is the kind of concession that it might have got from the World Bank. China may offer such generous terms more frequently. Last year it set up an agency to oversee its foreign aid, in part to turn the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; into a more co-ordinated development programme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this points to another concern that will be harder for China to deal with because it relates to the very nature of the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;: its sheer ambition. Potential benefits look impressive. A recent study by the World Bank concluded that &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; transportation projects could lift global &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; by 3%. That is larger than the benefits that are usually shown to be generated by free-trade agreements. It could yet bear out China’s notion that Westerners (save Donald Trump) just want to lower tariffs, whereas China is trying to build the roads that let trade happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This, though, is where the risks come in. The World Bank’s rosy analysis assumes that &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; projects are completed and work efficiently. The scale of the effort is a huge challenge, and such projects are a magnet for graft. Vast sums are being spent quickly in badly run places. The railway in Laos ought to make the landlocked country more accessible. But for it to prove effective, much more will be needed: better roads to link it to existing transport, new urban centres around the stations and freer trade with other countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China cannot achieve this alone, but its often overweening approach to the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; has alienated potential partners. America, India and Japan want little to do with it. One reason is that China is, in effect, asking others not only to sign up to its infrastructure plans but also to endorse Mr Xi’s worldview. It does not help that China reveals so little about its lending and that contracts go mainly to Chinese firms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some analysts in China have started to express unease. Economists at the Chinese Academy of Social Sciences, a think-tank, argued in a paper last year that the government must entice other countries to back &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; projects in order to share the risks. Otherwise, it could be China that finds itself trapped. Conservative estimates are that China will spend $1trn within the next decade on its monumental scheme—about as much as it holds today in American government bonds. Mr Xi would be wise not to let such an outlay turn sour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;China&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Seeds of suspicion&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 20:07:04 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A TV comedian-turned-politician wins a stunning victory in Ukraine]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/25/a-tv-comedian-turned-politician-wins-a-stunning-victory-in-ukraine]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_EUP001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;J&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;OKES ABOUT&lt;/small&gt; Ukraine’s newly elected president, Volodymyr Zelensky, come easily. He is, after all, a comedian. At times his campaign seemed too frivolous to be consequential. While Petro Poroshenko, the incumbent president, staged political rallies, Mr Zelensky could be found filming his popular &lt;small&gt;TV&lt;/small&gt; show, “Servant of the People”, in which he plays a schoolteacher who accidentally becomes president. His public announcement that he was fighting the election was enough of an afterthought that he forgot to tell his wife about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet Mr Zelensky’s victory in the second-round run-off election on April 21st, with 73% of the vote, is a serious achievement. In four months, he built the biggest majority since Ukraine’s independence in 1991, helped by votersʼ frustration with Mr Poroshenkoʼs chequered leadership and their hopes for a better future. While Mr Poroshenko ran a divisive and nationalistic campaign, Mr Zelensky, a native Russian-speaker of Jewish heritage hailing from Ukraine’s south-east, galvanised support from across the country. Ukrainian politicians have long exploited ethnic and linguistic divides, splitting the country into an “orange” west and a “blue” east. Mr Zelensky, whose name means “green”, carried all but one of 25 regions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although war with Russia is still simmering in the country’s east, the election was free, fair and peaceful. Civil society and independent media held politicians to account. Now, thanks to Mr Poroshenko’s prompt concession, Ukraine’s voters have removed a sitting president through the ballot box—a rarity in the region. Mr Zelensky celebrated the example it could set: “To all the countries of the former Soviet Union: look at us, everything is possible.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Zelensky’s improbable path to the presidency began in Krivoi Rog, a midsized industrial city. The son of a university professor and an engineer, he dreamed of studying international relations in Moscow or Kiev, but settled for law at the local university, where he became involved in a popular comedy contest. He spun his success on the show into a production company, became a household name and made a lot of money from producing and appearing in &lt;small&gt;TV&lt;/small&gt; programmes and films.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the election, being a celebrity outsider was an asset. Oligarchs control Ukraine’s main television channels, but Mr Zelensky’s fame helped bypass this barrier to entry. As a new face on the political stage, he appealed to voters who saw the promise of change after the 2014 revolution hijacked by the old elites, including Mr Poroshenko. At 41, he is too young to have participated in the theft by Ukraine’s political class of Soviet-era economic assets. His informality contrasts with the distance which most leaders in the former Soviet Union maintain between themselves and the voters. His first post-election message was a video posted on Instagram that begins with the grinning president-elect saying, “Heeeeyy everybody!” It has been watched 6m times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The presentation is undoubtedly appealing; it is the substance that will be Mr Zelensky’s main challenge. He has promised to maintain a pro-Western stance, to fight corruption and to end the war, but his course remains uncertain. Groups jockeying for influence include old friends from the entertainment world, shrewd advisers linked to powerful outside backers, and Western-oriented reformers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_EUM936_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190427_EUM936_0.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190427_EUM936_0.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190427_EUM936_0.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190427_EUM936_0.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190427_EUM936_0.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190427_EUM936_0.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190427_EUM936_0.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190427_EUM936_0.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190427_EUM936_0.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which has the upper hand will become clear only once he begins making appointments and proposing laws. Ukraine’s constitution gives the president responsibility for foreign and security policy, including picking the ministers of foreign affairs and defence, the heads of the intelligence service and of the military general staff, and the prosecutor-general. Among the policies that Mr Zelensky’s team is discussing are plans to strip immunity from &lt;small&gt;MP&lt;/small&gt;s and judges, to create a body to investigate financial crimes and to offer an amnesty for undeclared assets. Balazs Jarabik of the Carnegie Endowment for International Peace predicts that the new president will “try to build a state less preoccupied by ideology and more focused on offering people efficient services”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ukrainians tend to sour on their leaders quickly. Their most urgent demand, say the polls, is that Mr Zelensky lower utility prices—which lies outside the president’s prerogative and would violate the terms of the &lt;small&gt;IMF&lt;/small&gt; loan programme on which Ukraine’s economy depends. Public disappointment with the president is the subject of the second season of Mr Zelenskyʼs show, entitled “From Love to Impeachment”. As one aide says: “We know what can happen: we wrote all of this already.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To change the story, Mr Zelensky must overcome several adversaries. First is the Rada (parliament), which will remain hostile at least until elections this autumn. Mr Zelensky could try to force an early election, but since he has not yet built a party, he may prefer to wait. In the meantime, others are massing their forces against him. The current prime minister, Volodymyr Groysman, plans to form his own party. Mr Poroshenko will continue the fight. Pro-Russian parties, which won 16% of the vote in the first round of presidential elections, could unite and challenge Mr Zelensky in the east.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second is Russia, with which Ukraine remains in a stand-off. Prospects for resolving it are slim. Vladimir Putin can use his proxies in the Donbas region to test the new commander-in-chief’s mettle, and also has economic levers: even after five years of war, Russia remains Ukraine’s single largest trading partner. On April 24th, Mr Putin announced that Russia will allow Ukrainians living in the breakaway regions to receive Russian passports, a provocative move towards a de facto annexation of Ukrainian territory and a direct challenge to the new president. Both Mr Poroshenko and Mr Zelensky have called for an urgent &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt; security council meeting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Third, and most important, are Ukraine’s oligarchs. There is much speculation about Mr Zelensky’s links to Ihor Kolomoisky, whose &lt;small&gt;TV&lt;/small&gt; channel airs his shows. While both men deny ties beyond business, investigative journalists discovered that in recent years Mr Zelensky flew 13 times to Geneva and Tel Aviv, where Mr Kolomoisky has been living in exile since being accused of defrauding his bank, PrivatBank, of some $5bn. The two men also share cars, security guards and a lawyer. Days before the election, when Mr Zelensky seemed likely to win, a court in Kiev did Mr Kolomoisky a big favour by declaring the nationalisation of PrivatBank illegal; after Mr Zelensky’s victory, Mr Kolomoisky announced plans to return to Ukraine. Those moves may not be Mr Zelensky’s doing, but handling them will be his problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That points to the biggest risk of the Zelensky presidency: not that he turns out to be an oligarchic puppet or a Kremlin agent, but that he will not be strong enough to defend the progress that Ukraine has made against his powerful adversaries. The oligarchs will probably aim to weaken the presidency and concentrate power in the more easily controlled parliament. Mr Putin will seek to keep Ukraine from becoming a functioning democracy. Mr Zelensky will have to learn fast, with the cameras rolling and no second takes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Europe&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Ready for prime time?&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 20:07:03 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America wants to challenge rogue petrostates]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/04/25/america-wants-to-challenge-rogue-petrostates]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_FNP001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;A&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;MERICA HAS&lt;/small&gt; been a superpower for decades. As a superpower in global energy markets, however, it is barely an adolescent. As recently as 2015 it was illegal to export oil. Within ten years the shale boom has transformed it into the world’s biggest producer of crude. No longer must it tiptoe around regimes whose policies it detests but whose oil it craves. President Donald Trump touts an age of “energy dominance”. He has put its burgeoning energy prowess to the test with sanctions on Iran and Venezuela. But dreams of dominance are running into the realities of energy markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On April 22nd the American administration announced that no further waivers would be granted to countries importing oil from Iran. “We are going to zero,” declared Mike Pompeo, the secretary of state. Waivers to eight countries, granted in November, were due to expire on May 2nd. Even so, investors were shocked that no exceptions were allowed. According to the state department, Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates and America will help meet demand. But Brent crude, the international benchmark, quickly topped $74, the highest level in nearly six months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration is right to make to make a fuss about America’s oil boom. According to the International Energy Agency, by 2021 the country may be a net exporter of oil. This would be a stunning reversal. Not long ago, notes Amy Myers Jaffe of the Council on Foreign Relations, a think-tank, oil imports were the largest cause of America’s current-account deficit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it is wrong to think it can bring about dramatic change in Iran and Venezuela without risking dramatic spikes in petrol prices. (Those concerned about climate change might welcome expensive oil; Mr Trump is not one of those people.) America’s government does not control its oil industry. Oil firms are backed by investors whose interests do not necessarily align with those of the president. Nor can it control the world’s many buyers and sellers of crude. American production accounts for about 15% of global output, a striking increase from what it was but still a small share of total supply. Complicating matters, investors have struggled to anticipate the Trump administration’s actions. Rather than stabilise oil markets, America has been as likely to do the opposite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump announced last May that America would impose sanctions on Iran and withdraw from the deal on international oversight of its nuclear capacity signed during Barack Obama’s presidency—the “worst deal ever”, as Mr Trump liked to call it. He urged the Organisation of Petroleum Exporting Countries (&lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt;), privately and on Twitter, to boost production to help restrain oil prices. Saudi Arabia duly did so, increasing output by 600,000 barrels a day from June to November, when the sanctions were to take effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the last minute, however, Mr Trump announced that eight countries would be exempt from the waivers for six months—including China and India, the biggest importers of Iranian oil. Investors and Saudi Arabia were caught off guard. The kingdom requires oil at around $80 a barrel to meet its budgetary needs; in December Brent prices sank to $51. &lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt; and its allies scrambled to cut production and shore up prices. In December they said they would decrease output by 1.2m barrels a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next sanctions came in January, after opponents of Nicolás Maduro’s ruinous regime in Venezuela declared Juan Guaidó, the head of its national assembly, the legitimate leader. America recognised Mr Guaidó and unveiled sanctions to choke off the country’s oil company, Mr Maduro’s main source of cash. “America now appreciates that energy is a source of foreign-policy strength rather than a vulnerability,” says Meghan O’Sullivan, a former adviser to George W. Bush and a professor at Harvard University.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But using that strength effectively can be difficult. Sanctions on Iran and Venezuela have yet to produce the desired effect. Mr Maduro still clings to power. Iran has met none of Mr Trump’s demands. Its crude exports have fallen by about half since Mr Trump said America would withdraw from the nuclear deal last year, but they remained well above zero in March, at about 1.4m barrels a day, according to Kpler, a data firm. China, in particular, has continued to import Iranian oil (see chart). The announcement that waivers will expire seeks to change that. Countries that continue to import Iranian oil, the state department says, could be cut off from America’s banking system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_FNC769_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This manoeuvre is risky, says Helima Croft of &lt;small&gt;RBC&lt;/small&gt; Capital Markets, an investment bank. Iran’s foreign ministry is threatening to retaliate by closing the Strait of Hormuz, a major export channel for the region’s crude. With little left to lose, it may stop allowing international inspectors to monitor its nuclear programme. Oil markets, too, face uncertainty. Prices were already rising, because of plunging output in Venezuela and civil war looming in Libya. The state department has not said how soon America might impose sanctions on countries that continue to import Iranian oil. China may do so—an official from its foreign ministry declared that China “opposes the unilateral sanctions”. That could complicate a bilateral trade dispute that had looked close to resolution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of rigs drilling in America has risen since the start of the year, as the oil price has climbed. Yet American shale oil is mostly “light”. Refineries in America and elsewhere are thirsty for heavy crude, because Venezuela’s production of the stuff has dropped and demand for distillates made with it is strong. There is a “fundamental mismatch” between the type of crude the world increasingly wants and what America is pumping, says Bernadette Johnson of Drillinginfo, a research firm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much therefore depends on whether Saudi Arabia boosts production, as the Trump administration hopes. After last year’s flip-flops, it is unlikely to move fast. &lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt; and its partners have their next formal meeting in late June. Even if Saudi Arabia were to ramp up production quickly and dramatically, analysts debate how long that boost could be sustained. A recent bond prospectus for Saudi Aramco, the kingdom’s oil giant, disclosed that a famous oilfield is ready to sustain production of 3.8m barrels a day, about 25% less than analysts had assumed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neil Beveridge of Bernstein, a research firm, points out that &lt;small&gt;OPEC&lt;/small&gt;’s spare capacity could drop dangerously low as Iran’s production falls and Saudi Arabia works to ramp up. That would leave the oil price vulnerable to supply shocks—if fighting in Libya escalates, for instance. America, the energy adolescent, can certainly roil oil markets. But it is unable to control them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Finance and economics&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Crude tactics&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 20:07:02 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lyra McKee’s killing sparks revulsion with the “New IRA”]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/04/25/lyra-mckees-killing-sparks-revulsion-with-the-new-ira]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_BRP001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE SHOT&lt;/small&gt; that killed Lyra McKee, one of Northern Ireland’s most promising young journalists, was fired by a youth urged on by embittered ancients still convinced that Irish republicanism can prevail only through the barrel of a gun. Leaders of the so-called New &lt;small&gt;IRA,&lt;/small&gt; which has admitted responsibility, persuaded the unidentified killer that mainstream republicans had betrayed their followers by swapping violence for politics. Yet in provoking the murder, they have damaged their cause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The killing of Ms McKee, hit when rioting youths opened fire on police in Londonderry on April 18th, has caused shock waves. Her funeral in Belfast on April 24th was attended by the heads of the British and Irish governments, as well as Northern Irish political leaders, who made a rare show of unity after more than two years of bickering in which the region’s assembly has been suspended. Father Martin Magill, leading the service, received a standing ovation when he demanded of the politicians: “Why in God’s name does it take the death of a 29-year-old woman with her whole life in front of her to get to this point?” That she died on the eve of the anniversary of the Good Friday Agreement, which brought an end to three decades of sectarian Troubles in 1998, has only underlined what is at stake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one expects a return to violence of the scale seen in the Troubles, whatever Brexit or any other development may bring. By the time it disbanded in 1998 the &lt;small&gt;IRA&lt;/small&gt; had killed more than 1,700 people. Dissident republicans, who never accepted the peace, have since then killed fewer than 100. This is enough for the security services to rate their threat as “severe”. But the “micro-groups”, as Sinn Fein, the main republican party, dismisses them, lack the experience or skills to maintain an effective and sustained campaign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They are dangerous nonetheless. This has recently been illustrated twice in Derry, with Ms McKee’s killing and, in January, the detonation of a car bomb in a busy street following a warning of only 30 minutes. Dissident republicans also claimed responsibility for a number of parcel bombs posted to British addresses last month. The riot that Ms McKee was observing was sparked by police raids which gave troublemakers an excuse to blood young men in the arts of street warfare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So-called loyalist paramilitary groups represent a different sort of threat, still roaming the backstreets of Belfast but these days less interested in sectarian violence than everyday gangsterism. Since the end of the Troubles they have devoted themselves to lining their pockets through drug-dealing, loan-sharking and extortion in Protestant ghettoes. In January an east-Belfast man who had fallen foul of a loyalist organisation was murdered by a five-man gang who stabbed him in the back 11 times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the years the pattern has been that acts of terrorism which kill civilians cause widespread revulsion and lead to a dip in terrorist activity. Ms McKee’s killers have issued an apology, well aware that deaths like hers cost them public support. The Derry office of Saoradh, a political party supported by the New &lt;small&gt;IRA,&lt;/small&gt; was smeared with red handprints by protesters. “Not in our name” was painted beneath a local republican mural. Police said that by the end of the Easter weekend over 140 people had offered information on the killing, a “sea change” in a city that has historically been reluctant to talk. Many Derry doors which were once opened to dissidents may now be shut in their faces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Britain&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;A death in Derry&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 20:07:01 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Egypt’s economy thrills investors, but locals are struggling]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/04/25/egypts-economy-thrills-investors-but-locals-are-struggling]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_MAP001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE INVESTORS&lt;/small&gt; gathered at a posh Cairo restaurant were eager to pour money into an economy that, just three years ago, lacked the hard currency to import cooking oil. A revolution in 2011 (and a coup two years later) tipped Egypt into economic crisis. Investors and tourists fled. Growth was anaemic. Unemployment peaked at 13.2%. President Abdel-Fattah al-Sisi had to seek a $12bn loan from the &lt;small&gt;IMF&lt;/small&gt; in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since then, though, his government has followed what one executive admiringly calls “almost a caricature” of an &lt;small&gt;IMF&lt;/small&gt; programme. The state has raised electricity and fuel prices. This summer the (previously massively subsidised) official price of many types of petrol will be indexed to market rates. Quite a few people have been trimmed from subsidy rolls. A budget deficit that hit 12.5% of &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; in 2015-16 has fallen. Next year it is expected to be a manageable 7.5%. The current-account deficit, which bottomed out at $19.8bn three years ago, was $6bn last year (see chart). Investors call Egypt the world’s hottest emerging market. Bond sales are oversubscribed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the positive indicators, few Egyptians feel progress. The past few years have brought higher prices and stagnant wages. Mr Sisi has shown little sympathy for their distress. He dismissed complaints over a surge in the price of vegetables last year—then criticised Egyptians for being overweight. A new hint of discontent came earlier this month, when 89% of voters approved constitutional changes that let Mr Sisi stay in power until 2030, instead of 2022 under the previous charter. The result was a foregone conclusion, since his autocratic regime did not permit a “no” campaign. But turnout was just 44%. Sympathetic businessmen had to lure voters to the polls with boxes of food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_MAC771.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190427_MAC771.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190427_MAC771.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190427_MAC771.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190427_MAC771.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190427_MAC771.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190427_MAC771.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190427_MAC771.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190427_MAC771.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190427_MAC771.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For all the hot money flooding in, bricks-and-mortar investment is scarce. “I’m comfortable buying one-year paper,” says a trader from a big American firm. “Buying a factory would be a different story.” Inflows of foreign direct investment (&lt;small&gt;FDI&lt;/small&gt;) were $6.6bn in the first half of the current fiscal year, unchanged from the previous year and 11% lower than 2016-17. Net &lt;small&gt;FDI&lt;/small&gt; is down 35% over that two-year period. Much of it goes to hydrocarbons. Recent natural-gas discoveries have turned Egypt into a net exporter. Such investment boosts revenue, but creates few jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials insist that &lt;small&gt;FDI&lt;/small&gt; is coming—that it is always a lagging indicator. Trade tensions and uncertain growth forecasts have caused investment to fall around the world. Some firms had profits stuck in Egypt during the dollar shortages and are leery about coming back. “It takes time to rebuild that confidence,” says Razan Nasser of &lt;small&gt;HSBC&lt;/small&gt;, a bank. Though Egypt will not seek an extension when the &lt;small&gt;IMF&lt;/small&gt; scheme ends in November, most analysts think it will stick with its reforms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But sluggish investment also reflects the weakness of Egypt’s domestic market. Its size—almost 100m people, with 2.5m added annually—means it will always have robust demand for basic consumer goods. Last year both Coca-Cola and Pepsi announced $500m in investments. Mars, a confectionery giant, is opening two new production lines. Few Egyptians can afford products that would create better-paying jobs, however. “It’s a classic developing market where 20% of the population has 80% of the purchasing power,” says the head of a local business federation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take the car industry, which officials hope will be an engine of growth. Sales slumped after a devaluation in 2016 which halved the value of the pound. Even in a good year, though, only about 100,000 Egyptians can afford new cars. (Wealthy Saudi Arabia has one-quarter of Egypt’s population and sells about half a million.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of selling cars at home, Egypt wants to export them to other parts of Africa and the Middle East. The government plans to offer incentives for using domestic suppliers: firms that buy lots of locally made components could have 80% shaved off their customs bills. Nissan has agreed to produce 100,000 cars in Egypt each year with El Nasr Automotive, a state-run firm. But Egypt will have to compete with Morocco, which has invested heavily in infrastructure. Textile firms, another possible source of jobs, will struggle to undercut big players in Bangladesh and Vietnam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The improvement in Egypt’s current account comes entirely from travel and transfers. Tourism revenues more than doubled to $9.8bn (4% of &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt;) last year, while remittances grew by a fifth to $26.4bn. Both are important. Tourism employs one in ten workers. Hundreds of thousands of families rely on transfers. But the trade deficit in goods is getting wider. It hit $9.8bn in the first quarter of 2018-19, up $1bn from the previous year. Though the devaluation made Egyptian goods cheaper to export, it also made them more expensive to produce, because manufacturers depend on imports. Raw and intermediate goods make up 41% of Egypt’s import basket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After years of weak investment, there is little idle capacity at Egyptian factories. High interest rates mean local businesses cannot afford to borrow for expansion. In February the central bank cut the overnight lending rate by 100 basis points, to 16.75%. In March, however, the bank defied expectations and kept rates steady. The Ramadan holiday and a looming subsidy cut will bring higher inflation this summer, so further cuts are unlikely until autumn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is one final obstacle to growth: the institution where Mr Sisi spent most of his life. It is hard to quantify how much of Egypt’s economy is controlled by the army. Its budget is secret, its profits untaxed. But everyone agrees it is growing. The minister of military production, Muhammad al-Assar, said his revenues hit 11.6bn pounds last year, a 130% increase. It has a $2bn deal with a Chinese firm to manufacture solar panels and an agreement with a French pharmaceutical giant to make vaccines. When firms struggled to get hold of dollars, the army offered them a deal—all the foreign currency you need, in exchange for a share of your company. Several executives tell a version of the same joke: “There are two kinds of successful businesses in Egypt, those run by the military, and those that will soon be run by the military.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials like to contrast Egypt’s recent progress with the dark days after 2011. Take a slightly longer view, though, and it looks like a reversion to the norm. Before the revolution Egypt posted healthy growth rates and manageable deficits. It was also a poor country with a weak industrial base, low wages—and a president out of touch with the struggles of his people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Middle East and Africa&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Running to stand still&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 20:07:00 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>