<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Is Donald Trump preparing pardons for troops accused of war crimes?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/21/is-donald-trump-preparing-pardons-for-troops-accused-of-war-crimes]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_USP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-21T19:38:45Z&quot;&gt;May 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PRESIDENT DONALD TRUMP is reported to be considering a Memorial Day pardon for a number of American troops accused of killing civilians in Iraq and Afghanistan. As so often happens with Mr Trump, the cases appear to have come to his attention via Fox News. The accused troops have been championed by hosts including Pete Hegseth, himself an Afghan and Iraq war vet, as “men who went into the most dangerous places on earth with a job to defend us and made tough calls on a moment&amp;#x27;s notice.” This is familiar framing for Fox: lawyer versus warrior, activist versus cop, political correctness over the hard facts of a kill-or-be-killed world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iraq and Afghanistan were indeed environments in which combatants were hard-pressed to distinguish snipers from a bystanders, or commuters from car bombers, and had to make decisions fast. But most of the cases that may be under review by Mr Trump are not based on prosecutors second-guessing warriors from a place of safety. Rather, they are based on the testimonies of their comrades-in-arms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most prominent alleged defendant is Edward Gallagher, a decorated Navy SEAL platoon leader accused of killing an Islamic State prisoner during the siege of Mosul of 2017. He faces a court-martial later this month. The case against him is built on testimony from fellow SEALS, who say he also randomly gunned down civilians and threatened them. Clint Lorance, an Army lieutenant in Afghanistan who is serving a 19-year sentence for his role in the killing of two unarmed Afghans in 2012, was also denounced by men under his command, who said he gave them orders to shoot civilians they didn&amp;#x27;t think were a threat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The defenders of these men and the other accused offer justifications for why their men testified against them. Mr Gallagher&amp;#x27;s lawyer, for example, says that the men were malcontents who had been chewed out as &amp;quot;pussies&amp;quot; by their tough leader. Scapegoating, questionable informants, and stitch-ups cannot be ruled out in the military justice system any more than they can be in the civilian one. But most veterans find these scenarios far-fetched. Units are tight-knit. Grumbling against a leader may be common, but it is almost unheard of for a leader to be so unpopular his men would concoct a story against him—especially when he erred on the side of being too aggressive. &amp;quot;A platoon leader who is willing to loosen the reins a little and allow his subordinates to aggressively pursue the enemy will generally be a pretty popular guy,&amp;quot; commented one Afghan vet about Mr Lorance on Task and Purpose, a popular military blog.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To pardon men accused by their fellow soldiers and then convicted could cause grave damage to the military justice system and America’s standing. It is already extremely difficult for a prosecutor to reconstruct a shooting incident in a war zone and prove beyond a reasonable doubt that the shooter acted maliciously and not in reasonable fear of his or her life. Only the most egregious offenders, those whose actions were dreadful enough to have shocked their own comrades, come to trial. If even the baddest of bad apples get a pardon, why would anyone come forward? What hope does the US military justice system have of deterring war crimes in the first place?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many prominent former officers are horrified. General Barry McCaffrey, a long-time Trump critic, says circumventing military justice gives a &amp;quot;terrible signal”. Even some Trump allies, like Dan Crenshaw, a Republican Congressman and former SEAL, says a pardon should only be considered after evidence is produced in court.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;American commanders have long grappled with the damage civilian casualties did to missions that depended on winning the trust and cooperation of Iraqis and Afghans. In Iraq, for example, American and other foreign forces were responsible for perhaps 10-15% of the approximately 180-200,000 civilian deaths logged by the Iraq Body Count, an NGO. The vast majority of those were probably misjudgements or accidental killings, not deliberate murders of non-combatants. But your correspondent, who lived in Baghdad from 2003 to 2007, found that while Iraqis were statistically in greater danger from militias and insurgents, they often had a particular horror of the Americans, an alien force that could swat out their family&amp;#x27;s lives for a moment&amp;#x27;s inattention or impatience in traffic. Generals like David Petraeus, former head of the Central Intelligence Agency and America’s former commander in Afghanistan, regularly implored the troops to err on the side of caution when it came to opening fire. Critics of Mr Trump’s mooted pardon say it sends a signal to both American troops and the countries that might host them that America is not so worried about civilian deaths after all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But with Iraq and increasingly Afghanistan widely seen as failures, Americans are less concerned about the military&amp;#x27;s readiness to fight counterinsurgency wars. Some on the right treat the mere suggestion of war crimes as an insult to the American warrior. The left tends to see the crime in the war itself, not the fine details of the waging. Americans who care about a more restrained military, even if that also means a more effective military, may be thin on the ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 05:40:36 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A political dynast is favoured to be Japan’s next prime minister]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/21/a-political-dynast-is-favoured-to-be-japans-next-prime-minister]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_asp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-21T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;GLANCE AT THE members of the Diet and this much is clear: Japanese politics is a business for old men. The average age of a member of parliament hovers at around 55, and prime ministers tend to be even older than that. So it is striking that people are talking about a 38-year-old, Shinjiro Koizumi (still a man, of course), as a potential successor to Shinzo Abe, the incumbent prime minister, who must step down by 2021 according to the rules of the ruling Liberal Democratic Party (LDP).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Koizumi is the son of a prominent former LDP prime minister, and, like many MPs, won the seat his father vacated when he retired from politics. In the decade since he was elected, however, he has made a name for himself in his own right. He has charisma, is a good orator and is unusually candid; he cites JFK, whose portrait adorns his walls, as an inspiration because he was an idealist who “talked to people not the media”. It doesn’t hurt that Mr Koizumi is fodder for glossy magazines thanks to his film-star looks (his brother is an actor).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Koizumi has been trying to show he has substance, not just star appeal, even though he has never had a job in the cabinet. His most important role in the government to date has been monitoring the reconstruction effort after the Tohoku earthquake in 2011—a task he is said to have done well. He is also an enthusiastic advocate of reforming health care and pensions, a step he says might help Japan get over its gloom about its ageing and shrinking population. He speaks of transferring resources from the old to the young, by making people work longer, for example, and by making child-rearing easier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He earned a master’s degree at Columbia University and speaks fluent English—a rarity in the Diet. He is hardly an iconoclast, rejecting immigration as a balm for the country’s demographic ailments, as most politicians do. He is woolly on other social issues. But he says he wants to push diversity. “If I hadn’t gone to the US, I wouldn’t really understand what diversity is,” he says; “It is hard to feel in Japan.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many Japanese take it for granted that Mr Koizumi will eventually become leader of the LDP and prime minister (the two jobs tend to go together); the question is when. The LDP’s leadership race involves votes among both its MPs and its broader membership. Polling suggests he is the most popular choice among the public; the media refer to him as Japan’s Macron. It helps that there are few strong alternatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Koizumi has to tread a delicate line by being enough of an insider to gain support within the party, but enough of a critic to earn the respect of the public at large. He praises Mr Abe’s reforms, but did not vote for him in LDP leadership elections in 2012 and 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Koizumi is coy about whether he will stand in 2021: “Let’s see.” But he points out that on the one hand, young people are becoming estranged from politics, and on the other that the LDP attracts more young voters than any other party. “Japan is getting ready to see more young leaders in politics,” he says, with a generous seasoning of self-interest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 05:40:35 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Did pollsters misread Australia’s election, or did pundits?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/21/did-pollsters-misread-australias-election-or-did-pundits]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_woc967.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-21T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AUSTRALIAN ELECTION-WATCHERS appear to have given more credence to the opinion of a psychic crocodile named &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.ntnews.com.au/news/the-race-is-over-burt-the-psychic-croc-has-picked-saturdays-election-winner/news-story/f38616bb23fca38fedaf8a6e8d32b6cb&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Burt&lt;/a&gt;, who predicted a win for the Labor Leader, Bill Shorten, than they did to the true state of the public opinion polls. On May 20th the &lt;em&gt;Sydney Morning Herald&lt;/em&gt; wrote that pollsters had “spectacularly missed” the results of last week’s election, which ended in a “miracle” victory for Scott Morrison, the Liberal prime minister. The polls did indeed misfire—but only by a paltry two percentage points, slightly less than the historical average error in surveys taken during the final month of a campaign in Australia. Arguably it is pundits who have even more to answer for, having argued that the gap between the Liberals and Labor was much greater than the polls suggested. “Labor will win in this election,” Andy Marks, a political scientist, declared three weeks ago. “I think that’s virtually unquestionable.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Critics in Australia have compared the upset to big electoral surprises in other English-speaking democracies, such as America’s last presidential contest and Britain’s referendum on leaving the EU. However, polling before the vote gave Labor an even more tenuous lead than the modest advantages thought to be held by Hillary Clinton and the Remain campaign. Where America’s leading election forecasters gave Mrs Clinton anywhere from a 70% to 85% chance of winning the presidency, the odds of Mr Shorten becoming PM were much closer to 50%. According to a forecasting model developed by Peter Ellis, an Australian statistician for the Nous Group, a consultancy, the opposition party had merely a 54% chance of either winning an outright majority or capturing enough seats alongside minor-party allies to form a governing coalition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The count on a few closely contested seats has not yet been concluded. But forecasters currently predict that the coalition of the Liberal and National parties will win 78 of the 151 seats in the House of Representatives. Labor is projected to get just 67. Similar to the polls themselves, these outcomes are also narrowly within the realm of what analysts should have considered plausible based on a fair reading of the polls. Mr Ellis pegged the chance of an outright Coalition victory at 17%, though the magnitude of Labor’s disappointment was more surprising: he reckoned the probability that they would win 67 or fewer seats at just 4%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of this means that pollsters should be crowing about their performance. Their surveys showed a narrow Labor lead with metronomic regularity—so consistently, in fact, that it is likely at least some of them weighted their raw results to ensure their published figures resembled those of their competitors. Given the number of polls taken and their sample sizes, there was just a 3% chance that such a series of surveys would show so little variation if they had been truly random and independent. Although the polls indeed showed a close race, a lack of methodological transparency means the pollsters must share some blame for the public’s confusion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 05:40:35 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[When the chips are down—America and Huawei]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/21/when-the-chips-are-down-america-and-huawei]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/huawei.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-21T16:53:43Z&quot;&gt;May 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;HOW WILL the Trump administration’s &lt;strong&gt;restrictions on American companies selling products to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/20/holding-out-on-huawei&quot;&gt;Huawei&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; affect the Chinese telecoms giant? Can the world’s second biggest smartphone maker adapt to not doing business with America? Also, &lt;strong&gt;Michael Froman&lt;/strong&gt;, a former US trade representative and the vice-chairman of MasterCard, discusses &lt;strong&gt;how private companies can promote freer trade&lt;/strong&gt;. And &lt;strong&gt;Jennifer Eberhardt&lt;/strong&gt;, a professor of psychology at Stanford University, explains &lt;strong&gt;the science of racial bias&lt;/strong&gt;. Simon Long hosts. Runtime: 22mins&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/39fc4a99-8861-437d-81e2-684d13e48f92/moneytalks-whenthechipsaredown&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 03:40:30 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The footballer caught up in Armenia’s conflict with Azerbaijan]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/21/the-footballer-caught-up-in-armenias-conflict-with-azerbaijan]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_blp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-21T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;HENRIKH MKHITARYAN is no ordinary Armenian. At 30 years of age, he has won the “Armenian Footballer of the Year” award a record eight times. He captains his country’s national team, and has played for some of Europe’s biggest clubs.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Yet, despite such credentials, “Micki” (pictured above) finds himself caught up in Armenia’s ongoing conflict with Azerbaijan, its neighbour. He will not play in the Europa League final on May 29th, when his current team, Arsenal, play another London side, Chelsea, in Baku, Azerbaijan’s capital. Both club and player made the decision, seemingly due to fears over his safety. Arsenal said the club had not received “acceptable guarantees” from UEFA, the governing body of European football, that it would be safe for Mr Mkhitaryan to travel, and they have now taken matters into their own hands.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;That Arsenal seems to have felt it has no option but to pull its player out of the final has angered the club and its fans, who were already incensed with UEFA’s decision, after a bidding process by member states, to host the event in Azerbaijan. Baku is further east than Baghdad, and the club, like Chelsea, is being allocated just 6,000 tickets for a stadium that holds more than 68,000 people. But Mr Mkhitaryan’s situation is also a reminder that a little-known political rivalry is still tense. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The conflict centres on control of the Nagorno-Karabakh region, which declared independence from Azerbaijan in 1988 as the Soviet Union started to break apart. After the Armenians sided with Nagorno-Karabakh, a full-scale war broke out—in which some 30,000 people had died by 1994. The region has been under Armenian control ever since, but this has failed to bring a lasting peace. There have been frequent skirmishes along the Azeri-Armenian border. Some 200 people were killed in a “four-day war” in April 2016. What started as a dispute over territory has become “an interstate rivalry”, says Thomas De Waal, a senior fellow with Carnegie Europe, a think tank. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Recently there have been a few encouraging signs. The so-called velvet revolution in Armenia last year saw Nikol Pashinyan become prime minister and set up a democratic government. Mr Pashinyan has since met Ilham Aliyev, the president of Azerbaijan, several times and made positive public statements, breathing some life into the peace process. However, Mr De Waal notes there has not been much indication of compromise on either side yet.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Elkhan Mammadov, the general secretary of Azerbaijan’s football association, points out that Armenians have competed in sporting events in Baku before. Four years ago 25 Armenian athletes competed in the European Games there, though they were booed by local fans. Mr Mammadov also says that the country’s government had issued guarantees for Mr Mkhitaryan’s “protection and safety”. &lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;But this public reminder of the conflict with Armenia could overshadow the final. On such a huge occasion, Azerbaijan would have hoped to present itself as a “welcoming” and “accommodating” country, says Simon Rofe of London University&amp;#x27;s School of Oriental and African Studies. Its hosting of other sporting events, such as an annual Formula 1 Grand Prix, has also been criticised as an attempt to deflect criticism from its poor human-rights record.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;That an Armenian sportsman did not feel safe travelling to Azerbaijan reflects poorly on the two countries’ relations, but also on UEFA. The organisation said it had developed a “comprehensive security plan” in conjunction with authorities in Azerbaijan, and showed it to Arsenal. UEFA describes Mr Mkhitaryan’s absence as a “personal decision”. “Micki” has missed less important matches in Azerbaijan in the past, but this is different, he says. He wrote on Twitter: “It&amp;#x27;s the kind of game that doesn&amp;#x27;t come along very often for us players and I must admit, it hurts me a lot to miss it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 03:40:28 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Arab states waste heaps of food during Ramadan]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/21/arab-states-waste-heaps-of-food-during-ramadan]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_map501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-21T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS MUSLIMS HAVE for centuries, Ahmed Toufiq broke his Ramadan fast by nibbling a date while the call to prayer echoed across the Nile. Then he turned to the heaping plates in front of him. He made short work of a fragrant lentil soup, but his pace slowed as he picked through salads and scooped dips with steaming pita bread. When he walked outside for a cigarette 20 minutes after sunset, a server collected half a plate of untouched kebab and rice. “Before &lt;em&gt;iftar&lt;/em&gt;, you feel like you want to eat for two,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arab states waste a lot of food. A study in 2016 by the Economist Intelligence Unit, our sister company, found that Saudi Arabia bins 427kg per person annually, triple the average in Europe and North America. Some may chalk this up to traditions of hospitality: even a “light lunch” in Cairo or Beirut leaves guests in a torpor. The reasons are more varied, though. Half of the fruits and vegetables grown in Egypt are never eaten because they are often moved to market in open-air trucks and wilt quickly in the heat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The problem gets worse during Ramadan. Residents of the United Arab Emirates each produce an extra 1.8kg of waste per day in the holy month, a 67% increase. Food accounts for 55% of Dubai’s trash, up from 22% in other months. Bahrain’s food waste increases by half to 600 tonnes daily. Buffets are a major culprit, especially in the Gulf, where hotels and restaurants often serve through the night. A study by researchers at Masdar, a state-owned renewable-energy firm in Abu Dhabi, found that just 53% of food at &lt;em&gt;iftar&lt;/em&gt; buffets is eaten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is an expensive waste. Some governments see it as a security risk, too. The region is a net food importer. In the weeks before Ramadan, state-run media admonish their citizens to be less wasteful. On social media diners now swap recommendations not on lavish buffets but on a la carte options. Autocratic regimes that frown on civil society are happy for their citizens to take up the cause of food waste. Wahab, a Qatari start-up, sends volunteers to collect leftovers from hotels and restaurants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A few hotels in Dubai have installed cameras and scales to track what winds up in the bin. Chefs use the data to cook less of unpopular dishes. One Hilton property says the system cut buffet waste by 70%. Others are doing away with the buffet altogether—if not for &lt;em&gt;iftar&lt;/em&gt; then for &lt;em&gt;suhour&lt;/em&gt;, the pre-dawn “dinner”. A growing number of restaurants advertise &lt;em&gt;prix fixe&lt;/em&gt; menus as a waste-free way to break fasts. As an added perk, in an emirate struggling with an economic slump, these meals are cheaper. A lavish hotel buffet might set customers back 200 dirhams ($54). Set menus cost about half that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Egypt’s national food bank feeds about 1.8m families during Ramadan. Some of the food is sourced from hotels that package leftovers from their buffet trays. For health reasons, though, uneaten food from a customer’s plate must be thrown away. After 15 hours of fasting eyes are bigger than stomachs. High-tech cameras will not help. So one Cairo hotel found a low-tech solution for its buffet: it made the plates smaller.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 02:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Supreme Court stands up for the Crow Tribe’s right to hunt in Wyoming]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/21/the-supreme-court-stands-up-for-the-crow-tribes-right-to-hunt-in-wyoming]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_USP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-21T16:01:35Z&quot;&gt;May 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FIVE-TO-FOUR decisions usually indicate that the Supreme Court is divided along ideological lines. In the term that ended last June, 14 of the 19 cases resolved by a 5-4 vote pitted the five Republican-appointed justices against the four Democratic picks. Occasionally there are unexpected lineups. Last year, Justice Neil Gorsuch &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/17pdf/15-1498_1b8e.pdf&quot;&gt;joined&lt;/a&gt; the liberal justices against his fellow conservatives in an immigrant-rights case. He &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/18pdf/16-1498_q8l1.pdf&quot;&gt;did the same&lt;/a&gt; two months ago in a ruling favourable to the Yakama Nation in Washington state. On May 20th, Justice Gorsuch again swerved left to stand up for the rights of Native Americans. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/18pdf/17-532_q86b.pdf&quot;&gt;ruling&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Herrera v Wyoming,&lt;/em&gt; honours an 1868 treaty between the Crow Tribe (the Apsáalooke in their language) and the federal government.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The story behind the case began in the winter of 2013, when Clayvin Herrera and a group of Crow hunters tracked a small herd of elk from Montana across the Wyoming state line into the Bighorn National Forest. After killing three animals, Mr Herrera and his fellow hunters carried the meat back to their reservation in Montana to feed their families and other members of the tribe. Wyoming soon charged and convicted Mr Herrera of illegal hunting, but the Crow member believed he was well within his rights under the Reconstruction-era Treaty of Fort Laramie. In exchange for ceding 30m acres of land to the United States, the Crow would enjoy “the right to hunt on the unoccupied lands of the United States so long as game may be found thereon, and as long as peace subsists among the whites and Indians on the borders of the hunting districts”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lower courts balked at this argument, telling Mr Herrera that the treaty was invalid under &lt;em&gt;Ward v Race Horse,&lt;/em&gt; a Supreme Court ruling from 1896. &lt;em&gt;Race Horse&lt;/em&gt; held that Idaho’s Bannock tribe had lost its hunting rights on federal lands when Wyoming gained statehood. Part of being a sovereign state, the Supreme Court reasoned, is having dominion over the wildlife and game within the state’s borders. But a century later, the Supreme Court walked away from &lt;em&gt;Race Horse.&lt;/em&gt; In &lt;em&gt;Minnesota v Mille Lacs Band of Chippewa&lt;/em&gt; Indians (1999), a 5-4 liberal majority decided that Native treaty rights “are not impliedly terminated upon statehood” after all. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a majority opinion by Justice Sonia Sotomayor, the Supreme Court relied on &lt;em&gt;Mille Lacs&lt;/em&gt; to vindicate the Crow right to pursue game on federal lands. &lt;em&gt;Herrera&lt;/em&gt; began with some history. “The Crow Tribe first inhabited modern-day Montana more than three centuries ago”, Justice Sotomayor wrote. “The Tribe was nomadic, and its members hunted game for subsistence”. After the 1868 treaty, when the Wyoming Territory was established, Congress promised the new designation would not “impair the rights of person or property now pertaining to the Indians in said Territory, so long as such rights shall remain unextinguished by treaty”. The &lt;em&gt;Herrera&lt;/em&gt; majority also had to contend with &lt;em&gt;Crow Tribe of Indians v Repsis,&lt;/em&gt; a 1996 ruling at the Tenth Circuit Court of Appeals holding that because Bighorn National Park was not “unoccupied” within the meaning of the 1868 treaty, the Crow had no right to bring their hunting rifles there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justice Sotomayor dispatched &lt;em&gt;Repsis&lt;/em&gt; by clarifying that &lt;em&gt;Race Horse&lt;/em&gt; had been superseded by &lt;em&gt;Mille Lacs.&lt;/em&gt; The 1999 ruling had “upended both lines of reasoning in &lt;em&gt;Race Horse”&lt;/em&gt;, the court held, and “the crucial inquiry for treaty termination analysis is whether Congress has expressly abrogated an Indian treaty right or whether a termination point identified in the treaty itself has been satisfied”. The court’s conclusion in &lt;em&gt;Herrera&lt;/em&gt; is this, then: absent both explicit word from Congress and a clause in the treaty laying out terms of its own dissolution, the 1868 promise to the Crow tribe must be kept. Lest there be any confusion in the future, &lt;em&gt;Race Horse’&lt;/em&gt;s view that statehood implies the forfeiture of Indian rights is “repudiated”, Justice Sotomayor wrote. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As for the claim that Bighorn is not “unoccupied” and therefore closed to Native American hunting, Justice Sotomayor summoned more common sense. “Treaty analysis begins with the text”, she wrote, “and treaty terms are construed as ‘they would naturally be understood by the Indians’. There is no doubt that the Crow “would have understood the word ‘unoccupied’ to denote an area free of residence or settlement by non-Indians”. As there were (and are) no white men moving into homes in the park, the Crow would have no reason to construe it as occupied land.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A petulant dissent from Justice Samuel Alito called the majority’s view “puzzling”. How, he asked, could the court “plow ahead” with its interpretation of the 1868 treaty without adequately addressing the grounds of the decision in &lt;em&gt;Repsis&lt;/em&gt;? In any event, the park is not “unoccupied”, Justice Alito wrote, so Mr Herrera and his fellow tribe members must keep out. The dissent&amp;#x27;s tone sounds a discordant note alongside the majority’s plain reading of the treaty. Justice Gorsuch’s endorsement of the liberal interpretation gives &lt;em&gt;Herrera&lt;/em&gt; added weight and is no surprise: a Coloradan, he came to the Supreme Court from the Tenth Circuit, where he was vigilant on questions of tribal sovereignty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 01:40:26 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[As the trade war heats up, China looks to Japan’s past for lessons]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/21/as-the-trade-war-heats-up-china-looks-to-japans-past-for-lessons]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_fnd000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-21T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;HISTORY IS NEVER far from China’s mind in its trade dispute with America. A few months ago, when negotiations looked on track, staunch nationalists warned of echoes with the “unequal treaties” that foreign powers had forced upon China in the 19th century. In recent weeks the breakdown in talks has led state propagandists to draw comparisons with the Korean war of the 1950s, a bloody struggle between China and America. But the analogy that haunts Chinese economists does not involve China itself. They fear a replay of the Plaza Accord of 1985, when Japan, under American pressure, tried to resolve trade tensions by pushing the yen higher. That calmed the tensions but, most Chinese economists think, at an intolerable price: stagnant Japanese growth for two-plus decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The parallels are imperfect. Dependent on America for security, Japan was constrained in its pushback. The Plaza Accord also involved Britain, France and West Germany. Jeffrey Frankel of Harvard University has called it “a high-water mark of international policy co-ordination”, which is not President Donald Trump’s trademark. The substance was different, too. The five countries announced that they wanted the dollar to depreciate and intervened in currency markets to make it happen. Within a year the yen soared by nearly 50% against the dollar. By contrast, currencies are just one part of today’s tussle between China and America. Over the past decade China has worked to address complaints that the yuan is too low. So there are no calls for appreciation, only demands that China does not weaken it to help its exporters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looked at more generally, though, there are similarities. The Plaza Accord is best understood not as a one-off event but as a critical stage in a multi-year dispute, which ranged from agriculture to electronics. America accused Japan of stealing intellectual property and plotting to control future industries. Robert Lighthizer, America’s lead negotiator against China today, earned his spurs in these earlier battles. In 1990 the two countries agreed to a “Structural Impediments Initiative”, which bears a striking resemblance to the crux of the debate today. America wanted Japan then—and wants China now—to improve its competition laws, open more widely to foreign investors and weaken its giant conglomerates (&lt;em&gt;keiretsu&lt;/em&gt; groups in Japan, state-owned firms in China).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The case against the Plaza Accord is that it set Japan on a path to doom. To counter the effect of a strong yen, an obvious drag on exports, Japan slashed interest rates and unleashed fiscal stimulus. These moves brought about an economic rebound. But they also generated asset bubbles: stock and land prices tripled within five years. In 1990 these bubbles burst and the economy slumped, never to recover its former mojo. In nominal terms Japanese stocks are still 40% below their peak on the final trading day of 1989. The Plaza Accord, in this view, did succeed in defusing tensions between Japan and America, but only because it neutered Japan as a challenger. This has percolated into official thinking in China. As Cui Tiankai, China’s ambassador to America, said last year: “Give up the illusion that another Plaza Accord could be imposed on China.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sequence of Japan’s woes does seem to make for a damning indictment. But a closer look at each step shows that nothing was preordained. One point, clear in retrospect, is that Japan overcompensated for the slowdown in exports. Within 18 months of the Plaza Accord, it had cut benchmark interest rates from 5% to 2.5%. It also announced a big stimulus package—increasing spending and cutting taxes—in May 1987, though by then its recovery was already under way. It did not shift gears and raise rates again until 1989, when its asset bubbles were already a few years old.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the International Monetary Fund has argued, there were at least two other factors that could have led to a different outcome. Excessive stimulus, by itself, did not guarantee that Japan would suffer an asset bubble. It was that much more dangerous when combined with financial deregulation, which led banks to lend more to property developers and homebuyers. And the bursting of the bubble did not guarantee that Japan would suffer a lost decade, let alone three. A sluggish response by regulators compounded the trouble. Rather than pushing banks to raise capital, they encouraged them to go on lending to zombie firms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So the simplistic story—that the Plaza Accord felled Japan—misses the mark. Rather, China should draw two lessons from Japan’s experience of trade tensions with America. First, it must get its domestic policy response right. Japan feared that the deal with America would cause its growth to suffer; China fears the same about the absence of a deal. But the bigger dangers for Japan were over-stimulus and flawed regulation. China seems to grasp that. So far it has been cautious about pumping up growth. The real test will come if the trade war continues to escalate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ask the bellboy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A second lesson is the danger of resisting America’s demands, just because it is America that is making them. Had Japan acted on some of America’s long-standing gripes, it might have fared better in the 1990s. Domestic competition would have been stronger. A bigger role for foreign investors might have prompted Japanese banks to tackle their festering problems. Similarly, it is China, not America, that would be the biggest beneficiary if it moves more quickly to open its economy to foreign firms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China might also note a historical curiosity. The talks in 1985 were in New York’s Plaza Hotel, which was bought three years later by a property tycoon named Donald Trump. He paid nearly $1bn in today’s money. At the time he said he had “knowingly made a deal which was not economic”, because the hotel was a masterpiece, not just a building. Sure enough, in 1992 the Plaza Hotel entered bankruptcy. That Mr Trump ended up harming himself might be comforting for China. That he went ahead despite knowing the risks should be less so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 01:40:25 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[We need to break political tribalism to improve democracy]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/05/21/we-need-to-break-political-tribalism-to-improve-democracy]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_OPP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-21T15:27:41Z&quot;&gt;May 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT IS fashionable to reflect that politics is broken. Whether you are chatting to millennial socialists, populist nationalists or frustrated centrists, the idea that democracy in the West is malfunctioning is likely to be acknowledged without hesitation. But it is not true. Politics is not broken—it is working in the same way it has for generations. What it actually needs now is to be broken. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The problem is that the adversarial nature of the system is increasingly polarised at a time when the most pressing problems require ever-greater political co-operation. This conundrum bedevils many democracies, but it’s particularly distressing in Britain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The parliamentary system pits party interest against national interest, and career advancement against evidence-based policy. The tribal nature of party life discourages pragmatic consensus. The tumult of the ballot box means short-term thinking trumps long-term initiatives. No new political party, however well intentioned, is likely to change this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Political parties served 20th-century liberal democracies admirably. Now, although the parties have been broad churches, the classical left-right divide is no longer people’s lodestar. Popular opinions are more likely to be grounded in broader values and visible in questions over how we wish to interact with the world, whether we welcome cultural change and how secure we feel in the economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp501.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp501.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp501.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp501.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp501.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp501.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp501.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp501.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp501.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that political fault-lines have changed, it is no surprise that political parties seem like a spent force. Many MPs are frustrated by the bind in which they find themselves: either surrender free-thinking for party loyalty, or vote on individual conscience and be cast into the wilderness of the backbenches. Citizens are forced to buy in to the party platform in its entirety, which does not feel like a very modern way of doing things, like having to purchase the whole vinyl record album to get the song you want, rather than rip, mix and burn the tracks for yourself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This highlights the problem with the idea of new political parties in Britain. The proponents of a new centrist party assume that people just want a better political party. In fact they do not. They want something different.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know this first-hand; I worked inside the Westminster bubble for years. When I finally stepped out, I realised how absurdly artificial the party boundaries look to most people. Politicians and party apparatchiks hold up political parties as the only vehicle by which ideas can be turned into policies. Not only is that plain wrong but it also undermines democracy, by failing to serve the majority of the public who do not strongly identify with a party.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was my frustration with the shortcomings of the political system that inspired me in 2016 to create a nonprofit group, More United. The aim is to foster cross-party co-operation on specific issues that are chosen and funded by the public. People can sign on to a specific campaign, which signals to Westminster what issues have a groundswell of support. People can also donate, so we can channel those funds to MPs who agree to work with their counterparts across the political aisle to achieve reform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since we launched, more than 150,000 people have donated or joined a campaign on issues like the NHS, plastic pollution and immigration. In the general election in 2017, we crowdfunded £500,000 for more than 50 candidates across five political parties. In some ways, it is a pittance. But in other ways, it is a stunning demonstration of the public’s thirst for cross-party co-operation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In April, More United established the first, permanent network of MPs committed to working cross-party in Parliament. Some 54 MPs from seven parties have committed to working together on a range of issues (particularly those ignored because of Brexit, such as mental health, climate change and poverty). It pushes MPs beyond the traditional, single-issue committees that tend to stifle policy imagination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In one project, three MPs from Labour, Conservative and the Liberal Democrats jointly surveyed almost 20,000 More United members on immigration to identify programmes that enjoyed wide public support. We uncovered more common ground than the public debate suggests. For instance, both pro- and anti-immigration adherents agree on the same policy: extra support to the areas most affected by immigration. The group took these findings to the Home Secretary with a request to take it into account in modifying the policy, as he had previously done with a More United campaign to end a health-care charge on foreigners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Behind our activities is technology. The web lowers the cost of finding supporters, co-ordinating their activities and collecting contributions. It is impossible to imagine being able to do this just ten years ago. And we are not alone: other charities aim to reform British politics, such as the online petition sites 38degrees and Avaaz.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What this points to is an opportunity to rethink politics for the digital age. Last year some 14m Britons signed an online petition—that’s more than one in four adults. It is easy to sneer at so-called clicktivism but it demonstrates that the “currencies” of engagement, compassion and hopefulness are still in ready supply. The critical question for democracies is how we provide people with new ways to spend it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the surface, the tech makes the issue of awareness, public participation, fundraising and tracking politicians’ performance easier. On the back-end of politics, this sort of cross-party working has the potential to pass legislation in a way that might be harder under the current bare-knuckle system. And it delivers an important message about the public’s interest in co-operation among MPs to the government of the day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At a time of voter dissatisfaction with the main parties and a political environment infused with technology that pulls people towards the extremes, the ability to find ways to bring people together and rebuild a political centre is crucial. The focus has to be on breaking politics as usual—that is the only way we can repair it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;_____________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Bess Mayhew is the co-founder of More United, a non-partisan political group in Britain, and steps down this month as its chief executive. She worked for the Liberal Democrats from 2011 to 2015, managing online communications, digital campaigning and fundraising. More United’s staff is drawn from Britain’s major political parties.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 00:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Game of Thrones” comes to a controversial end]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/21/game-of-thrones-comes-to-a-controversial-end]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_BKP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-21T13:01:10Z&quot;&gt;May 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE LAST dragon has flown away. The army of undead White Walkers has been defeated. The Iron Throne has melted. After eight seasons “Game of Thrones”, HBO’s biggest-ever show, came to an end on May 19th. The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/17/how-unprecedented-is-the-decline-of-game-of-thrones&quot;&gt;last series caused fury&lt;/a&gt; among devoted fans, with more than 1m people signing a petition to have the season redrafted by “more competent” screenwriters. Some, given the chance, might make the producers re-enact the “walk of shame” suffered by Cersei Lannister, a key character, in season five (she was made to pass through a crowd naked while being pelted with rotten fruit). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is hard not to feel some sympathy for David Benioff and D.B. Weiss, the showrunners. As anyone who has read the books can attest, George R.R. Martin constructed an enormous, sprawling story with a bewildering cast of characters and a weird mix of politics, sex, gory violence and magic. It was never going to be easy to tie these elements together to make a satisfactory ending. Mr Martin has amply demonstrated that himself. He published the first book in 1996 and the fifth (of a planned seven) in 2011, but is yet to complete the saga.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The controversy should not overshadow the show’s success in creating an unmissable cultural event. “Game of Thrones” was the kind of series that schoolchildren would discuss at break time and office workers would chat about by the kettle. Critics devoted thousands of words to finding hidden clues and unpicking symbolism. Children were named after the central characters—a decision parents would often come to regret—and President Donald Trump used the imagery of the series to illustrate his political messages. In the binge-watching era, viewers waited patiently for each week’s instalment; fans outside America were forced into drastic action to avoid spoilers on social media. (Note to Twitter: there is no point allowing users to mute words when you list spoilers in the “Trending” column.) And, of course, the series inspired a subculture of those who proudly proclaim that they never watched an episode.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What explains the show’s success? A crucial component came from the books: Mr Martin’s willingness to kill off important characters. Sean Bean was the biggest star of the first series and, as the noble Ned Stark, seemed set to be the hero of the saga. But he was executed early on, while his wife and son were dispatched in the “Red Wedding” bloodbath in season three. Ever since no character has seemed safe. Viewers have been kept in a state of nervous tension.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second, the political struggle at the heart of the series had broader resonance. Mr Martin based his saga loosely on the Wars of the Roses in England in the 15th century, when rival families battled for the throne. But it is not hard to find echoes of the 20th century too, with the Starks as the English, complete with Northern accents, and the blond, ruthless Lannisters as the Germans. The latter could only be defeated by bringing in the forces of the “new world”, as represented by Daenerys and her dragons. Victory was achieved but only at a terrible cost; the destruction by fire of King’s Landing in the final series, which could be compared with the bombing of Dresden, or Hiroshima. Another theme, manifest in the oft-repeated warning “winter is coming”, was climate change. For much of the series, the rival families ignored (and indeed ridiculed) the threat posed by the White Walkers, an invading army from the frozen north.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Third, the series was a meditation on the nature of leadership. Ned Stark’s noble honesty was shown to be too naive; the callous rule of the Lannisters meant their subjects showed them no loyalty; the messianic appeal of Daenerys led the character to morph into a fanatical dictator. In some cases, the characters lost all morality in their pursuit of the Iron Throne, as best demonstrated when Stannis Baratheon burned his daughter alive in a desperate attempt to boost his chances. Alas, the show eventually awarded the kingdom to its single most irritating character, Bran Stark, a crippled boy who spoke only in fortune-cookie aphorisms. The only redeeming feature of this denouement was that Bran was shown to be a figurehead, guided by the show’s best character, Tyrion, the hard-drinking, wise-cracking dwarf played by Peter Dinklage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the best way of explaining the show’s success was that it was an elaborate soap opera, in the style of “Dallas” or “Dynasty”, two series that also featured battling families. Like those shows, “Game of Thrones” had larger-than-life heroes and villains, whom viewers could cheer and boo from the sidelines. Soap operas are designed never to end and “Game of Thrones” fans would only have been happy, one suspects, if the series had been extended by a final twist, so their favourite characters could bicker and conspire for a few more years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As it is, there are various prequels in the works. The decision of one of the Stark children, Arya, to set sail for unknown lands to the west suggests the possibility of a spin-off that echoes Europe’s colonial expansion in the 16th century. But it will be a miracle if any show can make the same cultural impact as “Game of Thrones”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 21:40:33 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>