<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Anish Kapoor’s menstrual art and the vexed question of appropriation]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/14/anish-kapoors-menstrual-art-and-the-vexed-question-of-appropriation]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BKP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-14T16:54:40Z&quot;&gt;May 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BLOOD LEAKS and gushes from the art in Anish Kapoor’s new show at the Lisson Gallery in London. Almost literally in the case of his silicone and fibreglass reliefs: the gauze dangling beneath them is spattered with scarlet. In his oil paintings, meanwhile, blood-red spurts emanate from corporeal pinks and black cavities and orifices. Black is deathly, says Mr Kapoor, but also, like red, a colour of earth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Kapoor, a British artist who was born in Mumbai, is best known for his monumental sculptures (including a gigantic tubular installation in the Turbine Hall of the Tate Modern in 2002). His new series of paintings contemplate the idea of ritual, and the meaning of blood—which, as he puts it, is “associated with the abject and impure”. In particular, the paintings evoke menstrual blood. That motif raises another question, a version of which these days confronts artists in every genre and form. “Can a man deal with women’s issues?” Mr Kapoor muses. “Is a man allowed to?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Would that anxiety have occurred to him, say, 20 years ago? “We live in times of political correctness,” he responds, adding: “I am for it.” All the same, Mr Kapoor insists, “we have to manage it rather carefully”—in other words, being sure to safeguard artistic freedom. “Give me a break! What crap is that?” he asks of the notion that, for instance, a white artist should not explore a black person’s experience. Such leaps are the purpose of what he calls “the artistic imagination”. The only real question, he thinks, is whether the resulting work of art is good or bad. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the shapes in his paintings—“partial objects”, Mr Kapoor calls them—are distinctly female, but the bodily references of others are more ambiguous. His white canvases suggest purity, and contamination, but also an androgynous disembodiment. In fact, while these paintings trespass on a particular “taboo” in their concern with menstruation, the curves and concavities of much of Mr Kapoor’s previous work likewise convey a preoccupation with bodies and sexuality. In his telling, the turn towards characteristically female forms goes well beyond him: he reckons that the entire history of art since Freud has involved a reorientation from phallic forms to the inward kind. In another of Mr Kapoor’s metaphors, instead of peering from the mouth of the cave up into the sky, artists have instead turned back into the shadows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The layout at the Lisson Gallery reinforces the theme of ritual. Several of the canvases hang around a pink onyx sculpture, in which twin ovoid shapes are encased in a sarcophagus or urn. As Mr Kapoor sees it, the blood in his paintings is pouring into the recesses of the stone, which to him resembles a &lt;em&gt;mikveh&lt;/em&gt; or Jewish ritual bath (he is Jewish, but also describes himself as a practising Buddhist). To this reviewer’s eye, the sculpture evokes a receptacle for the blood of a sacrifice; Mr Kapoor accepts that interpretation, too. Purity and defilement, sacrifice and cleansing: in art, as in life, contradictory things are often bound together.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Anish Kapoor” is showing at the Lisson Gallery, London, until June 22nd&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:07:29 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cory Booker’s educational successes do not play well in the primaries]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/14/cory-bookers-educational-successes-do-not-play-well-in-the-primaries]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_usp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-14T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON SEPTEMBER 24th, 2010 the Oprah Winfrey show hosted the unlikely trio of Cory Booker, who was then the Democratic mayor of Newark, Chris Christie, who was then the Republican governor of New Jersey, and a skittish-looking Mark Zuckerberg. They were there to announce an eye-popping $100m donation from the Facebook founder to help turn around Newark’s beleaguered schools. Mr Booker promised it would be a “bold new paradigm for educational excellence in the country” and helped fundraise another $100m in matching donations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now that Mr Booker is a New Jersey senator running for president in a crowded Democratic primary, he seldom brings up the Zuckerberg donation. That is not because the schools have failed to improve. They have done so significantly, though not to the degree envisioned by Mr Booker, who exclaimed that “you could flip a whole city!” Instead, it is that the ingredients of Newark’s education turnaround—the closing of bad schools, renegotiating teacher contracts to include merit pay, and significantly expanding high-performing charter networks—are anathema to the Democratic primary voting base.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Outside Newark, the public perception of the school reforms remain widely negative. Much of that is due to Dale Russakoff, a journalist, who wrote an influential and stinging portrayal of the efforts in her book, “The Prize”. Cami Anderson, the hard-charging superintendent appointed to oversee the plan, was vilified, and then resigned after Mr Booker decamped from Newark to Washington in 2013. Ras Baraka, a former high-school principal who is the current mayor, won election after making the contest a referendum over Ms Anderson’s popularity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A review of the recent evidence suggests this pessimism is misplaced. For district schools, the high-school graduation rate has climbed to 76%, up from 61% in 2011. A study done by researchers at Harvard found an initial drop-off in test scores, and then, after the reforms set in, a big improvement in English, but not maths tests. Two-thirds of the growth was attributable to changes in the composition of schools—the closing down of failing traditional public schools and expansion of high-performing charters. Today, 31% of black students attend schools that beat the state average, compared with 10% in 2011. All this, even though Newark remains profoundly poor. Nearly 40% of the children live with families making less than the federal poverty line (currently $21,300 for a family of three); the vast majority, 79%, of schoolchildren are poor enough to qualify for free or reduced-price school lunches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Mr Booker believes deeply in anything, it is school choice. In 1998, when he was still a little-known city councillor, he founded Excellent Education for Everyone, which advocates for charter schools and voucher programmes. He sat on the board of Alliance for School Choice, a national organisation, alongside Betsy DeVos, who would become education secretary under President Donald Trump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;School choice has always scrambled the usual left-right divide in American politics. Mr Booker’s belief in it differs strongly from Ms DeVos’s. As a senator he voted against her confirmation. While those on the right see parental choice as a good in itself—and as a way to expand religious education—progressive types favour charter schools as a path to opportunity for poor black and Hispanic children whom urban school systems have failed for decades. “What do middle-class people do? They don’t wait for the district to fix itself. If [school choice] is good enough for middle-class people, then poor people should be able to as well,” says Shavar Jeffries, a civil-rights attorney who runs Democrats for Education Reform, a pro-charter group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Anderson, the former superintendent who now runs a school-discipline reform initiative, feels vindicated. “I feel the results speak for themselves,” she says. “The fact that the establishment has been quiet is because it’s working.” The rhetoric from Mr Baraka, the mayor who pushed her out, has changed from outright hostility to comfortable neutrality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reforming the Newark school system would never be easy, reasons Ms Anderson. She talks of an ingrained culture of political cronyism—describing requests to hire the girlfriend of someone politically connected even though she could not write a cover letter; or not to sack another grandee’s nephew for punching someone in a school cafeteria. Ms Anderson also fired most of the district’s principals, whom she found unsatisfactory, and hired her own handpicked ones. Most of them remain, she notes proudly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disruption was also especially threatening because the school district was one of the largest employers in the city. The budget was nearly $1bn a year—meaning that even the impressive-seeming $200m donation, which was spent over five years, represented only a 4% annual increase in funding. Some of the jobs supported by the big budget seemed superfluous. In her book, Ms Russakoff documents a Gogol-like setting in which even the clerks had clerks. More than half of the district’s funding—a not-paltry $20,000 per head—was gobbled up in central bureaucratic costs before it reached classrooms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Newark, one-third of students now attend charter schools. According to an assessment done by CREDO, a research outfit at Stanford University, in 2015 Newark’s charters are the second highest-performing in the country. They deliver educational gains in maths and reading almost equivalent to a full additional year of instruction, the researchers estimated. The latest state assessments for reading and maths for pupils in the third to eight grades (roughly between the ages of 8 and 14) still show stark differences—60% of students in Newark’s charter pupils were proficient in English, compared with just 35% in the traditional public schools. For maths, the numbers were 48% compared with 26%. In both cases, the charters beat the state average—a remarkable fact given the impoverishment of Newark and the high quality of the state’s other schools. The differences in student population are not large enough to explain this divergence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a result, demand for charters among parents is high. Before a common enrolment system was in place, the waiting list for KIPP schools, a high-performing charter network, had 10,000 children on it, says Ryan Hill, the co-founder. Habib Ahad, a city contractor and graduate of the city’s public schools who has had three daughters attend KIPP schools, says he “wouldn’t even want to imagine if they went to the other schools”. One of the top-ranked high schools in the state of New Jersey is North Star Academy Charter School—which is 98% non-white and 85% poor. Last year’s valedictorian now attends Princeton.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, not all charters are so high-performing. On average, their outcomes are similar to traditional public schools. They do better in cities, and worse elsewhere. The problem is that teachers’ unions are at their strongest in precisely the places where charters are the highest-performing, making the politics of school reform treacherous for Democrats. Elizabeth Warren, the Massachusetts senator also running for the Democratic nomination, favoured school choice before she was a public figure, on similar progressive-minded grounds (she worried that the zero-sum race to buy property near good schools was endangering middle-class finances). But she opposed a referendum to increase the number of charters in Boston—despite the fact that these are the highest-performing in the country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Booker is trying to navigate these treacherous waters. His proposed education-policy platform for 2020 is to increase funding for educating special-needs children and to pay teachers more. These proposals are fine. Yet Mr Booker is the only candidate with a serious education achievement under his belt—and the essential ingredients of that turnaround look very different to his current platform. Although Mr Booker had originally touted his proposal as a national model, his campaign now says that there is no one-size-fits-all solution for education reform, employing one of those unilluminating truisms that abound in American politics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While it is shrewd politics to dodge unnecessary controversy, Mr Booker is already catching flak for his record in Newark. “Cory Booker Hates Public Schools” blusters a headline from Jacobin, a widely read democratic socialist magazine. He has some defenders too, though. “It is a shame to deride the good work that was done in Newark as a defect of his candidacy or his worldview,” says Derrell Bradford, a longtime education-reform advocate who worked with Mr Booker in the early days of his career. “Newark now is better than when I took my job in 2002. If you’re a poor kid, a black kid, your opportunity to succeed is much higher than before. Is it what it should be, or ought to be? Still no—but there’s been tremendous progress.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:07:28 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“It’s often called the forgotten war”—Yemen peace talks]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/14/its-often-called-the-forgotten-war-yemen-peace-talks]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_blp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-14T11:30:26Z&quot;&gt;May 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;UN NEGOTIATORS are trying to salvage a ceasefire agreement to keep open Hodeidah, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/04/27/congress-fails-to-claw-back-the-right-to-wage-war&quot;&gt;Yemen&lt;/a&gt;&amp;#x27;s main port. The Arab world’s poorest country is suffering terribly, but achieving a lasting deal remains difficult. In &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/11/john-bolton-and-the-monroe-doctrine&quot;&gt;Latin America&lt;/a&gt;, democracy is in peril. How to preserve it? And the political scandal of a splashy apartment building in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/13/an-apartment-scandal-embarrasses-senior-bulgarian-officials&quot;&gt;Bulgaria&lt;/a&gt;. Runtime: 23 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/supplydemands-yemenpeacetalks&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 19:06:50 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Deaths of despair, once an American phenomenon, now haunt Britain]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/14/deaths-of-despair-once-an-american-phenomenon-now-haunt-britain]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_brp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-14T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN RECENT YEARS America has witnessed a troubling trend: a rise in what have become known as “deaths of despair”. Sir Angus Deaton and Anne Case, an academic couple both of Princeton University, have tracked an increase in the number of middle-aged whites dying from drug overdoses, suicides and alcohol-related conditions. Their work has shaped political debate in America. Now a report by the Institute for Fiscal Studies (IFS), a British think-tank, published on May 14th, suggests that something similar is taking place on the other side of the Atlantic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is one of the initial findings of a five-year review of inequality begun by the IFS, which will look at everything from income to political participation. In its scale and scope, the exercise will be on a par with the Mirrlees Review, a gargantuan assessment of the tax system undertaken by the same think-tank, which issued its final report in 2011 and has been a reference point for researchers ever since. Sir Angus, who won the Nobel prize for economics in 2015, is chairing a panel of worthies overseeing the project.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BRC016.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190518_BRC016.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190518_BRC016.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190518_BRC016.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190518_BRC016.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190518_BRC016.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190518_BRC016.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190518_BRC016.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190518_BRC016.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190518_BRC016.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The analysis shows that, after steadying during the 2000s, deaths of despair among middle-aged British men have in the past eight years or so been moving in the wrong direction (see chart). In 2017 they drew level with deaths from heart disease. In part because deaths from cancer have stopped falling, overall mortality among middle-aged men is on its way up for the first time in decades. Deaths of despair among women are also rising, but less quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BRC012.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190518_BRC012.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190518_BRC012.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190518_BRC012.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190518_BRC012.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190518_BRC012.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190518_BRC012.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190518_BRC012.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190518_BRC012.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190518_BRC012.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Economists argue over what has caused the rise in deaths of despair in America. The ready availability of opioid painkillers is thought to play some part. So may economic misfortune: those with no education beyond high-school, among whom the rise has been particularly rapid, have also seen their income stagnate. However, Sir Angus and Professor Case put more emphasis on the impact of the erosion of traditional social structures, including trade unions, the church and marriage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far there is no comparable research on Britain, though the IFS is working on it. Circumstantial evidence points to some possible explanations, however. As in America, poor prescription practices may have contributed to a rise in opioid abuse (though to nowhere near the same extent). Deaths which were related to the use of opioids have risen from 800 a year in the mid-1990s to 2,000 a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Economic factors are likely to play a role too. Official data suggest that deaths of despair jumped in the mid-1980s, when traditional industries such as coal-mining were closing. The continued decline of manufacturing and the rise of service industries has probably favoured women. In 2004 the female employment rate exceeded the male rate in none of Britain’s local authorities. Now it is higher in 12. Men who no longer feel that they hold a privileged position in society may think they have little to live for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the fact that deaths from despair began rising again around 2010 points to another factor: fiscal austerity. A big tightening of welfare policy, including harsher use of sanctions against those who fail to meet job-searching requirements, has made the experience of looking for work progressively more uncomfortable—though why that should affect men more than women is not clear. Finding out what is really going on should be a priority for Sir Angus and his team. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 13:06:43 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Smartphones are driving Americans to distraction]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/13/smartphones-are-driving-americans-to-distraction]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_woc111.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-13T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EVER SINCE Apple launched the first iPhone in 2007 the small digital screen has become a ubiquitous part of life. Today in America there are some 260m smartphones in use, one for every adult. But the omnipresence of the device appears to be behind a recent increase in pedestrian deaths on America’s roads.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At first glance, Americans appear to be restrained when using their smartphone while driving. One survey conducted by the Department of Transport (DoT) reckons that around 5% of drivers used their mobile phones behind the wheel in 2017. DoT researchers arrive at this figure by observing drivers’ mobile-phone use in situ at randomly allocated stopping places. By contrast Zendrive, a startup, employs software that is able to remotely track drivers’ use of their mobile phones. Using data on 60bn journeys taken in 2018 Zendrive reckons that the true rate of smartphone use behind the wheel may be as high as 60%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To what extent is distracted driving causing people to crash more frequently? Data released by the DoT last month suggest that over the past five years smartphones have caused just 2,105 fatal crashes (1.2% of the total). But there is reason to believe that this figure undercounts the true toll as not all police agencies are able to report the true cause of a crash. About 20% of the victims of distracted-driving fatalities are not drivers or passengers, but other road users such as pedestrians and cyclists.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While cars have become progressively safer thanks to airbags, side-impact bars and the like, pedestrians remain just as vulnerable to reckless driving. Their vulnerability appears to be demonstrated in the data. Between 1994 and 2009 the rate of deaths on American roads fell by an average rate of 2.6% for motor-vehicle users and by 3.2% for pedestrians. However, since 2009, while deaths from those in vehicles have flat-lined, pedestrian deaths have risen steadily. They are now 36% higher than their 2009 rate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not all these deaths can be attributed to smartphone use and distracted driving. Higher sales of SUVs, which are bigger and more deadly vehicles, are partly to blame, too. And it is likely that some of the pedestrians who are killed are distracted by their smartphones when they should be focused on safely crossing the street. Whatever the proximate cause, a back-of-the-envelope calculation by &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; finds that if pedestrian deaths had continued their secular decline since 2009 an additional 20,000 deaths could have been averted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As things stand just 18 states in America ban the handling of mobile phones while driving. North Carolina is the latest state to be considering a ban and evidence suggests that it would save lives. Research published last month finds that states that banned texting-while-driving reduced emergency-room visits from car crashes by 4%, equivalent to 1,600 fewer ER visits per state per year. The more Americans focus on the road ahead, the safer everyone will be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 02:09:23 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[An apartment scandal embarrasses senior Bulgarian officials]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/13/an-apartment-scandal-embarrasses-senior-bulgarian-officials]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_eup503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-13T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FEW BULGARIANS who walk by the Letera, a new luxury apartment building in Sofia, can read the texts inscribed on its facade. They are written in the Glagolitic alphabet, a medieval ecclesiastic script. This is part of the building’s aesthetic, a sort of religious-nationalist elitism. The advertising video on its website is a tribute to early Slavic Christianity, featuring cowled monks in the mist. Over the entrance, the 91st psalm offers protection for the righteous from their enemies: “He who dwells in the secret place of the Most High, abideth in the shadow of the Almighty.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tsvetan Tsvetanov (pictured, right), the owner of the Letera’s penthouse, may wish he dwelt in a somewhat more secret place. In late March, Mr Tsvetanov, the second most powerful figure in the ruling GERB party, was revealed to have obtained his apartment in a complicated exchange that valued it at about €250,000 ($280,000), perhaps a quarter of the going rate. He denies any wrongdoing, but has resigned as GERB’s parliamentary leader. He is still chairman of the party’s campaign committee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since then nearly a dozen other highly placed government officials have been found to have received cut-price apartments in various buildings around Sofia. Many have stepped down, including the former justice minister. Even the chairman of the government anti-corruption commission is under investigation, for failing to declare that his top-floor loft included his building’s entire 186-square-metre roof terrace. (He claimed it was shared by all the residents, though it can be reached only from his apartment.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The “apartments scandal” has infuriated Bulgarian citizens, even though the sums involved are far smaller than in other corruption affairs, such as the billion-dollar collapse of the politically connected Corporate Commercial Bank in 2014. “The thing about this story is that you can touch it,” explains Polina Paunova of Svobodna Evropa, the Bulgarian branch of Radio Free Europe, which first reported the scandal. Unusually for eastern Europe, about 90% of Bulgarians own their homes, so property is an emotional subject—especially with values going up: housing prices rose 35% in Sofia between 2015 and 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The media have become obsessed by details of unlisted balconies and private elevators, but the real implications go much deeper. The most difficult problem for corrupt politicians is justifying cash holdings that vastly exceed their salaries, explains Nikolay Staykov of the Anti-Corruption Fund, a watchdog that collaborated with Svobodna Evropa to uncover the scandal. Property transactions provide ways to launder such money, such as declaring a purchase at the lowest plausible value, and then reselling it to a friendly party at the highest plausible price.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The scandal involves powerful commercial interests as well. The Letera was built by Arteks, a developer that is also building a 34-storey apartment tower that would be the tallest in Sofia. That project, the “Golden Century” building, is opposed by neighbourhood groups. More important, it may not be legal: its construction permit, granted in 2007, expired in November 2017. The company contends that amendments to the construction code passed by parliament in January 2017, when Mr Tsvetanov was leader of the GERB fraction, retroactively granted it an extra three years. Mr Tsvetanov says that when he was negotiating to buy his apartment from Arteks, he was not aware of the problem with the Golden Century’s permit, and that in any case the amendments do not apply. Arteks’s lawyers say they do.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since they joined the European Union in 2007, Bulgaria and Romania have been subjected to special monitoring by the European Commission to check that they are making progress against corruption. Romania established an independent prosecutor’s office that convicted thousands of officials, but has since backtracked and last year fired the prosecutor. Bulgaria, meanwhile, has been evasive from the start. The current government anti-corruption commission, formed in early 2018, is the third iteration: earlier versions accomplished little, and were dissolved under EU pressure for reform. With its commissioner now under investigation, the new version is just as compromised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boyko Borisov, Bulgaria’s prime minister for most of the past ten years, is a canny operator who has his party entirely in his grip. His position is not under threat. But the apartments scandal has pushed GERB’s popularity below that of the rival Socialist Party in some polls, and it may have wrecked Mr Borisov’s ability to deliver one of his campaign promises: ending the EU special monitoring programme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, Mr Tsvetanov is defending himself by trumpeting his role as an advocate for Bulgaria’s planned purchase of F-16 fighter jets from America. Like the others accused in the apartment scandal, he hopes the words of the psalm hold true: “No evil shall befall you, nor shall any plague come near your dwelling.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 02:09:22 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[From the Catholic faith&#x27;s European heartland, a cry of female protest]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/05/13/from-the-catholic-faiths-european-heartland-a-cry-of-female-protest]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BLP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-13T17:25:00Z&quot;&gt;May 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ACROSS MANY parts of the Christian world, soothing and well-worn sermons were preached on May 12th about the indispensable role of women in upholding the faith: it was, after all, Mother’s Day in many countries. But in Münster, a bastion of German Catholicism, a somewhat different female voice was raised. Catholic women in that city have been co-ordinating a nationwide, week-long “strike” to back their demand for greater female participation in the life of the church, and other reforms. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The protest, which involves staying away from Mass, holding outdoor services and withdrawing voluntary labour from church institutions, has been dubbed “Maria 2.0”. Its banner is a picture of the Virgin Mary with her mouth sealed by sticking-plaster, implying that she has been unfairly silenced. Organisers say the strike, which ends on May 18th, has won support in 100 locations across Germany, and messages of solidarity from other Teutonic places like Austria and Switzerland. “Many words [on this subject] have been exchanged and then disappeared into thin air, and now it is time for a different kind of protest,” one of the prime movers, Andrea Voss-Frick, told a local broadcaster. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The women want quicker progress to a reasonable gender balance in the management posts that are open to lay people; they have been promised a 30% quota by 2023. More controversially, they want their gender to be admitted to the “ordained ministry”. This ultimately means becoming priests, and at a minimum implies being accepted to the slightly lower but still important rank of deacon. They want the rule requiring priests to be celibate to be scrapped. One of their complaints against the celibate male priests who now dominate the church is that even where they are not directly responsible, they have mismanaged and covered up the problem of clerical abuse of minors.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The protest has thrown into sharp relief some dilemmas faced by Catholicism in the prosperous Western places which used to be the faith&amp;#x27;s principal locus, before the centre of gravity started shifting to the developing world. Given that the Catholic faith is a global body with a single leader, the German Catholic church cannot act unilaterally over sensitive matters like ordination and gender, but it cannot ignore pressure from its most dynamic members either. As Thomas Bremer, a professor of ecumenical theology at Münster University puts it: “[The protests are] an indication of the common mood in the mainstream Catholic church in Germany and the bishops will have to relate to it somehow....[given that] the people who took part in these actions, or sympathised, are also the ones who are most active in the church and keep its structures alive.&amp;quot;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nobody, however, should expect a revolution. Pope Francis all but admitted last week that the church’s internal deliberations over female deacons (let alone female priests) were deadlocked. He said a commission which has been examining whether there had been such a thing as ordained deaconesses in the early church had failed to reach any agreed conclusion. Conservatives (including the most conservative of Germany&amp;#x27;s bishops) argue that ordained female deacons clearly did not exist in the early Christian era, and they should not exist now, because that would imply rejecting God&amp;#x27;s revelation to the world through Jesus Christ and his immediate followers. Indeed at least one German bishop has taken the hard-line view that early Christianity differed from other religions of its time in not having female celebrants of its most important rites. This implies that the male monopoly was a conscious choice, not just a cultural reflex. Francis has assured traditionalists that he takes their arguments seriously, but he has cited the shift in Catholic thinking over the death penalty (from conditional acceptance to total rejection) as an example of how “divine revelation” can find new interpetations in a changing world. But that kind of logic is exactly what conservatives find flawed in the current pontiff&amp;#x27;s thinking, and some are determined to restrain his reforming instincts. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The immediate reaction of senior German Catholics to the week-long protest has laid bare the church’s internal divisions . The two mainstream organisations of Catholic women have voiced understanding for the protest. The Bishops’ Conference has expressed willingness to give a sympathetic hearing but lamented the form of protest chosen. At least one bishop, Franz-Josef Bode, and many ordinary priests have said the protest is on balance something to be welcomed. Germany, however, still has plenty of conservative prelates. One, Bishop Rudolf Voderholzer, has said it is a waste of time and energy to consider any changes to the celibate male priesthood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;German-speaking Europe is emerging as an arena for intra-Catholic conflict. Although declining, the German Catholic church is not in freefall, as it seems to be in other parts of western Europe, such as France and even Ireland. In 2017, the number of Catholics in Germany inched downwards by 270,000 to 23.3m but they remain the country&amp;#x27;s largest religious group. Among, for example, upwardly-mobile Catholics born to Irish or east European parents in England, the typical response to abuse scandals or other disappointments has been to give up on the church. In Germany, a significant percentage of Mass-goers, including some well-educated and articulate women, are determined to stay and fight for change. This will not be the last cry of protest from women in the Catholic church. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 May 2019 01:08:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A new podcast shows why some obituaries need sound as well as words]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/13/a-new-podcast-shows-why-some-obituaries-need-sound-as-well-as-words]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BKP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-13T13:00:21Z&quot;&gt;May 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHEN AUDREY HEPBURN died in 1993, newspapers’ obituaries often mentioned the unusual lilt of her voice. The &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; noted that she spoke with the “trace of a European accent”, “a hint of mischief”. Cecil Beaton, in the &lt;em&gt;Telegraph&lt;/em&gt;, described her “singsong cadence that develops into a flat drawl ending in a child-like query”: he thought it had “the quality of heartbreak”. The &lt;em&gt;Los Angeles Times&lt;/em&gt; said that “her melodic, hard-to-place accent and haunting beauty captivated audiences and helped win her the Academy Award as best actress”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Clearly Hepburn’s voice was part of her charm, but its precise sound is hard to capture on the page and hard for the reader to imagine. That is why, 26 years later, Mo Rocca has retold Hepburn’s story, this time in a different medium. On his new podcast, “Mobituaries”, the journalist dedicates 40 minutes to the movie star, tracing her life from her birth in Belgium in 1929, through her film career to her humanitarian work. The episode is interspersed with clips from “Funny Face” and “Breakfast at Tiffany’s”; there is room for her dreamy, melancholic rendition of “Moon River” (pictured). The voices of those who knew her, or who admired her work, are also included. The late Nora Ephron is recorded in an interview from 2011 gushing over Hepburn’s grace and beauty, saying that “there was no one like her, ever”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Free from the demands of the news agenda, “Mobituaries” eulogises individuals, characters and things (one episode contemplates “Neanderthals: death of a human species”; another “Death of a tree: roots of a rivalry”). It is experimental in form—each episode is an unusual blend of interviews, animated discussion, clips and music—and a way for Mr Rocca to explore subjects that intrigue him. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He is astute when picking those subjects. Only a podcast, for instance, could demonstrate the skill of Vaughn Meader, an impersonator of John F. Kennedy. The episode considers Meader’s rise to fame, what his career was like during the 12 months of Kennedy’s presidency, and what happened after the assassination in November 1963. It includes clips from “The First Family”, a hit album which launched Meader to stardom, as well as snippets of later interviews where he expressed exasperation—sadness, almost—at being asked to do “the voice”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Musicians, too, are a natural fit for the airwaves and Sammy Davis Jr., a talented singer and impressionist, is eulogised in the fifth episode. The featured interviewees maintain that it was the emotion Davis conveyed in his music that made his performances so special. The listener hears it for themself: Mr Rocca juxtaposes clips of the same song, performed first by Davis and then by another artist. The difference is surprising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere, Mr Rocca pursues more abstract discussions. An episode on deaths in sitcoms focuses on three types of death: the death of love for a character, a change of actor playing a character and the death of a character within the plot. Mr Rocca explores the phenomenon of “Chuck Cunningham syndrome”, whereby a character simply disappears (named after a figure in “Happy Days” who suffered that fate), with Alan Sepinwall, chief television critic for &lt;em&gt;Rolling Stone&lt;/em&gt;. Clips of dialogue from a number of shows support the discussion, but it is interviews that allow the listener to understand the impact of such passings. Lila Garret, a writer on “Bewitched”, laments that they had to replace actor Dick York due to his poor health. Decades on, Jamiee Foxworth expresses disbelief at her character being written out of “Family Matters” in 1992. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of this is to say that the written obituary has been left behind—a writer’s career, for example, is best weighed up in words, and the ambiguity of language can be useful—but Mr Rocca shows how some stories are enriched by sound. It makes for compelling listening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: The Economist, as well as running an obituary every week in print, also features them on occasion in “The Intelligence”, our daily podcast&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 21:05:50 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The IMF has agreed to break Pakistan’s fall. Again]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/13/the-imf-has-agreed-to-break-pakistans-fall-again]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_fnp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-13T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt; FAMILIARITY, THEY say, breeds contempt. Few countries are as familiar with the IMF as Pakistan. The over-indebted country of 200m people has obtained 21 loans from the fund, as many as Argentina. On May 12th this familiarity deepened further. The country’s government, led by Imran Khan, a former cricket star who heads the Pakistan Tehreek-e-Insaf party, said it had reached a deal with the IMF’s staff to borrow another $6bn over three years. The agreement now awaits formal approval from the fund’s bosses in Washington, and the support of other international lenders, including the World Bank and the Asian Development Bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The loan will relieve Pakistan’s dollar shortage but do little to improve the IMF’s standing in the country. In return for its money, the fund expects the government to raise tax revenues and utility prices—and to let the currency fall, if need be. That will help narrow Pakistan’s wide trade and budget deficits. But it will also curb growth and increase inflation in the short term. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The full agreement has not yet been published. But some details have been released and others leaked to the local press. Pakistan must cut its budget deficit (before debt service) to 0.6% of GDP next fiscal year (which starts in July) from the deficit of over 1.7% that the IMF expects for this year. To meet this goal, the government has reportedly promised to remove tax breaks worth about 350bn rupees ($2.5bn or 1% of GDP) next year and to raise the price of gas and electricity. It has pledged to give the central bank, the State Bank of Pakistan, more autonomy in its fight against inflation (which has increased sharply to over 8%). It will also let market forces dictate the rupee’s exchange rate, which has been devalued by over 18% against the dollar in the past year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To ease the public’s pain, the IMF will allow the government to spend more on welfare schemes, such as a cash-transfer scheme named after Benazir Bhutto, a former prime minister who was assassinated in 2007. But her son, Bilawal Bhutto Zardari, who now leads her party in opposition, seems unimpressed. After the government this month appointed a former IMF official to head the country’s central bank, Mr Bhutto Zardari accused it of surrendering Pakistan’s autonomy. “How can IMF negotiate with IMF?” he asked. A cartoon in the &lt;em&gt;Friday Times&lt;/em&gt;, a local news weekly, showed Christine Lagarde, head of the fund, sitting across the negotiating table from herself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In truth, Mr Khan’s government tried hard—perhaps too hard—to keep its distance from the fund. Instead of agreeing a deal as soon as it came to power in August 2018, it turned for help to friendly powers instead, including Saudi Arabia (which gave $3bn and deferred a similar amount of oil payments), the United Arab Emirates ($3bn) and China, which added another $2.2bn. China is investing heavily in Pakistan’s roads, ports and power plants, building what has been called the China-Pakistan Economic Corridor (CPEC). Some view this lending with suspicion, seeing Pakistan as a victim of China’s “debt-trap diplomacy”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such an assessment seems premature. CPEC spending may have contributed to the increase in Pakistan’s imports (the country’s current-account deficit exceeded 6% of GDP in the year to June 2018). But because this outflow of import spending was presumably matched by an inflow of Chinese capital, it cannot have been responsible for the dangerous dwindling of Pakistan’s foreign-currency reserves over the past year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was instead the result of Pakistan’s own macroeconomic muddle. The previous government pursued both an over-valued exchange rate, which was too strong for Pakistan’s beleaguered exporters, and imprudent fiscal spending, which was too strong for Pakistan’s feeble revenue-raising powers. The dollars provided by Pakistan’s allies in China and the Gulf have temporarily alleviated this problem of falling reserves. But solving it was always going to require policy reforms, which are difficult for bilateral allies to demand or monitor. Better to leave those tasks to the IMF.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not that the IMF will find it easy. Pakistan is a regular taker of the fund’s loans but not a diligent follower of its advice. Many of the reforms it has promised in the latest agreement have been pledged repeatedly before, including widening the tax net, rationalising utility prices and respecting the central bank’s autonomy. When push comes to shove, Pakistan’s governments have been reluctant to follow through, afraid of losing the support of powerful, but lightly taxed, domestic constituencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For their part, the IMF’s staff have been reluctant to cut Pakistan off, for fear of the upheaval that would ensue. “Governments have tried to ‘game’ the IMF, and achieved partial success each time,” write Ehtisham Ahmad and Azizali Mohammed, two former IMF advisers, in their history of the pair’s relationship. Pakistan’s public might dislike the IMF less, if they knew how frequently their leaders disregard it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 21:05:49 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“The president is the fount of all patronage”—Philippine mid-term elections]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/13/the-president-is-the-fount-of-all-patronage-philippine-mid-term-elections]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20199518_blm501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-13T11:30:32Z&quot;&gt;May 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PERSONALITIES, NOT policies, will determine poll results in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/11/the-philippines-mid-term-elections-will-tighten-the-presidents-grip&quot;&gt;Philippines&lt;/a&gt; today, where elections are underway to fill some 18,000 government jobs. Candidates who support the firebrand president, Rodrigo Duterte, such as his daughter, are likely to do well. Also, why is it that as the need for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/04/antibiotics-biotech-firms-are-struggling&quot;&gt;antibiotics&lt;/a&gt; increases, incentives to produce them are diminishing? And a trip to the tiny &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/05/11/a-groundbreaking-show-on-delos-mixes-classical-and-contemporary-art&quot;&gt;Greek island&lt;/a&gt; of Delos for an unusual meeting of modern art and protected antiquity. Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/sparetherodrigo-philippineelections&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 19:06:46 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>