<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Mark Esper looks set to be America’s next defence secretary]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/22/mark-esper-looks-set-to-be-americas-next-defence-secretary]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-22T06:20:14Z&quot;&gt;Jun 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN THE circumstances, President Donald Trump’s announcement on the evening of June 21st that he intended to nominate Mark Esper to be his defence secretary was as good as could be expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Esper, the current army secretary, would not be a distinguished occupant of the office held by Robert McNamara and Robert Gates. Aside from some odd jobs as a congressional staffer and in the Pentagon, the 55-year-old is best known as a successful former defence industry lobbyist. He has no significant foreign policy experience. Yet he has some credentials lacked by Patrick Shanahan, the acting secretary who will shortly leave the Pentagon: including a decade of active duty service in the army and influential admirers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump had previously announced his intention to nominate Mr Shanahan, a former Boeing executive, to become secretary permanently. Yet he refrained from doing so, as doubts about Mr Shanahan mounted. Though accommodating to the president (including in his support for siphoning billions off his own department’s budget in order to pay for some border fencing) he made no significant mark on the government during six months as acting successor to James Mattis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was a relative non-entity in security discussions on Iran, North Korea and elsewhere, even as Mr Trump contemplated launching military strikes on the former. He resigned from the government this week after the &lt;em&gt;Washington Post&lt;/em&gt; revealed serious incidents of domestic violence in Mr Shanahan’s family (His son beat up his ex-wife with a baseball bat). He was to be replaced, on the same acting basis, by Mr Esper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This will now complicate Mr Esper’s nomination. He cannot go through a Senate confirmation process for a job he is holding temporarily. He is therefore expected to be replaced as acting secretary of defence by the navy secretary, Richard Spencer. That would mean Mr Trump is set to have four defence secretaries in three years, a record rate of turnover. The administration’s current length of time without a defence secretary, over six months, is another record. (It also has no ambassador to the United Nations or secretary of the Department of Homeland Security, among other security-related jobs). Yet Mr Esper does at least look able to secure Senate confirmation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was confirmed as army secretary by the Senate with a large majority and has admirers there, including Jim Inhofe, chairman of the Senate Armed Services Committee. Whether Mr Esper could restore the primacy that the Pentagon, the federal government’s biggest department, has traditionally enjoyed in security decision-making is another matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since Mr Mattis resigned, in protest at Mr Trump, the Pentagon has been increasingly sidelined by the National Security Council, under John Bolton, and Secretary of State Mike Pompeo. Mr Trump was &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/21/donald-trump-orders-air-strikes-on-iran-then-cancels-them&quot;&gt;briefly persuaded&lt;/a&gt; to order an air strike on Iran under their belligerent guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fact that Mr Esper graduated from West Point in the same class as Mr Pompeo suggests he might have a firm ally in the secretary of state. He might in that case also be expected to support him in Mr Pompeo’s emerging rivalry with Mr Bolton. Given the national security adviser’s particularly extreme bellicosity, that would probably be for the best. Yet the notion that the secretary of defence could play such as secondary role in cabinet politics is also indicative of how far the Pentagon has fallen in the pecking order since Mr Mattis left it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 18:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Which Democrats can challenge Trump in 2020?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/21/which-democrats-can-challenge-donald-trump]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_blp509.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T17:07:04Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ANNE MCELVOY and John Prideaux, &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s US editor, interview two distinctive hopefuls &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/06/20/donald-trump-launches-a-familiar-sounding-re-election-campaign&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;running to replace Donald Trump&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;Pete Buttigieg&lt;/strong&gt;, the 37-year-old mayor of South Bend, Indiana, assesses America’s role in the world and sets out his plan to redress racial inequality. He also reflects on what he has learned both from Mr Trump and from Leslie Knope, a character in the TV comedy, “Parks and Recreation”. And &lt;strong&gt;Andrew Yang&lt;/strong&gt;, an entrepreneur, champions universal basic income as a way to restore the American Dream. Runtime: 30 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/56ac4e4c-1e63-4337-944a-7f022c054491&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 14:40:25 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How much trouble does Airbus’s new plane pose to Boeing?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/gulliver/2019/06/21/how-much-trouble-does-airbuss-new-plane-pose-to-boeing]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_WBP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T20:38:56Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BOEING, AN American aerospace giant, had once hoped that it would have a good week at this year’s Paris Air Show, which ends on June 23rd. It was expected to launch the 797, a new mid-sized jet to fill the gap in its range between its smaller 737 narrow-body airliner and its much larger 787 and 777 wide-body jets. But instead it was Airbus, its European arch-rival, that launched a plane that fitted this criteria. The A321XLR (the XLR stands for “extra long range”) is a version of the planemaker’s popular narrow-body adapted to boost its range to 5,400 miles (8,700 km). This is made possible by enlarging the aircraft’s centre fuel tank. It is a move that could spell trouble for Boeing’s own plans to fill the middle of the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The A321XLR is a plane “that is of interest to the entire world,” says Francois Caudron, a marketing boss at Airbus. He says the demand for the proposed jet came from airlines flying previous A321 models, which had a range of about 4,000 miles. “The market, asked us, ‘With the A321 now, we can fly from the East Coast of the United States into Europe, but we can’t really go deep into Europe. We can’t go to Rome. So Airbus, can you do something to give us another 500 nautical miles?’” The company responded, he says, with a new fuel tank configuration that added an extra 700 nautical miles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boeing had hoped to answer that same question with its proposed Boeing 797. The American firm had hoped that it would serve as a replacement for the Boeing 757 and 767, two older mid-sized jets. But Mr Caudron says that Airbus also sees the new model as a replacement for Boeing’s 757. Both are narrow-body jets and they offer the same range and similar seating capacities. The XLR also burns 30% less fuel than the 757. Boeing’s proposed New Midsize Airplane (NMA) is instead a wide-body aircraft with two instead of one aisle. It has a slightly larger seating capacity and has more range than the XLR. So it seems much more like a replacement for the Boeing 767 in terms of size and design. All the extra space would certainly make it a more comfortable plane than the XLR for flyers. But it would also be more costly plane to fly, as the wider fuselage increases the amount of drag on the plane. And as passengers increasingly choose the cheapest tickets whatever the service on board an airline is like, that could harm sales.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much has been made of Boeing’s other troubles for the postponement of the 797’s launch. It is true that the continued grounding of its 737 MAX planes, due to safety worried following two crashes of the type in Ethiopia and Indonesia that killed 346 people, does not help. But even before the 737 MAX’s problems, the business case for the 797 was already weak. Analysts have long said that the business plan only made sense if the profits from aftermarket services, such as maintenance checks and spare parts, were enough to make up the losses produced by designing and building the planes. With the XLR eating into the bottom of that market, it has become weaker still.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 06:40:29 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The justices side with a death-row inmate over race and juries]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/21/a-prosecutor-excluded-black-jurors-from-a-murder-trial]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_USP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T22:17:02Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 1986, the Supreme Court ruled 7-2 in &lt;em&gt;Batson v Kentucky&lt;/em&gt; that racial bias in jury selection violates the Sixth and Fourteenth Amendments. A lawyer cannot strike a potential juror from a case without a &amp;quot;neutral&amp;quot; reason, &lt;em&gt;Batson&lt;/em&gt; held, and defendants who suspect racial bias may raise an objection. More than three decades later, on June 21st, the justices &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/18pdf/17-9572_k536.pdf&quot;&gt;again split 7-2&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;em&gt;Flowers v Mississippi,&lt;/em&gt; a case involving a prosecutor who consistently excluded black prospective jurors from the six murder trials of Curtis Flowers, a black Mississippian. Mr Flowers was charged following the murder of four furniture-store employees in 1996. He was charged with each individual murder in the first four trials and for all four deaths in the fifth and sixth trials. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The majority opinion in &lt;em&gt;Flowers&lt;/em&gt;, penned by Justice Brett Kavanaugh, stretched to 31 pages but, as it said, broke “no new legal ground”. The ruling “simply enforce[s] and reinforce[s] &lt;em&gt;Batson&lt;/em&gt; by applying it to the extraordinary facts of this case”. The facts are, indeed, striking. In the six trials, Doug Evans, the prosecutor, used peremptory challenges (for which a lawyer need offer no reason, as opposed to a strike &amp;quot;for cause&amp;quot; that does cite a justification) to eliminate 41 of the 42 black prospective jurors. In the sixth trial, the one at issue in &lt;em&gt;Flowers&lt;/em&gt;, he excluded five of six. In the apparent hope of finding “pretexual reasons to strike” them, Justice Kavanaugh wrote, Mr Evans “engaged in dramatically disparate questioning of black and white prospective jurors”. And he excluded one black potential juror, Carolyn Wright, for reasons that should have resulted in a challenge to white jurors for whom the only relevant difference seemed to be their race. Prosecutors said Ms Wright was struck because she knew a few witnesses and worked at the same WalMart as Mr Flowers&amp;#x27;s father. But several white potential jurors were also familiar with players in the trial and faced less questioning and no challenge. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the first three trials, the Mississippi Supreme Court chastised Mr Evans for violating Mr Flowers’s right to an impartial jury and reversed the convictions. The fourth and fifth trials ended in hung juries, with no verdict. But Mississippi’s high court found no problem with Mr Evans’ behaviour the sixth time. In the latest trial, there were 26 potential jurors, six black and 20 white. The prosecution used five of its six peremptory strikes against black prospective jurors, resulting in 11 white jurors and one black juror. When Mr Flowers raised a challenge to the fairness of his trial under &lt;em&gt;Batson&lt;/em&gt;, the Mississippi Supreme Court rejected it. The United States Supreme Court then told the state court to take another look at the matter in light of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2016/05/24/the-supreme-court-cracks-down-on-racist-prosecutors&quot;&gt;its 2016 decision&lt;/a&gt; in&lt;em&gt; Foster v Chatman, &lt;/em&gt;another jury-discrimination decision. After a second examination, the Mississippi Supreme Court again sided with the prosecution. But the vote was 5-4, and a dissenting judge said he believed the majority had badly erred. “I cannot conclude that Flowers received a fair trial”, he wrote.The five-judge majority “completely disregard[ed] the constitutional right of prospective jurors to be free from a racially discriminatory selection process”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After walking through the justification and implications of &lt;em&gt;Batson&lt;/em&gt; and the facts of Mr Flowers’s case, Justice Kavanaugh concluded the four dissenting judges on the Mississippi Supreme Court had it right. The state’s case against Mr Flowers was “motivated in substantial part by discriminatory intent”. “Equal justice under law”—the words carved into marble above the familiar pillars of the Supreme Court’s main entrance—”requires a criminal trial free of racial discrimination in the jury selection process”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justice Kavanaugh’s thorough opinion attracted the votes of Chief Justice John Roberts and the four liberal-leaning justices. Justice Samuel Alito joined the judgment but wrote separately to emphasise that &lt;em&gt;Flowers&lt;/em&gt; is “a highly unusual case” and “likely one of a kind”. If not for the “unique combinations of circumstances present here”, Justice Alito would have affirmed the Mississippi Supreme Court’s ruling. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justices Clarence Thomas and Neil Gorsuch did not find any circumstances worthy of vindicating Mr Flowers’s constitutional rights. In a biting 42-page dissent, Justice Thomas recounted the 1996 killings in detail and blamed his seven colleagues for “needlessly prolong[ing] the suffering of four victims’ families” and disrespecting Mississippi’s state courts. (The majority may have sided with Mr Flowers, the dissent speculates, to “boost its self-esteem”.) Looking through the record, Justice Thomas finds no evidence of racist prosecutorial intent. “Any competent prosecutor would have exercised the same strikes as the state did in this trial”, he wrote. In a section of the dissent Justice Gorsuch did not join, Justice Thomas attacked &lt;em&gt;Batson&lt;/em&gt; itself: the ruling “was suspect when it was announced, and I am even less confident of it today”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 05:40:34 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[US-Iran tensions threaten the world’s most important oil-shipping route]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/21/us-iran-tensions-threaten-the-worlds-most-important-oil-shipping-route]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_wom945.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE STRAIT of Hormuz, a narrow stretch of water connecting the Persian Gulf to the rest of the world’s oceans, has long been recognised as the most important choke-point for global oil supplies. Accounting for about a third of the world’s sea-borne oil (and a fifth of the world’s total oil exports), the strait links oil and gas producers in the Middle East with consumers around the globe, including those in Europe, Asia and America. In 2016, according to America’s Energy Information Administration, the waterway carried some 19m barrels of crude and other petroleum products a day. Were it to be blocked, the world’s supply of oil would fall, and prices would spike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The risk of such an event is growing, and oil prices are rising as a result. In May last year, President Donald Trump pulled out of a nuclear deal with Iran and reimposed crippling sanctions on the country. Hassan Rouhani, Iran’s president, responded by threatening to block oil shipments; if Iran could not export oil, nor could others. Tensions have escalated further in recent days. On June 13th two ships were attacked in the Gulf of Oman. On June 20th an American surveillance drone flying over the strait was shot down by Iran’s Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps. After tweeting that “Iran made a very big mistake!”, Mr Trump &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/21/donald-trump-orders-air-strikes-on-iran-then-cancels-them&quot;&gt;reportedly ordered&lt;/a&gt; military strikes on Iran—only to change his mind hours later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One interpretation of the recent attacks on ships—if they were carried out by Iran, as America claims—is that they are intended to signal Iran’s readiness to act on its threat to block the waterway. The country could try to block the strait using speed boats, anti-ship missiles and mines. But doing so would probably be a desperate act of last resort. Iran would be risking a war with America and its regional allies. And military analysts think that America’s Fifth Fleet, based in Bahrain, would be able to re-open the waterway within weeks. In the meantime, at least some of the oil from Saudi Arabia and the UAE could be rerouted via pipelines away from the Strait of Hormuz.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 05:40:33 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Which Democrats can challenge Trump in 2020?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/21/which-democrats-can-challenge-trump-in-2020]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_blp509.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T17:07:04Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ANNE MCELVOY and John Prideaux, &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s US editor, interview two distinctive hopefuls &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/06/20/donald-trump-launches-a-familiar-sounding-re-election-campaign&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;running to replace Donald Trump&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;Pete Buttigieg&lt;/strong&gt;, the 37-year-old mayor of South Bend, Indiana, assesses America’s role in the world and sets out his plan to redress racial inequality. He also reflects on what he has learned both from Mr Trump and from Leslie Knope, a character in the TV comedy, “Parks and Recreation”. And &lt;strong&gt;Andrew Yang&lt;/strong&gt;, an entrepreneur, champions universal basic income as a way to restore the American Dream. Runtime: 30 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/56ac4e4c-1e63-4337-944a-7f022c054491&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 02:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A large share of Republicans hold progressive economic views]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/21/a-large-share-of-republicans-hold-progressive-economic-views]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_USP506_facebook.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T15:01:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN RECENT decades, the word “Democrat” has become synonymous with progressive economics and “Republican” with fiscal conservatism. Those on the left are believed to be in favour of big government—high social spending, generous welfare and an ambitious regulatory scope—and those on the right opposed. This view is not entirely accurate. According to a new study of voter attitudes in 2019, Republicans are more positive about state intervention than conventional wisdom suggests, but the party is divided. Lower-income Republicans have much more progressive attitudes on economics than wealthy members of their party. This should enable enterprising Democratic leaders to experiment with new ways of appealing to Republicans, especially those who changed their allegiance from Barack Obama to Donald Trump in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.voterstudygroup.org/publication/on-the-money&quot;&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; comes from the Democracy Fund Voter Study Group, a collection of public opinion researchers. Lee Drutman, Vanessa Williamson and Felicia Wong, political scientists, found that economic attitudes among Americans affiliated with the Republican Party are deeply divided by income level, with lower-income Republicans holding more progressive economic views. Factoring in only economic preferences—for raising the minimum wage, allowing workers to unionise and enacting government policies that decrease economic inequality—a significant share of Republicans would look like Democrats. “About 19% of Republicans held economic policy positions closer to the average Democrat than the average Republican”, say the authors, while “just 9% of Democrats held economic positions closer to the average Republican”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are many Republicans an astute Democrat could target, they reckon. Only 71% of “economically left Republicans”—who make up about 7% of the electorate overall—have pledged their support for Mr Trump in 2020, compared to 90% of economically right-leaning Republicans. Furthermore, according to the report, Democrats made gains among left-leaning independents in the 2018 mid-terms which could amount to a one percentage point increase in vote share next year. Though small, this increase would have been more than enough to tip the scales against Mr Trump in Midwestern states in 2016. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Candidates including Elizabeth Warren (pictured), a senator from Massachusetts, are betting that they can win these voters by putting class struggle rather than identity at the forefront of their campaigns. Ms Warren has focused her campaign on a tax on the super-wealthy, reforming the campaign finance system and corporate tax-dodging, for example. Last week, she unveiled a plan specifically designed to appeal to disaffected voters in the heartland. Her “Plan for Economic Patriotism” promises to deliver “faster growth, stronger American industry, and more good American jobs” instead of catering to companies that have “no particular allegiance to America”. Her patriotic messaging could tug at the nationalistic heartstrings Mr Trump strummed in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To succeed, Ms Warren’s approach relies on the de-emphasis of the politics of race. Anti-immigrant attitudes had a much bigger influence on Americans’ vote choice in 2016 than economic attitudes did. The odds that Mr Trump—who began his last campaign with a rhetorical assault on Mexican immigrants—will continue to rely on dog-whistle politics is high. On June 17th, he tweeted a proposal to expel millions of immigrants without documentation. The following day, when he launched his re-election campaign he mentioned immigrants, his border wall or immigration reform at least 20 times. By keeping issues of race and immigration on voters’ minds, Mr Trump would decrease the chance of a class-based message breaking through.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if 2016 was about how Republicans exploited social polarisation and last year’s mid-terms were about how Democrats exploited attitudes toward health care, the 2020 election could be decided at least in part by Republicans’ divide on economic attitudes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will Elizabeth Warren get the opportunity to try? This week, a survey of 1,500 Americans conducted on behalf of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; by YouGov, a polling firm, found that 26% of the party’s primary voters prefer Joe Biden, the former vice-president, over any other candidate. But Ms Warren is on an upward swing. YouGov&amp;#x27;s poll was the second one in which Ms Warren polled even or higher than Senator Bernie Sanders of Vermont. And her position may improve again after she appears in the first Democratic primary debate on June 26th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 02:39:55 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The race to become Britain’s next PM]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/21/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HERESA MAY&lt;/small&gt; stepped down as leader of the Conservative Party on June 7th, but she will remain as prime minister until her successor is chosen. The first round of voting among Tory MPs took place on June 13th. In the final round on June 20th, only Boris Johnson and Jeremy Hunt survived to progress to the last stage of the contest, a ballot of the 160,000 or so members of the party. The winner will be announced in the week beginning July 22nd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Betfair Exchange, a gambling website, has been tracking punters’ predictions on the next Tory leader. According to the wisdom of the betting crowd, a handful of candidates stand out. But there is only one clear frontrunner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anne McElvoy, host of &lt;i&gt;The Economist asks&lt;/i&gt;, spoke to Jeremy Hunt and Rory Stewart about their leadership plans: &lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-whocanleadbritainthroughbrexit-&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.betfair.com/exchange/plus/politics&quot;&gt;Betfair Exchange&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 02:39:54 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The political nausea when feelings replace facts]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/21/the-political-nausea-when-feelings-replace-facts]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_OPP504_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T14:46:47Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SINCE THE 17th century Western societies have elevated reason above feeling as the basis for political action. Emphasising reason in this way presumed that it could be neatly separated from feelings altogether, that they were discrete categories. Politicians who acted on reason alone were virtuous, whereas those who exploited emotions and feelings were deemed to be unscrupulous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this dimension of the Enlightenment has “run aground”, argues William Davies, a political economist at Goldsmiths, University of London. His latest book, “Nervous States”, documents the struggle between “reason” and “feelings” in politics. It is very much a book for our times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Davies argues that in pursuit of reason, European countries founded an intellectual architecture that largely survives to this day; the numerous Royal Societies, academies of science, universities, learned journals and newspapers (such as &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;, launched in 1843) that codified knowledge and developed what came to be known as logico-deductive modes of reasoning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The high priests of these institutions were “experts”, and, as Mr Davies, writes, “their ability to keep feelings separate from their observations was one of their distinguishing traits.” In public life still, he writes, “an accusation of being emotional traditionally carries the implication that someone has lost objectivity and given way to irrational forces.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp503_0.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But for a variety of reasons, some medical/scientific, some sociological and others political, neat distinctions between reason and feelings have broken down. As Mr Davies argues in his book, “Experts and facts no longer seem capable of settling arguments to the extent that they once did.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, expertise itself is under assault in the age of Trump and Brexit. A lot of polling demonstrates how trust in the intellectual architecture of reason has steadily dwindled, including trust in most professions, and most particularly trust in government, politicians and the media. Instead, people are now allowed to trust and express their own feelings as “alternative facts”. President Donald Trump, for instance, makes much of how he will trust his gut more than any adviser.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Davies argues, convincingly, that one reason for this is that, for all its impressive data collection and sophisticated modelling and analysis, “the facts produced by experts and technocrats simply do not capture lived reality for many people”. He attributes this largely to rising inequality in the West.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For instance, it does not matter how much an expert bangs on about rising aggregate employment levels and levels of inward investment if the individual does not feel better about themselves. “If there is one thing more important than prosperity to people’s well-being then it is self-esteem. Those suffering a collapse of self-esteem, for whatever reason, are often the most receptive to nationalist rhetoric,” he writes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For this reason, Mr Davies writes, “we have to take people’s feelings seriously as political issues, and not simply dismiss them as irrational.” This, surely, was Hillary Clinton’s mistake in fighting Donald Trump in 2016, hence her unfortunate reference to the “deplorables”, those most likely to vote for Mr Trump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Likewise, in Britain the campaign to remain in the EU in the lead-up to the referendum in 2016 relied entirely on tendentious economic forecasting at the expense of any emotional appeal to a shared European future. The Brexit campaign was the exact opposite, relying almost exclusively on appeals to “feelings” of nostalgia and patriotism. It was also, of course, a vivid rebellion against the tyranny of experts and the “mainstream media”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190622_opp502_0.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Democracies are being transformed, Mr Davies writes, “by the power of feelings in ways that cannot be ignored or reversed. This is our reality now.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So how should “bravado rationalists”, as Mr Davies calls them, respond to this new era? One response would be to double down on scientific objectivity and institutions in even bolder terms. “In the face of nationalist reaction, this strategy offers faith in facts as the only means of resistance,” he writes. “It assumes that the unrivalled capacity of rationalist argument among qualified experts will save us from demagogues and nationalists.” But as Mr Davies makes clear, this project has been undermined progressively, particularly now by the populist right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what would an alternative construct look like, a new philosophy of knowledge to inform our politics for these troubled times? We sat down with Mr Davies to pick his brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, argues Mr Davies, it behoves liberals and rationalists to acknowledge where things went wrong. Often they have placed too much faith in statistics and forecasts that proved erroneous. This undermined faith in the whole project of evidence-based analysis more generally: “Macro-economic indicators have been justifiably pulled apart in recent years,” argues Mr Davies. He characterises the era of the Great Moderation, roughly the period from the mid-1990s to 2007, as “an era of expecting numbers to do politics for us”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Governments, such as Britain’s New Labour, grew increasingly technocratic, staffed by policy wonks. Consequently they suffered from a deep ignorance of their own country, a situation that might have been rectified by recourse to other disciplines such as anthropology and ethnography. He particularly references the famous study of Tea Party America, “Strangers in Their Own Land”, by anthropologist Arlie Russell Hochshild.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Secondly, Mr Davies argues that there is now a lot of evidence to show that “story-telling” has the power to sway peoples’ opinions as much as statistics. Story-telling can be used just as well to accompany evidence-based politics and arguments as it can be abused by populists. Story-telling is what made the great wordsmiths, such as Winston Churchill, so successful; what these politicians are asking their listeners is not so much “do my words match up to reality?”, as “do my words mobilise you?”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equally, argues Mr Davies, rationalists are lagging behind the fact that we have moved from a “verbal public sphere” to an “image-based” sphere, where photos, videos and the attendant social-media channels predominate. People have not become more emotional over time, they do not have more feelings than they used to; rather they now have an infinite variety of ways to express those feelings in real time, on smart-phones for instance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Feeling has entered politics mainly for technological reasons,” argues Mr Davies, and populism is all about quick, unfiltered responses to events. As a riposte, rationalists can use infographics and data-visualisation as a way of presenting statistics and evidence, but, Mr Davies warns, these also risk “triggering” people into knee-jerk responses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lastly, advises Mr Davies, we should cherish those institutions, imperfect though they may be, that aspire to objectivity and truth-telling. Free marketeers, for instance, might deride the BBC for its funding formula, relying as it does on a taxpayer levy, but these concerns should now be outweighed by its contribution to maintaining a reasonable consensus on what constitutes real facts and news—a consensus that has already largely broken down in America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a quid pro quo, institutions have to be more obviously free of political influence than ever before. For a public broadcaster like the BBC, this means no longer appointing former politicians, such as Labour’s James Purnell, to top positions. It seems a reasonable trade-off to survive the post-truth world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If feelings have come to dominate politics to the detriment of good governance and evidence-led policy-making, then the rationalists need to reassert themselves; to show some emotion and take governance back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 23:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Toy Story 4” is another enjoyable, nostalgic adventure]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/21/toy-story-4-is-another-enjoyable-nostalgic-adventure]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_BKP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T12:51:58Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ONE OF the magical things about Pixar’s “Toy Story” films is the way they balance the comfort of the old and the shock of the new. The series’ first instalment, released in 1995, was also the first ever feature film to be rendered solely using three-dimensional computer-generated imagery (CGI), so it was as cutting-edge as cinema could be. But “Toy Story” was also an ode to sunlit childhoods, with such vintage toys as Mr Potatohead and Slinky Dog. Its lead character was Woody (voiced by Tom Hanks), a cowboy rag doll manufactured in the 1950s, and there weren’t many children playing with those in 1995. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the series’ fourth episode, “Toy Story 4”, the animation is more photorealistic than ever. Images of fairground lights and muddy rainwater rushing down gutters, for instance, are indistinguishable from footage shot with a camera. But, on this occasion, the film’s technical innovation is outweighed by its love of the past. Set largely in a quaint town of parks and carnivals, “Toy Story 4” never acknowledges that children now play with phones and tablets as much as they play with dolls, or that the toys they enjoy are often tied into “The Avengers”, “Star Wars”, “Harry Potter” and “Pokémon”. The setting also seems to be devoid of security cameras and webcams. How else could so many sentient toys scurry so cavalierly around playgrounds and along highways, day and night, without anyone noticing?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The plot has a retro ring to it, too: in many respects, it is the same old “Toy Story”. The film begins with Woody realising again that his owner likes another toy more than she likes him. In the 1995 version, the owner was Andy and the usurper was Buzz Lightyear (Tim Allen). In the 2019 version, the owner is Bonnie, and the favoured toy is, well, all of them except Woody: when Bonnie constructs imaginary towns, she leaves him in the cupboard. If that weren’t humiliating enough, she fashions a new toy (Tony Hale) out of a white plastic spork and names him Forky. He believes that he is a piece of cutlery, not a toy, just as Buzz believed he was an astronaut. And when Forky absconds from the family’s campervan during a driving holiday, Woody goes after him, just as he went after Buzz. Soon, his search-and-rescue mission leads him to an antique shop where he hopes to find Bo Peep (Annie Potts), his love interest in the first two films. Instead, he finds Gabby Gabby (Christina Hendricks), a doll who is planning to revitalise herself via the toy equivalent of organ harvesting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Considering how much of the film unfolds in an antique shop, it’s conceivable that one of the screenplay’s many drafts—there are ten credited screenwriters—may have admitted that toys just aren’t as central to childhood as they once were. The shop-owner even lets her granddaughter take Woody away when she finds him on the floor because, she says, “nobody ever buys the toys.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the film-makers don’t have the courage to confront their characters’ obsolescence—or, for that matter, their films’ obsolescence. A few years after “Toy Story 3” came out, a rival cartoon, “The Lego Movie”, sketched a much sharper and more accurate picture of how modern children play. What “Toy Story 4” opts for instead are the usual breakneck chases, death-defying leaps, snappy catchphrases, emotional reunions and nostalgic, warm images of America at its most wholesome. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That doesn’t mean it isn’t enjoyable. Even if it is weaker than the previous “Toy Story” episodes, the film is still a hugely endearing and consistently funny family adventure—and that can’t be said of many films which are the fourth in a series, animated or otherwise. What “Toy Story 4” offers, though, is the sentimental pleasure of getting a favourite old plaything from the attic, rather than the thrill of unwrapping something new.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Toy Story 4” is released worldwide on June 21st&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 20:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>