<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[The joy of absence]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/12/the-joy-of-absence]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_wbp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;RONALD REAGAN famously quipped that “it’s true hard work never killed anybody, but I figure, why take the chance?” Beyond a certain level, extra effort seems to be self-defeating. Studies suggest that, after around 50 hours a week, employee productivity declines sharply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that doesn’t stop some managers from demanding that workers stay chained to their desk for long periods. At the blood-testing firm Theranos, Sunny Balwani, boyfriend of the founder, Elizabeth Holmes, had an obsession with employee hours, and would tour the engineering department at 7.30pm to check people were at their desks. All those hours were wasted when the company eventually collapsed (prosecutors have charged Ms Holmes with fraud).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jack Ma, the founder of Alibaba, the Chinese e-commerce group, recently praised the 996 model, where employees work from 9am to 9pm, six days a week, as a “great opportunity”. To be fair, Mr Ma said employers should not mandate such hours. Still presenteeism is the curse of the modern office worker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will be days when you do not have much to do; perhaps because you are waiting for someone else in a different department, or a different company, to respond to a request. As the clock ticks past 5pm, there may be no purpose in staying at your desk. But you can see your boss hard at work and, more important, they can see you. So you make an effort to look busy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of this may be a self-perpetuating cycle. If bosses do not like to go home before their underlings, and underlings fear leaving before their bosses, everyone is trapped. Staff may feel that they will not get a pay rise, or a promotion, if they are not seen to be putting in maximum effort. This is easily confused with long hours. Managers, who are often no good at judging employees’ performance, use time in the office as a proxy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The consequence is often wasted effort. To adjust the old joke about the Soviet Union: “We pretend to work and managers pretend to believe us.” Rather than work hard, you toil to make bosses think that you are. Leaving a jacket on your office chair, walking around purposefully with a clipboard, and sending out emails at odd hours are three of the best known tricks. After a while this can result in collective self-delusion that it is actual work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But presenteeism has more serious consequences. It is perhaps most prevalent in Japan, where people attend the office even when they are in discomfort. In doing so, they are neither doing themselves, or their employers, any favours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As well as reduced productivity, this can mean greater medical expenses for the employer. According to a study in the Journal of Occupation and Environmental Medicine, these costs can be six times higher for employers than the costs of absenteeism among workers. To take one example, research published in the British Medical Journal found that Japanese employees with lower back pain were three times more likely to turn up for work than in Britain. As a result, those workers were more likely to experience greater pain and to suffer from depression. What could be more depressing than being in pain, and feeling trapped at work?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of this is to say that employers are not entitled to expect workers to be in the office for a decent proportion of time. Inevitably there will be a need for some (preferably short) meetings. Dealing with colleagues face-to-face creates a feeling of camaraderie, allows for a useful exchange of ideas and enables workers to have a better sense of their mutual needs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the grand sweep of humanity, presenteeism is a recent phenomenon. Before the industrial era, most people worked in their own farm or workshop and were paid for the amount they produced. Factories emerged because new machines were much more efficient than cottage-industry methods, and only a large employer with capital could afford them. Suddenly, workers were paid not for their output but for their time, and were required to clock in and out. But modern machinery like smartphones and laptops is portable. It can be used as easily at home as in the office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turning an office into a prison, with inmates allowed home for the evenings, does nothing for creativity that is increasingly demanded of office workers as routine tasks are automated. To be productive you need presence of mind, not being present in the flesh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 06:13:23 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Russia’s military gamble in Syria is paying off handsomely]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/12/russias-military-gamble-in-syria-is-paying-off-handsomely]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_map001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE GREAT victory train clattered across eight time zones and back before groaning into a military-exhibition ground outside Moscow last month. It pulled car after car of trophies from Syria, as well as wagon-loads of patriotism and conspiracy theories. Here was a pockmarked American-made Humvee; there pickup-trucks turned into battering-rams for suicide car-bombers. Various home-made bombs included one hidden in a can of Russian beer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amid the fanfare of military bands, veterans on the platform recounted how Russia had intervened in 2015 to stop Syria falling into the hands of jihadists, notably Islamic State (IS), who had been secretly armed by NATO. “A lot of what you’re seeing here could have been delivered directly by the Americans,” explains one guide. “It’s not just my opinion. Many think so.” Never mind that Russia fought mostly against non-IS groups, or that America did much to crush the IS “caliphate”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another display purported to show a chemical-weapons lab with barrels of precursors labelled in English—an apparent attempt to accuse rebels of using chlorine gas in Douma in 2018. Western powers blamed the regime of Bashar al-Assad and bombed Syrian air bases in retaliation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Propaganda aside, Russia is elated with its victory. It saved Mr Assad at relatively small cost to itself, became the kingmaker in Syria and returned as a power-broker in the Middle East for the first time since the dissolution of the Soviet Union. All this is gratifyingly different from the experience of America, whose invasion of Iraq turned into a bloody debacle; or of western Europeans, whose air campaign in Libya to topple the dictator Muammar Qaddafi sundered the country. Most important, breaking America’s hegemony in the Middle East shows that Russia is not merely a “regional power”, as Barack Obama once put it, but a global one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The “Syrian Breakthrough” tour revives the long tradition of &lt;em&gt;agitpoezd&lt;/em&gt; (agit-trains). Stalin, for instance, used them to show off Soviet victories against the Nazis. When the latest train arrived in Moscow, young army cadets clambered onto a tank chanting “To Berlin!” Many Russians—more than one million, according to the authorities—have come to ogle the loot. “They’re fighting not against some tribesmen shooting arrows but against people with serious technical capabilities—tanks, armoured vehicles, and mortars,” said Anton Sidorov, a salesman and veteran of the Russian navy, who brought his four-year-old son. To stop terrorism in Russia, he added, “we have to battle terrorism outside of our territory.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russia has surprised itself with its prowess. Many Russians recall how the intervention in Afghanistan in 1979 helped destroy the Soviet Union. Russia’s war in Georgia in 2008 exposed many inadequacies, not least the poor performance of the air force. Its annexation of Crimea and its undeclared war in eastern Ukraine in 2014 brought Western sanctions and isolation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The military success was much bigger than anyone expected,” says Fyodor Lukyanov, a foreign-policy adviser to the Russian government, “Russia demonstrated in Syria that it has a degree of efficiency in using military force, compared with the two previous experiences in Georgia and Ukraine. Politically, it was an even bigger surprise.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moscow has turned into a centre for Middle Eastern diplomacy. In 2017 King Salman became the first Saudi monarch to visit Russia. Binyamin Netanyahu, Israel’s prime minister, has met Vladimir Putin, Russia’s president, a dozen times since the intervention. Russian diplomats who spent decades as spectators to America’s management of the Israeli-Palestinian peace process delight in knowing that America must now watch as Russia, Turkey and Iran negotiate the future of Syria. Deaf to warnings of a looming humanitarian catastrophe, the Syrian government, backed by Russian bombers, this month resumed operations to retake the province of Idlib, the last major area still in rebel hands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Strikingly, Russia has been able to keep friends with all sides of the region’s bitter rivalries: Israel and Iran; Turkey and the Kurds; Saudi Arabia and Qatar. For Russian military commanders, the war in Syria has been a proving ground for new tactics and weapons, and a showcase for arms exports.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russia and Saudi Arabia struck an unprecedented deal in early 2017 to limit oil output. The so-called OPEC-plus accord has helped lift prices, which fell below $30 a barrel in 2016, to the current level above $60. In Mr Lukyanov’s view, the deal would not have been possible without Russia’s enhanced regional status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a result, there is a new swagger about Russia in the wider world. Mr Putin has used his Syrian success for advantage elsewhere. He plans to host a summit with African leaders in October, and has sent advisers and private military companies to help some of its despots. Russia is also helping to prop up the regime of Nicolás Maduro in Venezuela. These days it is America that complains of Russia meddling in its sphere of influence, not the other way around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This contest is less the product of ideological conviction than of self-interest. But if America until recently championed democracy, Russia is becoming, in effect, the foremost defender of autocracy—at least in the view of Arab rulers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kremlin-watchers reckon little of all this had been in Mr Putin’s mind when he ordered his forces into Syria. His priority had been to avert the collapse of Mr Assad’s regime, and the risk that Syria might become an exporter of jihadism to Russia. Another reason was to break out of the diplomatic isolation he faced over Ukraine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How did Russia succeed where others failed? In part, it absorbed the lessons of America in Iraq, relying mostly on its air power and on local proxies on the ground: the Syrian army, Iranian troops, Hizbullah fighters from Lebanon and others. It also drew on the experience of Arabists nurtured by the late Yevgeny Primakov, a former foreign and prime minister. “Damascus is closer to Sochi than it is to most European cities,” says one Russian think-tanker. “Russia feels a close connection to the Middle East, partly because of the legacy of the Byzantine empire.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Israel remembers that the Soviet Union had been the first country to recognise the infant Jewish state &lt;em&gt;de jure&lt;/em&gt;, and provided it with vital weapons via Czechoslovakia. Saudis note that the Soviet Union had been the first country to establish diplomatic relations with the new Saudi kingdom in 1926 (alas, the Soviet ambassador was executed during Stalin’s purges).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cynicism plays a part. Mr Putin is less troubled than Western leaders are by public opinion or civil-society groups making a fuss about Russia’s actions. He does not ask about democracy and human rights. “We have a common interest in non-intervention in our internal affairs,” notes one Arab diplomat. In the view of Arab leaders, Mr Obama forsook Egypt’s dictator, Hosni Mubarak, whereas Mr Putin stood by the vile Mr Assad. Even if Donald Trump is more partial to strongmen, they find him mercurial. “We disagree with Russia on many things,” says the diplomat. “But when Putin makes a commitment, he delivers.” Strangely, Israeli and Gulf leaders keep mum about Russia’s role in providing air power to the reviled “Shia axis”; instead, they say Russia is a counterweight to Iran’s influence in Syria.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the main reason that Russia can talk to all players in the region is that it is not America. For most of them America remains the all-important protector, so their dismay is all the greater when it appears to be losing interest in them. Israeli and Gulf leaders feared betrayal when Mr Obama negotiated a deal in 2015 to limit Iran’s nuclear programme in exchange for a partial lifting of sanctions. They care much less that Russia is selling Iran civilian nuclear technology, or has set up barter deals to help Iran circumvent sanctions. If the region’s rulers are flirting with Russia, it is mostly to regain America’s commitment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amid the swelling pride in Moscow, there is also much nervousness. Russia’s land may be vast but its economy is only the size of South Korea’s. Russians’ real disposable incomes have fallen five years running. For all the shows of patriotism, support for the war is soft: according to the Levada Centre, an independent pollster, 35% do not approve of Russia’s policy in Syria, against 51% who do; most think the military operation ought to be wound up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Opinion could turn more hostile if things go wrong in Syria, which Russian officials know is all too possible. They are learning another lesson from America’s ill-begotten war in Iraq: it is easier to win a short-term military victory than create a lasting political settlement. Few outsiders want to pay to repair the damage it has wreaked. And Russia is ensnared by its local ally. Mr Assad is strong enough to resist Russian entreaties to make political concessions, but too weak to be threatened without risking his collapse. Then there are more catastrophic risks: a confrontation with Turkey over Idlib, say, or a Turkish invasion to push back Syrian Kurds, or even a war between Israel and Iran. A surprising number of Russian experts worry about the venture “collapsing like a house of cards”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short, the power that Mr Putin tries to project abroad, in the hope that it will enhance his standing at home, is brittle. The multipolar world he has sought to bring about may yet leave Russia on the sidelines; it boasts neither the military power of America nor the economic strength of China. Tellingly, few in Moscow want to see America leave Afghanistan, fearing that might destabilise Russia’s southern flank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Right now, Mr Putin may like patriots chanting “To Berlin!” The danger for him is that they may yet start crying: “Bring our boys home!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 13 May 2019 06:13:22 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Some American carriers are installing cameras on their in-flight entertainment screens]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/gulliver/2019/05/10/some-american-carriers-are-installing-cameras-on-their-in-flight-entertainment-screens]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_BLP511.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-10T12:37:19Z&quot;&gt;May 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;FLYERS TRAVELLING ON one of America’s major airlines may soon notice a mysterious item on the back of the set in front: a small sticker under the in-flight entertainment screen. These stickers have appeared as the result of a public outcry in recent months over the unpublicised installation of video cameras on these screens on at least four airlines. The fuss began in February on a Singapore Airlines flight, when a passenger noticed what appeared to be a camera lens by her video screen. Her husband, a cybersecurity expert, tweeted a photo of it. The airline confirmed that it was a camera. On some of their planes with newer entertainment systems, the fitters of the interiors had installed devices with an embedded camera. But Singapore Airlines said that the cameras had been “disabled” and they had no plans to use them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;That did nothing to quell public anxiety, which only grew with news reports later the same month that some screens on the big three American carriers, American Airlines, Delta Air Lines and United Airlines, also had cameras on-board. In March two American senators demanded that eight American carriers disclose whether they were using cameras to monitor passengers and whether passengers were being informed. The airlines insisted that the cameras were not operational, but they scrambled to cover them up anyway. United and Delta recently began covering all the cameras on their entertainment systems. American has also announced plans to do the same.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That ought to end the panic. But it also raises the question of why people were worried about these cameras in the first place. Of course it would be wrong for airlines to spy on their customers. But the threat to privacy from this is nothing compared to the greater threat of hackers gaining access to the webcams on laptops in people’s homes, or to virtual assistants such as Amazon’s Alexa. Aircraft, particularly in economy class, are not private places. Anything a passenger says or does can be witnessed by dozens of people. It is undeniably important for airlines to protect passengers’ privacy when it comes to their personal data—and a strict legal requirement in Europe with so-called GDPR rules. But a passenger’s behaviour while sitting in an aircraft seat—snoring, or watching a low-brow movie, or maybe picking one’s nose—is just not all that private to begin with, nor is it of much interest to companies or hackers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bigger concern is what flyers would actually do with these cameras, if they became operational. The chief technology officer of Panasonic, one of the world’s biggest manufacturers of airline-entertainment systems, which recently rolled out a new generation of their devices containing cameras and microphones, told the &lt;em&gt;New York Times &lt;/em&gt;that these devices were intended to eventually allow airlines to offer seat-to-seat or plane-to-ground video calls. Imagine a plane on which half the passengers are video-chatting to friends a few rows away or relatives back home, if you want to read a book or do some work quietly. That sounds far more disturbing than any hypothetical spying. So, on second thought, it might be a good idea to keep those cameras covered up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 03:12:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why the public prefers eccentric Christians to archbishops]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/05/10/why-the-public-prefers-eccentric-christians-to-archbishops]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_BLP513.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-10T11:31:12Z&quot;&gt;May 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;CHRISTIANITY IS the world’s most popular religion, with over 2bn followers, according to the Pew Research Centre, an American think-tank. It is the historically predominant faith in most prosperous democracies. Yet over the past century, only a limited number of Christians have gained commanding respect and influence for the way they lived out their faith, in their own countries and beyond. And many—most, even—have been idiosyncratic characters who have chosen to live outside most formal structures, or at the very edge of those structures, rather than mighty hierarchs of the church. Often they were people who had the option of living conventional, secure lives but at a certain point made radically different choices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One such person was Jean Vanier, who died this week. He was a Canadian diplomat’s son who served as a naval officer, then as a professor of theology and philosophy, but was inspired to change course after seeing the dreary conditions inside an institution for men with learning difficulties near Paris. That inspired him to open a home where people with mental-health or cognitive problems would be valued and invited to contribute to the community. He promoted an ethos than turned on its head the conventional notion of what it means to be normal and successful, and the result was a movement that eventually spread to 35 countries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another strange and charismatic (in several senses) character was Brother Roger (pictured with Mother Teresa), who became a kind of monk despite being born into a French-Swiss Protestant tradition in which monasticism hardly exists. As the founder of the Taizé community in eastern France, he was somehow able to communicate with a younger generation that was abandoning formal religion in droves, but still felt a kind of spiritual thirst. Like Vanier, he died in France at the age of 90, but the end of Roger’s life, after he was stabbed by a mentally disturbed Romanian woman, was far uglier. By the time of his passing in 2005, prayer groups modelled on his community had formed across North America. If his style of spiritual guidance had a hallmark, it was a willingness to listen as well as preach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even harder to place in any box, perhaps, was Dorothy Day, a social and political activist who lived much of her life in rough areas of New York, where she rubbed shoulders with socialists, communists and hippies, while finding commonalities and differences with them all. As a founder of the Catholic Worker Movement, she declared herself a “pacifist even in the class struggle” although she professed to understand perfectly well why the poor wanted to rise up against their oppressors. It was a stance that exasperated both secular lefists and Christian conservatives, but her integrity compelled a grudging respect. For all her radicalism on economics, she adhered to Catholic teaching on sexual and reproductive issues, saying she regretted having an abortion. Utterly different as she was from the Catholic bishops of her day, she may eventually be proclaimed a saint. A process that could lead to canonising her began under Pope John Paul II in 2000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet another place on the spectrum of idiosyncratic sanctity was occupied by Mother Teresa, the ethnic Albanian nun who worked among the destitute in Kolkata and founded a missionary order that eventually spread to more than 130 countries. When she died in 1997, her labour among the “poorest of the poor” was saluted by the leaders of India and Pakistan, who were neither Christian nor in agreement about much else. She had her critics, some of whom branded her indifferent to the root causes of poverty, and opposed to the female empowerment which might have improved living standards. Some felt that she was too quick to seek the approval of the rich and powerful. But people respected her manifest indifference to her own material comfort.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As one more example of holy, disinterested eccentricity, take the figure of Maria Skobtsova, the cigarette-smoking Russian nun who lived among the down-and-out in Paris in the 1930s and was eventually executed in a Nazi gas chamber in 1945. Practising the ideal of unconditional hospitality, she was critical of the ritualistic piety of some fellow members of the Russian diaspora in France, and she doubtless infuriated some of them. But she was the one who was eventually recognised as a martyr, not her pious compatriots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What all these people have in common is the fact that they embraced uncomfortable lives, even though they had experienced a relatively comfortable existence and might have held onto it. Dorothy Day was the daughter of secular middle-class Americans, her father a sports writer. Mother Teresa could have practised her monastic vocation in Ireland, a land where she lived as a young woman. Skobstova was a talented poet and well-trained intellectual who could certainly have enjoyed the secular side of life as a Russian émigré.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reputation of a “saint”, whether in the strict sense or a somewhat broader one, is a fickle thing. The spectacle of self-abnegation in a higher cause is both fascinating and to some observers, a bit suspicious. Presented with any paragon of virtue, people immediately start asking themselves what flaws this altruistic individual had, and if the flaws turn out to be rather glaring, that can come as a kind of relief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But when facing public scrutiny, mitred princes of the church are at a particular disadvantage. They must convince sceptical onlookers that the trappings of power and prestige which they  enjoy by virtue of their office are being worn with humility, and in a spirit of concern for others. (If they have personal experience of persecution, as John Paul II did under Nazism and communism, that certainly adds credibility.) But in general, today’s world, both religious and otherwise, prefers a mud-caked eccentric to a gorgeous episcopal robe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 01:07:38 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The refugee train from Sarajevo]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/news/2019/05/11/the-refugee-train-from-sarajevo]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/bihac_train.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-11T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE flyblown plaza in front of Sarajevo’s railway station is called “Srebrenica Genocide Victims Square”. The echoey, empty station is like a cathedral. When Sarajevo, Bosnia’s capital, was at the heart of the former Yugoslavia it bustled. Now only 11 trains a day depart, and 11 arrive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To understand quite how sad a state of affairs this is, compare it to the central station in Zagreb, the capital of neighbouring Croatia. Its population is, admittedly, 40% larger than Bosnia’s. Yet Zagreb’s station has more than 16 times as much rail traffic, not counting trains serving the city’s suburban stations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was a time when you could get from Sarajevo by train to most of Europe. But in the last few years financial disputes have cut Bosnian railways off from the rest of the world. Now you can’t even take a train from here to Croatia, let alone farther away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have come to Sarajevo station to catch the train to Banja Luka, now the capital of the Serb part of Bosnia-Hercegovina. Its government denies that a genocide took place in Srebrenica, where Bosnian Serb soldiers killed some 8,000 Bosniak (Bosnian Muslim) men and boys in 1995, towards the end of the Bosnian war.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Most Bosnians have lost the habit of train travel. “You are mad” said friends when I said I was taking the train: it will be disgusting and the toilets will be clogged. They don’t know that it is as modern a train as you will find anywhere in Europe. The rolling stock was delivered from Spain in 2010 and then parked in a siding until 2016, when tracks and infrastructure was finally upgraded to take them.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The first railway to Banja Luka, which connected it to Croatia, was laid by the Ottomans in 1872. Then came the Austro-Hungarians and finally the Yugoslavs. The link to Sarajevo—built by prisoners of war and communist youth brigades, including thousands of foreigners—was completed only in the early 1950s. During the Bosnian war the railways stopped running, except for small sections.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;When the train pulls in to Sarajevo, only one door is unlocked for passengers to get on. “That way” says the conductor pointing right. “What about that way?” I ask. “Migrants” he says brusquely, but if I &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; want to sit with them that would be my choice. The migrants take the train on to Bihac, from where they try to sneak past border guards get to Croatia and then deeper into the EU. I am not here to write about them, but I join them anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Opposite me is Morsal, 26 years old. She is travelling with her two-year-old daughter, who was born in a refugee camp in Serbia. Morsal explains that she used to be a policewoman in Afghanistan. She shows me a picture of a woman surrounded by white cloth and has something white on her mouth. It takes me a few seconds to realise that the subject is lying in a coffin. Morsal had received a call from a man who warned her to quit the police; a week later four men burst into her home and shot her 16-year-old sister dead, thinking it was Morsal. Within hours Morsal began her flight via Pakistan, Iran, Turkey, Bulgaria, Serbia and now Bosnia.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Next to me is Asal, her parents and little brother. They are Iranian Kurds and for 15 years Asal’s father had been a member of an underground Kurdish political group. The Iranian security services discovered it, two members were executed and the family fled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last October Serbia ended a brief period of no-visa requirements for Iranians, but not before there had been an influx of asylum-seekers. “Did you fly to Serbia?” I ask. “No, we came with the mafia,” says a deadpan Asal. She is only 11-years old and speaks fantastic English.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;I have little doubt that Asal and Morsal will flourish in, and contribute to, any country that takes them in. I cannot say the same about a group of Algerian men in our carriage. One, who sports a top-knot, says his father is in France but he cannot get a visa to go there because, he chortles, he has been in jail four times “for fighting and that sort of thing”.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;At Banja Luka only one door opens, again. For some reason three of the migrants try to get off here. They are greeted by Bosnian Serb policemen who bark the equivalent of “Oi! Where do you think you are going?” No Muslim refugees are allowed off here.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;I ask the train crew why they separated the migrants from the other passengers, who are a mix of Bosniaks, Serbs and Croats. Answer: “Because they complain that the migrants smell.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I immediately remembered the many refugees of the Yugoslav wars: Bosniaks who flopped exhausted into Croatia, one night in 1992, having been driven out by Bosnian Serbs; Serbs who had fled Croatia to Banja Luka on their tractors; and Croats going the other way on theirs to get away from Serbs. “Have all of you actually &lt;em&gt;forgotten&lt;/em&gt; that this was you not so long ago?” I want to ask them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bosnian activists have helped the refugees. But for many Bosnians, regardless of ethnicity, the bitterness that lingers, almost a quarter of a century after the end of the war, seems to have squeezed out any sense of sympathy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 May 2019 00:31:50 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Success in academia is as much about grit as talent]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/10/success-in-academia-is-as-much-about-grit-as-talent]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_woc857.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-10T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 1968 ROBERT MERTON, a sociologist at Columbia University, identified a feature of academic life that he called the Matthew effect. The most talented scientists, he observed, tend to have access to the most resources and the best opportunities, and receive a disproportionate amount of credit for their work, thus amplifying their already enhanced reputations and careers. Less brilliant ones, meanwhile, are often left scrambling for money and recognition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New research suggests this may not tell the whole story. A working paper by Yang Wang, Benjamin Jones and Dashun Wang of Northwestern University finds that success in the sciences does not always breed more success, and that scientists who fail early in their careers may benefit from the experience. The authors discovered this by collecting data on grant applications submitted between 1990 and 2005 to America’s National Institutes of Health (NIH) by junior-level scientists. In particular, they focused on two groups of applicants: those who received relatively high scores on their submissions but just missed getting a grant, and those who scored similarly well but just succeeded in being awarded one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The three researchers found that, rather than automatically holding the failures back, as the Matthew effect might be thought to predict, an early-career setback of this sort was sometimes associated with greater academic success in the long run. While those who missed out on funding were more likely to drop out from the NIH system, the scientists who persevered and continued to apply for grants after their initial failure outperformed their counterparts who had succeeded first time, as measured by the number of citations of their research that they received over the subsequent ten years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While some of this can be explained by the weakest scientists in the no-grant group giving up, the three researchers showed that other, unobservable, characteristics such as “effort” or “grit” are also at work. Overall, the authors conclude, the findings are consistent with the concept that “what doesn’t kill me makes me stronger”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 07:05:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Does gender equality start in the home?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/10/does-gender-equality-start-in-the-home]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_blp512.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-10T14:20:02Z&quot;&gt;May 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anne McElvoy asks Melinda Gates whether gender equality starts in the kitchen. The American philanthropist explains why the tech world risks entrenching bias into the future, but defends the Gates Foundation’s decision to halve its paid family leave. And Anne and Melinda swap top tips for getting teenagers to do the washing up. Runtime: 20 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-melindagates&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2019 00:06:16 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Researcher (full-time, one-year contract)]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/news/2019/05/10/researcher-full-time-one-year-contract]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20180224_wop001_10_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-10T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; is the leading source of analysis on international business and world affairs. We are an international company, employing staff throughout the world. We deliver information, opinion and analysis in print and through a range of digital formats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research team provides some of the data that appears in &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; and helps to maintain the newspaper’s high standards. You will provide assistance to the journalists and deal with ad hoc requests and reader inquiries. Working closely with our data team, you will assist with gathering statistics and information for charts and tables and be responsible for final sign-off. Working to meet publication deadlines, you will need to check the facts in all articles in print and online. And work on the Indicators pages of the weekly newspaper. You will also be fact-checking scripts for our film unit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ideally educated to degree level with some economic/maths content, you will have some experience of working with information sources and statistics. You will have a general interest in current affairs, business and finance, politics and information. An adept user of IT, you will have a high level of numeracy and literacy coupled with excellent time-management skills. A high standard of accuracy and attention to detail is essential.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will be able to demonstrate:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent team-membership skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent communication skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A practical and flexible approach to duties&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good interpersonal relations with other staff members&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A keen interest in international and world affairs&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Economist Group values diversity. We are committed to equal opportunities and creating an inclusive environment for all our employees. We welcome applicants regardless of ethnic origin, national origin, gender, race, colour, religious beliefs, disability, sexual orientation or age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Please send your CV with a covering letter to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.commailto:researchjob@economist.com&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;researchjob@economist.com&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Closing date for applications is June 7th 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 22:06:23 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“The Biggest Little Farm” is a quiet call to arms]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/10/the-biggest-little-farm-is-a-quiet-call-to-arms]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_BKP511.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-10T12:21:08Z&quot;&gt;May 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NATURE DOCUMENTARIES are enjoying a moment in the sun. While politicians around the world have failed to pass much meaningful legislation on climate change, film-makers have captured melting ice caps, coral bleaching and devastating floods. On May 9th Netflix announced that “Our Planet”, a mini-series examining humanity’s impact on different species and habitats, was the most-watched title on the streaming site in Britain in April. These productions combine sumptuous cinematography, engaging animal narratives and policy recommendations, demonstrating how an individual’s behaviour can have wide-ranging repercussions. After “Blue Planet II” showed birds feeding their chicks debris from the ocean, an estimated 88% of viewers changed their consumption of single-use plastic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The Biggest Little Farm”, a new documentary, looks at the challenge of sustainability from a much more intimate perspective. There are no playful orangutans or majestic sea turtles; instead it chronicles the journey of two urban-dwellers as they try to reintroduce biodiversity to an abandoned farm. By keeping its focus on practical issues and the realities of running a smallholding, the film offers a feel-good story of environmental recovery that, while sometimes overly simplistic, encourages viewers to reflect on the small changes they might make in their own lives. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;John and Molly Chester start out as an average pair of health-conscious Angelenos. John is a wildlife cinematographer, while Molly is a chef with grand ideas about proper farming techniques but little experience of agricultural work. After being evicted from their home on short notice, they decide to put their passions to work and buy a farm. There they encounter soil that has been ruined by years of monoculture, so they hire a guide—Alan York, a “renowned expert in traditional farming practices”—to teach them how to cultivate more than 200 crops and feed a range of animals that will “self-regulate”. The idea is to create a system that will feed the soil and the people equally, and the Chesters approach this challenge with idealism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet they soon encounter problems, and persistent ones. Pests, ranging from snails to coyotes, move in immediately; natural forces such as droughts, floods and wildfires—all of which have been exacerbated by climate change—mount a considerable threat to their project. “The Biggest Little Farm” depicts a relationship with the natural world that is by turns both life-affirming and horribly grim. The coyotes prove a constant menace, and John’s efforts to stymie them become the central narrative of the film. Images of ravaged chickens recur. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp510.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there are also moments of exquisite cinematography, filmed by Mr Chester himself, who also directs. He focuses his lens on the most miniscule of creatures, from ladybugs to dung beetles. When an animal that lives in manure gets a moment in the spotlight, it reflects the idea that, on a truly biodiverse farm, every player matters. Mr Chester resists the temptation to anthropomorphise these creatures, instead demonstrating the key role each plays. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These shifts in tone represent the endless cycles of life and death, of frustration and success, that come with a working farm. It is not the most dramatic narrative: at points the cycles become predictable, even while the film heads towards its happy ending. And though “The Biggest Little Farm” pointedly leaves out some of the most brutal elements of farming—the film asks the viewer to mourn for those animals killed by predators, but make little reference to what awaits the animals raised for meat—it is likely to succeed in encouraging its audience to act.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Few will be able to copy the Chesters’ actions directly, but watching two ordinary people take initiative, face setbacks and overcome challenges in the name of a better world is inspiring enough. After witnessing the couple radically re-organise their priorities and risk their own livelihood, small sacrifices such as growing vegetables, eating less meat, avoiding plastic or taking public transportation more often may seem less daunting. It is a thoughtfully narrow approach, and a valuable addition to a thriving genre. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“The Biggest Little Farm” is released in America on May 10th&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 20:06:24 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Patrick Shanahan is likely to be America’s next defence secretary]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/09/patrick-shanahan-is-likely-to-be-americas-next-defence-secretary]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_blp904.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-09T23:48:37Z&quot;&gt;May 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PATRICK SHANAHAN has made little on mark on the Pentagon during his two years as deputy defence secretary and then acting secretary following James Mattis’s resignation in December. He has instituted no major reform. He has made no memorable statement on global affairs. People who have worked alongside the former Boeing executive sound ambivalent about him. A newcomer to foreign affairs and security policy, he is not known to have strong views, ideological or otherwise. He is said to be a competent manager, which might be considered a minimal requirement for leading America’s armed forces and the vast Pentagon bureaucracy. On May 9th the White House announced that Donald Trump intended to nominate Mr Shanahan to his job on a permanent basis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This represents a big change in what Mr Trump requires from his defence secretary. He picked Mr Mattis, a highly-respected former marine general, at a time when he was new to foreign affairs, unsure of the demands of the presidency and bedazzled by a man in uniform. He referred approvingly to him by his service nickname, “Mad Dog Mattis,” though the moniker was rarely used and Mr Mattis hated it. Mr Trump’s enthusiasm for Mr Mattis dwindled once it became clear that he was neither the bull-headed killer Mr Trump had taken him for, nor prepared to be the president’s own loyal general.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While on board with some of Mr Trump’s instincts—for example, in his stepped-up bombing campaigns against the Taliban and Islamic State—Mr Mattis quietly repudiated the president’s values. He spent much of his time flying around the world trying to reassure the traditional allies Mr Trump lambasted. He stymied Mr Trump’s efforts to ban transsexuals from the armed forces. He survived in the administration for as long as he did through a combination of discretion, chaos elsewhere in the cabinet, and the defence department’s enormous heft. By replacing Mr Mattis with a much less commanding figure, Mr Trump has signalled his preference for loyalty over stature in the most independent power-base within the government.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shanahan showed his loyalty earlier this year by endorsing Mr Trump’s scheme to siphon billions of dollars from the defence budget to put towards a border-wall. He has also argued for the proposed new Space Force—in effect a sixth service branch—that Mr Trump has demanded. This is said to have won him over to Mr Trump, who had previously resisted pressure to make Mr Shanahan’s acting tenure permanent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The announcement of Mr Shanahan’s impending nomination follows the conclusion of a month-long Pentagon investigation into whether he improperly promoted Boeing and disparaged its competitors within the department. Though exonerated by the Pentagon’s acting inspector general, Mr Shanahan was described in his report as speaking peculiarly often—in almost every meeting—about his experience overseeing Boeing’s 787 Dreamliner programme. That points, if not to corruption, to his unusual callowness in government, which Republican national-security hawks such as Lindsey Graham are said to be troubled by. It will also make him a target for Democratic senators in his confirmation hearings. An investigation by the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; found that the production facility in North Carolina that makes the Dreamliner has been subject to many allegations of poor safety standards, as managers rushed to meet production targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Assuming Mr Shanahan is confirmed, his low profile and business background could both turn out to be beneficial for the defence department. It is locked in a perpetual struggle with the sorts of glitches, including inefficient basing, overstaffing and costly acquisitions programmes, he prides himself on solving at Boeing. More traditional defence secretaries—including Mr Mattis—routinely vow to get grips with such problems, before getting distracted by global security. That is less likely to happen to Mr Shanahan, who announced when taking over from Mr Mattis that he intended to travel much less than his predecessor had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flip-side of his leadership would probably be a diminution of the Pentagon’s role in shaping foreign and security policy. This is good news for Mike Pompeo and John Bolton, the belligerent secretary of state and national secretary adviser. They are already profiting from Mr Mattis’s absence. Having the ear of Mr Trump, who likes their style if not necessarily their bellicosity, they have taken the lead on security issues such as Iran—to which Mr Pompeo promised on May 9th a “swift and decisive” US response to any provocation. As well as being far better versed in foreign affairs, both are more adept inter-departmental players than Mr Shanahan, who has the least government experience of almost any defence secretary of recent times. While presiding over by far the biggest government department, he might struggle to check his cabinet colleagues. He will not check Mr Trump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 20:06:23 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>