<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Alabama’s lawmakers want to challenge Roe v Wade]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/15/alabamas-lawmakers-want-to-challenge-roe-v-wade]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_usp001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEVER HAS the war sparked by &lt;em&gt;Roe v Wade&lt;/em&gt;, the 1973 Supreme Court ruling that declared abortion a constitutional right, been as intense as it is now. Lawmakers in conservative states are passing “heartbeat” bills banning abortion from the moment a heartbeat is detectable, around the sixth week of pregnancy—flagrantly violating &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt;. To defend abortion rights some liberal states are extending them, by making it easier to have abortions in the third trimester. That has encouraged President Donald Trump to mount a fresh assault on late abortions, which he routinely characterises as babies being “ripped” from their mothers’ wombs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most uncompromising attack on &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt; has been launched in Alabama. On May 14th the state’s Senate passed a bill that would effectively ban abortion outright. If it is signed into law by the governor, as seems likely, it will constitute the harshest abortion legislation passed in America in half a century. “The heartbeat bills don’t really tackle what &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt; is about,” says Eric Johnston, president of the Alabama Pro-life Coalition, alluding to &lt;em&gt;Roe’s&lt;/em&gt; protection of abortion until a fetus is viable, at around 24 weeks. “It seemed like the right time to challenge it properly.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bill, which the softly-spoken Mr Johnston wrote, does not mess around. Comparing abortion to the most murderous atrocities of the 20th century—“German death camps, Chinese purges, Stalin’s gulags, Cambodian killing fields, and the Rwandan genocide”—it makes performing one a felony, punishable by up to 99 years in prison. Because the bill defines a fetus as “a human being…regardless of viability” its sponsors resisted attempts, by Republican as well as Democratic senators, to allow exceptions in cases of rape or incest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The law will be struck down in the courts, just as heartbeat bills have been elsewhere, most recently in Kentucky and Iowa. Similar laws passed recently in Mississippi and in Georgia will meet the same fate, as will several more making their way through state legislatures if they become law. That is the purpose of extreme abortion laws—to prompt legal cases in the hope that one might come before the new conservative majority at the Supreme Court, which will use it to overturn &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until recently anti-abortionists were engaged in a stealthier battle. Rather than challenging &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt; directly they chiselled away, introducing state-level regulations so burdensome that clinics were forced to close. As social conservatives retreated in the culture war over gay marriage, they advanced over abortion. Between 2011 and 2017, more than 400 abortion restrictions have been introduced across America—more than a third of the total since 1973, according to the Guttmacher Institute. Eight states have only one abortion clinic left.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump’s appointment of two conservative Supreme Court justices has emboldened some pro-lifers to adopt a more aggressive strategy. Their hopes of directly overturning &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt; were boosted on May 13th when the justices voted 5-4 along ideological lines to overturn a 40-year-old precedent in a case unrelated to abortion. The move, wrote Stephen Breyer, one of the liberal justices, “can only cause one to wonder which cases the Court will overrule next.” Lest anyone wondered what sort of case he had in mind, he cited &lt;em&gt;Planned Parenthood v Casey&lt;/em&gt;, a ruling from 1992 that upheld &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some pro-life activists are cautious about the prospects of overturning &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt;. Clarke Forsythe, senior lawyer for Americans United for Life, which has drawn up successful state-level abortion regulations, says his organisation watches carefully every time the court overturns a precedent: “it happens more often than many imagine”. But he also points out that the court, and in particular Chief Justice John Roberts, seem in no hurry to overturn Roe. He does not expect the justices to take on a direct challenge for “two or three years”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is probably right. Casting himself as a pro-life warrior is useful for Mr Trump, who needs to keep the support of conservative evangelicals in 2020. But actually repealing &lt;em&gt;Roe&lt;/em&gt; before the next presidential election would be an electoral disaster for Republicans, since a large majority of Americans believe abortions should be legal up to the third trimester.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Undermining early abortion rights can be risky for state lawmakers, too. Georgia, which last week became the fourth state this year to pass a heartbeat bill, has long been a deeply conservative state. But it is becoming more diverse and urban, as the inroads made by Democrats in November’s mid-terms attest. A recent poll found that more voters in the state opposed the heartbeat bill than supported it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 03:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Saving face: San Francisco&#x27;s ban on recognition technology]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/15/saving-face-san-franciscos-ban-on-recognition-technology]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/babbage_13.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T18:25:13Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;LEGISLATORS IN San Francisco have just voted to ban the use of facial recognition—is this a victory for privacy or a setback for technology? Also, new research on how machine learning can be used to predict the likelihood of breast cancer. And Amazon&amp;#x27;s boss, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/15/to-understand-the-tech-lords-look-to-their-libraries&quot;&gt;Jeff Bezos&lt;/a&gt;, draws inspiration from science fiction in his aim to build space habitats. Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistbabbage/babbage-facingthefuture-&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 02:41:52 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jeremy Kyle and the media’s treatment of mental health]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/15/jeremy-kyle-and-the-medias-treatment-of-mental-health]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_brp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE FIRST episode of “Expedition Robinson”, a Swedish television programme, aired in September 1997. A precursor to “Survivor”, a hit American show, it was one of the first examples of so-called reality television, and the first exhibit in a debate on the effects of such shows on those who take part. Two months before the series aired, one of its cast, Sinisa Savija, had committed suicide after becoming the first person to be voted off. The producers responded by mostly editing him out of the broadcast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two decades later, attitudes have changed. On May 15th, in the middle of “mental-health awareness week”, ITV announced that it would cancel “The Jeremy Kyle Show”, a popular daytime programme that featured real people arguing furiously about infidelity, alcoholism, drug use and the like. A week earlier a participant, Steven Dymond, had been found dead after failing a lie-detector test on camera.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Worry about the welfare of reality-TV subjects is not new. Two former contestants on “Love Island”, another ITV show, have killed themselves in the past year. In 2016 the New York Post counted 21 suicides by American reality-TV participants since 2004.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet it is the Jeremy Kyle incident that looks most like becoming, as one MP put it, a “watershed moment”. One reason may be the programme’s vulnerable subjects. The families berating each other in episodes such as “My transgender love rival is trying to steal my husband!” are softer targets than the young wannabes who go on “Love Island” hoping for a career as a minor celebrity. Ten years of austerity have made poor-bashing less popular than elite-bashing. And viewers with an appetite for Kyle-style public shaming can nowadays get it on Twitter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there may be a more optimistic reason. There has been a “sea change” in attitudes to mental health, says Paul Farmer, the boss of Mind, a charity. Public figures, from MPs to royals, have spoken openly about their mental battles. “What starts off invisible, moves towards taboo, becomes acceptable. We’ve seen it in cancer, race, sexuality, disability and we see it in mental health,” says David Crepaz-Keay of the Mental Health Foundation, another charity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of people saying they were willing to live with someone who suffered from mental illness increased from 57% in 2009 to 72% in 2016. Those willing to work with them rose from 69% to 80%. And the media’s framing of mental-health issues has improved, shifting to being mainly non-stigmatising in 2016, according to Time to Change, a charity. The end of “The Jeremy Kyle Show” will presumably do no harm to this balance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 02:41:51 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America’s avocado supply is set to tighten]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/15/americas-avocado-supply-is-set-to-tighten]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_woc053.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;THE MARKET for avocados has undergone a transformation unlike that of any other fruit (yes, fruit) over the past few decades—from chic canapé of the 1970s to millennial staple today. In 2018 Americans consumed 3.5kg (7.7lbs) of avocado per person—nearly four times the level in 2000. Even McDonald’s is serving up guacamole. Yet the outlook for American avocado lovers is a concern.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;In California last year, where 80% of America’s avocados are grown, heatwaves and &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2018/11/17/despite-californias-inferno-global-wildfires-are-fizzling-out&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;wildfires&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; destroyed trees. This year was always destined to be a little less satisfying for farmers, as the alternate-year-bearing nature of avocado trees means that a large crop is followed by a smaller yield the following year. But rains and cold weather have exacerbated the problem, with this year threatening to be the worst harvest in over a decade.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Imports have risen sharply as American demand has grown. In the mid-1990s the Department of Agriculture (USDA) lifted an 83-year-old ban on Mexican avocados. Imports from Mexico, where avocados can be grown all year round, made up a staggering 87% of American avocado consumption in 2017-18. The USDA is forecasting this share to rise to 93% for the coming season.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span id=&quot;docs-internal-guid-3fd080b3-7fff-eb20-4b94-ee87817dd094&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Additional imports may also come from Chile and Peru. But the nature of the crop means that farmers can sit on their harvest and wait for prices to surge, as avocados can hang on trees for several months without rotting. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;On April 1st the price for Mexican Hass avocados rose by a third—the biggest one-day price rise in almost a decade. This may be down to a combination of factors: America’s increased threats to close the border and Mexican farmers waiting for Cinco de Mayo, a major festival on May 5th, to hike prices. The threat of new tariffs, border frictions and a low harvest in California might cause even more price volatility in the coming months. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;Millennials might want to try something else on their toast.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 01:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Britain’s bizarre, unwanted European election]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/15/britains-bizarre-unwanted-european-election]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_brp001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FEATHERSTONE Working Men’s Club, near Pontefract, has never seen anything like it. On a sunny May morning, a mass of Brexit Party supporters, armed with placards and warmed up by a tub-thumping speech from Ann Widdecombe, a former Tory minister, chant “Nig-el, Nig-el” as their hero clambers on to the platform. This month’s European election, Nigel Farage shouts, is about democracy and the betrayal of voters. Mentions of Theresa May, the Conservative prime minister, or Yvette Cooper, the local Labour MP, are greeted with howls of “Traitor!”. Outside, a kind soul from the Communist Party of Great Britain (Marxist-Leninist) distributes leaflets pointing out that his party also backs Brexit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Farage’s new party thrives on protest. Its supporters enjoy nothing more than being told their vote to leave the European Union in June 2016 has been betrayed by the establishment, the London elite, a useless prime minister, the civil service, treacherous MPs and the BBC. Mr Farage, who went from private school to a career in the City, is himself a prime elite specimen. Yet he manages to pose as an anti-establishment rebel. In a Labour stronghold, he raises cheers by denouncing Jeremy Corbyn as an Islington leftie. He offers no policies—they are promised only after the election—and does not even explain why Brexit is a good idea. His message is simple: we must walk out in October with no deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By any standards the European election taking place in Britain on May 23rd is bizarre. Nobody wanted it, as Brexit was meant to have happened on March 29th. But Parliament’s repeated refusal to pass the government’s Brexit deal was followed by a European Council decision to extend the deadline until October 31st. So Britain is having to join the rest of the EU in voting for a fresh set of MEPs next week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the face of it the result should not matter much. If a Brexit deal is passed before the summer recess, as the government still hopes, British MEPs will barely have time to take their seats. Both main parties play down the ballot’s importance. The Tories are invisible on the campaign trail, failing even to produce a manifesto. Labour is little better, as its leadership is divided over whether to support another referendum. Yet the smaller parties are enjoying themselves—and doing well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BRC055.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190518_BRC055.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190518_BRC055.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190518_BRC055.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190518_BRC055.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190518_BRC055.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190518_BRC055.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190518_BRC055.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190518_BRC055.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190518_BRC055.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The outcome will depend heavily on turnout. In European elections it is usually small (last time, in 2014, it was 35%). Yet this one may see turnout rise, as both pro- and anti-Brexit forces have been energised. Pollsters find that voters now identify more strongly with Remain or Leave than with their usual parties. The result is that support is bleeding from the Tories to the Brexit Party and, to a lesser extent, from Labour to the Liberal Democrats, Greens and Change UK (see chart).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The focus is on Mr Farage’s Brexit Party, as it has a good chance of coming first. Yet, given the Tories’ calamitous meltdown over Brexit, this would not be so extraordinary. In 2014, after all, Mr Farage led the UK Independence Party into pole position. The bigger surprise is the fall-off in Labour support. Mr Corbyn’s ambivalence on Brexit seems to be driving many Remain voters to the smaller parties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These three, especially the new Change UK, have come under justified attack for splitting the Remain vote. Change UK members claim this is less damaging than it seems, as they appeal to voters disillusioned by the Lib Dems or hostile to the Greens. If the three together score in the high 20s, they will do almost as well as the Brexit Party in vote share, though probably not in terms of seats. Yet Change UK is having a tough time, not least over its poor organisation and branding. This week its lead candidate in Scotland pulled out, asking voters to back the Lib Dems. The party has no candidate in the Peterborough by-election on June 6th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The biggest question is what impact next week’s election might have on Brexit and British politics. The Brexit deal still seems stuck. Brussels has switched off; no further negotiations are taking place. But Mrs May has announced that in early June she will bring the withdrawal agreement bill before the House of Commons. Her hope is that the Brexit Party’s success may shock Tory and Labour MPs into voting for the deal after all. She will also argue that, if the bill fails, the only alternative is a no-deal Brexit. Yet these arguments are weak. Labour still looks unlikely to back the bill. So do the Northern Irish Democratic Unionists and the hardline Tory Brexiteers. And no-deal is not the only alternative, as Brussels seems prepared to grant yet another extension of the deadline to avert it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The effect of the election on Mrs May’s own position may be more dramatic. As &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; went to press she was trying to fend off another attempt by the 1922 committee of Tory backbench MPs to change its rules to allow a leadership challenge. Even if she avoids such a contest, most ministers and MPs expect her to go soon. If her attempt to pass the Brexit bill fails, she will be under intense pressure to accelerate the timetable for her departure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What might her successor do? This is where the Brexit Party’s influence will count. It is not going away after the European election. Indeed, Mr Farage claims to be ready to run candidates, including himself, in any general election too. And for many Tories, the prospect of the Brexit Party eating away at their vote means their party must back a no-deal Brexit to survive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This may not be the right conclusion, however. For the Brexit Party’s success is also doing something else: making a Labour victory in a future election more likely. And here is the ultimate irony for those vociferous Farage supporters. Their actions could yet mean a Labour-led government overturns Brexit altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 01:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[In Venice, a “library of exile” reflects on displacement and language]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/15/in-venice-a-library-of-exile-reflects-on-displacement-and-language]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BKP503_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T14:55:27Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE ATENEO VENETO, a grand 16th-century palace near the Fenice Opera House, once hosted a fraternal order which cared for convicted prisoners in their final days. For the past 200 years, however, the site has been a forum for discussion, drawing together people from the city’s many communities to contemplate art, literature, science and politics. Now it is home to a different set of noisy and troubled souls. In the Aula Magna room—where scenes of conflagration adorn the ceiling—stands a porcelain box filled with 2,000 books by exiled writers, from Ovid, through Dante, Voltaire and Victor Hugo, to the present day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the heart of this piece by Edmund de Waal, a British ceramicist and writer, is a lost library. In 1938, weeks after the Nazi invasion of Austria, his great-grandfather’s home on the Ringstrasse in Vienna was stormed and the library was seized and Aryanised. The story of the tragic dispersal of that household formed the basis of Mr de Waal’s bestselling family memoir, “The Hare with Amber Eyes” (2010). “This is a project that I have always dreamed of doing,” he says of the Venice show. “It is about exile—what it means to move to another country, to speak another language.” He reckons it will be “the most significant sculpture of [his] life”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exhibition, entitled “psalm” after a book in the Old Testament, exists in two parts. In the Jewish Museum in the Venetian Ghetto, Mr de Waal has installed ten works of porcelain, marble and gold that reflect on the cultural heritage of the area (he is the first contemporary artist to create a major project for the Ghetto). In the Ateneo Veneto, he covered the exterior of his library in gold leaf, which was then coated with white porcelain slip, a kind of slurry. On that surface he has etched the names of more than 60 lost libraries, including Alexandria, Nineveh, the Rabbinical libraries of Lvov and Odessa, Aleppo, Mosul and the classical collection of Viktor von Ephrussi, his great-grandfather. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;Inside the library, alongside the shelves, are four glass vitrines holding small porcelain works. Mr de Waal says the layout of the space is intended to evoke the edition of the Talmud created by Daniel Bomberg, a Christian printer, in Venice in the early 16th century—around the same time the Ateneo was built. The project reflects the city’s long history “as a place of translation, a space to sit and read and be,” he says; the books are arranged chronologically by country, though most have been translated from their original language, and visitors are encouraged to seek out titles in their own tongue as well as those that have been translated from it. Readers search for the nations they know, and within them the writers they have loved and followed even as they fled abroad. Your correspondent was born in Africa, and was happy to find volumes by Patrice Nganang from Cameroon and Ngugi wa Thiong’o, a Kenyan writer who has said that “resistance is the best way of keeping alive.”&lt;p&gt;In the tumult of the Venice Biennale, there is something special about any spot that is quiet. The project encourages the visitor to reflect on returns, a theme that recurs throughout the artist’s work. Mr de Waal’s great-grandfather’s books were never recovered, probably dispersed throughout Austria or destroyed, but with this new “library of exile” he has devised his own kind of restitution. The exhibition will travel to Germany, to the Japanisches Palais in Dresden—which was operating as a public library when it was partially destroyed during the second world war—and then to the old King’s Library at the British Museum. After that, Mr de Waal aims to give the 2,000 books to the city of Mosul, which will house them in the new library the city is building to replace the one destroyed by Islamic State. He plans to add 800 books of his own, including the 18th-century edition of Voltaire that his grandmother managed to save from the Ephrussi library before she went into exile herself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“psalm”, an exhibition in two parts, continues in Venice until September 29th. The “library of exile” will be presented at the Japanisches Palais in Dresden from November 2019 to February 2020, and at the British Museum in London in 2020&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[To understand the tech lords, look to their libraries]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/15/to-understand-the-tech-lords-look-to-their-libraries]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_ldp501_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;LITERARY TYPES have long been sniffy about science fiction. Ian McEwan, a feted British novelist, has been at pains to distance his most recent book, about an intelligent android, from “sci-fi”, even though the idea is one of the most picked-over tropes in the genre. Such snobbery is misplaced. Humans are technological animals. Science fiction explores how that power might be used, what sorts of worlds might be built with it and what sublime new estrangements and transcendence may follow. It is a literature of ideas, and, as John Maynard Keynes observed (in a different context), the world is ruled by little else. To see the force of Keynes’s point, consider how the world’s richest man plans to spend his fortune.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On May 9th Jeff Bezos outlined his thoughts about the future of humanity. The founder of Amazon sells $1bn-worth of shares a year to fund his rocket company, Blue Origin, which wants to cut the cost of space flight, put tourists into space and help return humans to the moon. That is only the first part of a grander scheme to spread humanity throughout the solar system in artificial habitats. He is not alone. Elon Musk founded SpaceX with the goal of establishing a self-sufficient colony on Mars. Yuri Milner, a Russian tycoon, has promised $100m to send a robot to Alpha Centauri, the closest star system to the sun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Bezos is open about his influences. He grew up reading Isaac Asimov and Robert Heinlein, with their stories of rebellious lunar colonies, idiot-savant robots and societies founded on “psychohistory”, an amalgam of economics, history and what is now called big data. “Star Trek”, with its humane, liberal and internationalist re-imagining of the American frontier spirit, was another favourite. Decades later, Mr Bezos is using his money to help bring such a future about, rather as Heinlein’s D D Harriman did in “The Man Who Sold the Moon”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scratch a Silicon Valley nerd and chances are you will find similar influences, and similar ideas about how the future should look. One of the tech industry’s favourite writers is Iain M Banks, a Scottish socialist whose knockabout space operas were set in and around “the Culture”, a spacefaring utopia. Amid worries about superintelligent computers and robots taking jobs, they are a tonic. In Mr Banks’s society robots have indeed taken all the jobs, but the result is inexhaustible material abundance. Sentient beings, organic or artificial, are free to flourish. Everything is run by nigh-omnipotent and mostly benevolent AI philosopher-kings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His influence runs deep. A meeting room at DeepMind, a big AI firm, is named in his honour. When Mark Zuckerberg, the boss of Facebook, ran a book club in 2015, only two of his 23 recommendations were novels. Mr Banks’s “The Player of Games” was one. (“The Three-Body Problem”, a piece of science fiction by Liu Cixin, was the other). Mr Musk named SpaceX’s rocket-recovery “droneships” after AI-animated spaceships in Mr Banks’s “Culture” books. In 2018 Mr Bezos announced plans to film those books, as well as Larry Niven’s “Ringworld” and “Snow Crash”, a cyberpunk novel by Neal Stephenson—who was, for some of Blue Origin’s early days, its only employee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of Silicon Valley’s favourite stories feature grand, mostly benign futures. Of course, technology can change people, as well as the societies they build. Ursula le Guin has speculated about how societies might look when genetic engineering makes seemingly basic biological categories, like sex, fluid and malleable. Those who worry more about the perils of technology than its promises will find plenty to chew on, too. “1984” needs no introduction. Masayoshi Son, the boss of Softbank, worries about the “Singularity”, when machine intelligence exponentially exceeds the human sort and technological progress escapes all attempts at control. The term was popularised by Vernor Vinge, an American computer scientist and sci-fi author, and remains a popular topic in tech circles. Margaret Atwood has written of societies in the aftermath of technological apocalypses—although she, like Mr McEwan, resists the “sci-fi” label. Kim Stanley Robinson’s “New York 2140” is set in that city after it has been flooded by climate change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-ianmcewan&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One influential proponent of a less starry-eyed attitude to the future is William Gibson, who made his name by rejecting the togas-and-crystal-spires view common in mid-century sci-fi. His “high tech and low life” style of fiction, in which hacker gangs steal information for money and the rich grow ever more detached from the societies that sustain them, was prescient. Two of his aphorisms—that “the future is already here, it’s just not evenly distributed” and “the street finds its own use for things”—have become received wisdom for futurists. If you want to understand how those who are building the future think, ignore the snobs. Sci-fi is the place to start. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“It&#x27;s too much spending, not enough tax collecting”—Pakistan’s 22nd IMF loan]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/15/its-too-much-spending-not-enough-tax-collecting-pakistans-22nd-imf-loan]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/imf_pakistan.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T11:30:36Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE INTERNATIONAL Monetary Fund has struck another deal to bail out &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/13/the-imf-has-agreed-to-break-pakistans-fall-again&quot;&gt;Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;—its 22nd. How did the country’s economy end up in such a mess? Never mind rising numbers of vegetarians: the world is eating more &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/international/2019/05/04/global-meat-eating-is-on-the-rise-bringing-surprising-benefits&quot;&gt;meat&lt;/a&gt; and, in a way, that’s a good thing. And how &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/11/what-french-baby-names-say-about-the-country&quot;&gt;French names&lt;/a&gt; reveal social trends that census data cannot. Runtime: 21min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/don-tspenditallatonce-pakistanandtheimf&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 20:40:52 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China vows a “fight to the end” in trade feud with America]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/15/china-vows-a-fight-to-the-end-in-trade-feud-with-america]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_fnp001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THOUGH CHINA runs a massive trade surplus with America, over the past year it has run a massive rhetoric deficit. During that period President Donald Trump has tweeted about China 133 times; Chinese leaders, by contrast, have mostly kept mum about the trade dispute with America. But in the past few days that has begun to change. A sudden barrage of commentaries about the trade war in state media has struck a note of defiant nationalism. “If you want to talk, our door is wide open,” said an anchor on China’s most-watched news programme on May 13th, in a clip that went viral. “If you want to fight, we’ll fight you to the end.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The aggressive language comes as the two countries’ trade war heats up. Last week American negotiators alleged that China had reneged on a draft deal that was nearly complete. Chinese officials said it was the Americans who were making unreasonable demands. The breakdown in talks led to America’s decision on May 10th to raise tariffs on $200bn-worth of Chinese imports from 10% to 25%, covering products such as car parts and circuit boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On May 13th Mr Trump tweeted, warning China not to retaliate. It will only get worse, he said. Barely an hour later China ratcheted up tariffs on $60bn-worth of imports from America, including natural gas. And it did indeed get worse, with the United States Trade Representative shortly thereafter beginning the process of implementing tariffs on “essentially all” Chinese imports. When all is said and done, China’s nearly $560bn-worth of annual exports to America could face tariffs of 25%. Much of America’s $180bn of annual exports to China could also be subject to similar levies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those already in place will hurt. Many economists estimate that China’s growth this year could be dragged down by about half a percentage point, to 6%. In America consumers will start to see higher prices: inflation could rise by half a percentage point, according to economists at Société Générale, a French bank. If Mr Trump follows through on the threat to hit all Chinese imports with duties—and few doubt his love of tariffs—the damage could be far greater. Chad Bown and Eva Zhang of the Peterson Institute for International Economics in Washington, DC, reckon that the scale of American tariffs on China would resemble the Smoot-Hawley tariff of 1930, levied just before the Great Depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At that point China might well start making life difficult for American businesses in China. One possibility would be consumer boycotts, fanned by state media. Forecasting models scarcely capture the alarm that would spread through markets if the world’s two biggest economies engage in a full-blown trade war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is still hope that America and China will step back. A recovery in global share prices after a big sell-off on May 13th, when the tit-for-tat tariffs were announced, reflects optimism that cooler heads will prevail. Most of the latest measures are not yet in force. America’s new 25% tariffs apply only to goods that left China after they were announced. Because it takes about three weeks for ocean freighters to make the journey, it will be June before the pain is truly felt. China’s new tariffs take effect only on June 1st. So there is time to talk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In its official statements, China’s consistent message has been that, though it will not be bullied, it wants to work towards a deal with America. Mr Trump has also shown a willingness to resume talks, saying that he will hold meetings with Xi Jinping, China’s president, at a G20 summit in Japan at the end of June. The last time the two leaders met at a G20 summit, in November in Argentina, they agreed to a truce in the trade war. That might be a reason for optimism. Then again, given where the two countries are now, it could just as well be a reason for despair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 20:40:51 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A US-China game of nerves]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/14/a-us-china-game-of-nerves]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_opp501_3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-14T19:30:59Z&quot;&gt;May 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TWO-WAY TRADE between America and China hit $2bn a day last year. But the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/11/the-us-china-trading-relationship-will-be-fraught-for-years-to-come&quot;&gt;growing mistrust&lt;/a&gt; between the two countries is turning business from a safe space into a field of contention. David Rennie, &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s Beijing bureau chief, has travelled across both countries and found that, with China’s daunting rise, making money is no longer enough to keep friendly relations. Runtime: 26 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-aus-chinagameofnerves&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 06:08:30 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>