<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump and Kim Jong Un hold a border photo-op]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/30/donald-trump-and-kim-jong-un-hold-a-border-photo-op]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190706_blp902.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-30T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON THE morning of June 29th Donald Trump, America’s president, extended the most casual of invitations from his hotel room in Osaka, where he was attending a meeting of the G20 hosted by Japan. “If Chairman Kim of North Korea sees this, I would meet him at the Border/DMZ just to shake his hand and say Hello(?)!,” Mr Trump wrote on Twitter. After all, Mr Trump was already scheduled to visit the “demilitarised zone” between the two Koreas the next day, after a meeting with Moon Jae-in, South Korea’s president. Why not throw in a meeting with North Korea’s dictator, whom he had met twice before in an effort to get North Korea to abandon its nuclear weapons. Mere hours later, North Korea pronounced Mr Trump’s suggestion “very interesting”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interesting enough that, on the afternoon of June 30th, Mr Kim and Mr Trump met for the third time in just over a year. Following a tour of the South Korean side of the DMZ, which also took in a windswept guard post and a canteen where troops presented the president with a golfing outfit, Mr Trump strolled towards the dividing line in the truce village of Panmunjom. He shook hands with Mr Kim, who was waiting for him on the northern side, before stepping across the line into North Korea. The moment was heavy with symbolism: it was the first time a sitting American president had set foot in North Korea, and it came 69 years, nearly to the day, after American troops had entered the Korean war on the South’s side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During a brief chat on the northern side, Mr Trump said it was an “honour” to visit North Korea. Mr Kim appeared chuffed: “I never expected to see you in this place,” he told Mr Trump, who then invited the North’s dictator to visit the White House. Afterwards, the two stepped back across the line into South Korea, where they posed briefly for a photo with Mr Moon before retiring for talks to “Freedom House” on the southern side. Mr Moon, who needs negotiations between America and North Korea to restart in order to advance his ambitious agenda of inter-Korean economic cooperation, was effusive throughout. “The flower of peace is blossoming on the Korean peninsula,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As well as being a gift for Mr Moon, the summit was also a boon for Messrs Trump and Kim. The president’s comments during and around the meeting will have pleased Mr Kim. Mr Trump downplayed North Korea’s recent tests of short-range missiles, claiming America did not consider them missile tests. Mr Kim’s nuclear programme barely got a mention: for all the world, it looked as though Mr Trump was perfectly happy to engage with North Korea on its own terms, implicitly acknowledging the regime’s nuclear-armed status as legitimate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These comments, along with the pictures of Mr Trump stepping into North Korea and saying that he was honoured to be received by Mr Kim, are gold for the North’s domestic propaganda machine, which is bound to use them to demonstrate the great leader’s diplomatic acumen. They may go some way towards brushing up Mr Kim’s domestic image following the collapse of the pair’s previous summit, in Vietnam in February. North Korea’s failure to win relief from sanctions at that meeting seems to have so infuriated Mr Kim that he demoted his chief negotiator and is rumoured to have punished other aides. But the decision to meet Mr Trump again suggests that he still holds out hope of benefiting from continued negotiations. Mr Trump’s effusiveness about his friendship with Mr Kim is also likely to burnish the dictator’s image internationally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump, for his part, used the occasion to congratulate himself for saving the region from the devastating conflict that he claimed would be racking it had it not been for his efforts. “We are in a much different place than we were two and a half years ago,” he said. He complained repeatedly and at length about the media, whose lack of appreciation for his efforts he deemed “insulting”. He also seemed to enjoy the theatricality of the meeting, which was enhanced by its supposedly impromptu nature. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It remains unclear whether the encounter really was arranged in just 24 hours. On the one hand, the chaotic scenes at Panmunjom (including the White House press secretary getting into a fight with North Korean security officers) did not suggest extensive planning. On the other, the two leaders had been exchanging letters in the weeks leading up to the meeting, and Mr Trump had brought his entire team of nuclear negotiators along with him on his long-planned visit to Seoul. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If peace-making is taken to mean improving relations with a rogue dictatorship, the meeting certainly had some value. But it contributed very little to America’s aim to persuade North Korea to give up its nuclear weapons. In a press conference following his encounter with Mr Kim, Mr Trump told reporters that the two sides’ negotiating teams would get together in the coming weeks to arrange working-level talks. “They’ll start a process, and we’ll see what happens,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arms-control experts have been hoping for the start of that process ever since Mr Trump announced his meeting with Mr Kim in Singapore more than 13 months ago. The failure to get down to nitty-gritty talks had been taken as a sign that North Korea was not really serious about disarmament. Even if negotiators do finally start chewing over details, there is little reason to imagine that Mr Kim is ready at last to surrender his nuclear weapons. But he and Mr Trump do like a photo-op.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 17:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[DMZ photo-up by Donald Trump and Kim Jong Un signals a return to nuclear talks]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/30/dmz-photo-up-by-donald-trump-and-kim-jong-un-signals-a-return-to-nuclear-talks]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190706_blp902.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-30T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON THE morning of June 29th Donald Trump, America’s president, extended the most casual of invitations from his hotel room in Osaka, where he was attending a meeting of the G20 hosted by Japan. “If Chairman Kim of North Korea sees this, I would meet him at the Border/DMZ just to shake his hand and say Hello(?)!,” Mr Trump wrote on Twitter. After all, Mr Trump was already scheduled to visit the “demilitarised zone” between the two Koreas the next day, after a meeting with Moon Jae-in, South Korea’s president. Why not throw in a meeting with North Korea’s dictator, whom he had met twice before in an effort to get North Korea to abandon its nuclear weapons. Mere hours later, North Korea pronounced Mr Trump’s suggestion “very interesting”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interesting enough that, on the afternoon of June 30th, Mr Kim and Mr Trump met for the third time in just over a year. Following a tour of the South Korean side of the DMZ, which also took in a windswept guard post and a canteen where troops presented the president with a golfing outfit, Mr Trump strolled towards the dividing line in the truce village of Panmunjom. He shook hands with Mr Kim, who was waiting for him on the northern side, before stepping across the line into North Korea. The moment was heavy with symbolism: it was the first time a sitting American president had set foot in North Korea, and it came 69 years, nearly to the day, after American troops had entered the Korean war on the South’s side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During a brief chat on the northern side, Mr Trump said it was an “honour” to visit North Korea. Mr Kim appeared chuffed: “I never expected to see you in this place,” he told Mr Trump, who then invited the North’s dictator to visit the White House. Afterwards, the two stepped back across the line into South Korea, where they posed briefly for a photo with Mr Moon before retiring for talks to “Freedom House” on the southern side. Mr Moon, who needs negotiations between America and North Korea to restart in order to advance his ambitious agenda of inter-Korean economic cooperation, was effusive throughout. “The flower of peace is blossoming on the Korean peninsula,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As well as being a gift for Mr Moon, the summit was also a boon for Messrs Trump and Kim. The president’s comments during and around the meeting will have pleased Mr Kim. Mr Trump downplayed North Korea’s recent tests of short-range missiles, claiming America did not consider them missile tests. Mr Kim’s nuclear programme barely got a mention: for all the world, it looked as though Mr Trump was perfectly happy to engage with North Korea on its own terms, implicitly acknowledging the regime’s nuclear-armed status as legitimate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These comments, along with the pictures of Mr Trump stepping into North Korea and saying that he was honoured to be received by Mr Kim, are gold for the North’s domestic propaganda machine, which is bound to use them to demonstrate the great leader’s diplomatic acumen. They may go some way towards brushing up Mr Kim’s domestic image following the collapse of the pair’s previous summit, in Vietnam in February. North Korea’s failure to win relief from sanctions at that meeting seems to have so infuriated Mr Kim that he demoted his chief negotiator and is rumoured to have punished other aides. But the decision to meet Mr Trump again suggests that he still holds out hope of benefiting from continued negotiations. Mr Trump’s effusiveness about his friendship with Mr Kim is also likely to burnish the dictator’s image internationally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump, for his part, used the occasion to congratulate himself for saving the region from the devastating conflict that he claimed would be racking it had it not been for his efforts. “We are in a much different place than we were two and a half years ago,” he said. He complained repeatedly and at length about the media, whose lack of appreciation for his efforts he deemed “insulting”. He also seemed to enjoy the theatricality of the meeting, which was enhanced by its supposedly impromptu nature. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It remains unclear whether the encounter really was arranged in just 24 hours. On the one hand, the chaotic scenes at Panmunjom (including the White House press secretary getting into a fight with North Korean security officers) did not suggest extensive planning. On the other, the two leaders had been exchanging letters in the weeks leading up to the meeting, and Mr Trump had brought his entire team of nuclear negotiators along with him on his long-planned visit to Seoul. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If peace-making is taken to mean improving relations with a rogue dictatorship, the meeting certainly had some value. But it contributed very little to America’s aim to persuade North Korea to give up its nuclear weapons. In a press conference following his encounter with Mr Kim, Mr Trump told reporters that the two sides’ negotiating teams would get together in the coming weeks to arrange working-level talks. “They’ll start a process, and we’ll see what happens,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arms-control experts have been hoping for the start of that process ever since Mr Trump announced his meeting with Mr Kim in Singapore more than 13 months ago. The failure to get down to nitty-gritty talks had been taken as a sign that North Korea was not really serious about disarmament. Even if negotiators do finally start chewing over details, there is little reason to imagine that Mr Kim is ready at last to surrender his nuclear weapons. But he and Mr Trump do like a photo-op.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 16:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Microsoft’s transformation required a change of culture]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/29/how-microsoft-survived-creative-destruction]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_wbp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-30T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;LIKE AN NFL changing room, the technology industry is littered with the bodies of fallen champions, from AOL to Yahoo to Blackberry, in urgent need of rehabilitation. Ten years ago many might have expected Microsoft to end up in the same state. But the software giant has made a startling comeback, regularly vying for the title of the most valuable company on global stockmarkets, with a market capitalisation above $1trn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The story of this revival is the subject of a new case study by Hermania Ibarra and Adam Jones of London Business School (LBS). In large part, the success has resulted from a shift away from a focus on the Windows operating system and towards Azure, Microsoft’s cloud-based services offering. It involved a willingness to let Microsoft programs run on Apple and Android smartphones, something the company had previously avoided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the turnaround also required a change to the company’s culture and that is the main subject of the LBS study. The shift to cloud-based services meant that revenues would be generated in a different way. Under the old system, clients bought software under a fixed-term contract; once the sale was made, the revenue was guaranteed. Cloud services are paid for on a metered basis; revenue comes in only when customers use them. That required a new approach by the company’s sales team, led by Jean-Philippe Courtois.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shift was enormous. Around 40,000 people had to change how they did their jobs. Three elements were important. First, staff had to understand how customers were using cloud-based services, so that they could be encouraged to use them more. This required 5,000 specialist hires.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second, to permit existing sales staff to concentrate on attracting and retaining customers, they had to be relieved of some duties, such as preparing sales forecasts. Internal review meetings were reduced, including an intimidating ordeal known as the mid-year review in which senior executives grilled employees—and for which workers spent lots of time cramming like students for a test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, salespeople needed an incentive to put in the work to flog the new products, which were potentially less lucrative for them than the traditional fixed-term contracts. This involved a greater use of performance bonuses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This being Microsoft, technology chivvied the process along. A new productivity tool helped workers analyse how much time they spent in meetings or writing emails and whether they were interacting with fellow Microsoft employees or with clients. Among other things, it allowed the usefulness of meetings to be gauged: if staff were fiddling with their work smartphones, they were not listening to their colleagues and probably had better things to do than loiter in a conference room. (The test could be usefully applied to meetings at a lot more places than Microsoft.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Managers have had to change too. Microsoft is introducing a programme called “Reimagine Managers” which aims to foster an approach of coaching and caring for the staff. Technology has made some routine management tasks (like organising rotas) easier, leaving more time for more time-consuming non-routine ones, such as talking to employees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Changing a corporate culture is an enormous task, and Mr Courtois admits that it is a work in progress. Microsoft, he says, has shifted from a “fixed mindset” to a “growth mindset”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what is interesting about the Microsoft case study (which is mostly free of such management jargon) is that it highlights the practical changes needed to transform a company. Microsoft could have been a classic victim of “creative disruption”, so dependent on an existing technology (personal computers) that it failed to manage the shift to a world dominated by mobile devices. But the shift has only been successful (so far) because it has involved not just a strategic insight, but a change in approach across the workforce.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft can still trip up. Tech companies are like the Red Queen in Lewis Carroll’s “Through the Looking Glass”—constantly running to stay in the same place. IBM performed a successful shift from hardware to services in the 1990s, but has struggled to grow its revenues or lift its share price in recent years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the long run Microsoft’s fortunes may depend on whether acquisitions like LinkedIn, the career site, or GitHub, a software-development startup, prove wiser than its failed bet on Nokia’s mobile-phone business earlier in the decade. But it has already shown that, even in a big organisation, cultural change is possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jul 2019 15:40:18 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is China’s “one country, two systems” policy?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/06/30/what-is-chinas-one-country-two-systems-policy]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_CNP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-30T10:38:53Z&quot;&gt;Jun 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS of demonstrators repeatedly took to the streets of Hong Kong in June to protest against a proposed law that would allow the extradition of criminal suspects to mainland China. Their demonstrations, some of the largest in Hong Kong’s history, were instrumental in persuading the territory’s chief executive, Carrie Lam, to suspend the bill. In agitating against closer ties, Hong Kongers made use of freedoms that are denied in mainland China. What is their origin?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the late 20th century three historically Chinese territories remained beyond the control of the Chinese Communist Party: Taiwan, Macau and Hong Kong. Shortly after emerging as China’s paramount leader in 1978, Deng Xiaoping declared his ambition of achieving “reunification” with Taiwan. The island is technically the last stronghold of a government that once ruled all of China until a civil war ended in victory for the Communists in 1949, sending the defeated nationalist army into exile on Taiwan. Since then it has become a democracy, and its people increasingly identify as “Taiwanese”. Rulers in Beijing are sworn to unify the island with the mainland, if needs be by force.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deng promised Taiwan a “high degree of autonomy”, describing his proposal as “one country, two systems”. Taiwan would be allowed to retain its separate administration, capitalist way of life and even its own armed forces as long as it recognised the Communist government in Beijing as legitimate in all of China, including Taiwan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Taiwanese did not take the bait, but China used the “one country, two systems” idea when it took back Hong Kong from Britain and Macau from Portugal. Britain had secured the heart of Hong Kong in perpetuity as spoils of the 19th-century Opium Wars but the final part, the New Territories, was acquired on a 99-year lease in 1898. The Portuguese had ruled Macau since the 1500s, but eventually started withdrawing troops in 1975. With Britain’s lease expiring and Portugal abandoning Macau, China began talks with both countries in the mid-1980s to make arrangements for the return of the two territories and to decide their future political arrangements. Hong Kong and Macau were to become parts of China again in 1997 and 1999, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All parties, including China, recognised that imposing China’s political system on the two colonies would create panic and cause economic mayhem. “One country, two systems” would allow the territories to remain much as they were, with independent legal systems and police forces. Their political structures would change little, except that local “chief executives” would replace governors sent by the colonial powers. In Hong Kong, the chief executive would be elected by a 1,200-member electoral college from a pool of candidates approved by the Chinese government and would preside over a system modelled roughly on Britain’s, though with a single legislative chamber. China even promised that the chief executives would eventually be elected by “universal suffrage”, though its exact meaning in this context is unclear. The government in Beijing would be responsible for defence and diplomacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These arrangements are to last for 50 years. It is unclear what happens after 2047. In the meantime, democracy activists have been growing despondent as pro-establishment forces, some funded by Beijing, secured majorities in local councils and the territory’s legislature, and new loyalty tests were imposed on candidates for office. Frustration led to the so-called Umbrella Movement of 2014, a series of protests and sit-ins aimed at securing a promise of genuine democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In response, the central authorities doubled down on the “one country” side of the deal. In 2016 and 2017 they secured the disbarring of six legislators for disrespecting China by mangling their oaths of loyalty. This year they have changed Hong Kong’s constitution to require the passage of a law that would punish people for insulting the national anthem, mirroring a law China passed in 2017. And they have pushed to change the current, colonial-era law that specifically bars extraditions to China. The proposed bill does not cover political offences, but many fear that the Communist Party could use it to secure the extradition of people deemed offensive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though Ms Lam has suspended the extradition bill, political veterans expect the Communist Party to tighten its grip in myriad, less visible ways. The central government still praises “one country, two systems” as a great innovation. In January China’s leader, Xi Jinping, stressed the policy’s importance for securing what he called the “inevitable” unification of the mainland and Taiwan. Few in Taiwan are convinced. Recent events in Hong Kong have only increased their suspicions. Deng’s innovative solution to the problem of reunification has never faced greater scepticism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 21:26:28 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Microsoft’s transformation required a change of culture]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/30/microsofts-transformation-required-a-change-of-culture]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_wbp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-30T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;LIKE AN NFL changing room, the technology industry is littered with the bodies of fallen champions, from AOL to Yahoo to Blackberry, in urgent need of rehabilitation. Ten years ago many might have expected Microsoft to end up in the same state. But the software giant has made a startling comeback, regularly vying for the title of the most valuable company on global stockmarkets, with a market capitalisation above $1trn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The story of this revival is the subject of a new case study by Hermania Ibarra and Adam Jones of London Business School (LBS). In large part, the success has resulted from a shift away from a focus on the Windows operating system and towards Azure, Microsoft’s cloud-based services offering. It involved a willingness to let Microsoft programs run on Apple and Android smartphones, something the company had previously avoided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the turnaround also required a change to the company’s culture and that is the main subject of the LBS study. The shift to cloud-based services meant that revenues would be generated in a different way. Under the old system, clients bought software under a fixed-term contract; once the sale was made, the revenue was guaranteed. Cloud services are paid for on a metered basis; revenue comes in only when customers use them. That required a new approach by the company’s sales team, led by Jean-Philippe Courtois.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shift was enormous. Around 40,000 people had to change how they did their jobs. Three elements were important. First, staff had to understand how customers were using cloud-based services, so that they could be encouraged to use them more. This required 5,000 specialist hires.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second, to permit existing sales staff to concentrate on attracting and retaining customers, they had to be relieved of some duties, such as preparing sales forecasts. Internal review meetings were reduced, including an intimidating ordeal known as the mid-year review in which senior executives grilled employees—and for which workers spent lots of time cramming like students for a test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, salespeople needed an incentive to put in the work to flog the new products, which were potentially less lucrative for them than the traditional fixed-term contracts. This involved a greater use of performance bonuses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This being Microsoft, technology chivvied the process along. A new productivity tool helped workers analyse how much time they spent in meetings or writing emails and whether they were interacting with fellow Microsoft employees or with clients. Among other things, it allowed the usefulness of meetings to be gauged: if staff were fiddling with their work smartphones, they were not listening to their colleagues and probably had better things to do than loiter in a conference room. (The test could be usefully applied to meetings at a lot more places than Microsoft.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Managers have had to change too. Microsoft is introducing a programme called “Reimagine Managers” which aims to foster an approach of coaching and caring for the staff. Technology has made some routine management tasks (like organising rotas) easier, leaving more time for more time-consuming non-routine ones, such as talking to employees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Changing a corporate culture is an enormous task, and Mr Courtois admits that it is a work in progress. Microsoft, he says, has shifted from a “fixed mindset” to a “growth mindset”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what is interesting about the Microsoft case study (which is mostly free of such management jargon) is that it highlights the practical changes needed to transform a company. Microsoft could have been a classic victim of “creative disruption”, so dependent on an existing technology (personal computers) that it failed to manage the shift to a world dominated by mobile devices. But the shift has only been successful (so far) because it has involved not just a strategic insight, but a change in approach across the workforce.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft can still trip up. Tech companies are like the Red Queen in Lewis Carroll’s “Through the Looking Glass”—constantly running to stay in the same place. IBM performed a successful shift from hardware to services in the 1990s, but has struggled to grow its revenues or lift its share price in recent years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the long run Microsoft’s fortunes may depend on whether acquisitions like LinkedIn, the career site, or GitHub, a software-development startup, prove wiser than its failed bet on Nokia’s mobile-phone business earlier in the decade. But it has already shown that, even in a big organisation, cultural change is possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 21:26:27 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump meets Kim Jong Un on the border between South and North Korea]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/30/donald-trump-meets-kim-jong-un-on-the-border-between-south-and-north-korea]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190706_blp902.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-30T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON THE morning of June 29th Donald Trump, America’s president, extended the most casual of invitations from his hotel room in Osaka, where he was attending a meeting of the G20 hosted by Japan. “If Chairman Kim of North Korea sees this, I would meet him at the Border/DMZ just to shake his hand and say Hello(?)!,” Mr Trump wrote on Twitter. After all, Mr Trump was already scheduled to visit the “demilitarised zone” between the two Koreas the next day, after a meeting with Moon Jae-in, South Korea’s president. Why not throw in a meeting with North Korea’s dictator, whom he had met twice before in an effort to get North Korea to abandon its nuclear weapons. Mere hours later, North Korea pronounced Mr Trump’s suggestion “very interesting”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interesting enough that, on the afternoon of June 30th, Mr Kim and Mr Trump met for the third time in just over a year. Following a tour of the South Korean side of the DMZ, which also took in a windswept guard post and a canteen where troops presented the president with a golfing outfit, Mr Trump strolled towards the dividing line in the truce village of Panmunjom. He shook hands with Mr Kim, who was waiting for him on the northern side, before stepping across the line into North Korea. The moment was heavy with symbolism: it was the first time a sitting American president had set foot in North Korea, and it came 69 years, nearly to the day, after American troops had entered the Korean war on the South’s side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During a brief chat on the northern side, Mr Trump said it was an “honour” to visit North Korea. Mr Kim appeared chuffed: “I never expected to see you in this place,” he told Mr Trump, who then invited the North’s dictator to visit the White House. Afterwards, the two stepped back across the line into South Korea, where they posed briefly for a photo with Mr Moon before retiring for talks to “Freedom House” on the southern side. Mr Moon, who needs negotiations between America and North Korea to restart in order to advance his ambitious agenda of inter-Korean economic cooperation, was effusive throughout. “The flower of peace is blossoming on the Korean peninsula,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As well as being a gift for Mr Moon, the summit was also a boon for Messrs Trump and Kim. The president’s comments during and around the meeting will have pleased Mr Kim. Mr Trump downplayed North Korea’s recent tests of short-range missiles, claiming America did not consider them missile tests. Mr Kim’s nuclear programme barely got a mention: for all the world, it looked as though Mr Trump was perfectly happy to engage with North Korea on its own terms, implicitly acknowledging the regime’s nuclear-armed status as legitimate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These comments, along with the pictures of Mr Trump stepping into North Korea and saying that he was honoured to be received by Mr Kim, are gold for the North’s domestic propaganda machine, which is bound to use them to demonstrate the great leader’s diplomatic acumen. They may go some way towards brushing up Mr Kim’s domestic image following the collapse of the pair’s previous summit, in Vietnam in February. North Korea’s failure to win relief from sanctions at that meeting seems to have so infuriated Mr Kim that he demoted his chief negotiator and is rumoured to have punished other aides. But the decision to meet Mr Trump again suggests that he still holds out hope of benefitting from continued negotiations. Mr Trump’s effusiveness about his friendship with Mr Kim is also likely to burnish the dictator’s image internationally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump, for his part, used the occasion to congratulate himself for saving the region from the devastating conflict that he claimed would be racking it had it not been for his efforts. “We are in a much different place than we were two and a half years ago,” he said. He complained repeatedly and at length about the media, whose lack of appreciation for his efforts he deemed “insulting”. He also seemed to enjoy the theatricality of the meeting, which was enhanced by its supposedly impromptu nature. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It remains unclear whether the encounter really was arranged in just 24 hours. On the one hand, the chaotic scenes at Panmunjom (including the White House press secretary getting into a fight with North Korean security officers) did not suggest extensive planning. On the other, the two leaders had been exchanging letters in the weeks leading up to the meeting, and Mr Trump had brought his entire team of nuclear negotiators along with him on his long-planned visit to Seoul. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If peace-making is taken to mean improving relations with a rogue dictatorship, the meeting certainly had some value. But it contributed very little to America’s aim to persuade North Korea to give up its nuclear weapons. In a press conference following his encounter with Mr Kim, Mr Trump told reporters that the two sides’ negotiating teams would get together in the coming weeks to arrange working-level talks. “They’ll start a process, and we’ll see what happens,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arms-control experts have been hoping for the start of that process ever since Mr Trump announced his meeting with Mr Kim in Singapore more than 13 months ago. The failure to get down to nitty-gritty talks had been taken as a sign that North Korea was not really serious about disarmament. Even if negotiators do finally start chewing over details, there is little reason to imagine that Mr Kim is ready at last to surrender his nuclear weapons. But he and Mr Trump do like a photo-op.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 21:26:26 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America and China resume talks in a bid to end their trade war]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/29/america-and-china-resume-talks-in-a-bid-to-end-their-trade-war]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190706_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;XI JINPING and Donald Trump claim to be fond of each other. After a year of spiralling disputes between America and China, their professions of friendship are hard to believe. But it is true that whenever they get together, they usually succeed in stabilising their countries’ relationship, at least for a time. Their meeting on June 29th, on the sidelines of the G20 summit in Osaka, appears to have delivered again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two superpowers agreed to resume their on-again, off-again trade negotiations, and America desisted from applying further tariffs. That is a welcome respite for global markets and companies, and indeed for anyone who hopes that China and America can find a way to avoid a new cold war. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, it is also true that the periods of calm after previous Xi-Trump meetings have only lasted so long, and have ultimately been followed by a progressive escalation of the trade war. Whether that happens this time will hinge on the negotiations that are set to begin anew. There are many reasons for pessimism and one for guarded optimism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Details of what the leaders agreed during their 80-minute meeting are still scant. The biggest surprise was Mr Trump’s statement at a subsequent press conference that America would permit its tech companies to continue selling components to Huawei, a Chinese telecoms giant, an apparent reversal of an earlier decision to blacklist it. That is a big reprieve for Huawei, and a victory for Mr Xi. But Mr Trump also suggested that a final decision on how to handle Huawei would rest on the fate of the trade talks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America’s decision to hold off on further tariffs had been expected, because China had made that a precondition for the resumption of talks. But it is important all the same. America has so far levied tariffs of 25% on $250bn-worth of Chinese imports, about half of what China sells to America. Mr Trump had threatened to slap tariffs on almost all remaining Chinese imports if the talks with Mr Xi went badly. Chinese officials, for their part, emphasised the leaders’ agreement that talks would proceed “on the basis of equality and mutual respect”, wording that helps address their complaint that America was making one-sided demands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet one obvious lesson from the past year is that it will be exceedingly tough to reach a true deal. The longer the dispute goes on, the more intractable it seems to get. At the outset Mr Trump dwelled on China’s gaping trade surplus with America. But it soon became clear that his combative approach had uncorked a range of long-held American grievances. Among the issues to have figured in the talks: restrictions on foreign firms’ access to the Chinese market, China’s shoddy protection of intellectual property and the range of subsidies that underpin China’s economic model.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The commercial conflict has also laid bare a rivalry over technology that is destined only to get more intense. Even if America and China manage to roll back tariffs, these are just one part of their increasingly sprawling confrontation. Chinese investors and researchers in America face more restrictions and scrutiny. China has said it will blacklist foreign companies that cut off supplies to its firms. Both countries are developing plans specifically aimed at curbing technological reliance on the other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In some ways, too, the political dynamics have become worse. Mr Trump is heading into an election year and does not want to appear soft on China. In China itself the field has tilted in favour of those advocating a more unyielding stance. Since the breakdown in trade talks in early May, state media have unleashed a bombardment of commentaries that are highly critical of America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many assume that as the cost of the trade war rises—whether in the form of slower growth or sputtering markets—cooler heads will prevail. But Mr Trump so far likes what he sees. American stocks just notched up their best first-half performance in more than two decades (largely thanks to the Federal Reserve’s signalling that it will cut interest rates). China has felt more pain from the trade war, but its fiscal and monetary policies are also shifting in a pro-growth direction. So for the time being, both countries may feel emboldened rather than constrained by their economies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The one reason for cautious optimism is that the new round of talks should be grounded in greater realism. The breakdown in early May occurred when Chinese negotiators insisted on major revisions to a deal that the Americans thought was nearly done. It is not known whether there had been a change of heart on the Chinese side—a feeling that they had given away too much—or whether it was a negotiating tactic, a last-minute rollback of promises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In either case the deep freeze in talks over the past two months has not been a total waste. China has laid out its position more explicitly than before, making three core demands: America must scrap all tariffs imposed on China since the start of the trade war; commitments to buy more American goods must be “realistic”; and the text of the final deal must be balanced, not just a list of Chinese concessions. The American side has long been clear about what it wants from China: credible commitments both to reduce its trade surplus and reform its economic policies, backed up by enforcement mechanisms if it fails to do so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese and American officials should have a good idea by now of the scope of an eventual agreement. That they are ready to resume talks suggests they think a deal is possible. But if the result is yet another breakdown, no one should be surprised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 19:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Join us for a day of ideas, debate and inspiration]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/28/join-us-for-a-day-of-ideas-debate-and-inspiration]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_OPP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T21:14:10Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join journalists from &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; for the second annual Open Future Festival on Saturday, October 5th 2019. Held in three cities simultaneously—Hong Kong, Manchester and Chicago—it is a chance for people from across the ideological spectrum to meet and debate vital issues on the future of open societies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hear talks and panels by prominent figures from politics, business, civil society and the arts. The festival themes include free speech and free trade; the environment and inequality; the rise of populism and anxiety over the algorithmic society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Come and share your ideas during a day of exciting discussions, curated content and exhibitions, immersive experiences and the chance to make connections with hundreds of festival attendees. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More information for the festivals by region:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://events.economist.com/events-conferences/asia/open-future-festival-hong-kong?utm_source=EM8172_Web_OFHUB&amp;amp;RefID=EM8172_Web_OFHUB&quot;&gt;Hong Kong event details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://events.economist.com/events-conferences/emea/open-future-festival-manchester/?utm_source=EM1696_Web_OFHUB&amp;amp;RefID=EM1696_Web_OFHUB&quot;&gt;Manchester event details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://events.economist.com/events-conferences/americas/open-future-festival-chicago/?utm_source=EM2355_Web_OFHUB&amp;amp;RefID=EM2355_Web_OFHUB&quot;&gt;Chicago event details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn more about Open Future&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Open Future &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/openfuture&quot;&gt;content hub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Take part in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/26/our-essay-competition-for-young-people&quot;&gt;Open Future essay contest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Letter from the editor: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2018/04/16/a-letter-to-readers-from-the-editor&quot;&gt;Open Future explained&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Watch &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s editor-in-chief Zanny Minton Beddoes interview &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NAfm5L_DOLM&quot; data-tegid=&quot;ub0s0birid6siht0j726ov5houcptr88&quot;&gt;Steve Bannon&lt;/a&gt; at last year’s festival&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Is capitalism rigged in favour of the elites? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://debates.economist.com/debate/capitalism&quot;&gt;Read the online debate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Read &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/01/21/we-need-to-own-our-data-as-a-human-right-and-be-compensated-for-it&quot;&gt;“We need to own our data as a human right—and be compensated for it”&lt;/a&gt;, an Open Future essay by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://will.i.am/&quot;&gt;will.i.am&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 07:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[In their first primary debate Democrats focused on the issues]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/28/in-their-first-primary-debate-democrats-focused-on-the-issues]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic- data-infographic-js=&quot;/2019/debate-night-interactive/js/bundle.js&quot; data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/debate-night-interactive/css/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/debate-night-interactive/css/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;“America does&lt;/small&gt; not want to witness a food fight, they want to know how we’re going to put food on their table.” So said Kamala Harris, the junior senator from California, on the second night of this week’s Democratic primary debate on June 27th. The line, while clearly scripted, provoked raucous applause, suggesting that the assembled audience was more interested in policy disagreements than bickering and personal attacks. That is, for the most part, what the candidates gave them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to an analysis of the first Democratic debate by &lt;i&gt;The Economist&lt;/i&gt;, the vast majority of the candidates’ time—more than 70%—was spent discussing specific policies. Elizabeth Warren, a senator from Massachusetts, and Julián Castro, a former housing secretary, impressed with their command of health-care and immigration policy. These issues took up 10% and 9% of the debate, respectively. Bernie Sanders and Pete Buttigieg, meanwhile, spoke at length about economic and foreign policy, which each represented about 10% of debate time. Other topics, such as climate change and gun control, received less attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such issues may be of little concern to primary voters. According to YouGov, a pollster, America’s biggest political divides run along demographic, not policy lines. Nonetheless, this week’s debate may still prove consequential. During Thursday’s tussle, Ms Harris pressed Mr Biden, the front-runner, over his civil rights record, including his opposition to school busing ordered by America’s Department of Education in the 1970s. The exchange may damage his standing among his core supporters. Prior to the debate, punters on PredictIt, a political-betting market, gave Ms Harris a 14% chance of winning the primary in South Carolina, where most Democratic primary voters are black. After her performance on Thursday, her chances jumped to 43%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 03:40:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why did the justices rule that courts cannot curb partisan redistricting?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/28/why-did-the-justices-rule-that-courts-cannot-curb-partisan-redistricting]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_USP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T11:29:13Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR JOHN LOCKE, the 17th-century political philosopher, anarchy was when a leader “has the liberty to be judge in his own case”. In a properly constituted society, disputes between contending parties are turned over to a third party for adjudication—an independent judge who can apply the law and issue a fair judgement. America’s judiciary generally fills this role. But on June 27th, a bare majority of the Supreme Court declared a crucial issue—partisan gerrymandering—outside its portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The court told state legislators they are their own bosses when it comes to drawing electoral maps for their legislatures and for Congress. No matter how blatantly or egregiously the lines are skewed, the federal judiciary will remain studiously above the fray. Legislators may choose their voters, rather than the other way around, and nobody will blink. The decision will give a bigger boost to Republicans, because they control more state houses and governor mansions. While it closes the door to claims of political gerrymandering, race-based gerrymandering remains subject to judicial review. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/18pdf/18-422_9ol1.pdf&quot;&gt;opinions&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;em&gt;Rucho v Common Cause&lt;/em&gt; were penned by the court’s best writers: Chief Justice John Roberts for the five-man conservative majority, Justice Elena Kagan for the four liberal dissenters. But the opinions offer starkly different visions of the courts’ role in preserving democratic norms and institutions. Whereas the chief summoned a raft of arguments to explain why there is simply no manageable way for judges to determine when a gerrymander goes too far, the dissent characterised the ruling as abrogating a “duty to declare the law” on a matter that is fundamental to the very functioning of American elections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The districting plans at issue here are highly partisan, by any measure”, Chief Justice Roberts began, but the lower courts that struck them down inappropriately “exercised judicial power” by declaring them “unconstitutional as well”. In dutifully laying out the facts of cases from North Carolina and Maryland, the chief expressed no alarm and said little about the bigger picture. He did, however, note some of the most alarming details, including a comment in 2016 from an architect of North Carolina’s congressional map securing a 10-3 Republican advantage in the House of Representatives. The legislator stopped at 10-3—in a state that is fairly evenly split between Republicans and Democrats—because he did “not believe it [would be] possible to draw a map with 11 Republicans and 2 Democrats”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Judges cannot stop stunts like this, even those that may “reasonably seem unjust”, Chief Justice Roberts wrote, because challenges to engineered maps “present political questions beyond the reach of the federal courts”. Objections to partisan gerrymandering are, in technical terms, “non-justiciable”. Federal courts “have no license to reallocate political power between the two major political parties”, the chief justice wrote, because there are “no legal standards to limit and direct their decisions”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In dissent, Justice Kagan replied with a truism: what the court says “can’t be done &lt;em&gt;has&lt;/em&gt; been done”. In recent years, “federal courts across the country...have largely converged on a standard for adjudicating partisan gerrymandering claims” and struck down maps drafted by both parties that are extreme outliers. The same advances in technology that permit modern gerrymanderers to carve precise maps to entrench their power afford challengers a tool to demonstrate just how engineered the lines are. In North Carolina, the Republican Party&amp;#x27;s map was, according to software analysis, “the absolute worst of 3,001 possible maps” for Democrats, the “only one that could produce a 10–3 partisan split even as Republicans got a bare majority of the state-wide vote”. The chief may fret over how much partisanship is too much, and declare that there is nowhere to draw a line, but, the dissent argues, surely the courts could agree that such a map is unfair to voters of the state’s minority party.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a rather feeble attempt to soften the blow of his decision, Chief Justice Roberts wrote that the majority’s “conclusion does not condone excessive partisan gerrymandering” and points to reform measures in Congress and in the states that could ease redistricting concerns. Several states have, indeed, turned line-drawing over to independent commissions in an attempt to push toward fairer maps. But curiously, in 2015, Chief Justice Roberts wrote a strong dissent in a case &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2015/07/02/one-for-the-people&quot;&gt;narrowly upholding&lt;/a&gt; the constitutionality of just such a commission in Arizona. That solution may not survive another challenge in the hands of the Supreme Court’s strengthened conservative majority. And the chief set himself up for ridicule when observing that a redistricting reform bill, first drafted in 2005, “has been reintroduced in every Congress since”. Well, Justice Kagan quipped, it “might be reintroduced until the end of time”. What all the proposals “have in common”, she wrote, “is that they are not laws”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which brings us back to Locke. There is an obvious reason why legislative fixes are not on the horizon. “The politicians who benefit from partisan gerrymandering”, like judges in their own cases, have no incentive to deal fairly with rivals. These legislators “are unlikely to change partisan gerrymandering” and because they “maintain themselves in office through partisan gerrymandering, the chances for legislative reform are slight”. With no one watching over them, and with increasingly sophisticated methods of identifying optimal maps to warp elections, legislators are now empowered to gerrymander at will. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Partisan redistricting has already “debased and dishonoured our democracy”, Justice Kagan wrote, “turning upside-down the core American idea that all governmental power derives from the people”. But with the door now shut on lawsuits and assurances that no one in the federal judiciary will meddle in their plans, gerrymandering legislators have a green light to skew electoral maps exactly as they please—a regime that could “irreparably damage our system of government”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 01:40:28 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>