<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[America and Iran are on a collision course]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/08/america-and-iran-are-on-a-path-to-dangerous-escalation]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_map501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-08T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 8th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“THE UNITED STATES is not seeking war with the Iranian regime,” declared John Bolton, America’s national security adviser, when he announced on May 5th the deployment of an aircraft-carrier strike group from the Mediterranean to waters near Iran. It would be led by the &lt;em&gt;USS Abraham Lincoln&lt;/em&gt;. A separate bomber task-force was also being deployed to the region. The move, Mr Bolton said, was a response to “troubling and escalatory” intelligence warnings about Iran’s behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Few believed Mr Bolton’s peaceable intent. The accusations against Iran—unnamed officials let it be known that it might have been planning to attack America’s forces or its allies—was suspiciously unspecific. Mr Bolton was the man, after all, who in 2015 penned an op-ed article in the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; entitled “To Stop Iran’s Bomb, Bomb Iran”. More worrying, and perhaps of greater consequence, Iran’s president, Hassan Rouhani, appeared to play into Mr Bolton’s hands on May 8th by declaring that Iran would stop complying with some of its commitments under the nuclear deal it signed with America and European powers in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The accord, known as the Joint Comprehensive Plan of Action (JCPOA), placed strict limits on Iran’s nuclear programme, for a decade or more, in exchange for the partial lifting of Western sanctions. Mr Trump ripped up the accord in 2018, calling it “the worst deal in the world”, and reimposed sanctions on Iran. America also threatened harsh penalties against firms that traded with it. American waivers for some countries to continue buying Iranian oil were halted this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until now, Iran has abided by the terms of the JCPOA, in the hope that European states would shield it from the worst of the economic pain. They failed to do that, and it is surely no accident that Mr Rouhani chose the first anniversary of Mr Trump’s withdrawal from the accord to announce a calibrated response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He claimed Iran would be acting within the dispute-resolutions of the JCPOA, without breaching it. “The path we have chosen today is not the path of war, it is the path of diplomacy,” he declared in a televised speech. “But diplomacy with a new language and a new logic.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Rouhani said Iran would begin to build up its stockpiles of low-enriched uranium and of heavy water, which are used in different types of nuclear reactors, thereby threatening to breach limits set by the JCPOA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He told European powers that it would reverse these measures if they found ways to shield Iran’s economy (particularly its oil and banking sectors) within 60 days. If they did not, Iran would also end the limits on the level of uranium enrichment. Under the JCPOA it is producing enriched uranium at a concentration below 4%, used for nuclear reactors, far below the 90% or higher level required for nuclear weapons. Iran also warned that it could rebuild the Arak nuclear reactor, which had been disabled under the JCPOA.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Far from being a new diplomatic concept, this appears to be an old Iranian logic of pushing ahead with its nuclear programme—and so moving closer to the option of building a nuclear bomb—in response to rising pressure from the West. Iran has always claimed to be seeking to develop nuclear technology only for civilian power generation. But much of the same technology can be used to build nuclear bombs. And UN nuclear inspectors had found enough evidence in the past of weapons-related activity to raise serious concerns about Iran’s ultimate goal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Israel had openly considered unilateral military action against Iran, but was dissuaded from it by American pressure. Mr Bolton had been prominent among hawks who believed in using economic pressure to remove the clerical regime, and American (or Israeli) military action to set back the nuclear programme if necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diplomacy with Iran under Barack Obama was intended to break this escalatory cycle leading to the grim choice of an Iranian nuclear bomb or bombing Iran. The JCPOA pushed back Iran’s nuclear programme from being perhaps a few months away from being able to build a bomb to requiring more than a year. But critics said it placed only temporary restraints on Iran, did not restrict missile technology and, by releasing frozen Iranian funds, gave the regime greater means to spread its influence in the Middle East—notably in the wars in Iraq, Syria and Yemen—and fund allied militant groups such as Hizbullah, the Shia militia-cum-party in Lebanon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump’s decision to abandon the JCPOA, despite pressure from European allies and many of his own advisers to reconsider, all but killed the deal. European efforts to keep it on life support are failing; most European firms have chosen to abide by the sanctions despite a European mechanism designed to protect those trading in “humanitarian” supplies with Iran. Now Mr Rouhani may bury the accord altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Iranian president has been under pressure from his own hawks who detested the JCPOA and pressed him to act more forcefully. His announcement is also an attempt to split the Europeans from America. But it is a risky strategy. Breaching the JCPOA and moving towards a nuclear capability would alienate the Europeans, and give America a clear cause to take harsher action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the past, Iran appeared almost to be daring America to take military action, perhaps believing that it would not dare to do so at a time when American troops were deeply entangled in the war in Iraq and vulnerable to retaliatory attacks by Iran’s proxy militias.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That risk has lessened somewhat as the war in Iraq has wound down. And violence by Iran’s proxies may be just the sort of provocation that hawks like Mr Bolton are looking for to justify a military campaign. Mr Trump, a harsh critic of America’s wars in the Middle East, who has wanted to withdraw American forces from the region, probably does not want war. Neither does Mr Rouhani. But hawks on both sides are taking control. Strange as it may seem, next to Mr Bolton it is the president who now seems the cautious grown-up in the White House.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 23:08:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A new exhibition resurrects a forgotten modern master]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/08/a-new-exhibition-resurrects-a-forgotten-modern-master]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_BKP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-08T15:06:51Z&quot;&gt;May 8th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN THE early 20th century Native American art was dominated by the work of the Kiowa Six. The collective drew on Plains hide painting and Ledger art (sketches on paper or cloth), depicting scenes from oral histories to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/01/21/artistic-encounters-with-indigenous-america-is-timely-and-troubling&quot;&gt;evoke a seemingly lost way of life&lt;/a&gt;. Men and women were rendered in an almost cartoonish style, usually hunting, dancing or performing rites; they often wore headdresses or traditional clothing. Karen Kramer, a curator specialising in Native American and Oceanic Art, judges that such iconography persisted for decades because “the art market was hungry for this sentimental imagery of Native life that never seemed to change.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the ’60s, as other ideas about American identity were being questioned, so too did representations of Native Americans evolve. The Institute of American Indian Art in Santa Fe, New Mexico, encouraged its students to depict their heritage using all the tools art and art history provided. As Alfred Young Man, one pupil, explained, they “revelled in the popularity of pop and op [optical] art, and abstract expressionism, and how the French impressionists painted.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;T.C. Cannon, part Kiowa and part Caddo, was also among that group, and a new exhibition at the Museum of the American Indian in New York celebrates his unique visual style and pioneering depictions of Native Americans. Like other artists at the time, he gravitated towards more figurative art after an era defined by abstraction. Cannon was particularly drawn to the Fauvists and their expressive, non-naturalistic, use of colour. He combined styles found in the work of Western painters such as Henri Matisse and Vincent Van Gogh with traditional Native American imagery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In “Law North of the Rosebud, 1971”, for example, Cannon depicts a tribal policeman against a flat background of red, blue, purple and lime green. A sheriff’s star is pinned to his label and braids spill from a ten-gallon hat, but in his case aviator glasses obscure a more personal identity. He stands with his hand on his hip, slightly slouching, as if tired or unimpressed. The simple modernity of the picture—and its subject’s reluctance to pose—seems like a refusal to bow to what a viewer might want from an “Indian” picture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere, Cannon refers to the most recognisable figures in Western art history: the Madonna and the reclining nude. “Cloud Madonna” (1975, pictured top right) uses the intense shade of blue often found in pictures of Mary, but this woman is carrying a gourd, not an infant; she balances a ceramic water jar on her head. The nude in “Collector #3” (1974, pictured above), meanwhile, borrows the pose of Titian’s “Venus of Urbino” but makes the setting wildly colourful, a mishmash of patterns.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cannon enlisted in the US Army in 1966, and a large part of the show is given over to this period. Several posters on display elsewhere in the museum address the apparent paradox of Native American military service, questioning why individuals would serve an army and government that attacked their culture. For many, enlisting was seen as noble, a continuation of the Kiowa warrior tradition, but Cannon returned from his service deeply troubled about his role in the Vietnam war and more cynical about his country. This disillusionment influenced his art. “Two Guns Arakira” (1974-1976, pictured top left), made after his return from the war, seems at first to be another Fauvist delight. The aged warrior, sat in an armchair, has long, violet hair; polka dots form the background. But upon close inspection, it becomes clear that the painting is not playful. The man’s face is grave, peering out of the frame as if expecting someone. He clutches a pistol in each hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“T.C. Cannon: At the Edge of America” is an excellent survey of a dynamic, inventive and wide-ranging artist. As well as the 30 paintings on display, visitors can enjoy his beautiful and sombre poems and listen to his songs (Bob Dylan, one of Cannon’s musical influences, also appears as the subject of a portrait). The exhibition lays bare Cannon’s technical skill, his humour and his ability to distill emotion in both word and colour. Four decades after his death in a car accident, aged just 31, he is finally receiving the recognition he deserves for his outsize influence and talent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“T.C. Cannon: At the Edge of America” is at the National Museum of the American Indian in New York until September 16th&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 23:07:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America and Iran are on a path to dangerous escalation]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/08/america-and-iran-are-on-a-collision-course]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_map005_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-08T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 8th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“THE UNITED STATES is not seeking war with the Iranian regime,” declared John Bolton, America’s national security adviser, when he announced on May 5th the deployment of an aircraft-carrier strike group from the Mediterranean to waters near Iran. It would be led by the &lt;em&gt;USS Abraham Lincoln&lt;/em&gt;. A separate bomber task-force was also being deployed to the region. The move, Mr Bolton said, was a response to “troubling and escalatory” intelligence warnings about Iran’s behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Few believed Mr Bolton’s peaceable intent. The accusations against Iran—unnamed officials let it be known that it might have been planning to attack America’s forces or its allies—was suspiciously unspecific. Mr Bolton was the man, after all, who in 2015 penned an op-ed article in the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; entitled “To Stop Iran’s Bomb, Bomb Iran”. More worrying, and perhaps of greater consequence, Iran’s president, Hassan Rouhani, appeared to play into Mr Bolton’s hands on May 8th by declaring that Iran would stop complying with some of its commitments under the nuclear deal it signed with America and European powers in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The accord, known as the Joint Comprehensive Plan of Action (JCPOA), placed strict limits on Iran’s nuclear programme, for a decade or more, in exchange for the partial lifting of Western sanctions. Mr Trump ripped up the accord in 2018, calling it “the worst deal in the world”, and reimposed sanctions on Iran. America also threatened harsh penalties against firms that traded with it. American waivers for some countries to continue buying Iranian oil were halted this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until now, Iran has abided by the terms of the JCPOA, in the hope that European states would shield it from the worst of the economic pain. They failed to do that, and it is surely no accident that Mr Rouhani chose the first anniversary of Mr Trump’s withdrawal from the accord to announce a calibrated response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He claimed Iran would be acting within the dispute-resolutions of the JCPOA, without breaching it. “The path we have chosen today is not the path of war, it is the path of diplomacy,” he declared in a televised speech. “But diplomacy with a new language and a new logic.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Rouhani said Iran would begin to build up its stockpiles of low-enriched uranium and of heavy water, which are used in different types of nuclear reactors, thereby threatening to breach limits set by the JCPOA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He told European powers that it would reverse these measures if they found ways to shield Iran’s economy (particularly its oil and banking sectors) within 60 days. If they did not, Iran would also end the limits on the level of uranium enrichment. Under the JCPOA it is producing enriched uranium at a concentration below 4%, used for nuclear reactors, far below the 90% or higher level required for nuclear weapons. Iran also warned that it could rebuild the Arak nuclear reactor, which had been disabled under the JCPOA.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Far from being a new diplomatic concept, this appears to be an old Iranian logic of pushing ahead with its nuclear programme—and so moving closer to the option of building a nuclear bomb—in response to rising pressure from the West. Iran has always claimed to be seeking to develop nuclear technology only for civilian power generation. But much of the same technology can be used to build nuclear bombs. And UN nuclear inspectors had found enough evidence in the past of weapons-related activity to raise serious concerns about Iran’s ultimate goal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Israel had openly considered unilateral military action against Iran, but was dissuaded from it by American pressure. Mr Bolton had been prominent among hawks who believed in using economic pressure to remove the clerical regime, and American (or Israeli) military action to set back the nuclear programme if necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diplomacy with Iran under Barack Obama was intended to break this escalatory cycle leading to the grim choice of an Iranian nuclear bomb or bombing Iran. The JCPOA pushed back Iran’s nuclear programme from being perhaps a few months away from being able to build a bomb to requiring more than a year. But critics said it placed only temporary restraints on Iran, did not restrict missile technology and, by releasing frozen Iranian funds, gave the regime greater means to spread its influence in the Middle East—notably in the wars in Iraq, Syria and Yemen—and fund allied militant groups such as Hizbullah, the Shia militia-cum-party in Lebanon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump’s decision to abandon the JCPOA, despite pressure from European allies and many of his own advisers to reconsider, all but killed the deal. European efforts to keep it on life support are failing; most European firms have chosen to abide by the sanctions despite a European mechanism designed to protect those trading in “humanitarian” supplies with Iran. Now Mr Rouhani may bury the accord altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Iranian president has been under pressure from his own hawks who detested the JCPOA and pressed him to act more forcefully. His announcement is also an attempt to split the Europeans from America. But it is a risky strategy. Breaching the JCPOA and moving towards a nuclear capability would alienate the Europeans, and give America a clear cause to take harsher action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the past, Iran appeared almost to be daring America to take military action, perhaps believing that it would not dare to do so at a time when American troops were deeply entangled in the war in Iraq and vulnerable to retaliatory attacks by Iran’s proxy militias.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That risk has lessened somewhat as the war in Iraq has wound down. And violence by Iran’s proxies may be just the sort of provocation that hawks like Mr Bolton are looking for to justify a military campaign. Mr Trump, a harsh critic of America’s wars in the Middle East, who has wanted to withdraw American forces from the region, probably does not want war. Neither does Mr Rouhani. But hawks on both sides are taking control. Strange as it may seem, next to Mr Bolton it is the president who now seems the cautious grown-up in the White House.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 23:06:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“America sees an opportunity to deliver a lethal, decisive blow to Iran”—brinkmanship in the Middle East]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/08/america-sees-an-opportunity-to-deliver-a-lethal-decisive-blow-to-iran-brinkmanship-in-the-middle-east]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_blp504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-08T09:27:45Z&quot;&gt;May 8th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A YEAR after President Donald Trump pulled America out of the Iran nuclear deal—and days after America moved warships into the Persian Gulf—Iran has announced that it will break parts of the deal. Is this more than just sabre-rattling? We also examine an impressive new effort to get inside the minds of those unable to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/04/27/how-to-give-voice-to-the-speechless&quot;&gt;speak&lt;/a&gt;. And why does &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/04/how-globalisation-created-british-cuisine&quot;&gt;British food&lt;/a&gt; get such a bad rap? The answer stretches back to the Industrial Revolution. Runtime: 21min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/nucleardiffusion-iran&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 18:37:11 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Penny Mordaunt is on manoeuvres]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/08/penny-mordaunt-is-on-manoeuvres]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_brp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-08T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 8th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE POLITICAL arts are often likened to magic because they depend on the suspension of disbelief. David Lloyd George was nicknamed the Welsh wizard. Harold Wilson was called an illusionist. Penny Mordaunt got an early start in training for her current profession when, as a teenager, she landed a job as a magician’s assistant. Now, thanks to Gavin Williamson’s sacking over leaks from the National Security Council, she has been given another lucky break in the form of her promotion to defence secretary, making her the first woman to hold the position.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Conservative Party is no longer run by a magic circle. But Ms Mordaunt’s new job puts her in a prime position to appeal to the collection of MPs and party activists who perform the same function today. She has carte blanche to appear frequently in the press against a background of warships and parades. And as a former junior defence minister, in 2015-16, and long-standing naval reservist, she has experience and the goodwill of the military brass to help her make a success of the job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Mordaunt’s rise is far more significant than the reverse side of the coin, Mr Williamson’s fall, fascinating though that is. It is possible that Mr Williamson will succeed in clearing his name over the leaks, and exacting revenge on Theresa May. But so what? Mrs May is on her last legs and Mr Williamson’s reputation was shot to pieces even before the scandal. Ms Mordaunt’s rise, on the other hand, is reordering the race to succeed the prime minister, providing Brexiteers with a potential new champion who is less dodgy than Boris Johnson and more likeable than Dominic Raab.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The defence job will let her highlight her distinctive life story. Her father is an ex-paratrooper who named his daughter after a frigate, &lt;em&gt;HMS Penelope&lt;/em&gt;. Both her parents were struck by cancer during her youth—her mother died and her father recovered—and she became her younger brother’s main carer. She worked her way through sixth-form college (hence the brief career in magic). Everything about her is a rebuke to Jeremy Corbyn, Labour’s leader, who was born in privilege and has taken every opportunity to criticise “militarism”, at least when it is practised by his own country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her new job will also let her shake off one of her potential negative characteristics. No doubt for lamentable and atavistic reasons, voters continue to distinguish between what political strategists call “mummy issues”, like health and welfare, and “daddy issues”, like security and the economy. Female politicians can pay a high price if they are associated only with the former. But, as if by way of compensation, they can also reap a rich reward if they master the latter. Mrs May’s rise to power was much aided by the fact that she had held the law-and-order brief, as home secretary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is Ms Mordaunt’s second piece of luck in the cabinet. Her previous job, running the Department for International Development (DFID), also brought big benefits. It allowed her to burnish her reputation as a compassionate conservative. The department’s guaranteed budget of 0.7% of GDP also provided Ms Mordaunt with a lot of money to spend at a time when other departments were suffering. Cabinet colleagues were grateful for DFID projects that helped them with their own agendas in, say, health or education.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Mordaunt is well positioned on the subject that most obsesses her party. The Conservatives’ ascendant Brexiteer faction trusts her to a degree that it doesn’t trust vicars of Bray such as Sajid Javid and Jeremy Hunt, because, unlike them, she supported Leave in 2016 (when she notoriously made the false claim that Britain would be unable to veto Turkey joining the EU). Nevertheless, she is at the saner end of the Brexiteer spectrum, so she can also harvest votes from Tory Remainers who want to honour the referendum without wrecking the economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She is equally well placed on the conservative-moderniser axis. She is a leader of the party’s Women2Win campaign to recruit more female MPs, and since last year has combined her main cabinet post with a position as minister for “women and equalities”. Yet at the same time, perhaps most important of all in this febrile era, she is a perfect Farage-fighting machine. She is a creature of the very world of simmering resentment and disappointed dreams that Nigel Farage hopes to conquer with his new Brexit Party. Brought up in Waterlooville, a down-at-heel corner of Hampshire, she now represents Portsmouth, a struggling seaside city.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Steady as she goes&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For all her strengths, Ms Mordaunt has a big weakness: she is rather too similar to the current prime minister for comfort. On the face of it she is as different from the publicity-shy and humourless Maybot as you could get. She appeared on a reality-TV diving contest, “Splash!”, and once gave a parliamentary speech on poultry in order to use the word “cock” and “lay” as many times as possible, after losing a bet with navy chums. But at a deeper level there are similarities. She shares Mrs May’s suspicion of the posh boys who have always vied with her own sort for control of the Conservative Party. And she has the same inability to think big thoughts or utter inspiring ideas. Rory Stewart, her successor at DFID, has made a more compelling case for overseas aid in his first few days in the job than she did in two years of leaden management-speak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is easy to forget how much hope the Tories once placed in Mrs May. The populist wing of the party thought she could stick it to the snobs. Pragmatists saw her as a safe pair of hands. Visionaries imagined she could extend the Conservatives’ appeal to working-class voters who were terrified of Mr Corbyn. The party was so impressed by her credentials that it telescoped the leadership campaign and handed her the job just two weeks after she had declared her candidacy. Ms Mordaunt may prove to be a sturdier vessel for the party’s hopes then the current prime minister. But this time the Tories need to make sure they subject all candidates to the most gruelling examination possible. When it comes to choosing prime ministers, it is vital to let in daylight upon magic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 13:58:49 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Don&#x27;t read too much into the release of two jailed journalists in Myanmar]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/07/dont-read-too-much-into-the-release-of-two-jailed-journalists-in-myanmar]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_asp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I can&amp;#x27;t wait to go to my newsroom,” Wa Lone told a crowd of reporters as he walked free of Insein prison in Yangon, Myanmar&amp;#x27;s biggest city. Mr Wa Lone and Kyaw Soe Oo, who work for Reuters news agency, were released on May 7th. The pair were convicted in September 2018 of breaking the Official Secrets Act and received a seven-year sentence. They had served 511 days before being released as part of an amnesty of over 6,000 prisoners to mark the country&amp;#x27;s New Year holiday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the beginning, the case against the journalists was absurd. The pair had been working on an investigation into the killing of ten men from the Rohingya Muslim minority in Rakhine state, where soldiers forced more than 700,000 Rohingyas to flee to Bangladesh in 2017, murdering a further 7,000 or so. The government never denied that the killings took place and last year convicted ten soldiers for their role in them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trial of the two journalists was a farce, orchestrated by the military. The pair were alleged to have broken a law dating back to the colonial era. The defence argued that they were entrapped by police who invited them to dinner, handed them state documents, and arrested them shortly afterwards. One officer admitted to burning his notes of the arrest; another policeman said they had been ordered to set up the journalists. A third was caught consulting notes written on his hand when testifying against the pair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, Mr Wa Lone and Mr Kyaw Soe Oo were sentenced, much to the dismay, in particular, of Western governments. They saw it as yet another symptom of Myanmar’s failure to reform itself, even under the de facto leadership of Nobel Peace prize winner Aung San Suu Kyi, head of the ruling National League for Democracy party. Activists held the case up as an example of the continuing oppression of human-rights. Every new legal appeal made front-page news in Myanmar. Diplomats pleaded with government officials for the journalists&amp;#x27; release. But despite all the pressure, Ms Suu Kyi refused to intervene, arguing that she could not interfere with the judicial process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two weeks ago the journalists had their third and final appeal rejected. That meant that all legal avenues to free the journalists had been exhausted. A pardon, which leaves court rulings intact, allows Ms Suu Kyi to make a small but attention-grabbing concession to the West, while not being seen to backtrack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, the journalists&amp;#x27; release certainly does not indicate any change of heart by the government. Under Ms Suu Kyi freedom of expression in Myanmar is being severely curtailed. A report released in January by Human Rights Watch, an NGO, found that a piece of loosely worded legislation which was supposed to regulate the telecoms sector is being used to crackdown on journalists and silence government critics. Since the National League for Democracy took power in 2016, about 140 cases have been brought under this law, many of which are baseless. Scores of reporters still languish in prison. Many of those who remain free now feel compelled to self-censor. The situation, sadly, is all too reminiscent of journalism under the old military regimes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thus freeing Mr Wa Lone and Mr Kyaw Soe Oo is part of a “balancing act”, argues Gerard McCarthy of Australian National University. Ms Suu Kyi must weigh the preferences of Western governments, previously her strongest backers, against many Burmese, who think that the two journalists betrayed their country by appearing to side with the hated Rohingya. Objections from this constituency, and the generals, will be assuaged by the fact that 6,000 other prisoners were freed at the same time. The release of the two journalists is a welcome gesture, but a small one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 04:06:26 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cory Booker unveils an ambitious gun-control plan]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/07/cory-booker-unveils-an-ambitious-gun-control-plan]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_USP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T18:16:01Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON MAY 6th, the day Senator Cory Booker published his presidential plan to cut gun violence, there were two shootings in his state of New Jersey, in which two people were injured. Across America, that day alone, there were 71 shootings, in which 14 died and dozens were wounded, according to the Gun Violence Archive, a nonprofit research organisation. It reckons that so far this year guns have killed 4,764 Americans, including 873 teenagers—and 196 children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Booker is making much on the campaign trail of being the only Democratic presidential candidate to live in a poor inner city area—in Newark, where he was mayor—and he highlighted the relentless, daily nature of gun violence in America when he unveiled his plan. “This is an everyday experience to people like me and folks in my community”, he said. “And I&amp;#x27;m not unique. This is happening all over the country, ripping apart communities.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The senator’s gun-control plan is part of his effort to stand out in a crowded Democratic field. Earlier this month Mr Booker said his campaign was short of the number of donors that would qualify him to appear in the televised primary debates that begin in June. But his plan is notable for two other reasons. First, it is the most ambitious gun control proposal to have been put forward by a presidential candidate. Though it would ban assault weapons, close loopholes that allow domestic abusers to buy guns and prevent the bulk sale of firearms, its central feature is the creation of a national licensing programme. This would require prospective gun-buyers to undergo an extensive background check by the Federal Bureau of Investigation, entailing fingerprinting and an interview, in order to obtain a five-year gun licence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No such national programme currently exists, but research suggests that licensing is the best way to cut America’s gun death rate, which is by far the highest in the rich world. Mr Booker cited a study from 2015 that shows gun deaths in Connecticut dropped by 40% after the state introduced a gun licensing programme. Massachusetts, which requires buyers to obtain a permit—a weeks’ long process involving an interview and a background check—has one of the lowest gun death rates in America. In 2016 it had 3.4 gun deaths per 100,000 people. Nearby New Hampshire, where buying a gun is a much simpler process, had 9.4 deaths per 100,000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Booker’s plan also suggests the Democratic Party has changed its thinking on gun control as a possible election issue. Democrats have not always wanted to campaign on gun control. Many believe a ban on assault weapons passed during Bill Clinton’s presidency cost them control of the House of Representatives in 1994 and that Al Gore’s enthusiasm for gun control cost him the presidency in 2000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their political calculus seems to be changing. Thanks in part to a new student-led movement for gun control that was sparked by a mass school shooting in Parkland, Florida, last February, the issue was prominent in November’s mid-terms. In at least 12 races, Democrats given an “F” rating by the National Rifle Association kicked out “A”-rated Republicans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though there are concerns that support for gun controls could turn off the sort of working class swing voters that in 2016 helped elect President Donald Trump, most 2020 Democratic candidates have said they back tighter gun controls. Senator Kamala Harris said recently she would give Congress 100 days to pass gun control laws before she used presidential executive power to enforce them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The election of a Democratic president may mean not mean much for America’s gun laws, however. Any comprehensive legislation would have to be passed by Congress; while the Republican Party remains in control of the Senate that is unlikely to happen. In March, having taken control of the House, Democrats passed a universal background checks bill, the first major gun control bill since 1994. Though such a step is backed by a majority of Americans it has not gone anywhere in the Senate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One Republican senator was quick to proclaim his opposition to serious gun-control laws after Mr Booker unveiled his plan. “BREAKING: the latest terrible idea to come out of the Democrats’ 2020 primary is a federal gun registry”, tweeted gun-loving Senator Rick Scott of Florida. “...What’s next? Will we have to register sharp knives?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 03:11:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Two jailed Reuters journalists are released by presidential pardon]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/07/do-not-read-too-much-into-the-release-of-two-jailed-journalists]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_asp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I can&amp;#x27;t wait to go to my newsroom,” Wa Lone told a crowd of reporters as he walked free of Insein prison in Yangon, Myanmar&amp;#x27;s biggest city. Mr Wa Lone and Kyaw Soe Oo, who work for Reuters news agency, were released on May 7th. The pair were convicted in September 2018 of breaking the Official Secrets Act and received a seven-year sentence. They had served 511 days before being released as part of an amnesty of over 6,000 prisoners to mark the country&amp;#x27;s New Year holiday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the beginning, the case against the journalists was absurd. The pair had been working on an investigation into the killing of ten men from the Rohingya Muslim minority in Rakhine state, where soldiers forced more than 700,000 Rohingyas to flee to Bangladesh in 2017, murdering a further 7,000 or so. The government never denied that the killings took place and last year convicted ten soldiers for their role in them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trial of the two journalists was a farce, orchestrated by the military. The pair were alleged to have broken a law dating back to the colonial era. The defence argued that they were entrapped by police who invited them to dinner, handed them state documents, and arrested them shortly afterwards. One officer admitted to burning his notes of the arrest; another policeman said they had been ordered to set up the journalists. A third was caught consulting notes written on his hand when testifying against the pair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, Mr Wa Lone and Mr Kyaw Soe Oo were sentenced, much to the dismay, in particular, of Western governments. They saw it as yet another symptom of Myanmar’s failure to reform itself, even under the de facto leadership of Nobel Peace prize winner Aung San Suu Kyi, head of the ruling National League for Democracy party. Activists held the case up as an example of the continuing oppression of human-rights. Every new legal appeal made front-page news in Myanmar. Diplomats pleaded with government officials for the journalists&amp;#x27; release. But despite all the pressure, Ms Suu Kyi refused to intervene, arguing that she could not interfere with the judicial process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two weeks ago the journalists had their third and final appeal rejected. That meant that all legal avenues to free the journalists had been exhausted. A pardon, which leaves court rulings intact, allows Ms Suu Kyi to make a small but attention-grabbing concession to the West, while not being seen to backtrack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, the journalists&amp;#x27; release certainly does not indicate any change of heart by the government. Under Ms Suu Kyi freedom of expression in Myanmar is being severely curtailed. A report released in January by Human Rights Watch, an NGO, found that a piece of loosely worded legislation which was supposed to regulate the telecoms sector is being used to crackdown on journalists and silence government critics. Since the National League for Democracy took power in 2016, about 140 cases have been brought under this law, many of which are baseless. Scores of reporters still languish in prison. Many of those who remain free now feel compelled to self-censor. The situation, sadly, is all too reminiscent of journalism under the old military regimes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thus freeing Mr Wa Lone and Mr Kyaw Soe Oo is part of a “balancing act”, argues Gerard McCarthy of Australian National University. Ms Suu Kyi must weigh the preferences of Western governments, previously her strongest backers, against many Burmese, who think that the two journalists betrayed their country by appearing to side with the hated Rohingya. Objections from this constituency, and the generals, will be assuaged by the fact that 6,000 other prisoners were freed at the same time. The release of the two journalists is a welcome gesture, but a small one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 03:11:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Two jailed Reuters journalists are released by presidential pardon]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/07/two-jailed-reuters-journalists-are-released-by-presidential-pardon]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_asp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I can&amp;#x27;t wait to go to my newsroom,” Wa Lone told a crowd of reporters as he walked free of Insein prison in Yangon, Myanmar&amp;#x27;s biggest city. Mr Wa Lone and Kyaw Soe Oo, who work for Reuters news agency, were released on May 7th. The pair were convicted in September 2018 of breaking the Official Secrets Act and received a seven-year sentence. They had served 511 days before being released as part of an amnesty of over 6,000 prisoners to mark the country&amp;#x27;s New Year holiday.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;From the beginning, the case against the journalists was absurd. The pair had been working on an investigation into the killing of ten men from the Rohingya Muslim minority in Rakhine state, where soldiers forced more than 700,000 Rohingyas to flee to Bangladesh in 2017, murdering a further 7,000 or so. The government never denied that the killings took place and last year convicted ten soldiers for their role in them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trial of the two journalists was a farce, orchestrated by the military. The pair were alleged to have broken a law dating back to the colonial era. The defence argued that they were entrapped by police who invited them to dinner, handed them state documents, and arrested them shortly afterwards. One officer admitted to burning his notes of the arrest; another policeman said they had been ordered to set up the journalists. A third was caught consulting notes written on his hand when testifying against the pair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, Mr Wa Lone and Mr Kyaw Soe Oo were sentenced, much to the dismay, in particular, of Western governments. They saw it as yet another symptom of Myanmar’s failure to reform itself, even under the de facto leadership of Nobel Peace prize winner Aung San Suu Kyi, head of the ruling National League for Democracy party. Activists held the case up as an example of the continuing oppression of human-rights. Every new legal appeal made front-page news in Myanmar. Diplomats pleaded with government officials for the journalists&amp;#x27; release. But despite all the pressure, Ms Suu Kyi refused to intervene, arguing that she could not interfere with the judicial process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two weeks ago the journalists had their third and final appeal rejected. That meant that all legal avenues to free the journalists had been exhausted. A pardon, which leaves court rulings intact, allows Ms Suu Kyi to make a small but attention-grabbing concession to the West, while not being seen to backtrack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, the journalists&amp;#x27; release certainly does not indicate any change of heart by the government. Under Ms Suu Kyi freedom of expression in Myanmar is being severely curtailed. A report released in January by Human Rights Watch, an NGO, found that a piece of loosely worded legislation which was supposed to regulate the telecoms sector is being used to crackdown on journalists and silence government critics. Since the National League for Democracy took power in 2016, about 140 cases have been brought under this law, many of which are baseless. Scores of reporters still languish in prison. Many of those who remain free now feel compelled to self-censor. The situation, sadly, is all too reminiscent of journalism under the old military regimes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thus freeing Mr Wa Lone and Mr Kyaw Soe Oo is part of a “balancing act”, argues Gerard McCarthy of Australian National University. Ms Suu Kyi must weigh the preferences of Western governments, previously her strongest backers, against many Burmese, who think that the two journalists betrayed their country by appearing to side with the hated Rohingya. Objections from this constituency, and the generals, will be assuaged by the fact that 6,000 other prisoners were freed at the same time. The release of the two journalists is a welcome gesture, but a small one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 03:10:10 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tech’s raid on the banks]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/07/techs-raid-on-the-banks]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/mt_twitter_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-07T14:10:28Z&quot;&gt;May 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;DIGITAL DISRUPTION is coming to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/special-report/2019/05/02/young-people-and-their-phones-are-shaking-up-banking&quot;&gt;banking&lt;/a&gt; at last. Helen Joyce travels across Asia to see how fintechs like Ant Financial are transforming how people spend, save and invest their money, and asks whether traditional banks can catch up. Who will win the battle to be the bank of the future? And could having a bank in your pocket make your money safer? Runtime: 23 min &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-tech-sraidonthebanks&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 02:07:04 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>