<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Joe Biden provides a fossil record of how the Democratic Party has changed]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/04/25/joe-biden-provides-a-fossil-record-of-how-the-democratic-party-has-changed]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190427_USD000_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;E&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;NTERING TO&lt;/small&gt; Bruce Springsteen’s “We Take Care of Our Own”, as his friend Barack Obama used to, Joe Biden performed a dress rehearsal for his long-awaited entry to the Democratic primary in Washington, &lt;small&gt;DC&lt;/small&gt;, earlier this month. His audience, burly delegates of the International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, were the sort of working-class voters the 76-year-old former vice-president is counting on to nullify the hard-left. He duly regaled them with familiar lines about Scranton, the Pennsylvanian mining-town his family fled almost seven decades ago. He also cracked gags about the recent controversy over his career-long habit of sniffing, kissing and pawing at women. “I just want you to know,” he deadpanned to the union men—twinkly old Uncle Joe style—that he “had permission to hug” their leader. If that is how Mr Biden, who enters the primary this week as the front-runner, means to handle his long and spotted history of statements and behaviour anathema to the modern Democratic Party, he might not last long.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As things stand, he owes his lead status to propitious circumstances, including the apparent lack of an outstanding alternative and his association with the revered Mr Obama. There is an obvious risk that he will fizzle as he did during two previous presidential runs, when he was an outsider and much less of a target to his opponents than he is now. Mr Biden is knowledgeable, likeable, right-minded, hugely experienced and polished in the way of an old-style variety show host. The way he glides up and down the emotional register—one moment seething, the next lachrymose—is something to behold. He is also garrulous, gaffe-prone and not obviously au fait with modern America. In other words, he has work to do, assuming he has the energy for it. Meanwhile, the suspicion that his candidacy is an anachronism makes it an extreme test-case for the Democrats’ biggest dilemma: how to reconcile the ideological purity demanded by an activist wing increasingly dedicated to racial, gender and sexual equality, with the real world of muddy compromises and more mixed social attitudes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This tension in the party is in part a product of the erosion of its unionised base, which has left it with a more fractured coalition of hipsters, minorities and immigrants. Such diversity requires constant management, leading to an almost fetishistic attention to liberal unifying principles by Democratic activists, which engenders intolerance. This is at odds with the more nuanced views of most voters. Mr Biden’s partnership with Mr Obama—the hip son of an African migrant—bridged the gap. The question is whether the bridge can still stand in the absence of its Obama-sized pier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hence the early attention to the many ways Mr Biden—over the course of a career in Democratic politics that began when the party still contained segregationists—has offended against contemporary liberal standards. Early examples include his dismissive treatment, as chairman of the Senate Judiciary Committee, of Anita Hill, a black woman who accused Clarence Thomas of sexual harassment during his Supreme Court confirmation hearing; Mr Biden’s disdainful attitude towards busing as a means to racially integrate schools; and his support for Bill Clinton’s draconian criminal-justice reforms. More such examples will arise. Mr Biden has a decades-long reputation for stirring controversy and his current main rival, Bernie Sanders, an emerging one for ruthlessness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Certain kinds of past transgression are now straightforwardly disqualifying among Democrats. In light of #MeToo, Mr Clinton has become an embarrassment. The more interesting thing about Mr Biden’s case is that he does not appear guilty of anything that was considered inappropriate at the time. His mistreatment of Ms Hill reflected the usual 1980s male chauvinism. It was also intended to help a black man reach the Supreme Court bench. Similarly, some of his policy positions have come to seem controversial mainly due to ignorance about their circumstances. Criminal-justice reform in the 1990s was fuelled by a fear of violent crime that has been largely forgotten on the left. Busing was in many places counter-productive; it exacerbated racial tension and left schools as segregated but worse-run than they were before. These contradictions represent a challenge to the Democrats’ liberal mullahs which is further complicated by Mr Biden’s mercurial nature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;American politics has a strong redemption tradition. Yet Mr Biden’s career is not merely defined by a relentless and contrite movement towards more liberal positions. Rather, he has always been broadly liberal, but with a propensity to lapse. He started work on the Violence Against Women Act, one of his big achievements, a year before his mishandling of Ms Hill. This makes him, warts and all, as contradictory as most voters, and in that sense a cautionary lesson for the purist left. Whether it can learn from it, however, will depend less on Mr Biden’s record than his present skill at explaining, defending and, where necessary, apologising for it. This is also the main reason to worry about his candidacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;Handsy Uncle Joe&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The past is never past, it is always present”, Mr Biden’s favourite singer, Mr Springsteen, once said. In the same way, political skeletons tend to do damage only when they highlight some current weakness. Mr Sanders had no trouble brushing off his patchy history on gun control because his progressive bona fides were not in doubt. Hillary Clinton’s callousness towards her husband’s female accusers was damaging, because it chimed with her reputation for cynicism. Mr Biden, who enters the race much-loved on the left, despite his shortcomings, has an easier opportunity to account for his record. He should defend his support for criminal-justice reform, explain his opposition to busing—and apologise to Ms Hill and to anyone upset by his handsiness. But does he have the contemporary political nous to make such necessary judgments and the discipline to stick by them? If not, he will fail, because those are also the biggest questions about his candidacy. That is why his recent joking about groping was so ominous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;United States&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;A blast from the past&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 18:06:37 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Some see malevolence in China’s “Belt and Road” lending]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/china/2019/04/25/some-see-malevolence-in-chinas-belt-and-road-lending]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190427_CNP001_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;C&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HINESE ENGINEERS&lt;/small&gt; are drilling their way through the green hills of Laos, clearing a path for a railway that one day may traverse South-East Asia. Each time they complete a tunnel—at least three times in the past month—they hold a brief ceremony, waving Chinese flags for the cameras. They are celebrating not just their engineering success but also the evidence before them that the Belt and Road Initiative (&lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;), China’s global infrastructure-building scheme, is making progress. The full railway is a long way off. Work has barely begun in Thailand, the next link. But the section in Laos should be in use by 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It will be a test of what many see as a big economic danger of the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;: that it will saddle poor countries with unmanageable debts. China insists that its tens of billions of dollars in loans and investments are fostering global prosperity—a message that it is sure to repeat to foreign leaders attending the second Belt and Road Forum, which takes place from April 25th to 27th in Beijing (pictured is a floral display marking the event). But worries about the cost of the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;, a project closely linked with President Xi Jinping’s foreign policy, have become widespread. Malaysia, Pakistan and Sierra Leone are among a growing list of countries that have delayed or scrapped China-led projects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are three main concerns about the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;’s financial consequences. The most extreme is that the scheme involves what is pithily described as “debt-trap diplomacy”. In this view, China is deliberately overloading weak countries with loans; when they buckle, it seizes their assets and influences their politics. This idea has featured in speeches by some American officials, including the vice-president, Mike Pence, who see &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; as an attempt to undermine America’s global influence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the investments funded by Chinese cash are not in China, so China has limited ability to grab assets when governments default. If it pushes too hard it may merely stoke antipathy. Instead, it usually responds by reducing the amount of money that debtors have to repay. Countries with longer records of lending to poor countries often do the same: the Paris Club of creditors was formed in 1956 to devise ways of reducing defaulters’ debt loads. The Centre for Global Development, a think-tank in Washington, has counted more than 80 cases between 2000 and 2017 in which China provided relief to its debtors overseas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An oft-cited example of China’s supposedly predatory approach involves Hambantota, a Sri Lankan port which has flopped commercially. In 2017 Sri Lanka handed control of the port to a state-owned Chinese company on a 99-year lease. But Deborah Brautigam of Johns Hopkins University says that of more than 3,000 China-financed projects that she and others have tracked, Hambantota is the only one that is used in support of the debt-trap theory. It is the exception, not the rule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What it lacks in malevolence, the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; may make up in clumsiness. This is the second concern: that China is lending to vulnerable states without sufficient caution. Take a group of 37 poor countries monitored by the &lt;small&gt;IMF&lt;/small&gt;. Loans from traditional bilateral lenders, including America and Japan, have declined from 7% of the debtors’ &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; to 2% over the past decade. Loans from China, by contrast, have soared from virtually nothing to 4%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is welcome that China is supporting hard-up nations. But its enthusiasm generates foolhardiness. David Dollar of the Brookings Institution in Washington has found that Chinese development lending appears indifferent to political and economic risks. The Centre for Global Development has identified eight countries drowning in red ink that could be further swamped by &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; projects (see chart). A report in December released by Peking University ranked 94 &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; countries based on measures such as the quality of their financial regulation and their openness to trade. Pakistan came second to last. That is awkward for China: Pakistan may receive as much as $60bn in &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; loans, which would make it the biggest recipient of all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is truth to claims that &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; credit can be ruinously expensive. Consider China Eximbank’s lending to Kenya for the Nairobi-Mombasa railway. Local reports say half the $3.6bn loan was priced 3.6 percentage points above a floating market interest-rate. That is high for a poor country. It is just one of many such loans by Eximbank, which said this week that its outstanding &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;-related credit was more than 1trn yuan, or nearly $150bn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;’s success will depend on whether Chinese lenders can tighten their procedures for assessing creditworthiness while making their loans more affordable. There are some promising signs. This week’s forum in Beijing is expected to stress the need for &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; debt to be sustainable. In the case of the railway in Laos, caution is already evident. The project involves $6bn of Chinese lending, which is about one-third of the &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; of Laos. So a joint venture has been created. It draws 70% of its capital from China and 30% from Laos. To fund its portion, Laos took a $465m loan from Eximbank. The loan was generous, according to local reports: it matures in 35 years at a 2.3% annual interest rate, well below the commercial price of such debt. Laos has five years before it has to begin making repayments. That is the kind of concession that it might have got from the World Bank. China may offer such generous terms more frequently. Last year it set up an agency to oversee its foreign aid, in part to turn the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; into a more co-ordinated development programme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this points to another concern that will be harder for China to deal with because it relates to the very nature of the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;: its sheer ambition. Potential benefits look impressive. A recent study by the World Bank concluded that &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; transportation projects could lift global &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; by 3%. That is larger than the benefits that are usually shown to be generated by free-trade agreements. It could yet bear out China’s notion that Westerners (save Donald Trump) just want to lower tariffs, whereas China is trying to build the roads that let trade happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This, though, is where the risks come in. The World Bank’s rosy analysis assumes that &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; projects are completed and work efficiently. The scale of the effort is a huge challenge, and such projects are a magnet for graft. Vast sums are being spent quickly in badly run places. The railway in Laos ought to make the landlocked country more accessible. But for it to prove effective, much more will be needed: better roads to link it to existing transport, new urban centres around the stations and freer trade with other countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China cannot achieve this alone, but its often overweening approach to the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; has alienated potential partners. America, India and Japan want little to do with it. One reason is that China is, in effect, asking others not only to sign up to its infrastructure plans but also to endorse Mr Xi’s worldview. It does not help that China reveals so little about its lending and that contracts go mainly to Chinese firms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some analysts in China have started to express unease. Economists at the Chinese Academy of Social Sciences, a think-tank, argued in a paper last year that the government must entice other countries to back &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; projects in order to share the risks. Otherwise, it could be China that finds itself trapped. Conservative estimates are that China will spend $1trn within the next decade on its monumental scheme—about as much as it holds today in American government bonds. Mr Xi would be wise not to let such an outlay turn sour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;China&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Seeds of suspicion&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 18:06:36 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Some see malevolence in China’s “Belt and Road” lending]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/china/2019/04/27/some-see-malevolence-in-chinas-belt-and-road-lending]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190427_CNP001_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-27T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 27th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;C&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HINESE ENGINEERS&lt;/small&gt; are drilling their way through the green hills of Laos, clearing a path for a railway that one day may traverse South-East Asia. Each time they complete a tunnel—at least three times in the past month—they hold a brief ceremony, waving Chinese flags for the cameras. They are celebrating not just their engineering success but also the evidence before them that the Belt and Road Initiative (&lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;), China’s global infrastructure-building scheme, is making progress. The full railway is a long way off. Work has barely begun in Thailand, the next link. But the section in Laos should be in use by 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It will be a test of what many see as a big economic danger of the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;: that it will saddle poor countries with unmanageable debts. China insists that its tens of billions of dollars in loans and investments are fostering global prosperity—a message that it is sure to repeat to foreign leaders attending the second Belt and Road Forum, which takes place from April 25th to 27th in Beijing (pictured is a floral display marking the event). But worries about the cost of the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;, a project closely linked with President Xi Jinping’s foreign policy, have become widespread. Malaysia, Pakistan and Sierra Leone are among a growing list of countries that have delayed or scrapped China-led projects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are three main concerns about the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;’s financial consequences. The most extreme is that the scheme involves what is pithily described as “debt-trap diplomacy”. In this view, China is deliberately overloading weak countries with loans; when they buckle, it seizes their assets and influences their politics. This idea has featured in speeches by some American officials, including the vice-president, Mike Pence, who see &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; as an attempt to undermine America’s global influence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the investments funded by Chinese cash are not in China, so China has limited ability to grab assets when governments default. If it pushes too hard it may merely stoke antipathy. Instead, it usually responds by reducing the amount of money that debtors have to repay. Countries with longer records of lending to poor countries often do the same: the Paris Club of creditors was formed in 1956 to devise ways of reducing defaulters’ debt loads. The Centre for Global Development, a think-tank in Washington, has counted more than 80 cases between 2000 and 2017 in which China provided relief to its debtors overseas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An oft-cited example of China’s supposedly predatory approach involves Hambantota, a Sri Lankan port which has flopped commercially. In 2017 Sri Lanka handed control of the port to a state-owned Chinese company on a 99-year lease. But Deborah Brautigam of Johns Hopkins University says that of more than 3,000 China-financed projects that she and others have tracked, Hambantota is the only one that is used in support of the debt-trap theory. It is the exception, not the rule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What it lacks in malevolence, the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; may make up in clumsiness. This is the second concern: that China is lending to vulnerable states without sufficient caution. Take a group of 37 poor countries monitored by the &lt;small&gt;IMF&lt;/small&gt;. Loans from traditional bilateral lenders, including America and Japan, have declined from 7% of the debtors’ &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; to 2% over the past decade. Loans from China, by contrast, have soared from virtually nothing to 4%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is welcome that China is supporting hard-up nations. But its enthusiasm generates foolhardiness. David Dollar of the Brookings Institution in Washington has found that Chinese development lending appears indifferent to political and economic risks. The Centre for Global Development has identified eight countries drowning in red ink that could be further swamped by &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; projects (see chart). A report in December released by Peking University ranked 94 &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; countries based on measures such as the quality of their financial regulation and their openness to trade. Pakistan came second to last. That is awkward for China: Pakistan may receive as much as $60bn in &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; loans, which would make it the biggest recipient of all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190427_CNC774.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is truth to claims that &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; credit can be ruinously expensive. Consider China Eximbank’s lending to Kenya for the Nairobi-Mombasa railway. Local reports say half the $3.6bn loan was priced 3.6 percentage points above a floating market interest-rate. That is high for a poor country. It is just one of many such loans by Eximbank, which said this week that its outstanding &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;-related credit was more than 1trn yuan, or nearly $150bn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;’s success will depend on whether Chinese lenders can tighten their procedures for assessing creditworthiness while making their loans more affordable. There are some promising signs. This week’s forum in Beijing is expected to stress the need for &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; debt to be sustainable. In the case of the railway in Laos, caution is already evident. The project involves $6bn of Chinese lending, which is about one-third of the &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; of Laos. So a joint venture has been created. It draws 70% of its capital from China and 30% from Laos. To fund its portion, Laos took a $465m loan from Eximbank. The loan was generous, according to local reports: it matures in 35 years at a 2.3% annual interest rate, well below the commercial price of such debt. Laos has five years before it has to begin making repayments. That is the kind of concession that it might have got from the World Bank. China may offer such generous terms more frequently. Last year it set up an agency to oversee its foreign aid, in part to turn the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; into a more co-ordinated development programme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this points to another concern that will be harder for China to deal with because it relates to the very nature of the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt;: its sheer ambition. Potential benefits look impressive. A recent study by the World Bank concluded that &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; transportation projects could lift global &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; by 3%. That is larger than the benefits that are usually shown to be generated by free-trade agreements. It could yet bear out China’s notion that Westerners (save Donald Trump) just want to lower tariffs, whereas China is trying to build the roads that let trade happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This, though, is where the risks come in. The World Bank’s rosy analysis assumes that &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; projects are completed and work efficiently. The scale of the effort is a huge challenge, and such projects are a magnet for graft. Vast sums are being spent quickly in badly run places. The railway in Laos ought to make the landlocked country more accessible. But for it to prove effective, much more will be needed: better roads to link it to existing transport, new urban centres around the stations and freer trade with other countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China cannot achieve this alone, but its often overweening approach to the &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; has alienated potential partners. America, India and Japan want little to do with it. One reason is that China is, in effect, asking others not only to sign up to its infrastructure plans but also to endorse Mr Xi’s worldview. It does not help that China reveals so little about its lending and that contracts go mainly to Chinese firms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some analysts in China have started to express unease. Economists at the Chinese Academy of Social Sciences, a think-tank, argued in a paper last year that the government must entice other countries to back &lt;small&gt;BRI&lt;/small&gt; projects in order to share the risks. Otherwise, it could be China that finds itself trapped. Conservative estimates are that China will spend $1trn within the next decade on its monumental scheme—about as much as it holds today in American government bonds. Mr Xi would be wise not to let such an outlay turn sour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;China&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Seeds of suspicion&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 17:07:05 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why is the population of wider Chicago falling?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/04/24/why-is-the-population-of-wider-chicago-falling]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_USP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-24T20:35:14Z&quot;&gt;Apr 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;RAHM EMANUEL, who is poised to retire as Chicago’s mayor, recently bragged that on his watch the population of America’s third-largest city had grown. “It is up by about 30,000 in my tenure,” he said. That is a trifling increase for a city with 2.7m residents, but is at least a welcome sign of stability after decades of decline. In the decade to 2010 Chicago lost some 20,000 residents every year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Untangling the demography of any big city is messy. This month America’s census bureau released population estimates for American metropolitan areas in 2018. They show that even if Chicago as a city has a stable population, its wider metropolitan area is suffering stagnation or decline. The region includes suburbs across 14 counties, sprawling far beyond the official city limits, containing roughly 9.5m residents. The census bureau says that for the fourth year in a row the wider Chicago-area lost population last year. New York and Los Angeles also saw slight declines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What explains this fall? Critics of Illinois’s relatively high taxes point out that the state’s overall population is also falling; they also blame government dysfunction, corruption and high cost of living. On Twitter #IllinoisExodus has become a popular hashtag for residents debating the census figures and fuming about taxes. A widespread myth in Chicago suggests the population figures are shifting because many wealthy residents abandon the metropolitan area, fleeing to lower tax—and sunnier—alternatives in the South, especially Florida.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reality is strikingly different, argues Daniel Kay Hertz of the Centre for Budget and Tax Accountability, in Chicago. He points out that the most popular destinations for wealthy residents (defined as belonging to households earning at least $100,000 a year) who leave Illinois include the New York’s metro area, Los Angeles, San Francisco, the Twin Cities in Minneapolis, as well as Houston. That list, he argues, suggests residents are probably moving to take up jobs, or for family reasons, but they are not obviously hunting for low-tax destinations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is also the case that Chicago (the city) is mostly losing poorer residents who are overwhelmingly African-American, while it gains or maintains its population of higher-skilled people, whites and Asians especially. More prosperous residents appear most likely to remain in Chicago, while less-educated and poorer ones tend to move out. As Rob Paral, a Chicago-based demographer, points out: “without the decline in African-Americans, the city population would be stable or growing”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why black Americans continue to leave in droves is only vaguely understood. The most obvious reasons include their reasonable worries about high levels of violence, poor schools, run-down housing and a lack of amenities—such as supermarkets—in the fast-depopulating south side of Chicago. Some are also taking part in the “reverse great migration”, returning to live with extended families who stayed on in the South during a big shift of African-Americans to northern cities a century ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pete Saunders, an urban planner who has long blogged on demographic trends in mid-Western cities, argues that Chicago suffers – and fails to keep its black residents - because it remains deeply segregated by race and wealth. For professional and middle class African-Americans, he says mobility within the city remains too difficult. And Chicago fails, especially, to get African-Americans into colleges to learn skills needed for high-paying and service jobs that are now widely available in the city. “Chicago’s economy really restructured over the last 25 years, but in large part the African-American population has been passed by,” he says. He calls that economic change the “trend that undergirds everything”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exodus of black Americans has not yet bottomed out and may not do so for years to come. But even counting this steady flight of from Chicago, Illinois is not exceptional for the outflow of its people. Mr Hertz says that Illinois is akin to New Jersey or Arizona, for example. What really matters, he says, is how the state no longer draws in enough newcomers to compensate for the outflow: Illinois is exceptional in failing to bring in enough new migrants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Traditionally Chicago was one of a handful of gateways for immigrants to America, and thus to the rest of Illinois. Among legal, documented migrants, says Mr Paral, Chicago was one of a few big cities that attracted skilled workers. Manufacturing plants that long produced non-durable goods were also a magnet for low-skilled, undocumented migrants, overwhelmingly from Mexico. He calls Chicago (the city) a “conveyor belt” that brought in migrants who gradually moved out to settle in suburbs and the wider metro area.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That belt no longer works as it once did. Overall numbers of legal migrants to America have not fallen in the past decade or so, but high-skilled newcomers to Chicago prefer to head to big cities on the coasts, or to booming small ones in states such as Nevada or South Carolina. More significantly, undocumented migrants have come in smaller numbers to America in the past decade, with Chicago losing out. Mr Hertz adds that among domestic, American migrants, Chicago traditionally draws from the rest of the Midwest, not the rest of the country. It may now be that aging Midwesterners are becoming less willing to move to Chicago, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile another trend is reshaping where residents of the wider Chicago area live. A different conveyor belt once carried wealthy city residents into the suburbs, but it increasingly works the other way around. Mr Paral says rich residents increasingly shun suburbs and prefer to live in the booming downtown or other central parts of the city, especially on its northern side. This process is happening just as suburbs see poorer and racially diverse residents moving in. The result has been falling house prices in the “collar counties” around Chicago, for at least a decade, even as demand for property in expensive parts of the city booms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How much does a change in population matter? Mayors know the answer to that. Mr Emanuel is about to be replaced by Lori Lightfoot. She knows that Chicago—just like the state of Illinois—faces big financial difficulties in the coming years. As mayor she must find a way for the city to fund billions of dollars of pension debt and at the same time get to grip with big gaps in public finances. Those tasks will be painfully difficult. Taking them on if the population is falling will be more arduous yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 05:10:52 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America wants to challenge rogue petrostates]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/04/24/america-wants-to-challenge-rogue-petrostates]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_FNP001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-24T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMERICA HAS been a superpower for decades. As an energy superpower, however, it is barely a teenager. As recently as 2015 it was illegal to export oil. Within ten years the shale boom has transformed it into the world’s biggest producer of crude. No longer must it tiptoe around regimes whose policies it detests but whose oil it craves. President Donald Trump touts an age of “energy dominance”. He has put its burgeoning energy prowess to the test with tough sanctions on Iran and Venezuela. But dreams of dominance are running into the realities of energy markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On April 22nd the American administration announced that no further waivers would be granted to countries importing oil from Iran. “We are going to zero,” declared Mike Pompeo, the secretary of state. Waivers to eight countries, granted in November, were due to expire on May 2nd. Even so, investors were shocked that no exceptions were allowed. According to the state department, Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates and America will help meet demand. But Brent crude, the international benchmark, quickly topped $74, the highest level in nearly six months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration is right to make to make a fuss about America’s oil boom. According to the International Energy Agency, by 2021 the country may be a net exporter of oil. This would be a stunning reversal. Not long ago, notes Amy Myers Jaffe of the Council on Foreign Relations, a think-tank, oil imports were the largest cause of America’s current-account deficit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_FNC769_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it is wrong to think it can bring about dramatic change in two petro-states without risking dramatic spikes in petrol prices. (Those concerned about climate change might welcome expensive oil; Mr Trump is not one of those people.) America’s government does not control its oil industry. Oil firms are backed by investors whose interests do not necessarily align with those of the president. Nor can it control the world’s many buyers and sellers of crude. American production accounts for about 15% of global output, a striking increase from what it was but still a small share of total supply. Complicating matters, investors have struggled to anticipate the Trump administration’s actions. Rather than stabilise oil markets, America has been as likely to do the opposite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump announced last May that America would impose sanctions on Iran and withdraw from the deal on international oversight of its nuclear capacity signed during Barack Obama’s presidency—the “worst deal ever”, as Mr Trump liked to call it. He urged the Organisation of Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC), privately and on Twitter, to boost production to help restrain oil prices. Saudi Arabia duly did so, increasing output by 600,000 barrels a day from June to November, when the sanctions were to take effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the last minute, however, Mr Trump announced that eight countries would be exempt from the waivers for six months—including China and India, the biggest importers of Iranian oil. Investors and Saudi Arabia were caught off guard. The kingdom requires oil at around $80 a barrel to meet its budgetary needs; in December Brent prices sank to $51. OPEC and its allies scrambled to cut production and shore up prices. In December they said they would decrease output by 1.2m barrels a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next sanctions came in January, after opponents of Nicolás Maduro’s ruinous regime in Venezuela declared Juan Guaidó, the head of its national assembly, the legitimate leader. America recognised Mr Guaidó and unveiled sanctions to choke off the country’s oil company, Mr Maduro’s main source of cash. “America now appreciates that energy is a source of foreign-policy strength rather than a vulnerability,” says Meghan O’Sullivan, a former adviser to George W. Bush and a professor at Harvard University. But using that strength effectively can be difficult.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sanctions on Iran and Venezuela have yet to produce the desired effect. Mr Maduro still clings to power. Iran has met none of Mr Trump’s demands. Its crude exports have fallen by about half since Mr Trump said America would withdraw from the nuclear deal last year, but they remained well above zero in March, at about 1.4m barrels a day, according to Kpler, a data firm (see chart). China, in particular, has continued to import Iranian oil. The announcement that waivers will expire seeks to change that. Countries that continue to import Iranian oil, the state department says, could be cut off from America’s banking system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This manoeuvre is risky, says Helima Croft of RBC Capital Markets, an investment bank. Iran’s foreign ministry is threatening to retaliate by closing the Strait of Hormuz, a major export channel for the region’s crude. With little left to lose, it may stop allowing international inspectors to monitor its nuclear programme. Oil markets, too, face uncertainty. Prices were already rising, because of plunging output in Venezuela and civil war looming in Libya. The state department has not said how soon America might impose sanctions on countries that continue to import Iranian oil. China may do so—an official from its foreign ministry declared that China “opposes the unilateral sanctions”. That could complicate a bilateral trade dispute that had looked close to resolution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of rigs drilling in America has risen since the start of the year, as the oil price has climbed. Yet American shale oil is mostly “light”. Refineries in America and elsewhere are thirsty for heavy crude, because Venezuela’s production of the stuff has dropped and demand for distillates made with it is strong. There is a “fundamental mismatch” between the type of crude the world increasingly wants and what America is pumping, says Bernadette Johnson of Drillinginfo, a research firm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much therefore depends on whether Saudi Arabia boosts production, as the Trump administration hopes. After last year’s flip-flops, it may be reluctant to move fast. OPEC and its partners have their next formal meeting in late June. Even if Saudi Arabia were to ramp up production quickly and dramatically, analysts debate how long that boost could be sustained. A recent bond prospectus for Saudi Aramco, the kingdom’s oil giant, disclosed that a famous oilfield is ready to sustain production of 3.8m barrels a day, about 25% less than analysts had assumed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neil Beveridge of Bernstein, a research firm, points out that OPEC’s spare capacity could drop dangerously low as Iran’s production falls and Saudi Arabia works to ramp up. That would leave the oil price vulnerable to supply shocks—if fighting in Libya escalates, for instance. America, the energy adolescent, can certainly roil oil markets. But it is unable to control them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 05:10:51 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America, a young energy superpower, wants to challenge big petrostates]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/04/24/america-a-young-energy-superpower-wants-to-challenge-big-petrostates]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_FNP001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-24T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMERICA HAS been a superpower for decades. As an energy superpower, however, it is not even an adolescent. As recently as 2015 it was illegal to export oil. Within ten years the shale boom has transformed it into the world’s biggest producer of crude. No longer must it tiptoe around regimes whose policies it detests but whose oil it craves. President Donald Trump touts an age of “energy dominance”. He has put its burgeoning energy prowess to the test with tough sanctions on Iran and Venezuela. But dreams of dominance are running into the realities of energy markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On April 22nd the American administration announced that no further waivers would be granted to countries importing oil from Iran. “We are going to zero,” declared Mike Pompeo, the secretary of state. Waivers to eight countries, granted in November, were due to expire on May 2nd. Even so, investors were shocked that no exceptions were allowed. According to the state department, Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates and America will help meet demand. But Brent crude, the international benchmark, quickly topped $74, the highest level in nearly six months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration is right to make to make a fuss about America’s oil boom. According to the International Energy Agency, by 2021 the country may be a net exporter of oil. This would be a stunning reversal. Not long ago, notes Amy Myers Jaffe of the Council on Foreign Relations, a think-tank, oil imports were the largest cause of America’s current-account deficit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_FNC769_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190427_FNC769_0.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it is wrong to think it can bring about dramatic change in two petro-states without risking dramatic spikes in petrol prices. (Those concerned about climate change might welcome expensive oil; Mr Trump is not one of those people.) America’s government does not control its oil industry. Oil firms are backed by investors whose interests do not necessarily align with those of the president. Nor can it control the world’s many buyers and sellers of crude. American production accounts for about 15% of global output, a striking increase from what it was but still a small share of total supply. Complicating matters, investors have struggled to anticipate the Trump administration’s actions. Rather than stabilise oil markets, America has been as likely to do the opposite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump announced last May that America would impose sanctions on Iran and withdraw from the deal on international oversight of its nuclear capacity signed during Barack Obama’s presidency—the “worst deal ever”, as Mr Trump liked to call it. He urged the Organisation of Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC), privately and on Twitter, to boost production to help restrain oil prices. Saudi Arabia duly did so, increasing output by 600,000 barrels a day from June to November, when the sanctions were to take effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the last minute, however, Mr Trump announced that eight countries would be exempt from the waivers for six months—including China and India, the biggest importers of Iranian oil. Investors and Saudi Arabia were caught off guard. The kingdom requires oil at around $80 a barrel to meet its budgetary needs; in December Brent prices sank to $51. OPEC and its allies scrambled to cut production and shore up prices. In December they said they would decrease output by 1.2m barrels a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next sanctions came in January, after opponents of Nicolás Maduro’s ruinous regime in Venezuela declared Juan Guaidó, the head of its national assembly, the legitimate leader. America recognised Mr Guaidó and unveiled sanctions to choke off the country’s oil company, Mr Maduro’s main source of cash. “America now appreciates that energy is a source of foreign-policy strength rather than a vulnerability,” says Meghan O’Sullivan, a former adviser to George W. Bush and a professor at Harvard University. But using that strength effectively can be difficult.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sanctions on Iran and Venezuela have yet to produce the desired effect. Mr Maduro still clings to power. Iran has met none of Mr Trump’s demands. Its crude exports have fallen by about half since Mr Trump said America would withdraw from the nuclear deal last year, but they remained well above zero in March, at about 1.4m barrels a day, according to Kpler, a data firm (see chart). China, in particular, has continued to import Iranian oil. The announcement that waivers will expire seeks to change that. Countries that continue to import Iranian oil, the state department says, could be cut off from America’s banking system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This manoeuvre is risky, says Helima Croft of RBC Capital Markets, an investment bank. Iran’s foreign ministry is threatening to retaliate by closing the Strait of Hormuz, a major export channel for the region’s crude. With little left to lose, it may stop allowing international inspectors to monitor its nuclear programme. Oil markets, too, face uncertainty. Prices were already rising, because of plunging output in Venezuela and civil war looming in Libya. The state department has not said how soon America might impose sanctions on countries that continue to import Iranian oil. China may do so—an official from its foreign ministry declared that China “opposes the unilateral sanctions”. That could complicate a bilateral trade dispute that had looked close to resolution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of rigs drilling in America has risen since the start of the year, as the oil price has climbed. Yet American shale oil is mostly “light”. Refineries in America and elsewhere are thirsty for heavy crude, because Venezuela’s production of the stuff has dropped and demand for distillates made with it is strong. There is a “fundamental mismatch” between the type of crude the world increasingly wants and what America is pumping, says Bernadette Johnson of Drillinginfo, a research firm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much therefore depends on whether Saudi Arabia boosts production, as the Trump administration hopes. After last year’s flip-flops, it may be reluctant to move fast. OPEC and its partners have their next formal meeting in late June. Even if Saudi Arabia were to ramp up production quickly and dramatically, analysts debate how long that boost could be sustained. A recent bond prospectus for Saudi Aramco, the kingdom’s oil giant, disclosed that a famous oilfield is ready to sustain production of 3.8m barrels a day, about 25% less than analysts had assumed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neil Beveridge of Bernstein, a research firm, points out that OPEC’s spare capacity could drop dangerously low as Iran’s production falls and Saudi Arabia works to ramp up. That would leave the oil price vulnerable to supply shocks—if fighting in Libya escalates, for instance. America, the energy adolescent, can certainly roil oil markets. But it is unable to control them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 04:09:09 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A TV comedian-turned-politician wins a stunning victory in Ukraine]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/24/a-tv-comedian-turned-politician-wins-a-stunning-victory-in-ukraine]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_EUP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-24T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JOKES ABOUT Ukraine’s newly elected president, Volodymyr Zelensky, come easily. He is, after all, a comedian. At times his campaign seemed too frivolous to be consequential. While Petro Poroshenko, the incumbent president, staged political rallies, Mr Zelensky could be found filming his popular TV show, “Servant of the People”, in which he plays a schoolteacher who accidentally becomes president. His public announcement that he was fighting the election was enough of an afterthought that he forgot to tell his wife about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet Mr Zelensky’s victory in the second-round run-off election on April 21st, with 73% of the vote, is a serious achievement. In four months, he got the biggest majority since Ukraine’s independence in 1991, born out of votersʼ frustration with Mr Poroshenkoʼs chequered leadership and their hopes for a better future. While Mr Poroshenko ran a divisive and nationalistic campaign, Mr Zelensky, a native Russian-speaker of Jewish heritage hailing from Ukraine’s south-east, galvanised support from across the country. Ukrainian politicians have long exploited ethnic and linguistic divides, splitting the country into an “orange” west and a “blue” east. Mr Zelensky, whose name means “green”, carried all but one of 25 regions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although war with Russia is still simmering in the country’s east, the election was free, fair and peaceful. Civil society and independent media held politicians to account. Thanks to Mr Poroshenko’s prompt concession, Ukraine’s voters have removed a sitting president through the ballot box—a rarity in the region. Mr Zelensky celebrated the example it could set: “To all the countries of the former Soviet Union: look at us, everything is possible.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Zelensky’s improbable path to the presidency began in Krivoi Rog, a midsized industrial city. The son of a university professor and an engineer, he dreamed of studying international relations in Moscow or Kiev, but settled for law at the local university, where he became involved in a popular comedy contest. He spun his success on the show into a production company, became a household name and made a lot of money from producing and appearing in TV programmes and films.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the election, being a celebrity outsider was an asset. Oligarchs control Ukraine’s main television channels, but Mr Zelensky’s fame helped bypass this barrier to entry. As a new face on the political stage, he appealed to voters who saw the promise of change after the 2014 revolution hijacked by the old elites, including Mr Poroshenko. At 41, he is too young to have participated in the theft by Ukraine’s political class of Soviet-era economic assets. His informality contrasts with the distance which most leaders in the former Soviet Union maintain between themselves and the voters. His first post-election message was a video posted on Instagram that begins with the grinning president-elect saying, “Heeeeyy everybody!” It has been watched 6m times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The presentation is undoubtedly appealing; it is the substance that will be Mr Zelensky’s main challenge. He has promised to maintain a pro-Western stance, to fight corruption and to end the war, but his course remains uncertain. Groups jockeying for influence include old friends from the entertainment world, shrewd advisers linked to powerful outside backers, and Western-oriented reformers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which has the upper hand will become clear only once he begins making appointments and proposing laws. Ukraine’s constitution gives the president responsibility for foreign and security policy, including picking the ministers of foreign affairs and defence, the heads of the intelligence service and the military general staff, and the prosecutor-general. Among the policies Mr Zelensky’s team is discussing are plans to strip immunity from MPs and judges, to introduce more direct democracy, to create a body to investigate financial crimes and to offer an amnesty for undeclared assets. Balazs Jarabik of the Carnegie Endowment for International Peace predicts that he will “try to build a state less preoccupied by ideology and more focused on offering people efficient services”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The burden of success&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Ukrainians tend to sour on their leaders quickly. Their most urgent demand, say the polls, is that Mr Zelensky lower utility prices—which lies outside the president’s prerogative and would violate the terms of the IMF loan programme on which Ukraine’s economy depends. Public disappointment with the president is the subject of the second season of Mr Zelenskyʼs show, entitled “From Love to Impeachment”. As one aide says: “We know what can happen: we wrote all of this already.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To change the story, Mr Zelensky must overcome several adversaries. First is the Rada (parliament), which will remain hostile at least until elections this autumn. Mr Zelensky could try to force early elections, but since he has not yet built a party, he may prefer to wait. In the meantime, others are massing their forces against him. The current prime minister, Volodymyr Groysman, announced plans to form his own party. Mr Poroshenko has promised to continue the fight. Pro-Russian parties, which gathered 16% in the first round of presidential elections, could unite and challenge Mr Zelensky in the east.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second is Russia, with which Ukraine remains in a stand-off. Prospects for resolving it are slim. Vladimir Putin can use his separatist proxies in the Donbass region to test the new commander-in-chief’s mettle, and also has economic levers: even after five years of war, Russia remains Ukraine’s single largest trading partner. On April 24th, Mr Putin announced that Russia would allow Ukrainians living in the breakaway regions to receive Russian passports, a move towards greater integration of Ukraine’s territory and a direct challenge to the new president.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Third, and most important, are Ukraine’s oligarchs. There is much speculation about Mr Zelensky’s links to Ihor Kolomoisky, whose TV channel airs his shows. While both men deny ties beyond business, investigative journalists discovered that in recent years Mr Zelensky flew 13 times to Geneva and Tel Aviv, where Mr Kolomoisky has been living in exile since being accused of defrauding his bank, PrivatBank, of some $5bn. The two men also share cars, security guards and a lawyer. Days before the election, when Mr Zelensky seemed likely to win, a court in Kiev did Mr Kolomoisky a big favour by declaring the nationalisation of PrivatBank illegal; after Mr Zelensky’s victory, Mr Kolomoisky announced plans to return to Ukraine. Those moves may not be Mr Zelensky’s doing, but handling them will be his problem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That points to the biggest risk of the Zelensky presidency: not that he turns out to be an oligarchic puppet or a Kremlin agent, but that he will be too weak against his powerful adversaries to defend the progress that Ukraine has made. The oligarchs will probably aim to weaken the presidency and concentrate power in the more easily-controlled parliament. Mr Putin will seek to keep Ukraine from becoming a functioning, Western-style democracy. Mr Zelensky will have to learn fast, with the cameras rolling and no second takes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 04:09:08 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The opioid epidemic continues to ravage America]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/24/the-opioid-epidemic-continues-to-ravage-america]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_WOC673.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-24T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;DURING THE past two decades opioids have become one of America’s worst public-health problems. The magnitude of abuse—spanning prescription painkillers, heroin and synthetics such as fentanyl—is staggering. In 2016 11m Americans mis-used prescription opioids, and 2.1m adults reported that they were addicted. In the year to September 2018 opioid overdoses killed 48,000 people. That took the total death toll since 2000 to 400,000, greater than the number of American combat deaths in the second world war, the Korean war and the Vietnam war combined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On April 24th Donald Trump will make a speech to a group of health professionals and policymakers detailing his administration’s efforts to fight the “scourge” of opioid abuse. To his credit, Mr Trump did much to draw attention to the opioid epidemic when he was a presidential candidate. But in October 2017 the president meekly declared the epidemic a “national public-health emergency”, rather than invoking a formal “national emergency” as he had promised on the campaign trail (and as he did in an effort to get funding for a wall on America’s southern border). That delayed the federal government’s response. The White House reports that Mr Trump’s administration has so far spent or allocated just $1bn of federal money to tackle the crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- data-infographic-js=&quot;/2019/opioids-us/js/bundle.js&quot; data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/opioids-us/css/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/opioids-us/css/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;State governments that emphasise a public-health approach to the problem have cobbled together stronger reactions. They have organised needle exchanges and supervised consumption spaces, and made overdose-reversing drugs widely available. In West Virginia, where one out of every 200 residents has died from a drug overdose since 2000, the overdose rate declined by 20% in the year to September 2018, according to preliminary data released by the Centres for Disease Control. Although West Virginia’s overdose rate is still twice the national average, copying its policies could be a good blueprint for other states and the federal government.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 04:09:07 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Egypt’s economy thrills investors, but locals are struggling]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/04/24/egypts-economy-thrills-investors-but-locals-are-struggling]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_MAP001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-24T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE INVESTORS gathered at a posh Cairo restaurant were eager to pour money into an economy that, just three years ago, lacked the hard currency to import cooking oil. A revolution in 2011 (and a coup two years later) tipped Egypt into economic crisis. Investors and tourists fled. Growth was anaemic. Unemployment peaked at 13.2%. President Abdel-Fattah al-Sisi had to seek a $12bn loan from the IMF in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since then, though, his government has followed what one executive admiringly calls “almost a caricature” of an IMF programme. The state has raised electricity and fuel prices. This summer the (previously massively subsidised) official price of many types of petrol will be indexed to market rates. Quite a few people have been trimmed from subsidy rolls. A budget deficit that hit 12.5% of GDP in 2015-16 has fallen. Next year it is expected to be a manageable 7.5%. The current-account deficit, which bottomed out at $19.8bn three years ago, was $6bn last year (see chart). Investors call Egypt the world’s hottest emerging market. Bond sales are oversubscribed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_MAC771.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190427_MAC771.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190427_MAC771.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190427_MAC771.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190427_MAC771.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190427_MAC771.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190427_MAC771.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190427_MAC771.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190427_MAC771.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190427_MAC771.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the positive indicators, few Egyptians feel progress. The past few years have brought higher prices and stagnant wages. Mr Sisi has shown little sympathy for their distress. He dismissed complaints over a surge in the price of vegetables last year—then criticised Egyptians for being overweight. A new sign of discontent came earlier this month, when 89% of voters approved constitutional changes that let Mr Sisi stay in power until 2030, instead of 2022 under the previous charter. The result was a foregone conclusion, since his autocratic regime did not permit a “no” campaign. But turnout was just 44%. Sympathetic businessmen had to lure voters to the polls with boxes of food.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For all the hot money flooding in, bricks-and-mortar investment is scarce. “I’m comfortable buying one-year paper,” says a trader from a big American firm. “Buying a factory would be a different story.” Inflows of foreign direct investment (FDI) were $6.6bn in the first half of the current fiscal year, unchanged from the previous year and 11% lower than 2016-17. Net FDI is down 35% over that two-year period. Much of it goes to hydrocarbons. Recent natural-gas discoveries have turned Egypt into a net exporter. Such investment boosts revenue, but creates few jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials insist that FDI is coming—that it is always a lagging indicator. Trade tensions and uncertain growth forecasts have caused investment to fall around the world. Some firms had profits stuck in Egypt during the dollar shortages and are leery about coming back. “It takes time to rebuild that confidence,” says Razan Nasser of HSBC, a bank. Though Egypt will not seek an extension when the IMF scheme ends in November, most analysts think it will stick with its reforms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But sluggish investment also reflects the weakness of Egypt’s domestic market. Its size—almost 100m people, with 2.5m added annually—means it will always have robust demand for basic consumer goods. Last year both Coca-Cola and Pepsi announced $500m in investments. Mars, a confectionery giant, is opening two new production lines. Few Egyptians can afford products that would create better-paying jobs, however. “It’s a classic developing market where 20% of the population has 80% of the purchasing power,” says the head of a local business federation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Take the car industry, which officials hope will be an engine of growth. Sales slumped after a devaluation in 2016, which halved the value of the pound. Even in a good year, though, only about 100,000 Egyptians can afford new cars. (Wealthy Saudi Arabia has one-quarter of Egypt’s population and sells about half a million.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead of selling cars at home, Egypt wants to become an exporter to other parts of Africa and the Middle East. The government plans to offer incentives for using domestic suppliers: firms that purchase lots of locally-made components could have 80% shaved off their customs bills. Nissan has already agreed to produce 100,000 cars in Egypt each year with El Nasr Automotive, a moribund state-run firm. But Egypt will have to compete with Morocco, which has invested heavily in infrastructure and training. Textile firms, another possible source of jobs, will struggle to undercut big players like Bangladesh and Vietnam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The improvement in Egypt’s current account comes entirely from travel and transfers. Tourism revenues more than doubled to $9.8bn (4% of GDP) last year, while remittances grew by a fifth to $26.4bn. Both are important. Tourism employs one in ten workers. Hundreds of thousands of families rely on transfers. But the trade deficit in goods is getting wider. It hit $9.8bn in the first quarter of 2018-19, up $1bn from the previous year. Though the devaluation made Egyptian goods cheaper to export, it also made them more expensive to produce, because manufacturers depend on imports. Raw and intermediate goods make up 41% of Egypt’s import basket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After years of weak investment, there is little idle capacity at Egyptian factories. High interest rates mean local businesses cannot afford to borrow for expansion. In February the central bank cut the overnight lending rate by 100 basis points, to 16.75%. In March, however, the bank defied expectations and kept rates steady. The Ramadan holiday and a looming subsidy cut will bring higher inflation this summer, so further cuts are unlikely until autumn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is one final obstacle to growth: the institution where Mr Sisi spent most of his life. It is hard to quantify how much of Egypt’s economy is controlled by the army. Its budget is secret, its profits untaxed. But everyone agrees it is growing. The minister of military production, Muhammad al-Assar, said his revenues hit 11.6bn pounds last year, a 130% increase. It has a $2bn deal with a Chinese firm to manufacture solar panels and an agreement with a French pharmaceutical giant to make vaccines. When firms struggled to get hold of dollars, the army offered them a deal—all the foreign currency you need, in exchange for a share of your company. Several executives tell a version of the same joke: “There are two kinds of successful businesses in Egypt, those run by the military, and those that will soon be run by the military.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Officials like to compare Egypt’s recent progress to the dark days after 2011. Take a slightly longer view, though, and it looks like a reversion to the norm. Before the revolution Egypt posted healthy growth rates and manageable deficits. It was also a poor country with a weak industrial base, low wages—and a president out of touch with the needs of his people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 03:11:46 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America, a young energy superpower, is seeking to reshape oil markets]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/04/24/america-a-young-energy-superpower-is-seeking-to-reshape-oil-markets]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_FNP001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-24T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMERICA HAS been a superpower for decades. As an energy superpower, however, it is not even an adolescent. As recently as 2015 it was illegal to export oil. Within ten years the shale boom has transformed it into the world’s biggest producer of crude. No longer must it tiptoe around regimes whose policies it detests but whose oil it craves. President Donald Trump touts an age of “energy dominance”. He has put its burgeoning energy prowess to the test with tough sanctions on Iran and Venezuela. But dreams of dominance are running into the realities of energy markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On April 22nd the American administration announced that no further waivers would be granted to countries importing oil from Iran. “We are going to zero,” declared Mike Pompeo, the secretary of state. Waivers to eight countries, granted in November, were due to expire on May 2nd. Even so, investors were shocked that no exceptions were allowed. According to the state department, Saudi Arabia, the United Arab Emirates and America will help meet demand. But Brent crude, the international benchmark, quickly topped $74, the highest level in nearly six months.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Trump administration is right to make to make a fuss about America’s oil boom. According to the International Energy Agency, by 2021 the country may be a net exporter of oil. This would be a stunning reversal. Not long ago, notes Amy Myers Jaffe of the Council on Foreign Relations, a think-tank, oil imports were the largest cause of America’s current-account deficit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it is wrong to think it can bring about dramatic change in two petrostates without risking dramatic spikes in petrol prices. (Those concerned about climate change might welcome expensive oil; Mr Trump is not one of those people.) America’s government does not control its oil industry. Oil firms are backed by investors whose interests do not necessarily align with those of the president. Nor can it control the world’s many buyers and sellers of crude. American production accounts for about 15% of global output, a striking increase from what it was but still a small share of total supply. Complicating matters, investors have struggled to anticipate the Trump administration’s actions. Rather than stabilise oil markets, America has been as likely to do the opposite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump announced last May that America would impose sanctions on Iran and withdraw from the deal on international oversight of its nuclear capacity signed during Barack Obama’s presidency—the “worst deal ever”, as Mr Trump liked to call it. He urged the Organisation of Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC), privately and on Twitter, to boost production to help restrain oil prices. Saudi Arabia duly did so, increasing output by 600,000 barrels a day from June to November, when the sanctions were to take effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the last minute, however, Mr Trump announced that eight countries would be exempt from the waivers for six months—including China and India, the biggest importers of Iranian oil. Investors and Saudi Arabia were caught off guard. The kingdom requires oil at around $80 a barrel to meet its budgetary needs; in December Brent prices sank to $51. OPEC and its allies scrambled to cut production and shore up prices. In December they said they would decrease output by 1.2m barrels a day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next sanctions came in January, after opponents of Nicolás Maduro’s ruinous regime in Venezuela declared Juan Guaidó, the head of its national assembly, the legitimate leader. America recognised Mr Guaidó and unveiled sanctions to choke off the country’s oil company, Mr Maduro’s main source of cash. “America now appreciates that energy is a source of foreign-policy strength rather than a vulnerability,” says Meghan O’Sullivan, a former adviser to George W. Bush and a professor at Harvard University. But using that strength effectively can be difficult.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sanctions on Iran and Venezuela have yet to produce the desired effect. Mr Maduro still clings to power. Iran has met none of Mr Trump’s demands. Its crude exports have fallen by about half since Mr Trump said America would withdraw from the nuclear deal last year, but they remained well above zero in March, at about 1.4m barrels a day, according to Kpler, a data firm. China, in particular, has continued to import Iranian oil. The announcement that waivers will expire seeks to change that. Countries that continue to import Iranian oil, the state department says, could be cut off from America’s banking system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This manoeuvre is risky, says Helima Croft of RBC Capital Markets, an investment bank. Iran’s foreign ministry is threatening to retaliate by closing the Strait of Hormuz, a major export channel for the region’s crude. With little left to lose, it may stop allowing international inspectors to monitor its nuclear programme. Oil markets, too, face uncertainty. Prices were already rising, because of plunging output in Venezuela and civil war looming in Libya. The state department has not said how soon America might impose sanctions on countries that continue to import Iranian oil. China may do so—an official from its foreign ministry declared that China “opposes the unilateral sanctions”. That could complicate a bilateral trade dispute that had looked close to resolution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The number of rigs drilling in America has risen since the start of the year, as the oil price has climbed. Yet American shale oil is mostly “light”. Refineries in America and elsewhere are thirsty for heavy crude, because Venezuela’s production of the stuff has dropped and demand for distillates made with it is strong. There is a “fundamental mismatch” between the type of crude the world increasingly wants and what America is pumping, says Bernadette Johnson of Drillinginfo, a research firm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much therefore depends on whether Saudi Arabia boosts production, as the Trump administration hopes. After last year’s flip-flops, it may be reluctant to move fast. OPEC and its partners have their next formal meeting in late June. Even if Saudi Arabia were to ramp up production quickly and dramatically, analysts debate how long that boost could be sustained. A recent bond prospectus for Saudi Aramco, the kingdom’s oil giant, disclosed that a famous oilfield is ready to sustain production of 3.8m barrels a day, about 25% less than analysts had assumed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neil Beveridge of Bernstein, a research firm, points out that OPEC’s spare capacity could drop dangerously low as Iran’s production falls and Saudi Arabia works to ramp up. That would leave the oil price vulnerable to supply shocks—if fighting in Libya escalates, for instance. America, the energy adolescent, can certainly roil oil markets. But it is unable to control them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2019 02:10:00 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>