<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[The push to decriminalise sex work in New York]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/19/the-push-to-decriminalise-sex-work-in-new-york]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_USP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-19T20:17:27Z&quot;&gt;Jun 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;YANG SONG, a prostitute, worked in a massage parlour in Queens, New York. A Chinese immigrant, she was worried that her record of multiple arrests would block her path to citizenship and was reportedly saving up to get out of the business. One evening in late 2017, during a police raid from which she was apparently trying to escape, Ms Song fell four storeys from a balcony. She died the next morning. The Queens district attorney found no evidence of wrongdoing by the police.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In New York, as in most of America, selling sex is illegal and stories abound of the costs of criminalisation. Sex workers circle in and out of the criminal justice system for years. Their criminal records often prevent them from accessing housing and other kinds of work. Paying bail bonds puts many already impoverished sex workers into debt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On June 10th, New York introduced the first state-wide package of bills to decriminalise sex work. It would remove criminal penalties related to the buying and selling of sex and regulate workers’ place of business to make them safer. It would also allow sex workers to apply for criminal records connected to sex work to be expunged. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bill is unlikely to pass any time soon. It has many opponents, among them Gloria Steinem and the Catholic church. Critics worry that decriminisation will encourage trafficking and offences against minors, though laws against those offences would remain untouched. But Richard Gottfried, chair of New York state assembly’s health committee says its introduction is nonetheless a historic step and reflects a growing movement for decriminalisation. “Trying to stop sex work between consenting adults should not be the business of the criminal justice system”, he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the biggest benefits of illegalisation is that it allows sex workers to more easily report crimes of which they are the victims. Activists in New York say that prostitutes tend to be hesitant about telling the police if they are attacked or raped for fear they themselves will be arrested. Meredith Dank, a research professor at John Jay College of Criminal Justice, says New York’s bill “gives them a voice. They can speak out”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The push to decriminalise sex work, which is backed by a growing number of politicians stems from a recognition that sex workers are often especially vulnerable. According to one study of New York workers, around 40% reported being homeless or living in a temporary accommodation. Jessica Raven, a former sex worker who is now campaigning for decriminalisation, says sex work saved her from extreme poverty when, as a teen, she ran away from a foster home. “I didn’t see sex as the problem; I saw the lack of safe housing as the problem”, she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous attempts to reform the way sex workers are prosecuted in New York have largely failed. In 2013 the state’s chief judge established a number of “diversion courts” to help sex workers avoid jail. The courts referred sex workers to mental health services and offered help with housing. But a study by academics at Yale suggests they have failed. The courts, it said, embedded “social services within a coercive penal context that frames defendants as ‘victims’ but treats them like ‘criminals’”. Police efforts to focus on customers, meanwhile, have often resulted in sex workers being arrested too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New York’s move toward decriminalisation is part of a wider examination of prostitution statutes in America. Many laws have been on the books since the 19th century, as the use of such terms as “lewd persons” suggests. Earlier this month the city council in Washington, DC introduced a bill that would decriminalise sex work. Lawmakers in Maine and Massachusetts are considering decriminalisation bills. Rhode Island held hearings in April on the subject. The state has some history here. In 1980 when the state legislature amended its prostitution laws it inadvertently got rid of the law outlawing indoor prostitution. In 2003 a judge interpreted this to mean that indoor sex work was legal. It took until 2009 for lawmakers to close this accidental loophole. A study later found that although the sex business increased during those years, rapes and sexually transmitted diseases declined.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other evidence of the benefits of decriminalisation comes from Nevada, the only state in which prostitution is legal, in some counties. In her book, “An Economist Walks into a Brothel”, Allison Schrager (who has written for &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;) found that many of the workers she interviewed preferred working in legal brothels. This was despite the fact that the costs of working in regulated establishments, with guards and panic buttons and the requirement that workers pay taxes, meant their take-home pay was much reduced. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 06:40:01 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Patrick Shanahan stands aside from the DoD]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/06/19/patrick-shanahan-stands-aside-from-the-dod]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_usp002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-19T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERE ARE three reasons people are ejected from the top echelons of President Donald Trump’s administration. Either past personal failings come to light, or petty self-dealing scandals emerge while in office, or they suffer a sudden decline in the appraisal of a mercurial boss who likes a good firing now and again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ronny Jackson, the president’s personal doctor, who was appointed to run the Department of Veteran Affairs, bowed out after allegations emerged of drinking on the job and carelessly dispensing opioids. Scott Pruitt, the former administrator of the Environmental Protection Agency, and Tom Price, the former health secretary, got the boot after their lavish spending habits—overstuffed security details, private-plane travel—caused considerable embarrassment. Rex Tillerson, the former secretary of state, and Kirstjen Nielsen, the former homeland security secretary, irked the boss. And on June 18th the nomination of Patrick Shanahan, the acting defence secretary since General Jim Mattis (himself done for by number three) to succeed to the permanent post imploded after details of Mr Shanahan’s personal life were published by American newspapers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike the failed nominations of Andrew Puzder as labour secretary and Herman Cain as a member of the Federal Reserve’s board, or the ignominious sacking of Rob Porter, the White House staff secretary, Mr Shanahan personal accusations of hitting or groping are not at the centre of the controversy. Instead there were two episodes. In the first, Mr Shanahan’s wife at the time was arrested in 2010 on domestic-violence charges after she punched him in the face. In the second, which occurred in 2011, Mr Shanahan’s 17-year-old son beat his mother with a baseball bat, leaving her with a fractured skull and needing surgery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shanahan, who was in Seattle at the time working for Boeing, flew to Florida where the assault occurred and tried to provide a legal defence for his son and spare him jail time. In the immediate aftermath of the assault he wrote a memo claiming that his son had “acted in self-defence”. He told the &lt;em&gt;Washington Post&lt;/em&gt; that the characterisation was made before he had all the facts, and that he was wrong to write it. When it became clear that the news would break, Mr Shanahan travelled to the Oval Office to withdraw his nomination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shanahan’s predicament appears agonising. His difficulties do not so easily elicit moral outrage, as some of Mr Trump’s other nominations did. Yet they do illuminate the problem of a patchy vetting process and an impetuous chief executive who sometimes picks people simply because they look the part. Of the 713 top posts in the government which require the affirmation of the Senate, only 455 are currently filled by confirmed appointees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Department of Defence is perhaps America’s most important ministry, particularly now tensions with Iran are high. Already 1,000 more troops have been dispatched to the Middle East. The temporary replacement to the previous temporary replacement at the DoD is Mark Esper, a West Point classmate of Mike Pompeo, the hawkish secretary of state. Mr Esper is a supporter of dispatching troops to the southern border, which allows Mr Trump to portray illegal immigration as an invasion. If the polls are tight next autumn, expect to see Mr Esper deploy more soldiers to guard the Rio Grande. If he lasts that long. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 06:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Boris bubble that threatens Britain’s Conservatives]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/19/the-boris-bubble-that-threatens-britains-conservatives]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_brp001_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-19T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BORIS JOHNSON has been seducing people again. For months he has methodically worked his way down a list of fellow Conservative MPs, sweet-talking them to back his campaign to be leader. Phone calls with potential conquests have been set up. Drinks parties are arranged for others who want to experience Mr Johnson’s charms in person. If that is not enough, a dinner might persuade a reluctant MP. Former sceptics have been swept off their feet. One recent convert explained his shift: “Desperate times, desperate measures.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The contest to become the next leader of the Conservative Party—and thus prime minister—risks becoming a coronation. Tory MPs are expected to put Mr Johnson on a shortlist along with one other candidate, for a vote by the party’s 160,000 members. These are an unpredictable bunch, but surveys suggest that they strongly prefer Mr Johnson to any likely challenger. Short of a spectacular collapse, he will be named the next prime minister on July 22nd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MPs have flocked to Mr Johnson for three reasons. One group believe he has the charisma and campaigning clout to help them keep their seats in the next election. Nigel Farage’s Brexit Party leads the polls after hoovering up millions of Tory voters. Mr Johnson is seen as the candidate most capable of winning them back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A second group see Mr Johnson as a means for their own rehabilitation. Many of the people running his operation have seen their political careers blown off course in recent years. James Wharton, Mr Johnson’s “No” man, in charge of batting away distractions, lost his seat in the snap election of 2017. Gavin Williamson, the campaign’s de facto chief whip, was sacked as defence secretary last month for leaking details of a confidential security briefing (he denies this). Totting up the numbers is Grant Shapps, a former party chairman who found himself on the backbenches in 2015 after a bullying scandal on his watch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A third group of supportive MPs are there only because they think Mr Johnson will win the contest. “If he is going to win then you have to be inside the tent,” says one aide to a converted MP. If moderate MPs do not rein in Mr Johnson, he will be guided solely by the right of the party, goes their thinking. Best to get on board sooner rather than later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This alliance of true believers and cynics makes for a shaky foundation. It is made wobblier still by the fact that Mr Johnson’s team seems to have promised wholly contradictory things to MPs to win their support. A proposed high-speed railway between London and Birmingham will be built or cancelled; today’s cabinet ministers will be retained or sacked en masse: it all depends on whom Mr Johnson’s camp is speaking to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The biggest contradiction concerns Brexit. Mr Johnson has brought on board the hardest of hard Brexiteers, including Steve Baker, the ringleader of the Tory holdouts who want Theresa May’s deal torn up. His popularity with party members is in large part owing to his promise to take Britain out of the European Union on October 31st, with or without a deal. (More than half of members would proceed with Brexit even if it meant “significant damage” to the economy, losing Scotland or Northern Ireland, or even “destroying” the Tory party, according to a YouGov poll this week.) Yet Mr Johnson has also attracted Remainer MPs. Last month Matt Hancock launched his own leadership campaign with an attack on Mr Johnson for dismissing businesses’ concerns about Brexit, while decrying no-deal as not credible. This week he joined the Johnson campaign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doubts about Mr Johnson’s sincerity have in the past been allayed by his reputation as a Heineken politician: one who, to adapt the beer’s slogan, gets to parts of the electorate that others can’t reach. During the leadership campaign he has repeatedly brought up his two terms as mayor of London, a left-leaning city that backed Remain, as proof that he can win votes from across the spectrum. But Mr Johnson’s last victory in London was seven years ago, against a tired opponent. Turnout was 38%. His support was particularly strong in Leave-voting suburbs. The slogan is old—Heineken stopped using it in 2003—and so is the analysis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now Mr Johnson’s appeal is more akin to Marmite, a love-it-or-hate-it breakfast spread. His leading role in the Brexit campaign has made him a polarising figure. Leave voters may like him, but Remainers detest him. When asked in May whether Mr Johnson would be a good prime minister, 28% of voters said yes—higher than all his rivals. But 54% thought he would be a bad one—again, higher than the rest. Young voters have a problem with Mr Johnson, as do women, points out Ben Page, head of Ipsos MORI, a pollster: “He’s basically not refreshing the parts other Tories do not reach any more.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If this is true it represents a big problem for the Conservatives, because without his purported election-winning powers Mr Johnson has little going for him. As mayor he did a reasonable job in a limited role that was mainly about drumming up enthusiasm for the capital. But as foreign secretary he blundered. A careless remark about a British-Iranian imprisoned in Iran was seized on by Tehran and used against her in court. When London hosted a Balkans summit, Mr Johnson bunked off to be photographed drafting his resignation letter over Mrs May’s Brexit deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the team around him has been hyperactive, Mr Johnson himself has sat out most of the chances to debate or be interviewed. His is “the success of someone who avoids car crashes by sitting in a parked car”, according to Stewart Wood, a Labour peer. All of this means there is a danger that Boris-mania could end as quickly as it began. “The bubble is going to burst at some point,” says a member of one rival camp. “We do not know if it will burst tomorrow or before the contest is finished, or if it bursts in Number 10.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 04:40:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[To restore calm in Hong Kong, try democracy]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/19/to-restore-calm-in-hong-kong-try-democracy]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_ldp001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-19T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT WAS PROBABLY the largest political protest ever staged in Hong Kong. It may have been the biggest in China’s history. Organisers reckon that about 1.9m people joined the demonstration on June 16th. Even during the unrest in Tiananmen Square three decades ago, no single protest approached that scale. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The estimate may not be reliable. But there is no disputing the impact of this display of discontent, and others leading up to it. It came only a week after another demonstration of jaw-dropping size and four days after one that escalated into Hong Kong’s most violent disorder since the 1960s. The territory’s government and its overlords in Beijing could not have received a clearer message that Hong Kongers distrust their own leaders, as well as the central government’s. Even if Hong Kong’s chief executive, Carrie Lam, were to step down, trust would still not be restored. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The unrest was triggered by a proposed law that would allow the extradition of criminal suspects from Hong Kong (where the rule of law still more or less prevails) to the Chinese mainland (where those who displease the ruling party have little chance of a fair trial). The law would also let Hong Kong’s courts seize assets connected with crimes on the mainland. Less than a day before the latest record-breaking demonstration, Mrs Lam announced that the bill would be shelved indefinitely. However, that did not ease concerns. At a news conference on June 18th she apologised for her handling of the bill, but gave no indication that she would resign, as the protesters are demanding. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This crisis has vividly shown how disillusioned Hong Kongers have become. It was different in 2003, when hundreds of thousands of people took to the streets in protest against a proposed anti-sedition law. Then the Communist Party had reason to hope that it could defuse the problem by allowing Hong Kong to shelve the bill, and encouraging the unpopular chief executive, Tung Chee-hwa, to resign (he did so in 2005). At the time, many people in Hong Kong still thought that the party would eventually fulfil its pledge to give them more democracy. In the meantime they could grudgingly put up with the appointment system, which ensured that Mr Tung’s successor was loyal to the government in Beijing. For his first few months in office the new man, Donald Tsang, enjoyed strong public support. Some pro-democracy politicians even felt hopeful. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Their optimism faded as the party’s intentions became clearer. None remains now. During the “Umbrella Movement” of 2014, when protesters staged weeks of sit-ins to press for free and fair elections to the post of chief executive, China’s leaders dug in their heels. They made it plain that the “universal suffrage” Hong Kong had been promised would mean only the chance to vote for someone the party likes. That is why Hong Kongers are without illusion today. They see Mrs Lam, who took over in 2017, as the party’s stooge—as they will see her successor, too. Without democracy, or a credible promise of it, no leaders in the territory will be seen as legitimate, severely limiting their ability to govern. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;China’s leader, Xi Jinping, therefore has a stark choice. He can keep Hong Kong’s political system as it is and carry on trying to stifle the freedoms that Hong Kongers otherwise enjoy. The result would be more protests and probably more violence. Businesspeople would become more jittery, and Hong Kong’s reputation as a safe base from which to trade with the mainland would be at risk. Or Mr Xi can offer Hong Kong hope again, by setting out a timetable for real democratic reform. “We have to have the confidence that Hong Kong people can manage Hong Kong well,” goes a mantra of China’s leaders. It is time to let its people try. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 03:40:43 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cleaning up nuclear waste is an obvious task for robots]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/06/19/cleaning-up-nuclear-waste-is-an-obvious-task-for-robots]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_std001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-19T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SOME PEOPLE worry about robots taking work away from human beings, but there are a few jobs that even these sceptics admit most folk would not want. One is cleaning up radioactive waste, particularly when it is inside a nuclear power station—and especially if the power station in question has suffered a recent accident. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Those who do handle radioactive material must first don protective suits that are inherently cumbersome and are further encumbered by the air hoses needed to allow the wearer to breathe. Even then their working hours are strictly limited, in order to avoid prolonged exposure to radiation and because operating in the suits is exhausting. Moreover, some sorts of waste are too hazardous for even the besuited to approach safely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, send in the robots? Unfortunately that is far from simple, for most robots are not up to the task. This became clear after events in 2011 at the Fukushima Daiichi nuclear power plant in Japan, which suffered a series of meltdowns after its safety systems failed following a tsunami. The site at Fukushima has turned into something of a graveyard for those robots dispatched into it to monitor radiation levels and start cleaning things up. Many got stuck, broke down or had their circuits fried by the intense radiation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intelligence test&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Stopping such things happening again is part of the work of the National Centre for Nuclear Robotics (NCNR). This is a collaborative effort involving several British universities. It is led by Rustam Stolkin of the University of Birmingham, and its purpose is to improve the routine use of robotics in nuclear power stations as well as to ensure that robotic trips into irradiated areas are less likely to end up as suicide missions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One problem with the robots dispatched into the ruins of Fukushima Dai-ichi was that they were not particularly clever. Most were operated by someone twiddling joysticks at a safe distance. Such machines are awkward to steer and their arms are tricky to move accurately when viewed via a video screen. Dr Stolkin reckons the answer is to equip then with artificial intelligence (AI), so that they can operate autonomously.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nuclear industry, though, is extremely conservative and not yet prepared to let autonomous robots loose within its facilities. So, for the time being at least, AI will be used to assist human operators. For example, instead of relying on a remote human operator to manipulate all its controls, an AI-equipped robot faced with a pile of different objects to move would employ a camera to understand those objects’ shapes and positions relative to one another. It could then plan how best to grasp each object and move it to, say, an appropriately designed disposal skip without it colliding with anything else in the vicinity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A human being would remain in overall control of the process via a motorised joystick that exerts forces on the operator’s hand similar to those he or she would feel by actually grasping the object. But although the operator still uses the joystick to move the robot’s arm to carry out a particular task, it is the AI which takes care of the details. It makes sure the arm swings in exactly the right direction and picks things up properly. Such an arrangement has already been successfully tested at the Springfields nuclear-fuel facility in north-west England. It was used to cut up contaminated steel with a high-powered laser.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other members of NCNR are examining different aspects of the problem. At the University of Bristol, Tom Scott leads a group working on means for robots to identify materials, including various sorts of plastic, from the “fingerprints” provided by the distinctive ways they scatter laser light. At Queen Mary, a college of the University of London, Kaspar Althoefe’s team is working on radiation-resilient tactile sensors for robots’ fingers. Gerhard Neumann of the University of Lincoln is developing advanced navigation systems. And to ensure robots’ circuits don’t get frazzled, Klaus McDonald-Maier at the University of Essex is developing electronics toughened against the effects of radiation, including circuits that automatically detect and correct errors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Besides helping run nuclear power stations, all this will also assist with the growing need to clean up and recycle nuclear waste—and not just because of disasters like Fukushima. Early members of the nuclear club, such as America, Britain, France and Russia, have accumulated a vast legacy of the stuff. In Britain alone, some 4.9m tonnes of contaminated nuclear material are in need of safe disposal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lot of this is found at one of the most hazardous industrial sites in Europe, Sellafield, also in north-west England. Sellafield began producing plutonium for bombs in 1947. In 1956 the world’s first commercial-sized civil nuclear power station opened there. The site went on to become a centre for reprocessing nuclear fuel. Cleaning up Sellafield’s decaying buildings and nuclear-waste storage facilities will take decades. Robots with autonomous abilities would greatly hurry that process along.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nor is it just inside buildings that robots can help. This April Dr Scott and his colleagues at Bristol completed an aerial survey of the Red Forest in the Chernobyl exclusion zone in Ukraine using robotic drones. Even 33 years after the accident at the site’s number four reactor, they found previously undetected radiation hotspots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike a neat and tidy factory, where robots can be programmed to undertake repetitive tasks without any surprises, decontaminating an old nuclear site requires the ability to operate in an unstructured environment. In some cases, operators may not even know what they might find inside a building. Devising artificial intelligence clever enough to deal with all this will be tricky. But if Dr Stolkin and his colleagues succeed, their efforts are likely to have a wider impact, stretching even into the world of jobs that people are, at the moment at least, content to do themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 03:40:42 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Facebucks—can Zuckerberg’s digital currency go mainstream?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/19/facebucks-can-zuckerbergs-digital-currency-go-mainstream]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_blm508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-19T17:30:01Z&quot;&gt;Jun 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;FACEBOOK WANTS to create a global&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/18/facebook-wants-to-create-a-worldwide-digital-currency&quot; data-tegid=&quot;hjko57ld0b0qop9atg2bhvmmsoktbhom&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;digital currency&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;—what could possibly go wrong? Also, why billionaire &lt;strong&gt;Stephen Schwarzman&lt;/strong&gt;, founder of Blackstone private-equity firm, is donating £150m to fund a humanities centre at Oxford University. And, what can be done to increase public &lt;strong&gt;trust in artificial intelligence?&lt;/strong&gt; Kenneth Cukier hosts. Runtime: 19 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistbabbage/663ae749-bab0-4216-be71-27709b0a953b&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 02:40:52 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can countries lower taxes and raise revenues?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/19/can-countries-lower-taxes-and-raise-revenues]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_woc938.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-19T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;RARELY has a dinner-table scribbling created such a legacy. In 1974 Arthur Laffer, an economist, sketched a simple diagram on the back of a napkin to illustrate a truism of tax policy. Set income-tax tax rates to zero and governments will not collect any revenue. Set them to 100%, and they will also collect nothing because people will have little incentive to work. Somewhere in between lies a sweet spot where government revenues are maximised. From this simple proof, it follows that when tax rates are very high, it might be possible both to lower tax rates and raise revenues. Tax cuts might thus pay for themselves, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Laffer’s scribbling caught on. Some 45 years later some 15,000 journal articles mention the “Laffer curve” in their title. Today President Donald Trump will award the Presidential Medal of Freedom, America&amp;#x27;s highest civilian honour, to Mr Laffer—an adviser to Mr. Trump’s 2016 presidential campaign and co-author of the book “Trumponomics”. In its announcement of the event, the White House described Mr Laffer as “one of the most influential economists in American history.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Budget hawks might disagree. Supply-side economists have long used the Laffer curve to justify tax cuts, including Ronald Reagan’s in 1981 and George W. Bush’s in 2001. Both resulted in lower revenues. In December 2017 Mr Trump’s administration cut income taxes across the board, and slashed the corporate-tax rate from 35% to 21%. At the time, Steven Mnuchin, America���s treasury secretary, argued that the plan would “pay for itself” and even “pay down debt”.‬ But the promised revenues have yet to materialise. Federal tax revenues actually fell in 2018. The Congressional Budget Office, a government watchdog, now reckons that the national debt will hit 95% of GDP by 2027, up from 89% two years ago before the tax cuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America is not the only country that appears to be on the wrong side of Mr Laffer’s curve. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.econstor.eu/bitstream/10419/197646/1/1007192151.pdf&quot;&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt; published in 2017 by Jacob Lundberg, an economist at Timbro, a Swedish free-market think-tank, estimates Laffer curves for 27 OECD countries. Using data on Sweden’s income distribution and assumptions about how taxpayers respond to different tax rates, Mr Lundberg found that, even though five countries in his sample have top income-tax rates that exceed their revenue-maximising levels, only Sweden could meaningfully boost revenue by cutting tax rates on high-income earners. Most countries, in other words, appear to have set their highest tax rates at or below the optimal rate suggested by the Laffer curve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This may explain why many economists are so critical of Mr Laffer’s supply-side policies. In 2012 the Initiative on Global Markets, a research centre at the University of Chicago’s Booth School of Business, asked a panel of 40 economic experts whether a cut in income-tax rates in America would raise enough revenue to pay for itself in five years. Not one of them agreed. Richard Thaler, winner of last year&amp;#x27;s Nobel prize in economics, responded simply “That&amp;#x27;s a Laffer!”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 02:40:51 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The centre cannot hold]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/bagehots-notebook/2019/06/19/the-centre-cannot-hold-the-failure-of-change-uk-and-the-atrophying-of-political-thought]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_BRP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-19T16:08:05Z&quot;&gt;Jun 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest disasters to befall Change UK—Chuka Umunna’s decision to join the Liberal Democrats and the party’s decision to change its name for a third time—are a good excuse to reflect on the sad fate of one of the most ill-starred parties in British political history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s not that long since Change UK was poised to revolutionise British politics. There are lots of reasons why that never came to pass: Heidi Allen proved to be an incompetent acting head; the party failed to brand itself a “Remain party” but instead dithered around trying to reinvent the centre; it called itself Change but demanded that, as far as Europe was concerned, things stayed the same. But the biggest reason of all was the results of the council elections at the beginning of May, in which Change did not take part. There was only room for one anti-Leave party in the middle ground of British politics, and the Liberal Democrats’ strong council-election performance ensured that it would be that party. From that point on people who felt as strongly about remaining in the European Union as Nigel Farage’s supporters felt about leaving gravitated to the Liberal Democrats. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though exceedingly brief, the Change UK episode is nevertheless significant because it resolves a long-standing debate in the Labour Party. Ever since the Corbyn coup in 2015, members of the parliamentary party have been arguing about whether they should stay and fight or leave en masse. For a while it looked as if Tom Watson might follow Chukka Umunna and others out of the party. Change’s implosion has settled the argument in favour of stay-and-fight, even if, unfortunately, it doesn’t look as if the stay-and-fighters have much chance of winning. Mr Corbyn’s decision to humiliate Emily Thornberry by, for example, dropping her as his stand-in at Prime Minister’s Questions, is designed to demonstrate that he has the support of 80% of the party’s members whereas she is basically on her own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s also significant because it provides an important lesson about the nature of modern parties. Change UK was an attempt to create a party from the top down. MPs from both Labour and the Conservatives abandoned their ancestral parties and focused on attracting more MPs to their cause. But the days when politics was mainly fought between professional politicians in Westminster have disappeared along with Francis Fukuyama’s essay on “The End of History”. The Labour Party is now a movement as well as a party, thanks to the arrival of several hundred thousand committed Corbynistas. The same thing is happening on the right: the Brexit Party can draw on dozens of pro-Leave movements that have grown from the bottom up and are driven by genuine anger about the status quo. Centrists don’t just need to build a traditional party infrastructure, with MPs, local offices and dutiful but tame members. They need to create all the accoutrements of a mass-movement: think-tanks to provide a constant source of ideas, foot soldiers to campaign on the ground, keyboard warriors to fight the Twitter war. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The obvious kernel for such a movement is the People’s Vote campaign, but it is intertwined with the Labour Party. Many of the People’s Vote campaign’s leading figures are Blairites who are continuing to fight a Labour civil war, not least Alastair Campbell, Tony Blair’s chief spin-doctor. He was expelled from the Labour Party for acknowledging that he had voted for the Liberal Democrats but is nevertheless still a member of Labour’s squabbling tribe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;****&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another lot trying to shake things up are the so-called new progressives—the broad collection of people who embrace the politics of social justice and identity. I can understand why young people are attracted to the social-justice movement. They are the victims of one of the greatest acts of intergenerational justice for decades: the fact that the baby-boom generation has gobbled up the fruits of post-war prosperity (free university education, second homes, generous pensions) then discovered fiscal rectitude when it comes to designing policies for their successors (student loans, defined contributions, green taxes). But the social-justice movement certainly has not produced a compelling text comparable with the liberal classics produced by the same sense of injustice in the mid-Victorian era such as John Stuart Mill’s “On Liberty” or Matthew Arnold’s “Culture and Anarchy”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One reason for this is that the new progressives seem to be determined to drive down the intellectual blind alley of identity politics. Identity politics seems to be confused about the very thing at its heart—identity. Some of the time identity seems to be socially constructed: hence the preoccupation with gender fluidity, for example. We are told that gender is a social construct and people can jump from one gender to another according to choice. Some of the time identity seems to be taken as an adamantine fact: a person’s identity as a woman or a member of an ethnic minority seems to trump all other considerations. Thus Catharine MacKinnon, a leading feminist theorist at the University of Michigan, has argued that members of each ethnic, gender or cultural group have their own distinct moral and intellectual norms. “The white man’s standard for equality is: Are you equal to him?”, she argues. “That is hardly a neutral standard. It is a racist, sexist standard…But if you present yourself as affirmatively and self-respectingly a member of your own culture or sex…if you insist that your cultural diversity be affirmatively accommodated and recognised in ways equal to the ways theirs has been, that’s not seen as an equality challenge at all.” This sounds a little like the social biologists of the late 19th and early 20th century who argued that the world is divided into various racial-cultural groups that are locked in an inevitable struggle for dominance and that each group uses epiphenomena such as truth and morality as instruments of group power. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;****&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But I suspect the problem is more general than this: we’re suffering from a general atrophy of political thinking not just in political parties and movements but across the board. Academics have either been captured by identity politics or else have chosen to retreat into tiny specialisms. In America in particular the noble science of politics has been captured by political scientists who are deploying ever more powerful quantitative techniques to ever more trivial ends. The most interesting political theorists writing for the general public today are still Isaiah Berlin’s (somewhat aged) pupils such as Sir Larry Siedentop and John Gray. The chair that Mr Berlin once graced at Oxford lies empty. Public authorities in general, encouraged by pressure groups but also, I suspect, driven by their natural sympathies, have taken to closing down debates on subjects that are deemed too controversial such as diversity (which has been built into social policy without any serious debate about its advantages versus its disadvantages), and, increasingly, various aspects of sexual mores. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How long will this great stagnation of political debate last? In fact, I suspect that we could actually be on the verge of a golden period of political thinking. The collapse of the neo-liberal hegemony, the rise of a raw but sometimes exciting populism, the growing revolt against progressive totalitarianism on campus and, increasingly, in corporations… All this will lead to a recrudescence of interesting political theory. The human mind is too fertile to be tamed by high priests of various kinds—in the parties, media and the corporations—trying to enforce yesterday’s tired orthodoxies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I suspect that this recrudescence will come from the peripheries of today’s established political and intellectual empires (it’s a long time since I’ve read anything thought-provoking or original from publications with “New York” in their titles or from professors with chairs in the world’s ancient universities). It will come from repentant liberals and conservatives who want to understand why the great intellectual traditions that they once embraced degenerated so rapidly over the past couple of decades. I’m particularly struck by the mea culpas about (neo)conservative over-reach that regularly appear in the &lt;em&gt;American Conservativ&lt;/em&gt;e and the &lt;em&gt;Claremont Review of Books&lt;/em&gt;. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It will come from the collision between different intellectual traditions. Conservatism has always been at its most exciting when it tries to tame the individualistic excesses of liberalism (Walter Bagehot liked to say that he was as liberal as it was possible to be while still being a conservative and as conservative as it is possible to be while still being a liberal). I’d also hope that the collision between progressivism and older traditions will also be fruitful. Gay marriage, one of the most sensible social reforms of the past couple of decades, was produced by conservatives such as the British-born American journalist Andrew Sullivan who wanted to provide a conservative solution (marriage) to a progressive question (why shouldn’t I be allowed to express my sexuality in the public sphere?) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 01:40:16 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[African swine fever spreads to South-East Asia]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/19/swine-fever-is-spreading-from-china-to-south-east-asia]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_asp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-19T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERE ARE few dishes that a typical Filipino, Thai or Vietnamese would not consider improved by the addition of pork. What better to stuff a squid with, or garnish a bowl of steaming noodles or simply spit-roast and scoff? No wonder, then, that South-East Asia is home to more than 83m pigs. But the outbreak of African swine fever that has swept through China in recent months is now spreading across the region. Its governments are likely to find it no easier than China’s to contain the disease, which is harmless to humans but typically fatal to pigs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swine fever first crossed the border from China into Vietnam in February. It has gradually worked its way south, and in April spread to Cambodia (see map). Thailand fears it is next. In fact, the disease could already be there or elsewhere: experts worry that monitoring and reporting are patchy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pigs catch the disease from each other, from contaminated surfaces, from ticks and from food (slop containing infected pork or pig’s blood). There is also a risk that farmed pigs may be infected by wild ones and vice versa. Those transporting not just live pigs, but also pork, across borders risk introducing swine fever to new areas. Meanwhile, pork prices have jumped more than 40% compared with a year ago and analysts expect overall inflation to rise in Vietnam and Cambodia as a result. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Culling swine is one of the main ways officials hope to curb the disease. Vietnam has slaughtered 2.5m pigs, twice as many as China. Bans on the import of pigs and pork are another tactic. But many of the region’s pig farms are tiny, as in China. Their owners cannot afford to erect special fencing or buy commercial feed. The temptation, if they suspect their pigs are infected, is to kill or sell them quickly and quietly, to save themselves from financial ruin. Although the Vietnamese government compensates farmers who report sick pigs that are subsequently culled, the fear of slow or low payments can still put farmers off. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Fortunately, international co-ordination, especially between governments and companies in South-East Asia’s pork industry, has been impressive, says Wantanee Kalpravidh of the Food and Agriculture Organisation, a UN agency. She lauds a scheme to send Thai pork to Cambodia to meet demand at affordable prices—on carefully cleaned and monitored vehicles—to discourage the smuggling of possibly contaminated meat from Vietnam. Somkuan Choowatanapakorn of Charoen Pokphand Foods, a big Thai agribusiness that handles lots of pork, says the company has “taken steps already” to train farmers to recognise and respond to the disease’s symptoms. He adds that contingency plans for an outbreak are also in place. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Despite such efforts, the scale of the porcine plague in China means that South-East Asia will probably struggle with it for as long as its neighbour does. A working vaccine is still a long way off. It is hard to see what can save the region’s bacon. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 01:40:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is there an optimal level of taxation?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/19/is-there-an-optimal-level-of-taxation]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_woc938.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-19T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;RARELY has a dinner-table scribbling created such a legacy. In 1974 Arthur Laffer, an economist, sketched a simple diagram on the back of a napkin to illustrate a truism of tax policy. Set income-tax tax rates to zero and governments will not collect any revenue. Set them to 100%, and they will also collect nothing because people will have little incentive to work. Somewhere in between lies a sweet spot where government revenues are maximised. From this simple proof, it follows that when tax rates are very high, it might be possible both to lower tax rates and raise revenues. Tax cuts might thus pay for themselves, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Laffer’s scribbling caught on. Some 45 years later some 15,000 journal articles mention the “Laffer curve” in their title. Today President Donald Trump will award the Presidential Medal of Freedom, America&amp;#x27;s highest civilian honour, to Mr Laffer—an adviser to Mr. Trump’s 2016 presidential campaign and co-author of the book “Trumponomics”. In its announcement of the event, the White House described Mr Laffer as “one of the most influential economists in American history.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Budget hawks might disagree. Supply-side economists have long used the Laffer curve to justify tax cuts, including Ronald Reagan’s in 1981 and George W. Bush’s in 2001. Both resulted in lower revenues. In December 2017 Mr Trump’s administration cut income taxes across the board, and slashed the corporate-tax rate from 35% to 21%. At the time, Steven Mnuchin, America’s treasury secretary, argued that the plan would “pay for itself” and even “pay down debt”.‬ But the promised revenues have yet to materialise. Federal tax revenues actually fell in 2018. The Congressional Budget Office, a government watchdog, now reckons that the national debt will hit 95% of GDP by 2027, up from 89% two years ago before the tax cuts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America is not the only country that appears to be on the wrong side of Mr Laffer’s curve. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.econstor.eu/bitstream/10419/197646/1/1007192151.pdf&quot;&gt;paper&lt;/a&gt; published in 2017 by Jacob Lundberg, an economist at Timbro, a Swedish free-market think-tank, estimates Laffer curves for high-income earners in 27 OECD countries. Using data on Sweden’s income distribution and assumptions about how taxpayers respond to different tax rates, Mr Lundberg found that, even though five countries in his sample have top income-tax rates that exceed their revenue-maximising levels, only Sweden could meaningfully boost revenue by cutting tax rates on high-income earners. Most countries, in other words, appear to have set their highest tax rates at or below the peak of the Laffer curve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This may explain why many economists are so critical of Mr Laffer’s supply-side policies. In 2012 the Initiative on Global Markets, a research centre at the University of Chicago’s Booth School of Business, asked a panel of 40 economic experts whether a cut in income-tax rates in America would raise enough revenue to pay for itself in five years. Not one of them agreed. Richard Thaler, winner of last year&amp;#x27;s Nobel prize in economics, responded simply “That&amp;#x27;s a Laffer!”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 01:40:14 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>