<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[EU leaders fail to agree on who should lead the union for the next five years]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/charlemagnes-notebook/2019/06/21/eu-leaders-fail-to-agree-on-who-should-lead-the-union-for-the-next-five-years]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_blp907_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T07:00:33Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;IS THE Spitzenkandidat process dead? And if so, who killed it? In 2014 the EU introduced this convention by which the “lead candidate” of the largest parliamentary group becomes president of the European Commission, the EU’s executive. At the European Parliament elections last month most of the major party families duly presented their nominees. In theory, this would make allocating the EU’s various big jobs after the election easier. With the commission’s head selected, as it were, by the voters, leaders could fill the other posts, like the presidencies of the European Council (the body containing the union’s heads of government) and the European Central Bank (ECB), in a way that created a politically and ideologically balanced package. That, indeed, was the main task of last night’s discussion at the European Council summit in Brussels.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;It did not work out that way. The summit ended in deadlock as the Spitzenkandidat system came under attack from various directions. The convention has always looked rather shaky. Angela Merkel was not a fan in 2014 and had to be bounced into supporting it that time. But the story of the current mess really begins in Helsinki last November, when the European People’s Party (EPP), the main centre-right grouping and then as now the parliament’s largest force, picked Manfred Weber as its lead candidate. The Bavarian lacks televisual charisma, has no executive experience and has alienated centrists and centre-leftists with his long association with Viktor Orban, Hungary’s authoritarian prime minister. He made little impact during the European election campaign. A survey published on Tuesday by the European Council on Foreign Relations, a think-tank, found that only 4% of voters in France or Germany were motivated to vote by the Spitzenkandidat system.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;All of which provides the pretext for opponents of the system, and of Mr Weber, to rip it up. That they proceeded to do yesterday. Ahead of the summit the leaders of the parliament’s second- and third- largest groups, the centre-left Socialists and Democrats (S&amp;amp;D) and the centrist Renew Europe (RE), announced that they would not back him. That greatly dimmed his prospects, as an incoming commission president needs the backing of a majority of the European Parliament. At the dinner eleven of the 27 national leaders making the choice (Britain’s Theresa May is not involved) blocked his nomination. An irritated Mrs Merkel, who is backing Mr Weber, responded that in that case the other groups’ lead candidates or de-facto lead candidates—namely Frans Timmermans of S&amp;amp;D and Margrethe Vestager of RE—should also be ruled out. This aggravated Mark Rutte, the liberal Dutch prime minister, who characterised the stance as unreasonable. But it was probably a statement of reality: there is no clear majority in the parliament without EPP votes, and the EPP will be reluctant to back an alternative lead candidate if their own is rebuffed.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;With no majority for Mr Weber, Mr Timmermans or Ms Vestager—Emmanuel Macron declared all three “ruled out” on leaving the summit—there is no consensus around a commission president candidate in either the parliament or the council. And without that first building block its is tricky to allocate the remaining big jobs. So the meeting broke up in the early hours of this morning having settled on no nominations. Leaders will now meet again on June 30th, shortly before the new parliament convenes on July 2nd and ahead of an expected vote on the nominated commission candidate two weeks later. Adding to the sense of frustration at the summit was leaders’ inability to reach agreement on a common commitment to a zero-carbon EU by 2050, with objections from Poland, the Czech Republic, Hungary and Estonia getting in the way.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;What next for the big jobs jigsaw? Mr Weber is not yet entirely out of the running but is prospects look poor. Even Mrs Merkel seems to be resigning herself to this, acknowledging that leaders needed to find a commission candidate capable of commanding the broad majority necessary: “we do not under any circumstances want a crisis with the parliament”, she insisted last night. The German chancellor is expected to entertain alternative figures at the next discussion. One possible compromise candidate is Michel Barnier, a French EPP politician and the EU’s chief Brexit negotiator. But it may be that other names bubble up, perhaps at the G20 summit in Japan next week, where several major EU leaders will have the chance to cut deals before the next gathering in Brussels. One option has the leaders parking the discussion about the commission job and settling instead on candidates for the council and the ECB, then working back from there. An outlandish theory doing the rounds even has Donald Tusk, the council president, eventually putting himself forward to lead the commission.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;The deadlock, like the inability to form consensus on the climate goals, is a sign of the times. Europe is a more fractured place than in the past, with bigger divides between member states and a more fragmented political landscape both in the national capitals and in the incoming European Parliament (the successful commission president will probably need the backing of three or even four groups to secure a majority, where two used to suffice). Some member states are more used to this than others. The Netherlands, which has experienced political fragmentation for longer, and to a greater extent, than most, took seven months to form its last government—as Mr Rutte reminded waiting journalists last night, urging patience. Leo Varadkar, Ireland’s taoiseach (prime minister) was less emollient, despairing: “It’s quicker to elect the pope.”&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 15:40:48 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Supreme Court blesses a cross-shaped war memorial in Maryland]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/20/the-supreme-court-blesses-a-cross-shaped-war-memorial-in-maryland]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_USP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-20T22:48:03Z&quot;&gt;Jun 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE FIRST line of the First Amendment—“Congress shall make no law respecting an establishment of religion”—has inspired sharply divergent interpretations. To glance at the vote in&lt;em&gt; American Legion v American Humanist Association,&lt;/em&gt; a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/18pdf/17-1717_4f14.pdf&quot;&gt;7-2 ruling&lt;/a&gt; handed down on June 20th, one might get the impression those differences have been largely ironed out over the 72 years since the court first addressed the meaning of the Establishment Clause in a school-bussing case from New Jersey. That impression is misleading.&lt;em&gt; American Legion&lt;/em&gt; is no picture of judicial consensus: in additional to the plurality opinion six justices wrote separately to dissent or clarify their views. In all, seven justices agreed that a 40-foot cross-shaped memorial to soldiers who died in the first world war will continue to loom over a pair of roads in Bladensburg, Maryland. But very different opinions lay behind that decision and two justices expressed a much stricter view about the place of religious symbols on public ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justice Samuel Alito, author of the plurality opinion, struck a more generous and less testy note than he often does. In their separate concurring opinions, Justices Stephen Breyer (on the left) and Brett Kavanaugh (on the right) both praised Justice Alito’s opinion as “eloquent”. Justice Elena Kagan—with whom Justice Alito &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2014/05/06/niggling-distinctions&quot;&gt;sparred&lt;/a&gt; five years ago in another religion case—commended his ruling for showing “sensitivity to and respect for this nation’s pluralism, and the values of neutrality and inclusion that the First Amendment demands”. These four justices, along with Chief Justice John Roberts, formed partially overlapping Venn diagrams that save the Bladensburg cross with a narrow and historically nuanced justification.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The analysis in the main opinion is straightforward. Yes, Justice Alito wrote, “the cross has long been a preeminent Christian symbol”, but its use on public ground in Maryland “has a special significance” that is more secular than sectarian. The image of “row after row of plain white crosses marking the overseas graves” of fallen soldiers was “emblazoned on the minds of Americans” during the war, he wrote, and the American Legion’s decision to use the cross as its memorial “must be viewed in that historical context”. As a “prominent community landmark”, the memorial expresses “the community’s grief at the loss of the young men who perished” in battle. To require the demolition or “radical alteration” of the monument nearly a century later—in response to a challenge from atheists and non-Christians who view it as alienating—would not be a “neutral act”. It would be hostile to Christianity and to “the ideals of respect and tolerance embodied in the First Amendment”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justice Alito widened the lens beyond the busy intersection outside Washington, DC to reflect on other examples of symbols and institutions in public life. Crosses are found in “many registered trademarks”, he noted, from Blue Cross Blue Shield to Bayer, but non-Christians don’t bat an eye when flashing their health insurance cards or popping an aspirin. Residents of Corpus Christi, Texas or Providence, Rhode Island, don’t petition to change the deeply religious names of their cities. And communities often find meaning in certain faith-centred sites “without necessarily embracing their religious roots”. Notre Dame in Paris is a “striking example”, Justice Alito wrote. Tears and concern for the cathedral after the recent fire show Notre Dame is “a symbol of national importance to the religious and nonreligious alike”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justices Breyer and Kagan dissented from the Supreme Court’s legislative prayer case in 2014, but they were largely on board with Justice Alito’s approach this time around. Justice Kagan opted not to join in a disparagement of the so-called &lt;em&gt;Lemon&lt;/em&gt; test—a fraught method of identifying Establishment Clause violations by looking for a secular purpose and effect and gauging the level of church-state entanglement. She also left her name off of a section drawing lessons from history “out of perhaps an excess of caution”. Better to analyse the matters “case-by-case”, she wrote, than to draw overly broad conclusions. Echoing a concern he &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/03/02/americas-porous-wall-between-church-and-state&quot;&gt;expressed&lt;/a&gt; in the February oral argument, Justice Breyer clarified that “if the cross had been erected only recently, rather than in the aftermath of World War I”, it may not pass constitutional muster. Justice Alito included just enough references to “longstanding” monuments in his opinion—your correspondent counts four—to persuade Justice Breyer that his vote wouldn’t commit the court to upholding newly built crosses or those that seem to target members of religious minorities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To the right and left of these centrist camps stood two pairs of justices with different ideas about what the Establishment Clause means. For Justice Neil Gorsuch, the plaintiffs who objected to the cross should not just lose their case; they never should have been able to sue in the first place. The “‘offended observer’ theory of standing has no basis in law”, he wrote, taking a flame-thrower to the “endorsement test” first developed by Justice Sandra Day O’Connor in 1984. That test, which the courts have never applied consistently, says a government policy or monument might violate the Establishment Clause if a reasonable observer regards it as an official endorsement of religion. “Really, most every governmental action probably offends &lt;em&gt;somebody&lt;/em&gt;”, Justice Gorsuch wrote. The remedy is not to sue but to avert one’s eyes when something seems offensive. Justice Thomas signed this concurrence and penned one of his own repeating his idiosyncratic view that only the federal government—not states or cities—should be subject to the constraints of the Establishment Clause. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the other end of the bench sat the lone dissenters in&lt;em&gt; American Legion&lt;/em&gt;, Justices Ruth Bader Ginsburg (who took the unusual move of reading a portion of her dissent from the bench) and Sonia Sotomayor. For these stricter separationists, letting the “immense” cross remain on public land, supported with public funds, is a clear breach of the church-state wall. “Just as a Star of David is not suitable to honor Christians who died serving their country“, Justice Ginsburg wrote, “so a cross is not suitable to honor those of other faiths who died defending their nation”. The state’s endorsement of the cross “elevates Christianity over other faiths, and religion over nonreligion”. And there is no reason to fear a win for the humanists heralding the bulldozing of dozens of crosses around the country. Each cross must be analysed separately, Justice Ginsburg wrote, and those deemed unacceptable could be moved to private land. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his concurrence, Justice Kavanaugh sounded a note of sympathy with Jewish veterans and others whose “sense of distress and alienation” led them to object to the cross. There are “genuine and important interests” on both sides of the dispute, he wrote, and although the constitution does not require it, perhaps the Maryland legislature would see fit to remove the cross or transfer the land on which it stands to private hands. He added a line few would contest. “[P]inning down the meaning” of the Establishment Clause “has proved to be a vexing problem”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 05:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[And then there were two]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/bagehots-notebook/2019/06/20/and-then-there-were-two]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_BRP550.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-20T19:17:42Z&quot;&gt;Jun 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AFTER TWO days of voting Tory MPs have chosen two of their colleagues to go through to the next stage of the leadership election: a run-off when the party’s 160,000 members will choose the winner. They are Boris Johnson and Jeremy Hunt, the foreign secretary. Mr Johnson got more than half the votes with 160. Mr Hunt just pipped Michael Gove, the environment secretary, with 77 votes to 75.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boris Johnson’s ascent to the prime ministership now looks even more likely than it was a week ago. Mr Johnson’s biggest problem was always winning over his fellow Conservative MPs. He’s never been much of a team player: he has devoted more time to lining his own pockets (in one year he earned £540,000 from journalism and public speaking) than to campaigning for his colleagues. He’s also been a lacklustre and lazy performer at the dispatch box in parliament. But he is adored by the party members in the country who cherish his Bertie Wooster-with-a-thesaurus speeches and flamboyant style. They also agree with him on Brexit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Hunt is unlikely to be able to slow down his momentum. The foreign secretary is in many ways an impressive figure. He inherited a marginal seat and turned it into a safe one. He was health secretary for six years—longer than anyone since the creation of the NHS. He has been a much better foreign secretary than Mr Johnson, his predecessor: foreign office insiders say that he inherited a demoralised and disoriented department and quickly reinvigorated it. But Mr Hunt is a sensible man who is trying to win the support of a party that has gone slightly bonkers: fixated on Brexit, furious about the way Britain has been treated by Brussels, and given to chasing unicorns. The majority of party members say that they support a no-deal Brexit despite overwhelming evidence about the damage that that would do to the economy. Mr Hunt also bears the Conservative Party’s equivalent of the mark of Cain: he voted Remain in 2016. Thus, although he claims that he’s now determined to deliver Brexit, he provokes comparisons with Theresa May who, according to hard-core Brexiteers, failed to deliver Brexit not because of an intractable problem and a hung parliament, but because she didn’t “believe”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Johnson would have faced a much tougher fight against Michael Gove. Mr Gove is one of the party’s most accomplished debaters—quick on his feet, frequently funny and, unlike Mr Johnson, steeped in policy details. He also has an appetite to go for the jugular. Mr Gove might have done real damage to Mr Johnson. By contrast Mr Hunt is too emollient a figure—his critics would call him “bland”—to burst the Boris balloon. Once more, luck is with the front- runner. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tory MPs are also acting out of self-preservation in their choice of Messrs Hunt and Johnson to finish off the contest. MPs knew that a contest between Mr Johnson and Mr Gove could easily have degenerated into the modern equivalent of the contest between Polynices and Eteocles who murdered each other in their determination to rule over Thebes (Mr Johnson, who read classics at Oxford, is fond of classical references). The two men were close friends at Oxford and beyond, with Mr Johnson playing the senior role and Mr Gove being something of a courtier. Mr Johnson chose Mr Gove to run his campaign for the premiership in 2016. But then Mr Gove turned against his friend and former mentor and announced that he didn’t think that he was fit to be prime minister. By choosing Mr Hunt MPs have avoided a blood-letting, and distanced the their party from one of the great psycho-dramas of recent years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The party may have limited the potential damage of the race but it certainly hasn’t escaped Scott free. The two surviving candidates are both products of private schools and Oxford University, Mr Johnson Eton and Balliol, Mr Hunt Charterhouse and Magdalen. Conservatives eliminated the son of a Pakistani bus driver who arrived in the country with £1 in his pocket (Sajid Javid), the adopted son of an Aberdeen fishmonger (Michael Gove) and a foreign office high flyer turned author turned academic who is brimming with original ideas (Rory Stewart). Mr Johnson refused to turn up to the first televised debate and the parliamentary lobby hustings. His team also reportedly used tactics worthy of the Oxford Union (of which he was once president) rather than parliament: “lending” votes to various runners up (by encouraging loyal supporters to vote for them) in order to eliminate candidates, such as Mr Stewart and Mr Gove, who might cause him the most trouble. “There have been lies and lies and lies and loads of pomposity” was one Tory MP’s summary of the race so far. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever the truth of these rumours (and it’s impossible to know given the secrecy of the ballot box) it is important for the future of the Conservative Party that some of the personal damage that has been done during this leadership campaign and its predecessor is repaired. Messrs Johnson and Stewart need to make peace (and Mr Stewart needs to swallow his pride and rescind his promise that he won’t serve in a Johnson administration). Mr Stewart has demonstrated that a Conservative can still excite middle-of-the-road voters. He would also make a superb foreign secretary. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is even more important, from the Conservative Party’s point of view, that Messrs Johnson and Gove bury the hatchet. Mr Gove is that rare thing—a Brexiteer who understands the dangers of a no-deal Brexit. He is also gifted with the very strengths that Mr Johnson lacks: an ability to re-energise government departments with conservative ideas, a broad interest in public policy and an impressive command of detail. In an ideal world Mr Gove would make an excellent CEO to Mr Johnson’s chairman of the board. But then in an ideal world Polynices and Eteocles would not have slaughtered each other. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 05:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Britain&#x27;s leadership race, “Texafornia” dreaming and pets gain the upper paw]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/20/britains-leadership-race-texafornia-dreaming-and-pets-gain-the-upper-paw]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_10.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-20T17:30:10Z&quot;&gt;Jun 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A SELECTION of three essential articles read aloud from the latest issue of The Economist. This week, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/20/which-boris-would-britain-get&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Boris Johnson&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is the favourite to become Britain&amp;#x27;s next Prime Minister. America’s future will be written in the two mega-states—&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/20/texafornia-dreaming&quot;&gt;California and Texas&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;(8:23). And, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/22/pets-have-gained-the-upper-paw-over-their-so-called-owners&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;pets&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; have gained the upper paw over their so-called owners (16:50). Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/f3af74a0-3c5a-4081-8b10-f7ad9da4b2e0&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 01:40:28 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How many Americans live on $2 a day?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/20/how-many-americans-live-on-2-a-day]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_USP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-20T15:09:24Z&quot;&gt;Jun 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS AMERICA’S economy continues its recovery from the Great Recession, the official poverty rate has fallen—from 15.9% of the population to 13.4% in 2017. This is still a couple of percentage points higher than it was a decade ago. But in another hopeful sign, new measures of extreme poverty—defined as living on $2 a day or less—suggest it is much lower than previously thought. This is inconvenient for those on both the left and the right. It suggests that the welfare reform of the 1990s did not, as previously believed, much increase extreme poverty and that America’s safety net works better than is often argued. It also suggests arguments that poverty at home is as bad as poverty elsewhere in the world are overblown.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Previous estimates of extreme poverty have suggested it was concentrated amongst single parent families. These households bore the brunt of a major bipartisan reform in 1996, which made welfare payments conditional on recipients trying to find work and ruled that no one could receive them for more than five years. According to Kathryn Edin and Luke Schaefer, sociologists, survey evidence suggests the number of households with children living on less than $2 cash per person per day climbed from 600,000 in 1997 to more than 1.4m in 2010. Even including the Supplemental Nutritional Assistance Programme, once known as food stamps, which was designed to ensure that poor American families have enough to eat, the numbers appeared to have increased from below half a million in 1996 to 800,000 in 2010.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The $2 poverty line is broadly comparable to the World Bank’s global $1.90 “extreme poverty line.” It is a fraction of the official, income-based, poverty line in America, which is set at $21,330 for a family of three—or about $19 a day. Those earlier estimates of extreme poverty, suggestive of widespread destitution, prompted Angus Deaton, a Nobel prize-winning economist, to propose redirecting US foreign aid to America’s poorest people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new poverty estimates, by Carla Medalia from the Census Bureau and Bruce Meyer from the University of Chicago, tell a rather different story. They combine data from surveys and from government agencies. That helps overcome two problems from estimates that use survey data alone: respondents often under-report the benefits they get and sometimes they mis-report other income. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at all individuals’ survey-reported household income, about 2.6% report living on less than $2 a day. But when other benefits, under-reported earnings and other assets are factored in, that falls to 0.57%. Add in data from programme administrators on under-reported transfers including the earned income tax credit, social security payments, housing assistance and the Supplemental Nutritional Assistance Programme and the proportion falls to 0.11% percent, or around 336,000 people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The adjustments also suggest extreme poverty isn’t concentrated among families. On a survey-reported basis that excludes in-kind payments households with children make up the considerable majority of the extreme poor. But once the adjustments are made, poverty is almost exclusively concentrated amongst single, childless households. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the additional data sources certainly make the numbers more reliable, the analysis, as with previous estimates, excludes the homeless—half a million or more Americans. And some of the assumptions regarding data adjustments are arguable—including that benefits are worth the same as cash, that hours worked will necessarily pay at least the minimum wage and that households with considerable asset wealth will not be income-poor. On the other hand, the results exclude administrative data on some big transfer programmes including unemployment insurance, veteran’s benefits and worker’s compensation, which collectively spend over $200bn a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new evidence is important for two reasons. First, it suggests that extreme poverty cannot have risen significantly after welfare reform. The numbers living on $2 a day remain low and are not amongst those targeted by the reform measures. Second, the big gap between market income and consumption spending thrown up by the new research suggests that safety net programmes are doing their job of keeping people from utter destitution. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The overall impact of welfare reform continues to be debated. Research by Hilary Hoynes and Diane Schanzenbach, economists, suggests safety-net spending on families with incomes below the official poverty line has fallen from 87% of the total in 1990 to 56% in 2015, while per-child spending on families without earnings has declined since 1990. And even if the number of Americans living on $2 a day is in the thousands, rather than over 1m, it is still too high.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jun 2019 01:40:27 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Too Old To Die Young” and the problem of the unsupervised auteur]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/20/too-old-to-die-young-and-the-problem-of-the-unsupervised-auteur]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_BKP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-20T13:37:08Z&quot;&gt;Jun 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE RISE of subscription-based channels and streaming services has enabled cinema’s biggest names to develop their own television series, not as a way to make a quick buck between passion projects, but as a way to tell ever longer and richer stories. Following Paolo Sorrentino’s “The Young Pope”, Woody Allen’s “Crisis in Six Scenes” and Ava DuVernay’s “When They See Us”, the latest and most radical example is Nicolas Winding Refn’s ten-part series, “Too Old To Die Young”, released on Amazon on June 14th. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fans of the Danish director’s films, including “Pusher”, “Drive” and “Only God Forgives”, won’t be surprised to learn that he has come up with another seedy, brutal, yet coolly stylish urban crime thriller. But during its 13-hour running time, two things become clear. The first is that nothing quite like it has ever been made before. The other is that this is probably for the best. Shot by shot, “Too Old To Die Young” is startlingly beautiful. But when all those shots are strung together, the result is so stupefying as to be almost unwatchable. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Co-written by Ed Brubaker, the first episode introduces Martin (Miles Teller), a 30-year-old Los Angeles Country Sheriff, and his partner Larry (Lance Gross). They are both bad cops, but Larry is worse: a typical evening for him is spent harassing women, taking bribes and discussing whether he should murder his cokehead mistress before she can reveal their affair to his wife. It is difficult to be upset when a Mexican youth, Jesus (Augusto Aguilera), walks up to him in the street and shoots him dead. But Martin is afraid that he will be executed next, because he and Larry killed Jesus’s mother, the sister of a druglord. He needs the protection of a Nigerian gangster, Damian (Babs Olusanmokun), and to pay for that service he has to kill whomever Damian chooses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So much for the first 93-minute episode—or “Volume One” as Mr Refn calls it. The 97-minute second episode abandons Martin and heads down to Mexico, where Jesus meets Yaritza (Cristina Rodlo), a tarot-card reader who styles herself as “The High Priestess of Death”. The 76-minute third episode returns to Los Angeles, where Martin meets Viggo (John Hawkes), a retired FBI agent, and Diana (Jena Malone), a new-age therapist and victim-support officer. With Diana’s help, Viggo goes around murdering rapists, but he wants Martin to take his place as “an extermination machine eliminating all evil in the universe”. And so the series goes on, shifting from blackly comic Tarantino-esque violence to apocalyptic Lynchian surrealism—but doing so very slowly indeed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Too Old To Die Young” is relentlessly sleazy and politically dubious, but not many people will sit through it long enough for its exploitative aspects to be an issue. Wallowing in the freedom and the budget that Amazon has given him, Mr Refn lets his hard-boiled saga trudge along at such a lethargic pace that you can leave the room and make a cup of tea in the gaps between the lines of murmured dialogue. It could be argued that the blank, affectless Martin has been numbed by the shock of his partner’s death, but the other characters seem to be just as dazed and deadpan as he is. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps Mr Refn should be congratulated on conjuring up such a murky atmosphere. Expertly shot by Darius Khondji and Diego Garcia, with a synthesiser-heavy score by Cliff Martinez, “Too Old To Die Young” is set in a world sapped of energy, a purgatory where shaded lamps and neon signs furnish nothing more than faint patches of light in the gloom; so maybe it is appropriate that the characters drift around like ghosts. Perhaps, too, Mr Refn should be congratulated on challenging the audience’s expectations with an anti-thriller, an avant-garde art installation to compare with Andy Warhol’s “Sleep” and “Empire”. The decision to combine bloody-minded perversity with a torpid tempo is certainly daring. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But, for Amazon, it was a mistake to allow Mr Refn to do what he wanted for 13 hours: “Too Old To Die Young” would have been a lot more compelling if it had been 11 hours shorter. After an episode or two, viewers may feel as if they are too old to keep watching.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Too Old To Die Young” is available on Amazon Prime Video now&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 21:41:17 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[To restore calm in Hong Kong, try democracy]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/20/to-restore-calm-in-hong-kong-try-democracy]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_ldp001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-20T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;T WAS PROBABLY&lt;/small&gt; the largest political protest ever staged in Hong Kong. It may have been the biggest in China’s history. Organisers reckon that about 1.9m people joined the demonstration on June 16th. Even during the unrest in Tiananmen Square three decades ago, no single protest approached that scale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The estimate may not be reliable. But there is no disputing the impact of this display of discontent, and others leading up to it. It came only a week after another demonstration of jaw-dropping size and four days after one that escalated into Hong Kong’s most violent disorder since the 1960s. The territory’s government and its overlords in Beijing could not have received a clearer message that Hong Kongers distrust their own leaders, as well as the central government’s (see China section). Protesters are demanding that Hong Kong’s chief executive, Carrie Lam, step down. Yet, even if she did, trust would still not be restored.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The unrest was triggered by a proposed law that would allow the extradition of criminal suspects from Hong Kong (where the rule of law still more or less prevails) to the Chinese mainland (where those who displease the ruling party have little chance of a fair trial). The law would also let Hong Kong’s courts seize assets connected with crimes on the mainland. At a news conference on June 18th Mrs Lam apologised for her handling of the bill (but gave no indication that she would resign). Earlier, just before the latest record-breaking demonstration, she had announced that the bill would be shelved indefinitely. All this was welcome, but it is not enough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This crisis has vividly shown how disillusioned Hong Kongers have become. It was different in 2003, when hundreds of thousands of people took to the streets in protest against a proposed anti-sedition law. Then the Communist Party had reason to hope that it could defuse the problem by allowing Hong Kong to shelve the bill, and encouraging the unpopular chief executive, Tung Chee-hwa, to resign (he did so in 2005). At the time, many people in Hong Kong still thought that the party would eventually fulfil its pledge to give them more democracy. In the meantime they could grudgingly put up with the appointment system, which ensured that Mr Tung’s successor was loyal to the government in Beijing. For his first few months in office the new man, Donald Tsang, enjoyed strong public support. Some pro-democracy politicians even felt hopeful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their optimism faded as the party’s intentions became clearer. During the “Umbrella Movement” of 2014, when protesters staged weeks of sit-ins to press for free and fair elections to the post of chief executive, China’s leaders dug in their heels. They made it plain that the “universal suffrage” Hong Kong had been promised would mean only the chance to vote for someone the party considers loyal. That is why Hong Kongers are without illusion today. They see Mrs Lam, who took over in 2017, as the party’s stooge—as they will see her successor, too. Without democracy, or a credible promise of it, no leaders in the territory will be seen as legitimate, severely limiting their ability to govern.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China’s leader, Xi Jinping, therefore has a stark choice. He can keep Hong Kong’s political system as it is and carry on trying to stifle the freedoms that Hong Kongers otherwise enjoy. The result would be more protests and probably more violence. Businesspeople would become more jittery, and Hong Kong’s reputation as a safe base from which to trade with the mainland would be at risk. Or Mr Xi can offer Hong Kong hope again, by setting out a timetable for real democratic reform. “We have to have the confidence that Hong Kong people can manage Hong Kong well,” goes a mantra of China’s leaders. It is time to let its people try. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Leaders&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;China’s chance&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 21:41:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cleaning up nuclear waste is an obvious task for robots]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/06/20/cleaning-up-nuclear-waste-is-an-obvious-task-for-robots]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_std001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-20T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;S&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;OME PEOPLE&lt;/small&gt; worry about robots taking work away from human beings, but there are a few jobs that even these sceptics admit most folk would not want. One is cleaning up radioactive waste, particularly when it is inside a nuclear power station—and especially if the power station in question has suffered a recent accident.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those who do handle radioactive material must first don protective suits that are inherently cumbersome and are further encumbered by the air hoses needed to allow the wearer to breathe. Even then their working hours are strictly limited, in order to avoid prolonged exposure to radiation and because operating in the suits is exhausting. Moreover, some sorts of waste are too hazardous for even the besuited to approach safely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, send in the robots? Unfortunately that is far from simple, for most robots are not up to the task. This became clear after events in 2011 at the Fukushima Daiichi nuclear power plant in Japan, which suffered a series of meltdowns after its safety systems failed following a tsunami. The site at Fukushima has turned into something of a graveyard for those robots dispatched into it to monitor radiation levels and start cleaning things up. Many got stuck, broke down or had their circuits fried by the intense radiation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Intelligence test&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stopping such things happening again is part of the work of the National Centre for Nuclear Robotics (&lt;small&gt;NCNR&lt;/small&gt;). This is a collaborative effort involving several British universities. It is led by Rustam Stolkin of the University of Birmingham, and its purpose is to improve the routine use of robotics in nuclear power stations as well as to ensure that robotic trips into irradiated areas are less likely to end up as suicide missions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One problem with the robots dispatched into the ruins of Fukushima Daiichi was that they were not particularly clever. Most were operated by someone twiddling joysticks at a safe distance. Such machines are awkward to steer and their arms are tricky to move accurately when viewed via a video screen. Dr Stolkin reckons the answer is to equip them with artificial intelligence (&lt;small&gt;AI&lt;/small&gt;), so that they can operate autonomously.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nuclear industry, though, is extremely conservative and not yet prepared to let autonomous robots loose within its facilities. So, for the time being at least, &lt;small&gt;AI&lt;/small&gt; will be used to assist human operators. For example, instead of relying on a remote human operator to manipulate all its controls, an &lt;small&gt;AI&lt;/small&gt;-equipped robot faced with a pile of different objects to move would employ a camera to understand those objects’ shapes and positions relative to one another. It could then plan how best to grasp each object and move it to, say, an appropriately designed disposal skip without it colliding with anything else in the vicinity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A human being would remain in overall control of the process via a motorised joystick that exerts forces on the operator’s hand similar to those he or she would feel by actually grasping the object. But although the operator still uses the joystick to move the robot’s arm to carry out a particular task, it is the &lt;small&gt;AI&lt;/small&gt; which takes care of the details. It makes sure the arm swings in exactly the right direction and picks things up properly. Such an arrangement has already been successfully tested at the Springfields nuclear-fuel facility in north-west England. It was used to cut up contaminated steel with a high-powered laser.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other members of &lt;small&gt;NCNR&lt;/small&gt; are examining different aspects of the problem. At the University of Bristol, Tom Scott leads a group working on means for robots to identify materials, including various sorts of plastic, from the “fingerprints” provided by the distinctive ways they scatter laser light. At Queen Mary, a college of the University of London, Kaspar Althoefe’s team is working on radiation-resilient tactile sensors for robots’ fingers. Gerhard Neumann of the University of Lincoln is developing advanced navigation systems. And to ensure robots’ circuits don’t get frazzled, Klaus McDonald-Maier at the University of Essex is developing electronics toughened against the effects of radiation, including circuits that automatically detect and correct errors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Besides helping run nuclear power stations, all this will also assist with the growing need to clean up and recycle nuclear waste—and not just because of disasters like Fukushima. Early members of the nuclear club, such as America, Britain, France and Russia, have accumulated a vast legacy of the stuff. In Britain alone, some 4.9m tonnes of contaminated nuclear material are in need of safe disposal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A lot of this is found at one of the most hazardous industrial sites in Europe, Sellafield, also in north-west England. Sellafield began producing plutonium for bombs in 1947. In 1956 the world’s first commercial-sized civil nuclear power station opened there. The site went on to become a centre for reprocessing nuclear fuel. Cleaning up Sellafield’s decaying buildings and nuclear-waste storage facilities will take decades. Robots with autonomous abilities would greatly hurry that process along.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nor is it just inside buildings that robots can help. This April Dr Scott and his colleagues at Bristol completed an aerial survey of the Red Forest in the Chernobyl exclusion zone in Ukraine using robotic drones. Even 33 years after the accident at the site’s number four reactor, they found previously undetected radiation hotspots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike a neat and tidy factory, where robots can be programmed to undertake repetitive tasks without any surprises, decontaminating an old nuclear site requires the ability to operate in an unstructured environment. In some cases, operators may not even know what they might find inside a building. Devising artificial intelligence clever enough to deal with all this will be tricky. But if Dr Stolkin and his colleagues succeed, their efforts are likely to have a wider impact, stretching even into the world of jobs that people are, at the moment at least, content to do themselves.&lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Science and technology&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Cybernetic skivvies&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 21:41:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[African swine fever spreads to South-East Asia]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/20/african-swine-fever-spreads-to-south-east-asia]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_asp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-20T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HERE ARE&lt;/small&gt; few dishes that a typical Filipino, Thai or Vietnamese would not consider improved by the addition of pork. What better to stuff a squid with, or garnish a bowl of steaming noodles, or simply spit-roast and scoff? No wonder, then, that South-East Asia is home to more than 83m pigs. But the outbreak of African swine fever that has swept through China in recent months is now spreading across the region. Its governments are likely to find it no easier than China’s to contain the disease, which is harmless to humans but typically fatal to pigs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Swine fever first crossed the border from China into Vietnam in February. It has gradually worked its way south, and in April spread to Cambodia (see map). Thailand fears it is next. In fact, the disease could already be there or elsewhere: experts worry that monitoring and reporting are patchy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190622_asm939.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pigs catch the disease from each other, from contaminated surfaces, from ticks and from food (slop containing infected pork or pig’s blood). There is also a risk that farmed pigs may be infected by wild ones, and vice versa. Those transporting not just live pigs, but also pork, across borders risk introducing swine fever to new areas. Meanwhile, pork prices have jumped more than 40% compared with a year ago and analysts expect overall inflation to rise in Vietnam and Cambodia as a result.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Culling swine is one of the main ways officials hope to curb the disease. Vietnam has slaughtered 2.5m pigs, twice as many as China. Bans on the import of pigs and pork are another tactic. But many of the region’s pig farms are tiny, as in China. Their owners cannot afford to erect special fencing or buy commercial feed. The temptation, if they suspect their pigs are infected, is to kill or sell them quickly and quietly, to save themselves from financial ruin. Although the Vietnamese government compensates farmers who report sick pigs that are subsequently culled, the fear of slow or low payments can still put farmers off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, international co-ordination, especially between governments and companies in South-East Asia’s pork industry, has been impressive, says Wantanee Kalpravidh of the Food and Agriculture Organisation, a &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt; agency. She lauds a scheme to send Thai pork to Cambodia to meet demand at affordable prices—on carefully cleaned and monitored vehicles—to discourage the smuggling of possibly contaminated meat from Vietnam. Somkuan Choowatanapakorn of Charoen Pokphand Foods, a big Thai agribusiness that handles lots of pork, says the company has “taken steps already” to train farmers to recognise and respond to the disease’s symptoms. He adds that contingency plans for an outbreak are also in place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite such efforts, the scale of the porcine plague in China means that South-East Asia will probably struggle with it for as long as its neighbour does. A working vaccine is still a long way off. It is hard to see what can save the region’s bacon. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Asia&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Swine on the line&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 21:41:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The UN revises down its population forecasts]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/22/the-un-revises-down-its-population-forecasts]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_gdc100.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-22T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190622_GDC100_population1/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE UNITED NATIONS&lt;/small&gt; is the world’s most important watcher of human tides. Its demographers have a good record of predicting global population change, although they have made mistakes about individual countries. So it is worth paying attention when the &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt; revises its figures, as it does every few years. The latest bulletin is especially surprising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent revisions have sent the projected global population upwards. The one released on June 17th cuts it back. The &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt; now thinks the world will contain a little over 9.7bn people in 2050 and just under 10.9bn in 2100. The first figure is 37m lower than the &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt; forecast two years ago. The latter is 309m lower—almost an America’s worth of people revised away.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Birth rates are falling faster than expected in some developing countries. In the late 1980s Kenya had a fertility rate of 6.5, implying a woman could expect to have that many children. Two years ago the &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt; reckoned Kenya’s fertility rate would drop to 2.1 (the point at which the population sustains itself naturally) only in the late 2070s. Because of new data, it now thinks Kenya will reach that point a decade earlier. Uganda also looks less fecund. A smaller cut to India’s fertility rate has a big effect on the global population forecasts because India has so many people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190622_GDC100population2/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt;’s population model assumes that countries with fertility rates well below two will bounce back a little. Even in countries where babies have become rare, most people continue to believe that the ideal family contains two or even three kids. But the recovery keeps failing to happen in some places, so the demographers have changed their forecasts in a second way. They now expect some countries with extremely low birth rates, such as Italy, Japan and South Korea, to stay that way for years. Korea, which has a fertility rate of just 1.1, is now expected to have 30m people in 2100—down from 51m today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190622_GDC100population3/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another change has to do with death. Most people are living longer. The biggest improvement is in east and southern Africa, where &lt;small&gt;HIV&lt;/small&gt; is being treated better. In America, however, the opioid epidemic has pushed up the death rate, especially for men. The chance of a 15-year-old boy dying by the age of 50 is now higher in America than in Bangladesh. It would be nice if the American forecast, at least, proved to be too pessimistic. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Sources: UN; Gapminder&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Graphic detail&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Missing millions&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 20:40:25 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>