<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[An underwhelming start to the “ultimate” Israeli-Palestinian deal]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/25/an-underwhelming-start-to-the-ultimate-israeli-palestinian-deal]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_map503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-25T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT COULD have been Davos, or any of the other conferences on the annual circuit for the world’s wealthy. Jared Kushner, the son-in-law and a senior adviser to America’s president, took the stage to offer his vision for solving the Israeli-Palestinian conflict. The combatants, he lectured, were “trapped in an inefficient framework of the past”. Their obstinacy is a barrier to turning the West Bank and Gaza into “a bustling commercial and tourist centre”. If 70 years of warfare would simply come to a halt, “we can turn this region from a victim of past conflicts into a model for commerce and advancement across the world.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before he took office in 2017 Donald Trump vowed to broker the “ultimate deal” between Israelis and Palestinians. To oversee the effort he chose, Mr Kushner, a real-estate developer with no experience in diplomacy or the Middle East. The result has been about as expected. There is still no political plan for resolving the underlying conflict and its many thorny issues: borders, refugees or the status of Jerusalem, and the very notion of Palestinian statehood. Its release has been repeatedly delayed; diplomats hint that it may remain on the shelf until Mr Trump’s second term, if he wins one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead Mr Kushner organised this two-day confab in Bahrain. Dubbed the “Peace to Prosperity” workshop, the centrepiece is a 96-page plan that pledges $50bn worth of investment in Palestine and neighbouring countries after a peace deal. The document, to be fair, is impressive in scope. It suggests projects to boost agriculture and tourism, fix Palestine’s infrastructure and improve governance. All of this would be funded by a mix of grants, concessional loans and private-sector money, from the wealthy Gulf states and elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Missing amidst all this detail, however, is anything about the Israeli occupation, in its various forms, of the West Bank and Gaza Strip, or of schism between the Palestinian leaders in the two territories. The plan presupposes that the noxious politics of the conflict have simply vanished. Mr Kushner proposes spending $5bn to connect the West Bank and Gaza, for example. Israel has undertaken to do this for years but never has, because the link is not simply a matter of building a monorail. It raises political and security questions for Israel. Another proposal calls for $2bn to give the Palestinians 5G wireless infrastructure. Entrepreneurs would be thrilled. But there is no mention of how to overcome objections from the Israeli army, which let the West Bank install 3G only last year (a decade after the rest of the world).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As it stands, then, the plan is thoroughly unrealistic. That is the point, Mr Kushner’s supporters argue. It is meant to offer the Palestinians a peace dividend, an incentive to accept his (perhaps) forthcoming political vision. They certainly need economic help. Unemployment in the West Bank is 17%. In Gaza it is as high as 55%. Adjusted for inflation, GDP per person is almost unchanged from 20 years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But to the Palestinians this smells like a bribe from a hostile president. Mr Trump cut all American aid to them—even $25m in funding for hospitals in East Jerusalem that treat, among other things, children with cancer. He overturned decades of precedent to recognise Jerusalem as Israel’s capital. And aides hint that the political plan will give the Palestinians far less than the sovereign state along the pre-1967 borders that they demand. America’s ambassador to Israel, David Friedman, said this month that Israel had the right to annex some territory in the West Bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So the Palestinians are boycotting the event. Their president, Mahmoud Abbas, refused to send anyone from his government. “The deal of shame will go to hell,” he said in May. The private sector also declined invitations. Of the 5m Palestinians in the occupied territories, the only publicly-confirmed attendee is Ashraf al-Jabari, a former secret-police officer who has turned into a businessman and has cultivated unusual ties with Israeli settlers in his home town of Hebron. He also has a history of writing bum cheques&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Few of the other attendees are enthusiastic. “We tried to find the lowest level of representation that wouldn’t be offensive,” quips a European diplomat in Tel Aviv. Jordan and Egypt sent only their deputy finance ministers. With the Palestinians boycotting, Arab states were reluctant to share a stage with Israeli officials. But the latter weren’t invited either because of Arab misgivings (though some Israeli businessmen did come). Even press coverage is limited: organisers did not allow most foreign journalists covering the Middle East to attend. They did accredit reporters from six Israeli outlets, who have sent slightly fawning dispatches. The country’s largest newspaper, Israel Hayom, which backs both Mr Trump and the Israeli prime minister, Binyamin Netanyahu, dubbed Bahrain the “island of hope”, an odd appellation for a kingdom that crushed a popular uprising in 2011.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And that, perhaps, points to the real outcome of the workshop. It is the most public manifestation of a long and mostly private rapprochement between Israel and the Gulf states, one the Trump administration is keen to promote. The event will do nothing to end the Israeli-Palestinian conflict. But it is another sign that the Gulf states are looking to move past that conflict. Though they are not quite ready to recognise Israel, they see it as an important regional power, an ally against a shared threat from Iran. The Palestinians have far less to offer. “All we have is our moral power,” says Mkhaimer Abu Saada, a political analyst in Gaza. That still counts for something—but less and less with each passing day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 04:41:07 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is the most dangerous drug?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/25/what-is-the-most-dangerous-drug]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_woc294.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHY IS ALCOHOL legal but many other intoxicants not? That question is the subject of a report published today by the Global Commission on Drug Policy, an independent group of 26 former presidents and other bigwigs. They conclude that, as far as the scientific evidence is concerned, current drug laws have no rhyme or reason to them. The commission blames the UN’s drug classification system, which sorts some 300 psychoactive substances into “schedules” according to their harms and benefits. Some, such as morphine, have medical uses. Others, such as psilocybin (the active ingredient in magic mushrooms), are used mostly recreationally. Drugs without any apparent medical utility are automatically placed in the most dangerous category—and subjected to the strictest criminal penalties—regardless of the risk they pose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flaws of the UN’s system have been evident for years. In 2010 a group of British drug experts ranked 20 popular intoxicating substances on 16 physical, psychological and social harms, including those done to non-users, such as crime and family breakdown. Alcohol came out as the most harmful, followed by heroin and crack cocaine. Psychedelic “party” drugs, including ecstasy, LSD and mushrooms, were deemed mostly benign—with harm scores less than half that of tobacco—despite being lumped with cocaine and heroin in the UN’s classification system. This ranking is not without its own idiosyncrasies, many of which reflect how drugs are currently used and regulated. Alcohol’s position at the top is partly the result of its widespread use, which causes greater harms to others (crack cocaine is considered the most harmful drug for the user). Drugs such as heroin, meanwhile, would be ranked lower if users could always buy an unadulterated dose, and did not have to resort to sharing needles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Designing laws for drugs that are consistent with their dangers and benefits requires predicting how drug markets will respond. Difficult as that may be, it is the way forward, argues the Global Commission. The zero-tolerance approach adopted by many governments has led to a host of social problems, including soaring prison costs and ill-health. “It is past high time to accept the fact that a society without drugs is an illusion,” the report argues. Regulating drugs in a more sensible manner would make them safer—and not just for those who take them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 03:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bargaining chips—the US-China tech war]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/25/bargaining-chips-the-us-china-tech-war]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_blm508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-25T19:00:56Z&quot;&gt;Jun 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE TRADE war between &lt;strong&gt;America and China&lt;/strong&gt; is intensifying after America blacklisted five more Chinese technology entities. Will this jeopardise any talk of a trade deal &lt;b&gt;at the upcoming G20 summit&lt;/b&gt;? Could low-denomination treasury bills help Italy’s cash-strapped economy? Also, a new way of working called &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/13/for-the-future-look-to-the-past&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;“ghost work”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Phil Coggan hosts. Runtime: 17 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/0d818142-e5b7-4da0-927b-42a380d79b62&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 02:40:24 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Overmatched policymakers risk toppling the world economy into trouble]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/25/overmatched-policymakers-risk-toppling-the-world-economy-into-trouble]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_fnd000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE GLOBAL economic mood has taken to whipsawing between gloom and optimism. It can be hard to keep pace. This newspaper warned readers to prepare for “the next recession” in 2015 and 2018, pausing in 2017 to hail “the world economy’s surprising rise”. Lately, the periods of alarm and alacrity seem to have shortened. Markets began 2019 on the rebound and then took fright—only to surge in recent weeks. It is tempting to see the swings as mistaken attempts to find narratives in noise. But they have been accompanied by very real economic wobbles. Trade growth slumped in 2015, rebounded and is now decelerating. Global output, as reflected in measures of purchasing managers’ activity, bounced along with market gyrations, sinking in 2015 and lurching upward in 2017 before falling this year to levels not seen since the depths of the euro-area crisis. Rather than noise, the mood swings reflect investors’ attempts to work out which of two very different equilibria an unsettled global economy will land on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You might suppose that such uncertainty would be the norm. Though highly integrated, the global economy lacks a centralised, stabilising hand, like a national Treasury or central bank. During the financial crisis, the members of the G20 managed an impressive degree of policy co-ordination. But the desire to co-operate has rather waned since then. America’s Federal Reserve has some ability to call a global tune; Silvia Miranda-Agrippino of Northwestern University and Hélène Rey of the London Business School argue that American monetary policy strongly influences the global financial cycle. Similarly Emine Boz and Gita Gopinath of the IMF and Mikkel Plagborg-Moller of Princeton University reckon that fluctuations in the dollar have an enormous influence on volume of global trade. But in a world of flexible exchange rates countries should still enjoy plenty of room to go their own way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The world’s problem, however, seems less that national governments are working at cross-purposes, and more that policymakers are torn between incompatible aims. Take central banks. The world’s monetary maestros are eager to leave behind the near-zero interest rates that have prevailed since the financial crisis. But the soft spots into which the global economy keeps stumbling suggest that this desire may be inconsistent with steady, robust growth. Last year the Fed raised its benchmark interest rate by a percentage point, to 2.4%, and reckoned it would rise above 3% by the end of 2019. After its meeting on June 19th, however, Jerome Powell, its chairman, all but told markets to expect rate cuts later this year, “in light of increased uncertainties”. Other central banks have also chosen to beat a hasty retreat. The European Central Bank (ECB) ended its programme of stimulative asset purchases in December 2018 and suggested that its policy rates could rise in 2019. But at its June meeting it too abandoned talk of rate rises for discussions of the need for additional stimulus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Governments are likewise conflicted. China’s leaders want to rebalance their economy away from excessive investment and to shrink the role of state-owned firms. They keenly feel the need to depend less on rapid growth in credit. Yet both domestic tranquillity and the ability to project power abroad depend on economic growth. Whenever steps toward economic reform cause too rapid a slowdown, China’s government quickly returns to stimulus. In response to the sudden slowing late last year, it flooded the economy with credit, zapping the global economy with a jolt of energy. New data reveal that China’s total debt-to-GDP ratio, excluding the financial sector, leapt by more than five percentage points in the first quarter of 2019, to nearly 250% of GDP.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile President Donald Trump is trying to harangue the Fed into a more accommodative monetary policy in the run-up to next year’s elections. But he is unwilling to abandon his belligerent approach to trade relations. At a meeting of the G20 on June 28th and 29th he and Xi Jinping, his Chinese counterpart, are expected to hold talks regarding their intensifying trade war. Unless they resolve a number of significant disputes America will probably extend its tariffs to an additional $300bn of Chinese imports. So far America’s tariffs have probably had only modest macroeconomic effects, though their impact is growing. But markets’ tendency to reel in the face of trade-war escalations suggests a growing concern that the present is prologue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stick a fork in it&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;World leaders must always manage trade-offs between competing aims. So why are policy conflicts unsettling markets just now? Except during financial crises (and none appears imminent), economic growth is rarely so balanced on a knife-edge. But interest rates around the world remain very low, leaving little tolerance for policy correction. In the euro area both short-term and long-term interest rates are close to or even below zero. New ECB easing, if it occurs, will mostly help the economy by pushing down the value of the euro and boosting European exporters, at the expense of firms elsewhere. America’s position is not much better. When markets were expecting rate increases, the Fed could give a sagging economy a boost simply by delaying them. But markets now expect the Fed to cut rates by at least 0.75 percentage points during the next year. It can either disappoint them and risk adding to pessimism, or move rates much of the way back to zero.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Any misstep by Mr Trump or Mr Xi thus leaves central banks hard-pressed to keep economies on an even keel. And a central-bank slip-up, such as one interest-rate rise too many, increases the strain on already-conflicted governments. As slackening global demand crimps purchases of Chinese exports, for instance, the trade-off between domestic deleveraging and robust growth in Beijing becomes much starker. The global mood has not yet settled, meaning that a happy outcome remains possible. But if policymakers do not decide soon to put growth ahead of their other goals, the next turn toward pessimism could be decisive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 02:40:22 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why William Hogarth’s polemics were so successful]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/25/why-william-hogarths-polemics-were-so-successful]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_BKP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-25T16:24:30Z&quot;&gt;Jun 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A CAT struggles as a dog tears out its guts. A group of children smirk as they hang two more tabbies by their tails from a post. Other figures scribble graffiti, or torture a dog with a cudgel. The violence in William Hogarth’s sketch, made in 1750, almost feels senseless, even as it is softened with humour (a well-dressed boy peddles pies amid the chaos). But it did contain a warning: later pictures show one of the boys graduating from abusing dogs to beating horses, before becoming a ruthless murderer. He eventually ends up dead—in a drawing subtitled “Reward of Cruelty” his corpse is splayed out for medical research. Violence, Hogarth is saying, starts young. Get a taste for it as a child and the gallows might be your fate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The series, “Four Stages of Cruelty”, features in a small but pithy new exhibition of Hogarth’s work at the Morgan Library and Museum in New York. “Cruelty and Humour” never loses sight of the art’s brutality, nor its wryness. One early image shows the aftermath of the South Sea Bubble in 1720, a stock scam which ruined many Britons. Hogarth shows personified figures of “Honour” and “Honesty” being thrashed by “Self-Interest” and “Villainy”; a merry-go-round of corruption reflects the scale of the disaster as a priest, a prostitute and a nobleman all ride together. In “Gin Lane” (1751, pictured) a sallow alcoholic lies in the gutter, dropping her baby; a man gnaws a bone alongside a dog. There can be few better warnings against the dangers of cheap liquor in art.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It might be tempting to consign Hogarth and his pictures, with their powdered wigs and random barbarity, to history. That would be a mistake, Jennifer Tonkovich, the show’s curator, says: it should be impossible to live in New York and “divorce yourself from thinking about these issues”. Just as wealthy Londoners once gobbled up townhouses in Mayfair, “never to be met with” in the smelly neighbourhoods further east (to quote the anonymous author of one 18th-century book), New York has Hudson Yards. With its 720,000 square-foot luxury mall and $800-a-cut barbers, the development has been dubbed a “fantasy city” for the rich. Gin addicts might be a rare sight on Madison Avenue, but extreme poverty is not. Around 60,000 New Yorkers currently sleep in municipal shelters, and homelessness in the city has reached its highest level since the Great Depression. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hogarth drew the injustices of his age in order to point his contemporaries towards a better London. The visceral and scatological humour was key, Ms Tonkovich says, as “looking at a picture of virtue is not much fun. On the other hand, looking at a picture of vice can motivate people.” With Henry Fielding, a magistrate, satirist and friend, Hogarth argued that new legislation was needed to tidy up the streets. Thanks in part to their lobbying, Parliament passed the Gin Act in 1751. Among other things, it promoted the sale of beer—and the wholesome civic life conjured by Hogarth in “Beer Street”, a mellow ale-soaked foil to the hard spirits that ruined “Gin Lane”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All this has useful lessons for today’s activists. Straight moralising is not just unpopular: it may be ineffective. Follow Hogarth in spiking your polemic with humour, however, and views might soften. A recent study found people felt stronger support for Syrian refugees after watching political satire compared to similar stories on CNN. It helped, the researchers added, that being persuaded felt like fun. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Tonkovich thinks the tone of Hannah Gadsby, a Australian comedian, is particularly effective. In her comedy special “Nanette” she offered a darkly funny exploration of growing up gay in Tasmania. “I think most people who watch it would reflect on times that they’ve been cruel or unfair, or harsh or uncharitable,” Ms Tonkovich says. “There is something about having that held up in a naked, obvious way that does make you reflect.” This is true of Hogarth, too. His pictures of urban squalor can still make the viewer smile, and think.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Hogarth: Cruelty and Humour” continues at the Morgan Library and Museum until September 22nd&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 00:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Supreme Court strikes down a bar on offensive trademarks]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/25/the-supreme-court-strikes-down-a-bar-on-offensive-trademarks]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_USP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-25T08:34:40Z&quot;&gt;Jun 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ERIK BRUNETTI (pictured), the proprietor of a streetwear brand called FUCT, says the name is an acronym for “Friends U Can’t Trust”. The United States Patent and Trademark Office (PTO) saw it rather differently. FUCT, it said, was “highly offensive” and “vulgar” with “decidedly negative sexual connotations”. Pointing to a provision in the Lanham Act that bars the registration of “immoral or scandalous” marks, the agency declined to bless the brand name. Mr Brunetti took the PTO to court and won; the agency’s director then asked the Supreme Court to review the case. On June 24th, Justice Elena Kagan wrote &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/18pdf/18-302_e29g.pdf&quot;&gt;an opinion&lt;/a&gt; siding with Mr Brunetti.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She did so for a straightforward reason: for years, the Supreme Court has interpreted the First Amendment to prohibit discrimination “against speech based on the ideas or opinions it conveys”. Like a cousin of the rule the justices &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2017/06/21/the-supreme-court-says-offensive-trademarks-are-protected-speech&quot;&gt;dispatched in 2017&lt;/a&gt;—a bar on “disparaging” trademarks—the “immoral or scandalous” no-no violates the constitution because, Justice Kagan wrote, it “disfavours certain ideas”. It is fine to refuse to register a mark because it too closely resembles another or because it is “merely descriptive” (two of a handful of other criteria in the Lanham Act), but turning down an application because the term communicates an edgy idea undermines the freedom of speech.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The heart of Justice Kagan’s opinion in &lt;em&gt;Iancu v Brunetti&lt;/em&gt; is her analysis of immorality and scandalousness, the two concepts the PTO relied upon to deny FUCT a registration. “When is expressive material ‘immoral’?” she asked. “According to a standard definition, when it is &amp;#x27;inconsistent with rectitude, purity, or good morals’; ‘wicked’; or ‘vicious’.” The Lanham Act thus approves of marks that “champion society’s sense of rectitude and morality” but rejects those that challenge social norms. That is blatant discrimination based on the slant of a speaker’s ideas. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Up to this point, Justice Kagan’s analysis commanded a unanimous vote. All nine justices agreed that the bar on immoral marks must be thrown out. But an interesting divide opened over how to conceive of the “scandalous” half of the rule under review. For Justice Kagan and five of her colleagues, “scandalous” is just as problematic as “immoral”: it applies when a message is “shocking to the sense of truth, decency or propriety” or “offensive”, she wrote. The Lanham Act empowers bureaucrats to approve of marks “aligned with conventional moral standards” and to reject “those provoking offense and condemnation”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But three members of the court—Justices Stephen Breyer and Sonia Sotomayor and John Roberts, the chief—opted to read “scandalous” more narrowly. In an opinion partially concurring with and partially dissenting from Justice Kagan’s ruling, Justice Sotomayor warned the decision “will beget unfortunate results”. The PTO will no longer have any basis for turning down marks “containing the most vulgar, profane, or obscene words and images imaginable”. This situation could have been prevented, she suggested, if the court had understood scandalous to mean “simply indecent, shocking or generally offensive”. Alleged immorality should not be a basis for denying an application, Justice Sotomayor acknowledged, because that has to do with the content of ideas. But scandalous marks should be proscribable “because of the mode in which they are expressed”. The First Amendment protects your right to communicate &lt;em&gt;what&lt;/em&gt; you want in a mark, in other words, but it doesn’t require the PTO to bless every &lt;em&gt;way&lt;/em&gt; you might want to say it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chief Justice Roberts did not sign Justice Sotomayor’s opinion but went out of his way to praise her “narrowing construction” of the Lanham Act and to agree with her point that there is no First Amendment right to vulgar trademark protection. Businesses are free to use whatever names they like, whether or not the mark is registered, but it is fine for Congress to deny extra benefits to those who express themselves rudely. Justice Breyer joined Justice Sotomayor’s 19-page opinion and added a concurrence/dissent of his own urging a more pragmatic, less rule-bound approach to limning the boundaries of protected expression. “The First Amendment is not the Tax Code”, he quipped. Better to use “rules of thumb” than formal categories and to ask whether regulations serve worthy goals without clamping down too much on expression. The government is right to “disincentivise” the use of vulgarity in commerce by withholding extra benefits from those who spout them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All the justices seem to agree that Congress can write a new law targeting flat-out profanity or vulgarity as long as only modes of expression—not ideas themselves—are cabined. But as Justice Samuel Alito wrote, the justices “are not legislators and cannot substitute a new statute for the one now in force” on their own. If Congress does not accept this invitation—which seems probable given the Senate’s penchant for not legislating—will America’s malls and parks soon be filled with trademarked vulgarities and epithets? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The warning from Justice Sotomayor that there will now be a “rush to register such trademarks” seems overblown. There are already quite a few “viscerally offensive words and images” on the roster of registered marks. “FCUK” is there, as is “FWORD”. “FUCK BITCHES GET MONEY” has even earned a bureaucrat’s blessing. In fact, a search for the four-letter word beginning with “f” on the PTO’s database &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://tmsearch.uspto.gov/bin/gate.exe?f=searchss&amp;amp;state=4806:3wltxh.1.1&quot;&gt;yields&lt;/a&gt; 383 relevant records. Few people—beyond those who read deeply into this case’s court filings—have encountered these terms, and nobody will face them out shopping or on public transport. Along with its other virtues, the decision in &lt;em&gt;Iancu&lt;/em&gt; should not boost those odds very much at all. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 00:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Killings and claims of an attempted coup rock Ethiopia]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/25/killings-and-claims-of-an-attempted-coup-rock-ethiopia]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_blp904.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A YEAR AGO, on June 23rd 2018, Ethiopia’s newly-inaugurated prime minister, Abiy Ahmed, took to the podium wearing a bright green T-shirt. Smiling and waving he offered hope to the tens of thousands of people who had flocked to a rally in the capital, Addis Ababa, in support of his promise to bring democracy to a country that has seen precious little of it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost to the day a year later he again addressed the nation, this time on national television wearing army uniform to declare, stony faced, that his government had just thwarted a coup. It was a sharp reminder of the fragility of his democratic revolution.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Abiy said that the putsch had originated in the northern region of Amhara, Ethiopia’s second-biggest by population, and was the work of General Asamnew Tsige, Amhara’s head of security. The prime minister’s office claimed that General Asamnew was responsible for an attack on government offices in the regional capital, Bahir Dar, on June 22nd in which the Amhara region’s president, Ambachew Mekonnen, and other senior officials were shot dead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a separate attack in Addis Ababa, the army’s chief of staff, Seare Mekonnen, was allegedly shot and killed in his home by a bodyguard. Also killed in this attack was a retired general who had been visiting. The government said both attacks were linked, and claimed the coup was an attempt “to scupper the hard won peace of the region”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since then the government has shut off the internet and released few details of the plot. But, from what little information has emerged the incidents look more like an unplanned outbreak of violence than a calculated attempt to seize power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;General Asamnew was a former political prisoner sentenced in 2009 for his alleged role in another failed coup. He was released and appointed by Abiy last year in an attempt to reach out to the opposition and include it in positions of power. But General Asamnew provoked alarm with his strident ethnic nationalism and talk of defending Amhara territory against incursions by members of Ethiopia’s other ethnic groups. Underpinning such concerns has been a worrying spread of ethnic violence and nationalism across the country as Abiy has lifted the repressive hand of one-party rule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Abiy’s ascent to power was fuelled by rising nationalism among his own ethnic group, the Oromo. They make up about one-third of the population and had felt dominated by the Tigrayans, a group that accounts for less than one-tenth of the population but that had largely called the shots in government since the toppling of a Marxist dictatorship, the Derg, in 1991. Rising Oromo nationalism has been mirrored in other groups, including the Tigrayans and the Amhara, who make up about one-quarter of Ethiopia’s population and had once ruled the roost under its last emperor, Haile Selassie, deposed in 1974.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;General Asamnew raised further eyebrows when he began strengthening the region’s paramilitary forces, including a special police unit that answered directly to him. It was not just the federal government that seemingly wanted to clip his wings but also Ambachew, the region’s more moderate president. People familiar with the events on June 22nd say that Ambachew had called a meeting to discuss ways of stopping General Asamnew from recruiting more people for his paramilitary forces. The meeting was also intended to discuss firing him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seems that General Asamnew sent in men from his special police force to the meeting; there are also some suggestions that he may have been present outside the building at the time. It is not clear whether he intended for his men to open fire and kill the region’s president or the confrontation spiralled bloodily out of control. General Asamnew fled immediately afterwards—a further indication that this may not have been an organised putsch—but was tracked down and killed by the army in Amhara two days later, according to the government.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are still many unanswered questions, including how events in Bahir Dar may have been connected to the killing of the head of the national army in his home in Addis Ababa. If the incidents were indeed linked, as the government claims, that would imply some degree of forethought by the plotters and point to the possibility of a wider conspiracy. If that is the case then it would suggest that Abiy faces a threat from elements of the national army.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The political ramifications may be far reaching in a country that hitherto stood out for offering hope of political and economic reform in Africa. Some now expect a campaign to suppress “nationalist” forces in Amhara, including youth groups and opposition movements. This in turn may stoke further resentment in the region, in which many young people are beginning to feel discriminated against by Abiy and his Oromo faction of the ruling coalition. Whatever the exact details of the events on June 22nd, the euphoria that greeted Abiy’s rise to power a year ago is beginning to seem a distant memory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 20:40:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“It reads like a report from a consulting firm”—Kushner’s peace plan]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/25/it-reads-like-a-report-from-a-consulting-firm-kushners-peace-plan]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_blm503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-25T11:20:09Z&quot;&gt;Jun 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TENSIONS BETWEEN Iran and America are distracting from Jared Kushner’s long-awaited Israeli-Palestinian peace plan. It’s got plenty of dollar signs, but no sign yet of a political solution. We ask why &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/05/23/argentinas-former-president-wants-to-be-veep&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Argentina’s former president&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; is now running for vice-president, and whether Argentines will want more of her populism. And, be careful what you tweet if you’re heading to America; more and more, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/06/06/foreign-travellers-to-america-face-scrutiny-of-their-online-activity&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;border officials&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; are watching. Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/a30a8787-0780-402f-956a-6cbac5cc7240&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 18:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Medical marijuana is not the way out of America’s opioid crisis]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/24/medical-marijuana-is-not-the-way-out-of-americas-opioid-crisis]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_USP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-24T18:58:34Z&quot;&gt;Jun 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WEEDMAPS, an app that allows cannabis users to find sellers and review their wares, advertises its services through “Weedfacts”—marijuana-promoting factoids on bus stops and billboards in Washington, DC, where recreational use has been decriminalised. The signs proclaim that the legalisation of cannabis improves property values and decreases teenage use and crime. Harmless advertising perhaps. But some of its signs also allege that cannabis helps protect against opioid addiction, which is killing nearly 50,000 Americans a year. “Cannabis has been shown to reduce opioid deaths 25%”, says one poster. If that claim seems too good to be true, that is probably because it is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea that cannabis legalisation—for both medical and recreational purposes—could seriously make a dent in America’s opioid crisis is common. This month, the state health commissioner of New York issued emergency regulations allowing anyone with an opioid addiction to obtain medical marijuana, calling it “a critical step in combating the deadly opioid epidemic affecting people across the state”. Illinois has introduced a similar programme. Yet the evidence behind the theory that legalising marijuana can help combat opioid addiction is thin. And the consequences of bad policy could be severe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The chief evidence for the theory is a paper published in the &lt;em&gt;Journal of the American Medical Association (JAMA)&lt;/em&gt;. Analysing the relationship between opioid overdose deaths and medical marijuana laws from 1999 to 2010, the authors found a strong negative association between the two. “States with medical cannabis laws had a 24.8% lower mean annual opioid overdose mortality rate compared with states without medical cannabis laws,” they wrote. They took pains to describe this as correlational and not causal. But their findings were not interpreted so carefully by cannabis advocates and some policymakers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recent paper by Chelsea Shover, an epidemiologist and a postdoctoral fellow at Stanford University, showed that this was a mistake. By simply extending the study period up to 2017—the time period during which the opioid crisis accelerated—she shows that the association between opioid deaths and medical marijuana legalisation flipped from strongly negative to strongly positive. Rather than the 25 percentage-point reduction in the opioid overdose mortality rate cited by cannabis promoters, the study shows a 23 percentage-point increase between 1999 and 2017. “One way to interpret that would be causally: To say that cannabis was saving people then, and is killing people now. But we don’t believe that,” says Ms Shover. “That’s one reason why it’s fraught to make policy decisions based on this data.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flawed interpretations of the original paper fell afoul of what statisticians call the ecological fallacy, when an inference is made about an individual based on statistical data for a group. Poorer states may be more likely to vote for Republicans, but that does not mean that poorer people are more likely to vote for the party, for example. There are very few individual-level studies, either observational or clinical, that would allow researchers to support the claim that access to marijuana limits addiction to opioids or successfully treats those recovering from addictions. The only individual-level analysis to date, a nationally representative observation study of 57,000 Americans, found that medical cannabis users were more likely to misuse prescription painkillers. This does not mean that marijuana-decriminalisation laws worsen opioid addiction—only that a lot more research is needed before policymakers make up their minds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is danger in haste. Opioid addiction is a chronic disorder characterised by repeated relapses. It is exceptionally hard to kick. People who receive medically-assisted treatment—generally methadone, buprenorphine or naltrexone—are much less likely to relapse than those who try mere abstention. But only one in five Americans with an opioid use disorder—the medical term for addiction—are currently receiving treatment. If people were to errantly substitute cannabis for one of the proven treatments, it could cause greater rates of relapse and more overdose deaths. “The suggestion that patients should self-substitute a drug (ie, cannabis) that has not been subjected to a single clinical trial for opioid addiction is irresponsible,” wrote Keith Humphreys and Richard Saitz, two experts on addiction in&lt;em&gt; JAMA&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This does not mean that decriminalising marijuana is a bad idea. Cannabis is probably not the panacea advocates claim, but it does not have the deleterious effects of other banned drugs like heroin or cocaine. There is solid evidence for the medical benefits of CBD, a non-psychoactive cannabis compound, for some forms of epilepsy. And enough patients report that cannabis relieves their pain for such claims to be taken seriously. But combating a crisis as urgent and widespread as the opioid epidemic requires responses that are proven to be effective. These include drastically increasing medically-assisted treatment, increasing the distribution of naloxone (which reverses fatal overdoses), and reducing the prescription of pain killers. Until these responses are prioritised, it is hard to justify turning to speculative—and possibly spurious—options.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 04:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Missouri’s only abortion clinic loses its licence]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/24/missouris-only-abortion-clinic-loses-its-licence]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_woc953.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-24T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 2009 George Tiller, an American doctor and abortion provider, was shot and killed while attending church in Wichita, Kansas. The gunman, an activist with a history of mental illness, testified that he had to kill Dr Tiller or else “babies were going to die”. Today the battle over abortion in America is fought less with guns and explosives than with laws hammered out in the country’s statehouses. This year Alabama, Ohio and Georgia passed laws to restrict access to abortions. Some of them in effect ban the procedure even in cases of rape or incest. Last Friday state officials in Missouri chose not to renew the licence of a Planned Parenthood clinic in St Louis. If a judge in the state’s Circuit Court allows the decision to stand, the clinic will no longer be allowed to perform abortions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It would be a momentous decision. If the St. Louis clinic shuts down, Missouri would become the only state in the country without a legal abortion-providing facility for the first time since the Supreme Court legalised the procedure in 1973. Even if the clinic is allowed to continue providing abortions, it will face a slew of new restrictions. These include a ban on abortions after the eighth week of a pregnancy—an unusually early date. On average, states allow women to have abortions until the 21st week of pregnancy, according to Advancing New Standards in Reproductive Health (ANSIRH), a research group at the University of California, San Francisco.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_woc949.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Access to abortions in the “show-me” state is already limited. According to an analysis of ANSIRH’s data by &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;, Missourians live an average of 80 km (50 miles) from the nearest abortion facility, whether it be there or in another state. This pales in comparison with the hundreds of miles travelled by abortion-seekers in Wyoming or North Dakota. When measured in terms of women of childbearing age per facility, however, abortion clinics are scarcer in Missouri than in any other state. According to ANSIRH, five other states—Kentucky, Mississippi, West Virginia, South Dakota and North Dakota—have just one abortion facility. But whereas each of their facilities serves an average of 486,000 reproductive-age women, Missouri’s serves a whopping 1,365,000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 04:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>