<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[A terrible fire destroys much of the cathedral of Notre Dame]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/15/a-terrible-fire-destroys-much-of-the-cathedral-of-notre-dame]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_blp903.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THEY GATHERED on the bridges over the Seine to watch in disbelief. Some Parisians were in tears; most watched in eerie silence. The devastating fire that broke out in the wood-timbered roof of the gothic cathedral of Notre Dame in the early evening of April 15th rapidly spread before their eyes, consuming the central spire and defeating the efforts of fire-fighters to bring the flames under control. President Emmanuel Macron, spoke for many across France when he tweeted that he was witnessing “part of us burn.”  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By midnight in Paris the worst seemed to be over. The main stone struture appeared to have been saved, and the prompt action of hundreds of fire-fighters had rescued many works of art from the burning building. But as well as the mediaeval roof and the later-built spire, the cathedral&amp;#x27;s 13th-century great stained-glass windows are gone, and the damage to the interior will have been immense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 850-year-old edifice had survived war, revolution and Nazi occupation, an emblem of resistance in the face of a constantly disrupted history. It was the site of Napoleon’s coronation in 1804 and the inspiration for literary works, most famously Victor Hugo’s “The Hunchback of Notre Dame”, and one of the city’s most iconic landmarks, visited by 13m tourists each year. Notre Dame was at once a living place of worship for the French Catholic church and the property of the French secular state: a symbol in itself of the country’s history and its present, in all its glorious contradictions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The heartbreak felt by many as they watched nine centuries of history dissolve in flames was profound. Bertrand Delanoë, the former mayor of Paris, called the cathedral a “jewel of the heritage of humanity”. Mr Macron, who had been preparing to give a televised address to the nation at the end of his “great national debate”, cancelled the speech and went straight to the site of the disaster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It will take time and a full investigation before the exact cause of the fire is established. Early reports from the Paris fire service suggested that it was not a work of arson but an accident that broke out in the central roof, where building works were underway to renovate the 19th-century spire. But already questions are being asked about disaster-planning for a monument of this scale and national importance, situated amid narrow streets on an inaccessible island in the centre of the city.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The search for somebody to blame will absorb France for weeks and months to come. The public prosecutor has opened an inquiry. When shock and disbelief turns to anger, many will want to know exactly what precautions were taken by those working on the renovation, and why it was so difficult for fire-fighters to stop the blaze spreading. Five hundred were deployed, but it took them ages to get there. Some will look to Anne Hidalgo, the mayor of Paris, who tweeted that she had “no words for the pain” she felt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Others still will look to Mr Macron, who visited the scene and pledged to rebuild the cathedral. The unpopular president already had his hands full dealing with the gilets jaunes (yellow jackets) protests, which have dragged on since last November. This evening was supposed to mark the moment that he reconnected with the French people, and put his reputation for haughty rule behind him. Now he has a different challenge. Paris, and all of France, is hurting. The tragic devastation of Notre Dame will touch the country for a long time—and put the head of state’s capacity to touch the French with the right words of consolation to a severe test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 06:08:29 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sudan’s protesters stand firm for civilian rule]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/04/15/sudans-protesters-stand-firm-for-civilian-rule]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_MAP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AWAD IBN AUF was leader of Sudan for just over a day. In his brief spell as head of state the former vice-president and defence chief declared a three-month state of emergency, suspended the constitution, arrested a few senior officials and announced a curfew. “The people asked us to take over...and we did,” he said in a stony-faced televised address on April 11th, shortly after placing his boss, Omar al-Bashir, under house arrest. It looked as if four months of nationwide protests against Mr Bashir and his 30-year-old autocracy had culminated in a coup.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sudan’s demonstrators, who have been camped outside the headquarters of the armed forces in central Khartoum since April 6th, were having none of it. Though they had called on the army to side with them in order to topple Mr Bashir, who has ruled since 1989, his bloodstained deputy was far from the replacement they had in mind. Mr Auf has had sanctions placed on him by America for his role in war crimes (his former boss has been indicted by the International Criminal Court for genocide in Sudan’s Darfur region). Faced with a storm of popular outrage, the short-lived autocrat stepped down on April 12th. He was replaced by another general, Abdel-Fattah Burhan, then head of the army. Mr Burhan is said to be more popular with rank-and-file soldiers, many of whom are sympathetic to the demonstrators. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Burhan has so far made a better fist of the job. His speech on April 13th was less tone-deaf than that of his predecessor. He commended the revolution, particularly noting the prominent role played by women in the protests that began in December in response to rising food prices. He paid tribute to the civilians who have been killed by security forces in the past four months. More concretely, he promised to hand over power to civilians after a transition period of no more than two years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On April 13th the opposition nominated delegates to begin negotiating with a military council headed by Mr Burhan. In the first meeting the council promised to repeal all repressive laws and to oversee a predominantly civilian administration, according to the Sudanese Professionals’ Association (SPA), which organised many of the protests. Alongside this, the military council moved to weaken the power of the former tyrant. It replaced Salah Abdallah Gosh, the intelligence chief widely regarded as the second most powerful man in the country after Mr Bashir. On April 14th the military council said it had arrested members of Mr Bashir’s National Congress Party (NCP) and would begin seizing the party’s assets. It also promised to restructure Mr Gosh’s notorious intelligence agency and to allow the opposition to choose a new prime minister.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the protesters remain dissatisfied. “We can’t live on promises,” says Hamid Murtada, an activist. The SPA has called for the sit-in outside the defence ministry to continue until the “deep state” is fully dismantled. Many people are particularly worried by the appointment of Mohamed Hamdan Dagalo (known as Hemeti) as the military council’s deputy leader. A paramilitary unit he was in charge of, the Rapid Support Forces, with links to the notorious Janjaweed militia, was involved in the mass rape and butchery of civilians while battling rebels in Darfur. He and others in the junta’s top ranks are close to Saudi Arabia and the United Arab Emirates, both of which welcomed developments over the weekend. Saudi Arabia has promised aid to help ease the country’s economic woes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whether the junta will actually relinquish power remains to be seen. “It’s very possible the military said all that just to end the sit-in,” says Mohammed Osman, an analyst in Khartoum. Indeed, on the morning of April 15th it tried again to disband the protest, this time asking demonstrators to help clear roadblocks. After a brief stand-off the soldiers retreated. “Clean up the regime and we’ll clean up the square,” shouted protesters as they departed. The generals had better put their aprons on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 05:08:53 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A new era at Goldman Sachs starts in the shadow of a scandal]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/04/15/a-new-era-at-goldman-sachs-starts-in-the-shadow-of-a-scandal]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_FNP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-15T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;NO ONE IS more aware of the value of a brand than Goldman Sachs. The investment bank, founded in 1869, has advised the biggest and best American companies on the value of theirs for the past 150 years. It helped F.W. Woolworth, a pioneering department store, with its initial public offering in 1912. It took Ford and Disney public in the 1950s, helped Amazon buy Whole Foods in 2017 and will take Uber public later this year. Yet these are troubling times for its own brand, tarnished by association with a fraud-ridden Malaysian state-run fund, 1MDB, and hurt by the bank’s failure to adapt after the global financial crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These issues were echoed in the firm’s first-quarter results, released on April 15th. Revenues came in below expectations—13% lower than for the first quarter of 2018—largely as the result of lower trading revenues. The share price fell more than 3% and the earnings call was peppered with analysts asking questions about 1MDB.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first task for David Solomon, who took over as chief executive last October, is to clean up Goldman’s reputation. In 2012 and 2013 it helped 1MDB raise $6.5bn across three bond offerings, earning $600m in fees—way above the norm for such work. American and Malaysian authorities have alleged that much of the money raised was stolen in a scheme masterminded by Jho Low, a Malaysian financier. He has denied wrongdoing (and vanished).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last November America’s Department of Justice (DoJ) announced that a former senior partner at Goldman, Tim Leissner, had pleaded guilty to conspiracy to launder money and to violate foreign bribery laws. And they indicted Mr Low and another former Goldman banker, Roger Ng, who has also denied wrongdoing. Goldman claims that Mr Ng and Mr Leissner, who transferred embezzled funds into his personal bank account, kept the bank in the dark about their actions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But criminal charges have been filed against the firm in Malaysia, where it has been stripped of its banking licence. Though Goldman is contesting the case, it is spooking shareholders, who worry about both onerous fines and what it implies about oversight at the bank. Since November its share price has underperformed an index of other bank stocks by 10.3 percentage points, suggesting that the scandal may have wiped as much as $9.1bn off its value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is against these headwinds that Mr Solomon must try to convince investors that Goldman can reinvent itself. Its peers have already digested the fact that Wall Street’s traditional model, in which banks advise on huge corporate deals and make bold trades on their own behalf, has become less profitable. According to Michael Spellacy of Accenture, a consultancy, 90% of the economic profit made in the capital-markets industry is now earned on the buy side—that is, by those who manage assets or investments—and just 10% from sell-side investment-banking activities. A decade ago, he says, that split was closer to 50-50.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Goldman’s slowness in reacting to these structural changes has allowed its competitors to catch up. In 2010 its return on equity (ROE) was 11%, easily beating the 8% average for “bulge-bracket” American investment banks, a group including JP Morgan and Morgan Stanley. But last year that group averaged an ROE of 11.2%, placing Goldman, at 12%, near the middle of the pack. And investors are becoming concerned about the way it earns its returns. Volatile profits, like those from trading businesses, mergers and acquisitions, are considered less valuable than steady fee-based income, for example from wealth management.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2016 Mr Solomon’s predecessor, Lloyd Blankfein, took the first steps towards a new strategy by launching a consumer bank, Marcus. In 2017 Goldman announced a target of increasing yearly revenues by $5bn by 2020. But the focus on expanding consumer lending, which offers a relatively low return on investment, did not impress shareholders.&lt;br/&gt;They have had a rough ride. Holding shares in the firm since 2010 would have earned just 13% (without adjusting for inflation), compared with an average of 71% for its bulge-bracket peers and 152% for the S&amp;amp;P 500. Goldman continues to trade at just 0.9 times its tangible book value, a measure of the money that might be returned to shareholders if it were liquidated. The average ratio of price to tangible book value for a bulge-bracket bank is 1.15.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As far as 1MDB is concerned, the big worry for shareholders is the size and scope of the penalties. A large fine is all but inevitable. It could be based on the $600m Goldman earned from the bond issuance—or the $2.7bn American authorities say was stolen from the proceeds. That will be multiplied by anything up to four, depending on the degree to which the firm is found culpable. That Goldman is co-operating with the DoJ will bring the multiplier down; if the DoJ decides the firm’s oversight of compliance procedures was inadequate, it will be towards the higher end. Steven Chubak of Wolfe Research, an equity-research firm, thinks the total will be somewhere between $1bn and $4bn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When it comes to the required shift in strategy, however, Goldman’s efforts may soon start to bear fruit. Its expansion into consumer businesses is continuing apace. In 2018 it acquired Clarity Money, a personal-finance app. Last month Tim Cook, Apple’s chief executive, announced that it will launch a credit card with Goldman this summer. When Marcus launched it was as a consumer lender; since then it has added deposit-taking. Though it offers market-leading rates, deposits are still a cheap source of funding. In 2012 just 8% of Goldman’s funding came from deposits. Last year that share had risen to 19%. If it can keep replacing wholesale funding with deposits at the pace of the past five years, says Mr Chubak, it will have reduced funding costs by $500m by 2022.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The consumer space is not the only place Goldman is rolling out new technology. More than a quarter of Goldman’s employees are now engineers, says Heather Kennedy Miner, the bank’s head of investor relations. The firm is deploying a new platform, called Marquee, in 2020 for institutional investors and new expanding into corporate cash management, which will further increase low-cost deposits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The firm also seems to be planning an overdue restructuring of its fixed-income, currency and commodities (FICC) business. Revenues earned from FICC have fallen from $13.6bn in 2010, accounting for more than a third of Goldman’s revenues, to $5.9bn now, or just a sixth. Last October Stephen Scherr, Goldman’s newly appointed chief financial officer, announced a review of all its business lines, which will be published early next year. In January the Wall Street Journal reported that the commodities business would be scaled back. (Mr Scherr emphasises that Goldman has no plans to abandon commodities entirely, as some of its competitors, including JP Morgan and Morgan Stanley, have.) In March Mr Solomon announced plans to cut the number of staff in sales and trading by 5% this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Its new strategy will mean Goldman is competing on less familiar territory. Consumer deposits and corporate cash management are competitive markets that JP Morgan and Bank of America have dominated for decades. But they are also huge markets. Even a small slice could have a big impact on Goldman’s profits, says Mr Scherr. Compared with established banks, Goldman is able to develop and deploy new technology easily; but unlike startup digital competitors, its innovations are backed by a $925bn balance-sheet. America’s financial-services industry has been slow to adapt to technological change. An old bank with a new direction might be well-placed to disrupt it.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 03:34:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Right-wing populist parties are polling well in Britain]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/15/right-wing-populist-parties-are-polling-well-in-britain]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_WOC717_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BRITAIN’S NEW Brexit party has gathered support with remarkable speed. Formed in January 2019, it is already registering double-digit support in opinion polls and has nearly caught up with the UK Independence Party (UKIP), from which it split.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new party is headed by Nigel Farage, the former leader of UKIP, who successfully pushed the Conservative party to call a referendum on Britain’s membership of the European Union in 2016—and helped the Leave campaign to victory. It was a stunning achievement for what had been regarded as a fringe party, and Mr Farage announced his retirement from politics. Now he is back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Without Mr Farage, UKIP has drifted ever farther to the xenophobic far right under successive leaders. The Brexit Party, for its part, says it aims to draw support from across the political spectrum, from both Conservatives and Labour Brexiteers, to ensure that Britain leaves the EU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The referendum marked UKIP’s high point. In the general election held in 2017 it received just 1.8% of the votes, down from 12.6% in 2015. Even as it became clear that Brexit—at least as hardline Brexiteers had imagined it—was running into trouble, UKIP still polled only about 4% on average in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But populist parties have regained momentum since the beginning of this year. The government lost one vote after another on its deal with the EU, and Brexit has been repeatedly delayed. The original deadline of March 29th has been pushed back to October 31st. Unless an agreement is reached soon, Britain will have to hold elections to the European Parliament next month, which will be another humiliation for Theresa May, the prime minister.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Populists and hard Brexiteers accuse members of Parliament of betraying Brexit. The latest survey gives populist parties a combined vote of 21%. The Brexit Party, which Mr Farage recently described as “a virtual” party, consisting of little more than a website, is just behind UKIP on 10%. Both are ahead of the pro-Remain Liberal Democrats on 8% and not far behind the Conservatives on 14%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The contrast between the Brexit party and Change UK, another new party made up of Remainers drawn from Labour and the Conservatives, does not even figure in the polls despite having lots of favourable press coverage and several prominent MPs. It suffers from a serious branding problem: it faffed around with its name, does not have a leader and failed to present itself as a full-throated anti-Brexit Party. It could learn a lesson or two from the astute Mr Farage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 03:34:55 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Have Arthur Miller’s plays lost their edge?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/04/15/have-arthur-millers-plays-lost-their-edge]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BKP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-15T16:20:27Z&quot;&gt;Apr 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ARTHUR MILLER did not aim to please his audiences. He reckoned that new ideas were a “humiliation” and an “affront” not only to people’s sensibilities but to their convictions, too. Like the ancient Greeks, Miller thought of drama as a “civic art”, a discipline that could contribute towards a state’s social and political progress. Unlike his contemporaries, he was not commercially minded. He said what no one else had the courage to, and his audiences would weep, or sit with their heads bowed. Irate patriots picketed theatres, and producers shied away from his work. Actors who appeared in his plays were shunned by their friends. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miller’s observations hold true in the 21st century, particularly about the fallacy of the American Dream. Many still think of material wealth and status as essential to happiness, as Willy Loman does in “Death of a Salesman”. “The American Clock”, which reflects on the Wall Street Crash and the Great Depression, is a reminder of the perils of short-termism. “The Price”, set 30 years later, focuses on the longer-term repercussions. In “All My Sons” Miller questions individualist thinking. “The Crucible” examines the destructive allure of ideologies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those insights, far from alienating today’s audiences, are now Miller’s selling points. Productions of his work have increased since his death in 2005, according to Susan Abbotson, the president of the Arthur Miller Society. He has been among the ten most-performed playwrights in American theatres for the past four years. Six productions of his work are currently being staged in London, an unusually high number for any playwright other than William Shakespeare. Tickets in the West End sell for as much as £142 ($186), a sum Miller would no doubt have been uncomfortable with given his belief that theatre should be affordable. Does this popularity suggest that his plays have lost their subversive edge?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps—time can dull even radical ideas. It is no longer shocking to hear that humans are doomed to repeat their mistakes. But Miller’s fashionableness also suggests that directors have stopped confronting their audiences, and have started pandering to them. A recent production at the Union Theatre of “An Enemy of the People”, Miller’s adaptation of Henrik Ibsen’s play, had an image of President Donald Trump on its poster. The action was set in a contemporary “small-town Republican” community. Mayor Stockmann, a manipulative politician, dresses in a red suit, grinning and waving to chants of “USA! USA!” Miller never assigned a political persuasion to the play’s characters—he saw himself as a mediator, showing disparate groups what they have in common—but the suggestion here was that only Republicans can succumb to populist rhetoric and misinformation. This version of “An Enemy of the People” reinforced divisions, and allowed its audience to leave feeling smug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Productions can also be too reverent of the source material. “The Price” (at Wyndham’s Theatre) strives for a historically accurate depiction of New York in the 1960s. The audience sees Gregory Solomon, a Russian-Jewish émigré, blessing his meagre lunch—a hard-boiled egg—in Hebrew. When the play was first performed in 1968, such details invited audiences to reflect on their city’s recent past, particularly the emotional fall-out from the boom and busts of the ‘20s and ‘30s. Now heightened for comic effect, they seem alien and strange. Miller wanted his plays to be relatable, not preserved in aspic—“there are museums for such activities,” he said—and so the setting must be familiar. In 2012 a production in Mumbai turned Solomon into a Muslim nonagenarian to great effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miller’s plays provoked because they were about the audience as much as for them. “The Crucible” (pictured, at the Yard Theatre) opens with the townspeople of Salem dressed in the same style of clothing—beanie hats, baggy t-shirts, cargo trousers—as the audience of this edgy North London theatre. They are invited to confront an uncomfortable truth: any society, no matter how educated or tolerant it believes itself to be, can submit to hysteria. Reactions ranged from brow-furrowed confusion to wide-eyed fascination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is difficult for Miller’s plays to have the same effect today as when their themes were still unfamiliar, even taboo. Perhaps contemporary playwrights are better placed to touch modern nerves. But thoughtful stagings can continue to make audiences reflect on their own prejudices and shortcomings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 00:08:43 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[India’s enormous election, and more from our daily podcast]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/15/indias-enormous-election-and-more-from-our-daily-podcast]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/the_intelligence_53.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-15T11:09:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE WORLD’S largest democratic exercise is under way in India. The prime minister, Narendra Modi, looks likely to win on a divisive platform of Hindu nationalism and aggression towards Pakistan, even if those are not voters’ biggest concerns. Social-media companies are increasingly under the microscope of regulators; we take a look at the seemingly intractable problem of policing online content. And pole-dancing is trying to shed its seedy image. But can it develop into a global sport? Runtime: 21 min. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/modi-soperandi-india-senormouselection&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 19:06:29 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tiger Woods wins his fifth Masters in a comeback for the ages]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/04/15/tiger-woods-wins-his-fifth-masters-in-a-comeback-for-the-ages]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BLP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-15T03:02:53Z&quot;&gt;Apr 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUST A YEAR and a half ago, the most common question about Tiger Woods’s future was not whether he would win another major tournament, but whether he would ever play competitively again. After an unprecedented run of glory in which he won 14 majors in just over 12 years, Mr Woods saw his career derailed by an infidelity scandal, injuries and over-use of prescription drugs. Already on the wrong side of 40 years old, Mr Woods’s legacy appeared to be fixed: a star that burned brighter than any other but was extinguished far too soon, a victim of the hubris caused by too much success at too young an age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was then. On April 14th Tiger unleashed his roar once again—literally. After winning the Masters Tournament for the fifth time and a major championship for the 15th, he screamed at the top of his lungs while lofting his arms and putter high into the air, before embracing his caddy, family members and vanquished rivals as he seemed to fight back tears of joy. Much like the broader narrative of his career, it was also the first time he had come from behind to secure a major: in all of his previous victories, he had led at the start of the final round. Mr Woods’s title is not only a personal triumph, but also a welcome boon to golf as a game. Only the presence of its biggest star atop the leaderboards enables it to compete with the most popular team sports for viewership and cultural relevance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one would confuse the play of the grizzled, 43-year old Mr Woods with that of the 21-year-old phenom who won the Masters by a record 12 strokes in 1997. Whereas the young Mr Woods was so dominant that he barely seemed to be playing the same sport as his competitors were, this version seemed all too human. He frequently sprayed drives into the trees and misfired on straightforward putts, turning birdies into pars and pars into bogeys. He trailed by four strokes after the first round, by one at the cut and by two on Sunday morning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But just as Mr Woods has learned how to deal with adversity in his personal life, so too has he mastered how to limit the cost of mistakes on the golf course. Time and again, Mr Woods found a window through trees or a path around hazards, recovering from an errant tee shot with a pinpoint approach. (His driving accuracy of 62.5% was among the worst in the tournament, while his 81% rate of reaching greens in regulation was the best.) On the par-four ninth hole on the final day, his second shot landed at the far end of a long, downward-sloping green—a predicament in which the younger Mr Woods rarely found himself, where escaping with a par would feel like an eagle. Now a wily veteran, Mr Woods uncorked a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.golf.com/news/2019/04/14/masters-2019-tiger-woods-lag-putt&quot;&gt;lag putt for the ages&lt;/a&gt;. He aimed the ball on a line far above the straight path to the hole, and barely tapped it despite the vast distance. It almost stopped short as it approached the ridge—and then veered hard towards the hole, gaining speed as it plunged downhill, before coming to rest just inches from its target. The stroke he saved after tapping in for par wound up constituting his entire margin of victory, encapsulating the story of the tournament: unlike his rivals, Mr Woods refused to beat himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/tiger_winprob.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/tiger_winprob.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/tiger_winprob.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/tiger_winprob.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/tiger_winprob.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/tiger_winprob.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/tiger_winprob.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/tiger_winprob.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/tiger_winprob.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/tiger_winprob.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even after that par save, Mr Woods trailed Francesco Molinari by a stroke—a deficit that doubled after he bogeyed the tenth hole. EAGLE, &lt;i&gt;The Economist&lt;/i&gt;’s statistical win-probability model for golf tournaments, gave Mr Molinari a 65% chance of victory heading into the 12th hole, while Mr Woods languished at 16% (see chart). Just last July, Mr Molinari got the better of Mr Woods, when they were in the same playing group on the final day of the Open Championship in Scotland and Mr Molinari went on to win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This time, however, Mr Molinari succumbed to the demons that have undone so many a contender on the back nine on Sunday at Augusta National Golf Club. He left his tee shot short on the par-three 12th, seeing it disappear into the waters of Rae’s Creek, and then failed to make his putt for bogey. Mr Woods, in contrast, played it safe and made par. Three holes later, Mr Molinari saw his hopes of trying on his first Masters victor’s green jacket dashed for good. A poor drive on the par-five 15th forced Mr Molinari into an awkward approach shot, which bounced off a tree and wound up in the water as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Woods, meanwhile, displayed the steely resolve that made him an icon a decade ago. On the same hole that finished Mr Molinari, Mr Woods secured a birdie with a dead-centre drive, a meticulous approach to the green, and a clean two-putt. And on the next hole, the par-three 16th, he delighted the fans with a taste of his magic of yesteryear. His high-arcing tee shot first hit the green beyond one-putt range. But it then rolled sideways towards the hole like a heat-seeking missile, until he was assured of a tap-in birdie and a two-stroke lead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even then, Mr Woods wound up needing stumbles from his rivals to compensate for his own. Both Dustin Johnson, who by most statistical measures is currently the best player in the world, and Brooks Koepka, who had won three of the past six majors he had entered, reached the 18th green at 12 under par with achievable, if challenging, birdie putts. Both missed—barely, in Mr Johnson’s case. That wound up making the difference in the tournament, as Mr Woods muffed both his approach shot on the 18th and his putt for par. No one dreams about winning the Masters with a bogey, but it was a fitting end to a gritty triumph.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Must it be St Nicklaus?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Woods’s victory gives him a long-overdue 15th major title, leaving him three behind Jack Nicklaus’s all-time record of 18. Mr Nicklaus won his last at the age of 46, suggesting that Mr Woods has at least three more years to bridge the gap. Now that Mr Woods has rediscovered his form, might golf’s most treasured record now be within reach?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The afterglow of Mr Woods’s win is probably not the best time to preach faith in statistical golf models. EAGLE gave him just a 2.2% chance of winning the Masters, less than half the probability implied by pricing in betting markets. Although such odds might appear uncommonly long, they were no knock on Mr Woods’s game: most major victors start the tournament with less than a one-in-20 chance. In EAGLE’s estimation, Mr Woods was playing sufficiently well before the Masters began that he was already one of the top ten players in the world. Instead, the daunting odds were merely a reflection of how much good fortune is required, in addition to elite skill, to beat a field containing all of the world’s best players over just 72 holes. Even Mr Johnson, whom the model anointed as the favourite and finished tied for second, had less than a 10% shot to win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brutal arithmetic of large golf tournaments suggests that if Mr Woods is now a top-five player, he would be expected to win another major roughly once every 3.5 years. As a “mere” top-ten competitor, that frequency would fall to around one every six years. From this perspective, Mr Nicklaus should only feel threatened if Mr Woods manages to regain his former status as the unquestioned world number one despite his advanced age. That would mean following up this Masters victory with a steady drumbeat of scores in the 60s and finishes in the top 5 and 10 of PGA Tour events. (Mr Woods’s Masters performance alone has improved EAGLE’s estimate of his expected score on a typical course by over a tenth of a stroke per round).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Otherwise, the smart money will probably remain on Mr Woods’s major-championship tally remaining at 15. However, statistical models rely on extrapolating historical patterns into the future. And since no one has ever played golf as well as Mr Woods did at his best, there is no precedent on which to train a model for the second act of such a career. As the crowds roared following his every birdie and his rivals’ every misstep, distracting players two or three holes away, a victory that was still statistically improbable already felt inevitable in the heart of every fan who had seen Mr Woods in his heyday. Much to the delight of the lords of golf, even the most casual of observers will make sure to tune in the next time Mr Woods strides to the tee box with a major on the line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 16:07:41 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tiger Woods wins his fifth Masters in a comeback for the ages]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/04/14/tiger-woods-wins-his-fifth-masters-in-a-comeback-for-the-ages]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BLP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-14T23:02:53Z&quot;&gt;Apr 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUST A YEAR and a half ago, the most common question about Tiger Woods’s future was not whether he would win another major tournament, but whether he would ever play competitively again. After an unprecedented run of glory in which he won 14 majors in just over 12 years, Mr Woods saw his career derailed by an infidelity scandal, injuries and over-use of prescription drugs. Already on the wrong side of 40 years old, Mr Woods’s legacy appeared to be fixed: a star that burned brighter than any other but was extinguished far too soon, a victim of the hubris caused by too much success at too young an age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was then. On April 14th Tiger unleashed his roar once again—literally. After winning the Masters Tournament for the fifth time and a major championship for the 15th, he screamed at the top of his lungs while lofting his arms and putter high into the air, before embracing his caddy, family members and vanquished rivals as he seemed to fight back tears of joy. Much like the broader narrative of his career, it was also the first time he had come from behind to secure a major: in all of his previous victories, he had led at the start of the final round. Mr Woods’s title is not only a personal triumph, but also a welcome boon to golf as a game. Only the presence of its biggest star atop the leaderboards enables it to compete with the most popular team sports for viewership and cultural relevance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one would confuse the play of the grizzled, 43-year old Mr Woods with that of the 21-year-old phenom who won the Masters by a record 12 strokes in 1997. Whereas the young Mr Woods was so dominant that he barely seemed to be playing the same sport as his competitors were, this version seemed all too human. He frequently sprayed drives into the trees and misfired on straightforward putts, turning birdies into pars and pars into bogeys. He trailed by four strokes after the first round, by one at the cut and by two on Sunday morning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But just as Mr Woods has learned how to deal with adversity in his personal life, so too has he mastered how to limit the cost of mistakes on the golf course. Time and again, Mr Woods found a window through trees or a path around hazards, recovering from an errant tee shot with a pinpoint approach. (His driving accuracy of 62.5% was among the worst in the tournament, while his 81% rate of reaching greens in regulation was the best.) On the par-four ninth hole on the final day, his second shot landed at the far end of a long, downward-sloping green—a predicament in which the younger Mr Woods rarely found himself, where escaping with a par would feel like an eagle. Now a wily veteran, Mr Woods uncorked a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.golf.com/news/2019/04/14/masters-2019-tiger-woods-lag-putt&quot;&gt;lag putt for the ages&lt;/a&gt;. He aimed the ball on a line far above the straight path to the hole, and barely tapped it despite the vast distance. It almost stopped short as it approached the ridge—and then veered hard towards the hole, gaining speed as it plunged downhill, before coming to rest just inches from its target. The stroke he saved after tapping in for par wound up constituting his entire margin of victory, encapsulating the story of the tournament: unlike his rivals, Mr Woods refused to beat himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/tiger_winprob.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/tiger_winprob.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/tiger_winprob.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/tiger_winprob.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/tiger_winprob.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/tiger_winprob.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/tiger_winprob.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/tiger_winprob.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/tiger_winprob.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/tiger_winprob.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even after that par save, Mr Woods trailed Francesco Molinari by a stroke—a deficit that doubled after he bogeyed the tenth hole. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://eagle.economist.com&quot;&gt;EAGLE&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;i&gt;The Economist&lt;/i&gt;’s statistical win-probability model for golf tournaments, gave Mr Molinari a 65% chance of victory heading into the 12th hole, while Mr Woods languished at 16% (see chart). Just last July, Mr Molinari got the better of Mr Woods, when they were in the same playing group on the final day of the Open Championship in Scotland and Mr Molinari went on to win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This time, however, Mr Molinari succumbed to the demons that have undone so many a contender on the back nine on Sunday at Augusta National Golf Club. He left his tee shot short on the par-three 12th, seeing it disappear into the waters of Rae’s Creek, and then failed to make his putt for bogey. Mr Woods, in contrast, played it safe and made par. Three holes later, Mr Molinari saw his hopes of trying on his first Masters victor’s green jacket dashed for good. A poor drive on the par-five 15th forced Mr Molinari into an awkward approach shot, which bounced off a tree and wound up in the water as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Woods, meanwhile, displayed the steely resolve that made him an icon a decade ago. On the same hole that finished Mr Molinari, Mr Woods secured a birdie with a dead-centre drive, a meticulous approach to the green, and a clean two-putt. And on the next hole, the par-three 16th, he delighted the fans with a taste of his magic of yesteryear. His high-arcing tee shot first hit the green beyond one-putt range. But it then rolled sideways towards the hole like a heat-seeking missile, until he was assured of a tap-in birdie and a two-stroke lead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even then, Mr Woods wound up needing stumbles from his rivals to compensate for his own. Both Dustin Johnson, who by most statistical measures is currently the best player in the world, and Brooks Koepka, who had won three of the past six majors he had entered, reached the 18th green at 12 under par with achievable, if challenging, birdie putts. Both missed—barely, in Mr Johnson’s case. That wound up making the difference in the tournament, as Mr Woods muffed both his approach shot on the 18th and his putt for par. No one dreams about winning the Masters with a bogey, but it was a fitting end to a gritty triumph.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Must it be St Nicklaus?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Woods’s victory gives him a long-overdue 15th major title, leaving him three behind Jack Nicklaus’s all-time record of 18. Mr Nicklaus won his last at the age of 46, suggesting that Mr Woods has at least three more years to bridge the gap. Now that Mr Woods has rediscovered his form, might golf’s most treasured record now be within reach?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The afterglow of Mr Woods’s win is probably not the best time to preach faith in statistical golf models. EAGLE gave him &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/06/our-masters-forecast-is-lukewarm-on-tiger-woods&quot;&gt;just a 2.2% chance&lt;/a&gt; of winning the Masters, less than half the probability implied by pricing in betting markets. Although such odds might appear uncommonly long, they were no knock on Mr Woods’s game: most major victors start the tournament with less than a one-in-20 chance. In EAGLE’s estimation, Mr Woods was playing sufficiently well before the Masters began that he was already one of the top ten players in the world. Instead, the daunting odds were merely a reflection of how much good fortune is required, in addition to elite skill, to beat a field containing all of the world’s best players over just 72 holes. Even Mr Johnson, whom the model anointed as the favourite and finished tied for second, had less than a 10% shot to win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brutal arithmetic of large golf tournaments suggests that if Mr Woods is now a top-five player, he would be expected to win another major roughly once every 3.5 years. As a “mere” top-ten competitor, that frequency would fall to around one every six years. From this perspective, Mr Nicklaus should only feel threatened if Mr Woods manages to regain his former status as the unquestioned world number one despite his advanced age. That would mean following up this Masters victory with a steady drumbeat of scores in the 60s and finishes in the top 5 and 10 of PGA Tour events. (Mr Woods’s Masters performance alone has improved EAGLE’s estimate of his expected score on a typical course by over a tenth of a stroke per round).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Otherwise, the smart money will probably remain on Mr Woods’s major-championship tally remaining at 15. However, statistical models rely on extrapolating historical patterns into the future. And since no one has ever played golf as well as Mr Woods did at his best, there is no precedent on which to train a model for the second act of such a career. As the crowds roared following his every birdie and his rivals’ every misstep, distracting players two or three holes away, a victory that was still statistically improbable already felt inevitable in the heart of every fan who had seen Mr Woods in his heyday. Much to the delight of the lords of golf, even the most casual of observers will make sure to tune in the next time Mr Woods strides to the tee box with a major on the line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 09:05:46 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chevron is buying Anadarko for $33bn]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/04/13/chevron-is-buying-anadarko-for-33bn]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-13T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN RECENT MONTHS a question has been hanging over the plains of Texas: what would be the next big shale deal? The logic for consolidation seemed clear. Texas’s Permian basin is America’s most productive oilfield, despite a patchwork of plots with hundreds of owners. Shale companies looked cheap, with investors sceptical about firms’ ability to produce both oil and profits. On April 12th the curious got their answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chevron, a giant oil company, will pay $33bn in cash and shares to buy Anadarko, an independent producer with rich holdings in the Permian. It will also assume Anadarko’s $16bn debt. The deal transforms Chevron into the world’s second-biggest publicly traded oil-producer, behind only ExxonMobil. It is the latest sign of shale’s growing importance to the world’s biggest energy firms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oil majors have arrived relatively late to fracking. Small, independent companies were first to set about coaxing oil from shale. They developed ways to drill not just down but horizontally, then assault shale with water and sand until the rock gave up its hydrocarbon riches. But the industry titans have warmed to the idea. Unlike, say, a complex deepwater project in a distant jurisdiction, shale offers quick drilling times, predictable cashflow and favourable American regulation. Smaller companies have often fracked frenetically, eager to reinvest proceeds and chase growth. Too frenetically at times; some took on more debt than they could handle. Giant companies have less experience with the technique. But their diversified revenue and larger balance-sheets allow them to accumulate acreage even as they drill at a more measured pace. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year &lt;span&gt;BP&lt;/span&gt;, a British firm, paid $10.5bn to acquire the shale assets of BHP, a giant miner. ExxonMobil and Chevron have placed the biggest bets. Chevron’s shale holdings were vast even before the Anadarko deal. The company controlled 1.7m acres (690,000 hectares) in two of the Permian’s most productive regions. In March ExxonMobil said it expects production in the Permian to exceed 1m barrels a day within five years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Anadarko, Chevron’s Permian production may be 60% higher than ExxonMobil’s, according to Rystad Energy, a research firm. Anadarko gives Chevron more than just shale. Its assets include a liquefied-natural-gas project in Mozambique and holdings in the Gulf of Mexico. Still, Anadarko’s Permian plots would have been the main lure. With them, Chevron can drill more wells, more efficiently. Adjacent plots will let the company move farther sideways through the rock and simplify the transport of equipment and other inputs, such as the millions of gallons of water required to wrest oil from each well. Chevron reckons that the deal will bring $2bn in savings, all told. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some investors hope that, as shale companies consolidate, they will mature and their performance will improve. Independent producers may now bulk up, following the lead of Concho Resources. Last year it bought RSP&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Permian, a rival, for $9.5bn. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, the supermajors’ holdings look poised to expand. ExxonMobil has said it would consider additional shale acquisitions. Royal Dutch Shell is rumoured to be weighing the purchase of Endeavor Energy, whose headquarters sit in the heart of the Permian. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not all investors are sold on the attractions of shale. Follow This, a group of them concerned about climate change, expressed disappointment that Chevron would spend $33bn on Anadarko, rather than on renewable energy. At its annual meeting next month, Chevron’s shareholders will vote on a resolution that would compel the company to disclose how it can reduce its carbon footprint in line with the Paris climate agreement. Chevron insists that it is “positioned to win in any environment”. An environmentally friendlier one may be an exception. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(此域名已被污染，谢谢大家一直以来的支持)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 23:42:17 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pete Buttigieg is emerging as a serious contender for the Democratic nomination]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/04/12/pete-buttigieg-is-emerging-as-a-serious-contender-for-the-democratic-nomination]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190413_USP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-12T17:11:47Z&quot;&gt;Apr 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETE BUTTIGIEG does a good line in self-deprecation. He knows that many voters do not know who he is. On the stump he describes how a woman at an airport asked if he was a reporter covering a political campaign. He jokes about his lack of physical height. He speaks of the “audacity of someone like me”, meaning a 37-year-old mayor of a smallish city joining the 2020 race for the presidency. He also tells crowds he is not a “prototypical candidate”, saying his youth is a virtue that makes him focus on long-term concerns, like climate change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a man with a hard-to-pronounce Maltese name and little experience of national politics, Mr Buttigieg is enjoying an extraordinarily good start to his campaign. His political memoir is selling fast. Television news shows and other media are following him closely. That interest is driven in part by the novelty of his having a husband, Chasten. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Buttigieg has been on the road and fundraising for weeks but will formally launch his campaign on April 14th in South Bend, the city in Indiana where has been mayor since 2012. On April 11th he received his first serious endorsement, from Steve Grossman, a former chairman of the national Democratic Party and a well-known political figure in Massachusetts. Mr Grossman will no doubt encourage more donors to give to the campaign. Mr Buttigieg has already raised a decent $7m, a figure that includes many small donations, a hallmark of a serious candidate. He mentions, over a beer in a New Hampshire brewery, that he now has the means to expand his campaign team across several states, and notes that everything is moving faster than he had expected a few weeks ago. He says he is braced for a “marathon, not a sprint”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Polls show voters warming to him. Bernie Sanders and Joe Biden (who has not yet declared) are consistently ranked in the lead in the Democratic race, but Mr Buttigieg seems to be jostling for the third spot in a crowded field. A poll in Iowa, published on April 11th, gave him 9% overall support. That rises to 12% among voters who are under 50 and 12% among respondents with a college degree. That is a big shift: three months ago Mr Buttigieg did not register among pollsters at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The veteran, who served in Afghanistan, is proving to be a capable campaigner and a strong orator. With his measured speaking style he can sound a bit like Barack Obama (who, he sometimes reminds his audiences, described him once as a future prospect for the party). As a participant in televised debates between Democratic candidates later this year he is likely to perform well. Much of the recent interest in him was sparked when he spoke eloquently at a town-hall meeting broadcast by CNN in early March. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At recent events in New Hampshire the crowds were large. When an art gallery in Manchester overfilled with 300 guests, he addressed the roughly equal number that had gathered outside. Standing on a bench he spoke about freedom, security and democracy. He also touched some emotional notes, mentioning his father’s recent death and the loving support of his husband. He repeated the performance inside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rise of long-shot candidates from outside Washington has a long tradition. Bill Clinton’s jump from governor of Arkansas to Democratic nominee in 1992 surprised many. Jimmy Carter, who had been governor of Georgia, was little known before his successful run in 1976.  His clean-cut, God-fearing, small-town, virtuous persona appealed to many after the Nixon presidency.  Mr Buttigieg also emphasises his Christian faith and small-town virtues, playing up his distance from Washington. He talks, earnestly, of a public yearning for moral national leadership, saying “people are ready for something different” and it is time for “decency, honesty”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How far can this carry him? The fact that Mr Buttigieg is openly gay is, on balance, an asset—progressive Democrats can less easily shun him as a white man who studied at Harvard and Oxford before working as a consultant for McKinsey. At the same time, his identity as a Christian, married, with business and military experience, all suggest he could be popular among more centrist Democrats. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He has weaknesses. Just over a quarter of South Bend’s population is African-American, but he has so far said little about their needs as unusually poor community. In his memoir he describes a battle to rename one avenue after Martin Luther King Junior, but mentions little else about African-Americans there. He has tried reaching out to black voters, for example by saying he would support the study of reparations for descendants of slaves. But it is unlikely African-Americans would see him as their most powerful champion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He has also been a bit shy about which policies he would make his own. He suggests there is little variation between Democrats on policy, saying it matters more to talk of values and aspirations rather than offer up a “14-point plan” for every policy area. He mentions issues—such as cyber security and climate change—that matter to him. But he is not ready to spell out in detail how he would address them. Before long he will have to do so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 02:06:21 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>