<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Muhammad Morsi, Egypt’s only democratic ruler, dies in court]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/17/muhammad-morsi-egypts-only-democratic-ruler-dies-in-court]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_blp905.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-17T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE cases against Muhammad Morsi, now in their sixth year, long ago took on the air of a Kafka novel. Every few weeks Egypt’s sole democratically-elected president, deposed in a coup in 2013, would appear in court to answer one charge or another. He was accused of espionage and torture, and of stealing livestock. Most Egyptians lost interest, but the wheels of Egyptian justice, a deeply flawed variety, ground on. And then, abruptly, they stopped. Shortly after 6pm on June 17th state television reported that Mr Morsi had died of a heart attack during a court session. He was 67.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Born in the Nile Delta, Mr Morsi trained as an engineer and finished his PhD in America. He returned to Egypt in 1985 and took up a university post in Sharqia governorate, where he had grown up. For the next 15 years he was an academic and a high-climbing member of the Muslim Brotherhood, the Islamist group that was then banned but tolerated by Hosni Mubarak’s government. In 2000 he was elected to parliament—as an independent, since the Brotherhood was not allowed to field candidates. He served only one term.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was an unlikely CV for the man who would emerge as Egypt’s president after Mr Mubarak was toppled in the Arab spring of 2011. Indeed, Mr Morsi was not even the Brotherhood’s first choice. The group wanted to run its deputy leader, Khairat al-Shater, a wealthy and well-known businessman. But the army decided that a recent prison term made him ineligible to compete. Mr Morsi was a compromise option—uncharismatic, perhaps, but a trusted member of the group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Egyptian liberals, who split their vote during the election’s first round, did not share Mr Morsi’s Islamist politics, but he seemed the democratic choice, a break from the old regime. Many held their noses and voted for him in the run-off in June 2012 against Ahmed Shafiq, Mr Mubarak’s last prime minister. After his victory was confirmed, Mr Morsi’s first act was to address a crowd in Tahrir Square, the heart of the revolution. There he awkwardly unbuttoned his jacket to show the crowd that he was not wearing a bulletproof vest—a man-of-the-people gesture that he hoped would endear him to the nation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The goodwill was short-lived. Mr Morsi and his allies never got a grip on Egypt’s factious state. From the start the army undermined him, while the intelligence services worked to bring him down. The Mubarak-era courts became a major source of opposition: judges dissolved parliament, in which the Brotherhood held a plurality, and repeatedly blocked Mr Morsi’s efforts to schedule a new election. In November 2012 the president issued a decree that shielded his decisions from judicial review. Anti-Morsi protesters who surrounded his palace were soon attacked by Brotherhood supporters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His edict, and the violence that followed, caused a lasting rupture with the revolutionaries who helped put Mr Morsi in office. When the army removed him in July 2013—led by his hand-picked defence minister, Abdel-Fattah al-Sisi—many were happy to see him go. Even the killing of hundreds of pro-Morsi protesters the following month, a massacre unprecedented in Egypt’s modern history, drew only muted public criticism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Brotherhood is again banned, and now not even tolerated. Once a strict hierarchy, it is no longer a coherent organisation, its leaders crammed into heaving jails or exiled to Doha, Istanbul and European capitals. Nor is there any other source of opposition. In April Egyptians approved constitutional amendments that allow Mr Sisi (now the president) to rule until 2030. An engineer named Ahmed Badawi held a one-man protest on a Cairo street. He was swiftly arrested. Mr Morsi’s death might provide a rallying point for Mr Sisi’s foes. The interior ministry put its forces on alert, and police will surely round up some Brotherhood supporters as a “preventive” measure. But it is unclear whether there is anyone with the standing to lead protests, nor Egyptians willing to risk the consequences of joining them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three hours after Mr Morsi died Egypt’s public prosecutor, acting with unusual alacrity, published a report on his death. Unsurprisingly, it found no signs of mistreatment, so no reason to blame the state. But Mr Morsi’s family had long worried about his health. He was held in solitary confinement in Tora prison, notorious for its grim conditions. Human Rights Watch, a pressure group based in New York, alleges that the diabetic ex-president received inadequate medical care. During a court session he hinted that guards were trying to poison his food. Concerned British lawmakers tried to visit him in prison last year. Amr Darrag, a former minister in Mr Morsi’s government, calls his death “tantamount to state-sponsored murder”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Morsi’s final years are a stark contrast with those of his predecessor, a man who misruled Egypt for 30 years. Mr Mubarak faced his own trial after the revolution. He was held not in Tora prison but in a military hospital in a pleasant Cairo suburb. With the cases against him now dismissed, he is enjoying a peaceful retirement. Mr Morsi was a poor president. But he was the only popularly-elected one in Egypt’s long history. It is a tragic coda for Egypt’s revolution that he spent his final years rotting alone in a cell, his death almost a footnote in a country that long ago slid back into dictatorship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 05:40:27 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Greenland ice sheet is melting unusually fast]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/17/the-greenland-ice-sheet-is-melting-unusually-fast]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_woc543.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;GREENLAND’S misnomer is the result of a marketing campaign by Erik the Red who wished to attract Viking settlers to its icy landscape. Little did he know that the land had been covered in lush forests many millennia before he was born. Nor could he have fathomed that, a millennium after his death, the vast ice sheet would be in rapid retreat.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ice atop Greenland holds enough water to raise global sea levels by more than seven metres, should it all melt and run off into the oceans. For this reason, climate scientists closely monitor its seasonal trends, and in particular how quickly it melts in the spring leading up to the late summer “ice minimum”, after which it starts to grow again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest data shows that the area of melting ice this year is unusually high. On June 12th 712,000 square kilometres of the ice-sheet (over 40% of the total) were melting. This is well outside the norm for the past 40 years (see chart).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several factors are to blame. First, a natural cycle known as the North Atlantic Oscillation is encouraging ice-melt. Then there is long-term warming driven by rising greenhouse-gas emissions. Third, climate change has also weakened the jet stream, allowing a warm and humid weather system to settle over northeastern Greenland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a result, the seasonal ice melt began two weeks early. According to data published on the Polar Portal, a Danish climate-research website, Greenland is currently losing 3bn tonnes of ice every day, roughly three times the average for mid-June in 1981-2010.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The extent of the melting is not entirely unprecedented for this time of year. Researchers have seen similar events in 2002, 2007 and 2012. Each portended a record low at the end of the summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although a switch in the weather could still turn things around, the early melt will result in darker snow and ice, which absorb more sunlight and hastens the melting process, says Thomas Mote of the US National Snow and Ice Data Centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“If this year is anything like 2012 [which set the current record for ice melt], then we will get in the region of 1mm of sea-level rise in one year just from Greenland,” says Jason Box, a professor at the Geological Survey of Denmark and Greenland. The oceans are rising by 3.3mm each year because of global warming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Greenland may not be green, yet, but it is far less icy than in Erik’s time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 05:40:26 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lee Krasner’s colourful, creative destruction]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/17/lee-krasners-colourful-creative-destruction]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_BKP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-17T17:23:26Z&quot;&gt;Jun 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 1951 Lee Krasner hosted a show of her large, brightly coloured geometric paintings at a gallery in New York. Critics liked it, but the paintings didn’t sell. Distraught, Krasner began working on a series of even bigger pieces—black-and-white drawings that spanned from floor to ceiling—but she decided she hated them, and tore them to pieces. When she returned to the studio a few weeks later, she was surprised. All of a sudden, she said, she saw “a lot of things there that began to interest me”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She collaged the torn-up drawings onto the colourful canvases from her gallery show. She added more paint, burlap, fragments of newspaper and bits of discarded paintings by her husband, Jackson Pollock. The resulting works, unveiled at an exhibit in 1955, were inventive and evoked the chaos of nature. They marked the beginning of a process which Krasner would often use: the dismantling of old work to make something new.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Lee Krasner: Living Colour”, a retrospective of the artist’s work at the Barbican Centre—and the first major show of her work in Europe in more than 50 years—explores these cycles of destruction and regeneration. It traces her development from art student in New York to prominent abstract expressionist, moving deftly through periods in her painting such as her “Little Drawings” (small canvases packed with colour, texture and hieroglyph-like forms) and what a friend called her “Night Journeys” (massive explosive paintings in umber made in the wake of Pollock’s death). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp501.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exhibition demonstrates Krasner’s great skill as a colourist, and how much of her work is rooted in nature. Two of her early self-portraits, created as a student, featured plants. After her father’s death Krasner struggled to paint until she moved out to Springs, Long Island, in 1945 and started observing the outside world. Among the flowers and leaves and birds, a creative impulse began to come through, realised on vibrant, small canvases thick with textured paint and in two marvellous mosaic tables made out of wagon wheels, studded with bits of glass, coins, keys and plastics. The visitor can glimpse her startling creativity, her adeptness with bits and pieces, and the interplay between order and chaos, all of which would feature in her later paintings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Her range is impressive, too. Krasner could do the monumental canvases for which abstract expressionists are best known. For example, in deft strokes of red and white “Another Storm” (1963) evokes the movement of butterflies. She could also work with smaller forms. A side-room is devoted largely to Krasner’s watercolours, calligraphic works of bright hues that are also explorations of negative space. These intimate works are as arresting as the large canvases.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a cliché to say that Krasner “lived in Jackson’s Pollock’s shadow”—a phrase which appeared in her obituary in the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; in 1984 and has been repeated over and over in reviews of the current show, 35 years later. It is also not really true: the bulk of Krasner’s major artworks were created before her 11-year marriage, or after Pollock’s death. She was respected by critics in the 1950s and 1960s, and internationally recognised in her lifetime (though it took longer for her to earn that acclaim than for many of the men she worked alongside; a documentary shown at the end of the exhibit highlights both the force of her personality and the institutional misogyny she faced). “Lee Krasner: Living Colour” is a celebration of her creative life, and one which does not require constant references to her marriage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190622_bkp503.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, the visitor emerges from this exhibition wondering whether she was a better painter than her spouse; she was certainly a more inventive one. In 1974 she rediscovered drawings that she had made while a student of Hans Hofmann, an influential painter, and promptly cut them up. Hofmann was known to be strict, sometimes tearing up his students’ drawings, so the deliberate act of slicing with scissors provided a kind of childish delight. But the resulting works were revelatory: 11 canvases arranged with angular slices of her former self. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The past, for Krasner, wasn’t something to preserve or revere—it was something that ran through the present, something to play with in paint. “All my work keeps going like a pendulum; it seems to swing back to something I was involved with earlier, or it moves between horizontality and verticality, circularity or a composite of them,” she said. “For me, I suppose that change is the only constant.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Lee Krasner: Living Colour” continues at the Barbican Centre in London until September 1st&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 02:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The race to become Britain’s next PM]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/17/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-17T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HERESA MAY&lt;/small&gt; stepped down as leader of the Conservative Party on June 7th, but she will remain as prime minister until her successor is chosen. The first round of voting took place on June 13th; Boris Johnson topped the ballot of Tory MPs, with Jeremy Hunt a distant second and Michael Gove third. Three candidates, Andrea Leadsom, Mark Harper and Esther McVey, failed to get enough votes to go through to the next round and Matt Hancock pulled out on June 14th. The remaining six candidates will go through to the second round of voting, which is scheduled for June 18th. After further votes MPs will then send two names to party members, who will make the final choice. The result of their vote will be announced before Parliament rises for summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Betfair Exchange, a gambling website, has been tracking punters’ predictions on the next Tory leader. According to the wisdom of the betting crowd, a handful of candidates stand out. But there is only one clear frontrunner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anne McElvoy, host of &lt;i&gt;The Economist asks&lt;/i&gt;, spoke to Jeremy Hunt and Rory Stewart about their leadership plans: &lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-whocanleadbritainthroughbrexit-&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.betfair.com/exchange/plus/politics&quot;&gt;Betfair Exchange&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 20:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“It’s been an astonishing weekend”—Hong Kong’s shocking U-turn]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/17/its-been-an-astonishing-weekend-hong-kongs-shocking-u-turn]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_blm501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-17T11:23:08Z&quot;&gt;Jun 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALLS FOR the resignation of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/china/2019/06/15/hong-kongs-leader-backs-down-over-controversial-extradition-bill&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Carrie Lam&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, the territory’s leader, are intensifying. Hong Kongers may have put a recent freedom-crimping bill on ice, but more challenges to their independence await. We speak to the mother of a child &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.1843magazine.com/features/the-curse-of-genius&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;genius&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; who reveals the private agony of being an exceedingly clever kid. And a new podcast in &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/06/06/latin-is-dead-yet-it-also-lives-on&quot;&gt;Latin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; gets our columnist thinking about language evolution and resurrection. Runtime: 23 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/lamtotheslaughter-hongkong-sshockingu-turn&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 18:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A big fall in aircraft orders is expected at this year’s Paris Air Show]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/gulliver/2019/06/17/a-big-fall-in-aircraft-orders-is-expected-at-this-years-paris-air-show]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_WBP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-17T10:18:14Z&quot;&gt;Jun 17th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE PARIS AIR SHOW, which began on June 17th, is the largest event of its type in the world. Aerospace and defence firms flock to Le Bourget to show off their wares to potential customers, and to rack up orders for the future. The last few shows have been money-spinners for commercial-aircraft makers, particularly Europe’s Airbus and America’s Boeing, the two firms that between them make almost all the world’s large jetliners. At the last air show, in 2017, orders for civil aircraft worth $115bn at list prices were made. The one before that, in 2015, was almost as bountiful, with $107bn in orders. This year expectations are much lower. Nonetheless, analysts expect the two giants to be doing well even with orders at a fraction of the level of previous years. Why?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boeing had hoped to be very busy in Paris this week. It was expected to launch the 797, a new mid-sized jet to fill the gap in its range between its smaller 737 narrow-body airliner and its much larger 787 and 777 wide-body jets. But now all bets are off. Boeing is likely to have a low profile at Paris. Its chief executive, Dennis Muilenburg, still has his tail between his legs over the indefinite grounding of the new Boeing 737 MAX—an aircraft said to produce a third of the firm’s revenues and profits—over safety worries, after two crashes in just five months killed 346 people. Mr Muilenburg will be spending much of his time trying to reassure airlines that, one day, the 737 MAX will fly again. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that is by no means Boeing’s only problem. Its bigger aircraft are also in trouble. The new 777X, once expected to be at Paris, is stuck on the ground in America because of engine problems. And its flagship 787 Dreamliner has been branded by American regulators as a “risk to the flying public” owing to problems with a switch that activates fire-fighting equipment on board.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No wonder that Airbus, its arch-rival, is expecting a good air show. It is showing off five of its airliners in Paris, unlike Boeing which is able to display only one. The European aerospace giant is planning to launch the A321XLR, an aircraft designed to knock Boeing’s 797 out the sky. It is a simple adaptation of its popular A321neo aircraft and building it will therefore require only a fraction of the cost of developing the all-new Boeing 797. In theory, the new Airbus aircraft should also be more fuel efficient, as it has a much smaller cross-section than that proposed for the Boeing 797, so creating much less drag.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Beyond Boeing’s particular problems at this year’s show, some commentators will inevitably leap on a fall in overall sales to say something is going wrong in the market for commercial jets. Some analysts have already cited disappointing global air-passenger traffic growth in recent months as a reason behind the announcement on June 9th of a merger between United Technologies, an American conglomerate mainly involved in civil aviation, with Raytheon, an American defence contractor, in a deal worth over $120bn. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But a few disappointing months of traffic figures does not make an aviation recession. Many airlines are sitting on their hands as neither Boeing nor Airbus have any spare production slots available in the near term for their most popular planes. Both already have huge backlogs of orders to keep busy. The number of aircraft on Airbus’s orderbook will keep its assembly lines busy for over nine years at current rates of production; that number for Boeing is over seven. There is no need for either to panic about orders—yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 18:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The promotion curse]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/16/the-promotion-curse]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_wbd001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-16T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IS YOUR promotion really necessary? Many workers focus their hopes on climbing the hierarchy of their organisations. The prospect of higher pay helps to explain their ambition, but so does the greater status that comes with each successive title.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This scramble can often end in disappointment. The Peter principle, developed by Laurence Peter for a book published in 1969, states that workers get promoted until they reach their level of incompetence. It makes perfect sense. If you are good at your job, you rise up the career ladder. Eventually, there will be a job you are not good at and at that point your career will stall. The logical corollary is that any senior staff members who have been in their job for an extended period are incompetent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is another problem with chasing the promotion chimera. In a recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://voxeu.org/article/promotions-and-peter-principle&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt; for VoxEU, the records of almost 40,000 salespeople across 131 firms were studied by Alan Benson, Danielle Li and Kelly Shue. They found that companies have a strong tendency to promote the best sales people. Convincing people to buy goods and services is a useful skill, requiring charisma and persistence. But, as the authors point out, these are not the same capabilities as the strategic planning and administrative competence needed to lead a sales team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The research then looked at what happened after these super-salespeople were promoted. Their previous sales performance was actually a negative indicator of managerial success. The sales growth of workers assigned to the star sellers was 7.5 percentage points lower than for those whose managers were previously weaker performers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scott Adams, the cartoonist, described this problem in his book, the “The Dilbert Principle”. In his world, the least competent people get promoted because these are the people you don’t want to do the actual work. It is foolish to promote the best salesperson or computer programmer to a management role, since the company will then be deprived of unique skills. That’s how the workers in the Dilbert cartoon strip end up being managed by the clueless “pointy-haired boss”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bartleby is not an expert at climbing the greasy pole. When he was last promoted, Iraq had yet to be invaded. In part, that is because he has observed a variant on the Peter and Dilbert principles; what might be dubbed the Bartleby curse. People get promoted until they reach a level when they stop enjoying their jobs. At this point, it is not just their competence that is&lt;br/&gt;affected; it is their happiness as well. The trick to avoiding this curse is to stick to what you like doing. If you enjoy teaching, don’t be a headmaster or college principal. If you like writing articles and columns, editing other people’s work may not give you the same degree of satisfaction (let alone conducting career reviews).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another problem with pursuing frequent promotions is that it turns you into a supplicant, endlessly in search of favourable feedback from the higher corporate ranks. This can mean that you lose control of your work-life balance. In Charles Handy’s new book, “21 Letters On Life And Its Challenges”, the veteran management theorist recalls a moment of epiphany when working for Shell, an oil giant. “In exchange for the promise of financial security and guaranteed work, I had sold my time to complete strangers with my permission for them to use that time for their own purposes,” he writes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The higher up the ladder you go, the greater the demands are likely to be on your time. The chief executive will expect you to be available on weekends; after all, that is why you get paid the big bucks. Subordinates will also feel that they are able to ask you tricky questions whenever they arise; they don’t want to take decisions that are above their pay grade. If you are in charge of a geographical region, you may spend much of your time on planes, visiting the corporate troops. And when you are not travelling, your day will be filled with meetings. At the end of the day, you will have been extremely busy, but with a nagging feeling that you have achieved nothing of substance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So that shiny promotion may not be for everyone. Beware the curse of overwork and dissatisfaction. Some people like to devote their whole lives to their job and be at the centre of events. It is best to let them get on with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2019 04:40:16 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The gift of overcoming barriers eludes the world’s Orthodox Christians]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/06/15/the-gift-of-overcoming-barriers-eludes-the-worlds-orthodox-christians]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_blp904.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-15T16:24:56Z&quot;&gt;Jun 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SCORES OF millions of Orthodox Christians will on June 16th mark the feast of Pentecost. This celebration centres on the moment when, according to church tradition, the Holy Spirit bestowed upon the disciples of Jesus Christ the mysterious power to communicate across language barriers. Each member of the multicultural crowd that gathered in Jerusalem is said to have heard the Apostles speaking in his or her own tongue. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately the ability to communicate successfully across other barriers, whether geopolitical or simply personal, is currently eluding the Christians of the East, or at least their hierarchs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The global split which opened within Orthodox Christianity six months ago over church jurisdiction in Ukraine shows no sign of healing. The dire state of diplomatic relations among regional powers is certainly not helping. The Patriarchate of Moscow abruptly severed relations with the Istanbul-based Ecumenical Patriarch, Bartholomew I, after he recognised the existence of an independent Ukrainian church. The split has left the 12 other self-ruling Orthodox churches in an awkward position of having to choose between the two Patriarchates, and the tension has ricocheted across the Orthodox world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far, no church has followed the Ecumenical Patriarchate in fully recognising the Ukrainian body, nor has any followed Moscow in completely severing ties with Patriarch Bartholomew. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Moscow Patriarchate, which hews close to the presidency of Vladimir Putin and at times defends it from popular protest, regularly pours scorn on its counterpart in Istanbul for acting as a stooge of American diplomacy. That America’s State Department supported the right of Ukrainians to organise their own independent church only added to Moscow’s fury. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, the Muscovite attacks oversimplify the position of the ancient Istanbul-based see, which must keep a delicate balance between many different earthly powers in order to survive as a tiny Christian enclave in a Muslim country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But in the coming weeks, the Ecumenical Patriarch’s profile in the Western and Anglophone world will certainly rise. The average age of his most visible representatives will plunge by nearly 40 years as younger clerics take over Greek-Orthodox sees in New York, London and Sydney. Mike Pompeo, President Donald Trump’s secretary of state, has invited Patriarch Bartholomew to America in July to give a speech on the environment. The choice of topic will come more naturally to the guest, a staunch greenie, than to the host.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of an apparent effort to counter-balance Muscovite influence in the Orthodox world, Patriarch Bartholomew has in recent weeks visibly mended his relations with the Archbishop of Athens, Ieronymos, by patching up their arcane quarrels over church jurisdiction in parts of Greece. That paved the way for Archbishop Ieronymos to join the primate of the new Ukrainian church, Epifaniy, and many other Bartholomew-minded hierarchs at celebrations in Istanbul of the Ecumenical Patriarch’s personal feast-day on June 11th. To judge by the reaction on social media, this innocent-seeming event caused much fury in the Muscovite camp and much pleasure in the opposing one. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile in Ukraine, ecclesiastical disputes roll on in an often bizarre way. Controversy swirls around 90-year-old Filaret Denysenko, a veteran and still-vigorous player in the high politics of Orthodoxy since the Soviet era. Having narrowly failed to become Patriarch of Moscow, he led a breakaway Ukrainian church in 1992 and was duly defrocked and disgraced by his erstwhile colleagues in Moscow, some of whom he had helped to consecrate as bishops.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since then the nonagenarian has styled himself the Patriarch of Kiev, a title that few people outside Ukraine recognise. In recent months, he has voiced bitter disappointment over the fact he was not put in charge of the newly-established Orthodox Church in Ukraine, and he has openly challenged the authority of 40-year-old Epifaniy, who was once his close aide. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In their handling of these inter-Ukrainian squabbles, the hierarchs in Istanbul feel they have trodden a careful line. They recognised Filaret as a valid cleric with the rank of retired bishop, which was enough to incur Muscovite rage, but they flatly rejected his claim to the title of Patriarch. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To all this, organs of the Muscovite media that are close to church thinking have reacted in a surreal way. While still snubbing the claims of “Mr Denysenko” to have any kind of clerical status, they report with gleeful satisfaction on the lively old man’s campaign to undermine his young successor. To anyone used to the relatively vertical structure of the global Catholic church, this will seem like an unseemly mess. But the story may not quite end there. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The feast of Pentecost, like every other landmark in the Orthodox calendar, will be marked by ceremonies of immense complexity, antiquity and beauty. Mastering and participating in such intricate rites can create mysterious, but also fissile, bonds between celebrants. They can quarrel suddenly, but also have sudden reconciliations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 01:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hong Kong’s leader backs down over controversial extradition bill]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/china/2019/06/15/hong-kongs-leader-backs-down-over-controversial-extradition-bill]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_blp903.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT WAS a remarkable climbdown in the face of mass protests. Just three days after suggesting that to retreat would be like spoiling a child, Hong Kong’s chief executive, Carrie Lam, announced the indefinite shelving of a proposed law that would allow the extradition of criminal suspects to mainland China. Mrs Lam now says she wants to avoid “chaos” in Hong Kong. Her U-turn came after the bill had provoked the biggest demonstration in many years, and another protest that escalated into the most violent social unrest in decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Few had expected the government to make such a concession, let alone so soon. The government had earlier planned to get the bill adopted by the Legislative Council by the middle of July, when the body is due to begin its summer break. It had described getting the law passed as “urgent”. But on June 15th Mrs Lam told reporters that the government would suspend the proceedings and would not set a deadline for resuming them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It appears that public pressure has succeeded—for now, at least—in making the government reconsider a policy that had strong backing from the Communist Party in Beijing. Protests have not always proved so successful. In 2003 the government shelved a controversial anti-subversion bill after hundreds of thousands of people took to the streets. But in 2014 protesters occupied streets in busy commercial areas for 79 days to push for democratic reform and secured no concessions. Since then many observers thought leaders in Hong Kong and Beijing had become even less inclined to give way to public opinion on sensitive political matters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On this occasion, however, opposition has involved far more than the usual critics of the party’s policies in Hong Kong. Businesspeople, lawyers and foreign governments have expressed considerable anxiety about the legislation. Although the proposed bill would allow extraditions to more than 170 other jurisdictions, the protests have focused on the potential for people in Hong Kong, including foreigners there, to be sent to mainland China, where courts are explicitly under the Communist Party’s control and dissidents are jailed on trumped-up criminal charges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Opponents of the bill have been organising what they hope will be another large demonstration in Hong Kong on June 16th. They say it will go ahead despite Mrs Lam’s announcement, in order to push for the complete scrapping of the bill and to protest against what they say was the excessive use of force by the police during the outbreak of violence on June 12th. Amid reports of suspected protesters being sought among the scores of wounded in hospital, some also want Ms Lam to guarantee that there will be no prosecutions. It is telling that Mrs Lam has not retracted her claim that the unrest had been “a riot”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hong Kong’s government had argued that the main reason for introducing the bill now was to enable a suspect to be sent to face trial in Taiwan, where he is alleged to have murdered his girlfriend. The man is currently in prison in Hong Kong for a money-laundering offence and is due to be released in October. The bill would remove a provision in Hong Kong’s current law that excludes extraditions to “other parts of China”, which in Hong Kong means the mainland, as well as Macau and Taiwan. But Mrs Lam noted that Taiwan has said it will not accept the suspect’s extradition under the new law. She said that since the bill would not solve that one case, it was no longer urgent to pass it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On June 12th Liu Xiaoming, China’s ambassador to Britain, told the BBC that the government in Beijing had nothing to do with initiating the bill. At her press conference, Mrs Lam said the central authorities had supported both her efforts to introduce the bill and her decision to shelve it. But there has been widespread speculation that the central leadership has been far more actively involved. Mrs Lam owes her position to a committee of local residents that is deliberately stacked with sympathisers of the Communist Party’s policies in the territory. She would be highly unlikely to make any move on such an important matter without seeking the party’s blessing. She declined to comment on local reports that she met one of China’s most senior politicians, Han Zheng, in the Chinese border city of Shenzhen on June 14th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The U-turn is a humiliation for Beijing, which has sought to tighten its grip on Hong Kong. But at least it is one the Communist Party can pin on Ms Lam rather have the Chinese president, Xi Jinping, portrayed in poor light. Even within the limits imposed by the Communist Party, Hong Kong enjoys a degree of free expression and political flexibility, which is more than can be said for mainland China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mrs Lam, for her part, deflected reporters’ repeated questions about whether she would heed the demands of protesters that she resign. There would be a precedent for doing so. Tung Chee-hwa, who was chief executive when the anti-subversion law was shelved, stepped down a few months later, apparently because of his handling of that bill. Mrs Lam said the central government had shown her “understanding, trust, respect and support”. To keep her job, she will need more such backing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 21:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Toronto Raptors’ risky bet on Kawhi Leonard pays off with a title]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/06/14/the-toronto-raptors-risky-bet-on-kawhi-leonard-pays-off-with-a-title]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_BLP510.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-14T18:54:18Z&quot;&gt;Jun 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;”FLAGS FLY forever”, they say in baseball as an explanation when teams mortgage their futures in trades in order to make one improbable run at a championship. After winning the first National Basketball Association (NBA) title in their 24-year-long history, the Toronto Raptors may need to coin a similar phrase for their sport.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly a year ago, Canada’s only NBA team pushed its chips all-in. When LeBron James, the superstar whose teams had reached the playoffs’ final round for eight consecutive years, announced he would sign with the Los Angeles Lakers, he opened the path for a new victor in the league’s Eastern Conference. The East might have seemed like a poisoned chalice, since the prize for winning it was likely to be a date in the NBA Finals with the dominant Golden State Warriors, who had won three of the past four league titles. But Toronto, undaunted, seized the opportunity, trading away DeMar DeRozan, a long-time Raptor and local fan favourite, in a deal for Kawhi Leonard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The deal was extraordinarily risky. When healthy, Mr Leonard is one of the five or so best hoopsters on Earth, and perhaps the only player in the league who could conceivably lead the league in scoring and win its Defensive Player of the Year award in the same season. However, he had missed almost the entire previous season with a mysterious injury that refused to heal itself, and alienated his old team, the San Antonio Spurs, by insisting on managing his own medical treatment. Moreover, he had only one year left on his contract, and was widely thought to be plotting a move to one of the league’s California-based franchises once he became a free agent. If he either failed to regain his previous form, or did so but then departed after a single season, the Raptors would be left with little to show for their investment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, the gamble worked out better than Toronto could possibly have expected. After resting Mr Leonard regularly during the NBA’s gruelling 82-game regular season to maintain his energy and reduce his risk of injury, the Raptors turned him loose in the playoffs. Mr Leonard rose to the occasion, delivering a performance that brought to mind the highlights of Mr James or Michael Jordan. In the decisive seventh game of the second round, he made one of the most improbable &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.youtube.com/watch?v=ChT3ewZXTfM&quot;&gt;buzzer-beating shots&lt;/a&gt; in NBA history to send the Raptors to the semi-finals. After Toronto lost the first two games of the following best-of-seven series, the Raptors’ coach, Nick Nurse, gave Mr Leonard primary responsibility for guarding Giannis Antetokounmpo, the Milwaukee Bucks’ superstar. Even though Mr Antetokounmpo stands four inches taller, Mr Leonard largely kept him in check the rest of the way, enabling the Raptors to win four consecutive games and make their first-ever Finals—as expected, against the Warriors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Betting markets gave Golden State nearly a three-in-four chance to win. But rather than rolling over meekly to the Warriors, as Mr James’s teams had done in the previous two championship series, the Raptors decisively dismantled the league’s reigning dynasty. Toronto did not even need to make use of the home-court advantage that they would have enjoyed in a hypothetical Game Seven, as they won the title on the road in the series’ sixth game, 114-110, on June 13th. The Raptors’ victory was indisputably a team effort: all seven of their regular rotation players, including Kyle Lowry, their star point guard; Pascal Siakam, a versatile, athletic forward likely to win the NBA’s Most Improved Player award; and Marc Gasol, a veteran centre whom they acquired in a trade in February, performed well. But there was no doubt about who would be named the Finals Most Valuable Player. Mr Leonard, who had already won the award once with San Antonio in 2014, amassed video-game-like statistics during the series, averaging 28.5 points, 9.8 rebounds, 4.2 assists, 2.0 steals and 1.2 blocks per game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Golden State partisans will insist that Toronto’s title comes with an asterisk, as the team lost far more in this year’s Finals than just the chance to three-peat. The team’s dynasty is built around four stars: Stephen Curry, the best shooter in NBA history; Kevin Durant, one of the league’s top overall individual scorers; Draymond Green, arguably the NBA’s best defensive forward and passing big man; and Klay Thompson, another elite long-range shooter. The team entered the series hobbled, as Mr Durant had missed all of the previous round with a calf strain. By the time it ended, the Warriors’ hopes of winning a title next season had been dimmed as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After sitting out during the Finals’ first four games, Mr Durant lasted just 12 minutes on the floor in Game Five before his right leg buckled with a torn Achilles tendon. This heel injury is the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/01/18/demarcus-cousins-is-unlikely-to-be-the-golden-state-warriors-silver-bullet&quot; data-tegid=&quot;br59nhh7vbc8mofn32lk88mks4df4uth&quot;&gt;single worst fate that can befall a basketball player&lt;/a&gt;, one that is not only expected to keep Mr Durant out for much or all of the 2019-20 campaign, but may also prevent him from ever becoming the player he once was again. And adding, well, injury to insult to injury, Mr Thompson ruptured his anterior cruciate ligament in Golden State’s final losing effort in Game Six, which will probably keep &lt;i&gt;him&lt;/i&gt; out for nearly a year as well. With both players’ contracts expiring, Golden State will have to let them go and try to sign another marquee free agent—perhaps Mr Leonard himself—to remain a serious contender.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one knows how Toronto would have fared against the Warriors at full strength. Over the course of the series, the Raptors outscored Golden State by six points per 100 possessions. Mr Durant probably improves his clubs by seven or eight points per 100 possessions relative to a typical end-of-bench player at the same position. So assuming that Mr Durant would have played around four-fifths of each game if healthy, the series might have been extremely close. Moreover, if Toronto does not deserve full credit for beating a depleted Warriors team, then the Warriors’ &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/game-theory/2015/06/18/most-valuable-loser&quot; data-tegid=&quot;idnuqjgtc3m4jm53nghd3oo91h5v1894&quot;&gt;victory over the injury-wracked Cleveland Cavaliers in 2015&lt;/a&gt; was just as questionable. Injuries are part of the game, and flags fly forever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the NBA will surely be the worse for the absences of Mr Durant and Mr Thompson in the 2019-20 season, it is probably good for the league that the Warriors’ era is drawing to a close. When Mr Durant &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/game-theory/2016/07/05/if-you-cant-beat-em-join-em&quot; data-tegid=&quot;hvoiu0s6mqs6mrgi0hbbqobu86n5cq04&quot;&gt;signed as a free agent&lt;/a&gt; with Golden State in 2016, many fans feared that the following seasons would amount to little more than suspense-free coronation ceremonies. That was, in fact, more or less what happened. Now, a whole host of exciting teams, including Houston, Philadelphia and Milwaukee, will get their chance to shine. If Mr James can lure another superstar to join him on the Lakers, then one of the NBA’s marquee franchises will get back in the hunt as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And then, of course, there are the Raptors. Now that Mr Leonard has brought Canada its first-ever NBA title, he might be tempted to build a dynasty of his own in the Great White North.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 04:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>