<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[China’s maritime ambitions are becoming more evident]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/china/2019/04/23/chinas-maritime-ambitions-are-becoming-more-evident]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/articles/20190427_cnp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-23T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS MILITARY PAGEANTS go, multinational parades of warships deliver quite a complex message. Over a dozen countries—ranging from friends to overt rivals—sent naval vessels to the eastern Chinese city of Qingdao on April 23rd. There they steamed past a destroyer carrying China’s commander-in-chief, President Xi Jinping, in honour of the 70th anniversary of the founding of the People’s Liberation Army Navy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paint gleaming and brass fittings buffed to a hospital shine, there were frigates from near-allies such as Russia, and destroyers from almost-foes like India. Their mission was friendship and diplomacy. But these were heavily armed peace envoys, warily visiting a China whose emergence as an ocean-going nation is shaking Asia, and may one day change the world. Visitors involved in territorial disputes with China, including Japan and Vietnam, sent ships bristling with advanced weaponry. America sent no ships at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China sent mixed messages, too. As celebrations began, the visitors were hailed by Mr Xi as a sort of floating United Nations. A peace-loving China yearned to work with foreign navies to secure international sea-lanes and safeguard the ocean’s riches, Mr Xi declared. On state television presenters noted that, as a mainstay of anti-piracy patrols in the Gulf of Aden since 2008, the Chinese navy had escorted more than 6,600 ships, from China and other countries, through bandit-infested waters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then came the bit which many Chinese viewers probably preferred: shots of their newest warships, dwarfing foreign visitors. Here came a Chinese ballistic missile submarine—nuclear-powered and designed for destroying enemy cities, not arresting Somali pirates. It glided past the destroyer carrying Mr Xi, who boarded wearing a dark Mao suit befitting his other jobs as the Communist Party’s general secretary and chairman of the Central Military Commission. “Comrades, greetings!” barked Mr Xi over a radio. “Chairman, greetings!” came the submariners’ shouted reply. On state television, presenters compared China’s newest destroyer, the 10,000-tonne Type 055, to the most powerful of America’s. Screens filled with archive footage of jets roaring from the deck of the Liaoning, China’s first aircraft carrier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On shore in the handsome, fog-shrouded port city of Qingdao, bilingual posters celebrating the naval anniversary offered variations on Mr Xi’s favourite diplomatic slogans, such as: “The Ocean connects us all, a community with a shared future.” Others, in Chinese, hailed the navy’s role as a political force, under the direct control of Mr Xi as the party’s chief. A banner outside Qingdao’s naval museum suggested that Mr Xi’s peace of mind was the ultimate test of naval modernisation. “Obey Chairman Xi’s commands. Answer to Chairman Xi. Let Chairman Xi be reassured,” it read.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cui Junkai, a 19-year-old student, had travelled from the city of Chengdu, hundreds of kilometres inland, for the fleet review. The parade-eve found Mr Cui in Qingdao’s naval museum, inspecting a wooden torpedo-boat from the years when China’s navy was a merely a “brown-water” one, tasked with launching guerrilla attacks in muddy coastal waters. A mighty navy offers China a double benefit, Mr Cui said. “It not only defends the nation, but demonstrates our power to the outside world.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Behind the teenager, rusty patrol boats bobbed at the museum quayside, recalling the decades when China boasted a “green-water navy”, capable of intimidating smaller neighbours but powerless when American battle-groups steamed by. That navy was a defensive force tasked with warding off sea-borne threats, not with projecting power over far horizons. In 1990 China’s then-president, Jiang Zemin, urged the navy to be “the motherland’s great wall at sea”. The next Communist leader, Hu Jintao, signalled a change in 2012 when he called for China to become a “great maritime power”. The navy saw its budgets soar and its fleet quality transformed. Today China has the region’s largest navy with over 300 ships, of which as many as 78 will be submarines, according to a Pentagon report to Congress in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese scholars have pored over the theories of Alfred Thayer Mahan, an American navy captain and 19th-century writer on “sea power” as a source of global strength resting on three pillars: commerce, naval firepower and access to far-flung bases. Mahan was a prescient man. On April 19th Chinese state television reported on China’s first naval base abroad, which opened in Djibouti last year. The report included a revealing on-camera prediction from the base’s political commissar: that support for far-flung missions would increasingly depend on such facilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Change of PLAN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Such talk alarms military chiefs in America and other countries. Their anxiety in turn worries Hu Bo, a leading maritime strategist at Peking University. For as China’s navy rises it has more than one goal, he says. First, to become a blue-water navy capable of providing security worldwide, which may perhaps involve opening a few more bases, for instance around the northern Indian Ocean. China’s other goal is “near-sea control”, Mr Hu says, meaning the capability to contain any threat in the western Pacific and northern Indian oceans—just as America and Russia currently enjoy comparative advantages close to home. That does not mean that China can or will evict all American ships from the South China Sea or other nearby waters, Mr Hu insists. In a generation’s time he can imagine a more restrained America and a more confident China reaching a new balance of power in those near seas, after a period of competition. The dangerous period is the next five or ten years, he says. “China’s capability is growing fast, but the United States is not ready to grant China status matching that power.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A balance must be reached, though. After millennia as an agrarian, continental power, China is a maritime nation, bound to the seas by strategic and commercial interests. Few foreigners would recognise the Chinese naval ensign today. That will change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:17:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Critics of Francis embrace the other “pope”, Benedict XVI]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/04/22/critics-of-francis-embrace-the-other-pope-benedict-xvi]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/000_1ft5f3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-22T14:57:40Z&quot;&gt;Apr 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;AS WAS CLEARLY observed on April 21st by excited pilgrims as well as television-watchers across the world, only one white-robed prelate appeared on a balcony overlooking Saint Peter’s Square to deliver the traditional Easter message. Pope Francis (pictured) duly chided rich countries over the arms race, called for peace in the greater Middle East and Africa, and lamented the victims of terror in Sri Lanka. The power of such occasions depends both on modern technology and on a centuries-old tradition, which holds that the task of representing Jesus Christ as his “vicar” on earth falls to a single, uniquely legitimate office-holder.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;But in the grounds of the Vatican, there are two gentlemen who use the title of pope: Francis and his predecessor, Benedict XVI, who lives nearby in a comfortable former convent. Officially, they get along well. On April 15th the current pontiff called on Benedict to offer congratulations on the eve of his 92nd birthday. But in photographs, Francis looked less genial than usual, and some wondered whether the wishes had been delivered through gritted teeth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;For several years, it has been clear that the relatively liberal, relatively inclusive style that Francis brings to the papacy is triggering a wave of theological and political opposition in many Catholic quarters. And some of that opposition is crystallising around Benedict, who styles himself “pope emeritus” and has retained some of the trappings of his old office, including the all-white garb plus a papal ring and dangling cross.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;What is not so clear is how far Benedict himself, and/or people with strong influence over him, are encouraging people to think of him as a counter-weight to Francis. But Massimo Faggioli, an Italian theologian, has likened the present situation to a “post-modern version” of a medieval schism: between 1378 and 1417, two and sometimes three clerics vied for the title of pope.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Recent events have brought the contrast between the two clerics to a head. Benedict’s newly-published &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/04/12/a-former-pope-blames-the-swinging-sixties-for-clerical-crimes&quot;&gt;essay&lt;/a&gt;, blaming the surging sex-abuse crisis on the swinging sixties and “homosexual cliques” in seminaries, was his most blatant intervention since stepping down in 2013. Francis showed a very different style when, in a TV show aired on April 19&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt;, he assured a gay British comedian that “only people who don’t have a heart” would fail to respect him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;For Vatican-watchers, all this simply marks one more episode in a long-term build-up of tension between the two popes, egged on by conservative critics of Francis. It was three years ago that Matteo Salvini, the anti-immigrant politician who is now Italian interior minister, sported a T-shirt with a pun in capital letters. “IL MIO PAPA E BENEDETTO” could either mean “my pope is Benedict” or “my pope is blessed”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;On the ecclesiastical front, four conservative cardinals (of whom America’s Cardinal Raymond Burke was the best-known) showed their hand in November 2016 with a letter that challenged a Vatican document which had promised more generous treatment to Catholics who divorce and remarry. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;A few months later, the Benedict camp seemed to offer moral support to that challenge. At the funeral of one of the four signatories, a German prelate who is one of Benedict’s close&lt;span &gt; &lt;/span&gt;aides, Georg Gänswein, read a letter from the ex-pontiff, saying pointedly that God would not abandon the church “even if the boat [is] on the verge of capsizing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Whereas traditionalist clerics take issue with Francis over reproduction and sexuality, worldly politicians find fault with him (and see merit in his predecessor) over questions like immigration and the protection of traditional Western culture. European conservatives loved Benedict for his perceived attachment to the heritage of their continent; their American counterparts resent Francis for his anti-capitalism and his embrace of the grievances of the global South. All these impulses have come together in the increasing prominence of a right-wing Catholic think-tank located not far from Rome, the Dignitatis Humanae Institute, with which Cardinal Burke and Steve Bannon, a former adviser of President Donald Trump, are deeply involved.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;In the world of Catholic theology, as opposed to its political exploitation, there are those who insist that the Francis-Benedict rift is either exaggerated or being mischievously fanned by people who have little real concern for either cleric. Indeed, even among theologically-minded fans of Francis, some still profess admiration for Benedict “at his best” as a clear thinker and teacher. Michael Sean Winters, a Catholic writer, responded to the 6,000-word essay by calling it a mixture of flawed analysis and trivial anecdote which nonetheless contained glimmers of the “genius and beauty” which characterised the work of Benedict (formerly Cardinal Joseph Ratzinger) at its finest.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;And to right-wing Americans who loathe Francis’s aversion to capitalism and embrace of the environment, it can be pointed out that both Benedict and his predecessor John Paul II had some harsh things to say about the unrestrained market. Nor has any recent pope been a fan of America’s military policy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;On the other hand, Benedict has hardly made life easy for his successor.&lt;span &gt;  &lt;/span&gt;After his surprise retirement in March 2013, he vowed to “remain hidden to the world”. He could have retired to a monastery in his native Bavaria and never said another public word. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Instead, he gave himself scope for future interventions. He not only kept many of the paraphernalia of office but, so critics argue, seemed keen to retain its essence. Many canon lawyers say his chosen title of “pope emeritus” is a dubiously-founded provocation, and that it would have been more correct to call himself bishop emeritus of Rome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Others note that Benedict’s resignation speech, in Latin, was profoundly and perhaps deliberately ambiguous. He said that, because of his age, he no longer had strength to exercise the papal ministry (munus in Latin). But he then went on to say that the munus had aspects: one consisted of acting and speaking and the other of praying and suffering. Father Stefano Violi, a canon-law teacher, reckons that Benedict was merely surrendering the administrative duties of a pope but not the pastoral ones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;For conservatives who want to present themselves as anti-Francis but loyal (perhaps more loyal than the pontiff himself) to the Catholic tradition, Benedict’s presence in the Vatican city is, at a minimum, a golden opportunity.&lt;span &gt; And Benedict seems unable to resist the temptation of offering that opportunity.&lt;/span&gt;  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 05:17:18 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Congress fails to claw back the right to wage war]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/04/23/congress-fails-to-claw-back-the-right-to-wage-war]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/articles/20190427_usp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-23T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WERE THE founding fathers to return, suggested Michael Beschloss, a historian, in last year’s “Presidents of War”, they would be “thunderstruck” to discover how the power to kick off major wars could now “rest on the whim of a President”. Presidents have “regularly told Congress to go to hell” on such matters, as Harry Truman admiringly noted of his predecessor, James Polk.&lt;br/&gt;Donald Trump is keeping up that tradition. On April 16th he wielded his veto for only the second time in his presidency to strike down a groundbreaking law that might have forced him to end America’s support for the Saudi-led war against the Houthi militia in Yemen. The fighting has caused what the UN calls the world’s worst humanitarian crisis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That the bill got so far, so quickly, is notable in itself. It sped through Congress–passing the Senate on 13th March and the House on 4th April—because of expedited procedures, never before used, granted by the War Powers Resolution (WPR). This act was passed in 1973 in response to Richard Nixon’s secretive expansion of the Vietnam war. &lt;br/&gt;In theory, the WPR tied presidents’ hands by requiring them first to consult Congress before sending forces abroad, and then to ask Congress for a declaration of war or a specific mandate to keep them there beyond 60 days. In practice, most presidents have either stretched or ignored the law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much of the recent stretching has occurred as a result of America’s sprawling “war on terror”. Three days after the terrorist attacks of September 11th 2001, Congress passed an Authorization for Use of Military Force (AUMF) permitting George Bush to go after those who “planned, authorized, committed or aided” the atrocity. That was clearly a reference to al-Qaeda, then holed up in Afghanistan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But by 2016 the AUMF had been used by Mr Bush and his successor, Barack Obama, 37 times to justify action in 14 countries s–“even against groups that did not exist on 9/11”, points out Christopher Anders of the American Civil Liberties Union (ACLU). Mr Obama, for instance, deployed the AUMF in defence of his war on Islamic State in Iraq and Syria even though the group angrily split from al-Qaeda long ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the WPR was gutted long before the elastic AUMF created loopholes wide enough to fly F-16s through. Most presidents after Nixon have simply ignored it, declaring its demands to be an unconstitutional infringement on their executive powers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some presidents have tried to conjure up a mandate in dubious ways. When the Kosovo war crossed the 60-day mark in 1999, Bill Clinton insisted that Congress had expressed approval by ponying up money for it—never mind that the WPR explicitly says that does not count, and that lawmakers are loth to cut off funds for troops in the line of fire.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most inventive approach has been to pretend that, contrary to appearances, there is in fact no war. In 2011 Mr Obama said he was free to bomb Libya because the action was led by NATO, did not involve “sustained fighting or active exchanges of fire” and was unlikely to escalate—and so did not meet the definition of “hostilities” envisaged by the WPR. Mr Trump has put forward much the same argument for his own entanglement in Yemen (which started under Mr Obama). Indeed had he signed the Yemen bill rather than nixing it, it is likely that his administration would have claimed its provisions did not apply to Yemen anyway.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lawmakers are right to roll their eyes at such make-believe. After all, American commanders sit in an operations room in Riyadh next to their Saudi counterparts. American engineers service the Saudi warplanes taking off to drop bombs. Until recently American planes refuelled the Saudi bombers mid-flight. War at arms-length is still war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile the fighting has left ten million Yemenis “one step away from famine”, warned the UN’s World Food Programme. Congress, though exasperated, does not have the numbers to override Mr Trump’s veto. But it is likely to continue the fight in other ways, such as by tacking riders onto the annual National Defense Authorization Act (NDAA), which is much trickier for the president to quash. At least some of the founding fathers would have approved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 03:16:25 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China throws a revealing party for the anniversary of its navy]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/china/2019/04/23/china-throws-a-revealing-party-for-the-anniversary-of-its-navy]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/articles/20190427_cnp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-23T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS MILITARY PAGEANTS go, multinational parades of warships deliver quite a complex message. Over a dozen countries—ranging from friends to overt rivals—sent naval vessels to the eastern Chinese city of Qingdao on April 23rd. There they steamed past a destroyer carrying China’s commander-in-chief, President Xi Jinping, in honour of the 70th anniversary of the founding of the People’s Liberation Army Navy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Paint gleaming and brass fittings buffed to a hospital shine, there were frigates from near-allies such as Russia, and destroyers from almost-foes like India. Their mission was friendship and diplomacy. But these were heavily armed peace envoys, warily visiting a China whose emergence as an ocean-going nation is shaking Asia, and may one day change the world. Visitors involved in territorial disputes with China, including Japan and Vietnam, sent ships bristling with advanced weaponry. America sent no ships at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China sent mixed messages, too. As celebrations began, the visitors were hailed by Mr Xi as a sort of floating United Nations. A peace-loving China yearned to work with foreign navies to secure international sea-lanes and safeguard the ocean’s riches, Mr Xi declared. On state television presenters noted that, as a mainstay of anti-piracy patrols in the Gulf of Aden since 2008, the Chinese navy had escorted more than 6,600 ships, from China and other countries, through bandit-infested waters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then came the bit which many Chinese viewers probably preferred: shots of their newest warships, dwarfing foreign visitors. Here came a Chinese ballistic missile submarine—nuclear-powered and designed for destroying enemy cities, not arresting Somali pirates. It glided past the destroyer carrying Mr Xi, who boarded wearing a dark Mao suit befitting his other jobs as the Communist Party’s general secretary and chairman of the Central Military Commission. “Comrades, greetings!” barked Mr Xi over a radio. “Chairman, greetings!” came the submariners’ shouted reply. On state television, presenters compared China’s newest destroyer, the 10,000-tonne Type 055, to the most powerful of America’s. Screens filled with archive footage of jets roaring from the deck of the Liaoning, China’s first aircraft carrier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On shore in the handsome, fog-shrouded port city of Qingdao, bilingual posters celebrating the naval anniversary offered variations on Mr Xi’s favourite diplomatic slogans, such as: “The Ocean connects us all, a community with a shared future.” Others, in Chinese, hailed the navy’s role as a political force, under the direct control of Mr Xi as the party’s chief. A banner outside Qingdao’s naval museum suggested that Mr Xi’s peace of mind was the ultimate test of naval modernisation. “Obey Chairman Xi’s commands. Answer to Chairman Xi. Let Chairman Xi be reassured,” it read.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cui Junkai, a 19-year-old student, had travelled from the city of Chengdu, hundreds of kilometres inland, for the fleet review. The parade-eve found Mr Cui in Qingdao’s naval museum, inspecting a wooden torpedo-boat from the years when China’s navy was a merely a “brown-water” one, tasked with launching guerrilla attacks in muddy coastal waters. A mighty navy offers China a double benefit, Mr Cui said. “It not only defends the nation, but demonstrates our power to the outside world.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Behind the teenager, rusty patrol boats bobbed at the museum quayside, recalling the decades when China boasted a “green-water navy”, capable of intimidating smaller neighbours but powerless when American battle-groups steamed by. That navy was a defensive force tasked with warding off sea-borne threats, not with projecting power over far horizons. In 1990 China’s then-president, Jiang Zemin, urged the navy to be “the motherland’s great wall at sea”. The next Communist leader, Hu Jintao, signalled a change in 2012 when he called for China to become a “great maritime power”. The navy saw its budgets soar and its fleet quality transformed. Today China has the region’s largest navy with over 300 ships, of which as many as 78 will be submarines, according to a Pentagon report to Congress in 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese scholars have pored over the theories of Alfred Thayer Mahan, an American navy captain and 19th-century writer on “sea power” as a source of global strength resting on three pillars: commerce, naval firepower and access to far-flung bases. Mahan was a prescient man. On April 19th Chinese state television reported on China’s first naval base abroad, which opened in Djibouti last year. The report included a revealing on-camera prediction from the base’s political commissar: that support for far-flung missions would increasingly depend on such facilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Change of PLAN&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Such talk alarms military chiefs in America and other countries. Their anxiety in turn worries Hu Bo, a leading maritime strategist at Peking University. For as China’s navy rises it has more than one goal, he says. First, to become a blue-water navy capable of providing security worldwide, which may perhaps involve opening a few more bases, for instance around the northern Indian Ocean. China’s other goal is “near-sea control”, Mr Hu says, meaning the capability to contain any threat in the western Pacific and northern Indian oceans—just as America and Russia currently enjoy comparative advantages close to home. That does not mean that China can or will evict all American ships from the South China Sea or other nearby waters, Mr Hu insists. In a generation’s time he can imagine a more restrained America and a more confident China reaching a new balance of power in those near seas, after a period of competition. The dangerous period is the next five or ten years, he says. “China’s capability is growing fast, but the United States is not ready to grant China status matching that power.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A balance must be reached, though. After millennia as an agrarian, continental power, China is a maritime nation, bound to the seas by strategic and commercial interests. Few foreigners would recognise the Chinese naval ensign today. That will change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 02:10:51 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why wages for the poorest Americans are on the rise]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/23/why-wages-for-the-poorest-americans-are-on-the-rise]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/money_talks_12.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-23T17:50:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS THE debate about raising the minimum wage in America intensifies, it seems that wages for the lowest-paid Americans are already on the increase. And why is wage growth in Britain picking up at last? Finally, the most expensive homes are becoming a bit less expensive. Simon Long hosts.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-wagingbull&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id420929545?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/2Yvo8QxZf7WlSEsIwKjtX4&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWVjb25vbWlzdG1vbmV5dGFsa3M&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=18377&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/Business--Economics-Podcasts/The-Economist-Money-Talks-p603831/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 01:07:35 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to predict a coup]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/23/how-to-predict-a-coup]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_WOC735.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-23T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TWO AGEING PRESIDENTS, one bad and one awful, were forced from office this month: Abdelaziz Bouteflika in Algeria and Omar al-Bashir in Sudan. Mr Bouteflika had been in power since 1999; Mr Bashir, since 1989. Their hasty and unlamented departures raise a question: how easy is it to predict a coup?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One obstacle to building a good coup-predicting model is that coups are extremely rare and becoming even more so. However, as our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/international/2019/04/20/how-to-predict-when-a-despot-will-fall&quot; target=&quot;_self&quot;&gt;print-edition story&lt;/a&gt; explains, social scientists now have more tools than ever before at their disposal. Perhaps the most rigorous quantitative forecast of sudden regime changes is CoupCast, published by One Earth Future, an NGO.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;CoupCast finds that economic misery is linked to higher coup risk, as is extreme weather. But political factors matter more. Dictators tend to lose popularity when they stay in office for too long. Autocrats who cling to power after losing elections are particularly likely to be deposed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The strongest predictor of future instability is past instability. CoupCast rated Algeria the country most likely to experience a coup just before Mr Bouteflika&amp;#x27;s exit. As for who might be next, the leaders of Burkina Faso, Afghanistan and South Sudan should be nervous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 01:07:34 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[On Saint George’s Day, Catalans lust for literature]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/04/23/on-saint-georges-day-catalans-lust-for-literature]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_bkp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-23T16:26:49Z&quot;&gt;Apr 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;CARE SANTOS begins every Diada de Sant Jordi (Saint George’s Day) the same way: by inscribing a copy of her latest book, and leaving it in a public place as a gift for a stranger. “I used to dream of being a writer,” she says. “If someone had told me that I would get to experience Sant Jordi as an author, I would have gone crazy with joy.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Catalonia, Sant Jordi is a curious blend of Valentine’s Day and open-air literary festival. April 23rd marks the feast day of the region’s patron and coincides with the day both William Shakespeare and Miguel de Cervantes are said to have died in 1616. Traditionally men give roses to women and women give books to men, though such distinctions are now frequently ignored. Street stands pop up in Barcelona and other Catalan cities, while authors meet with readers and sign books all day. As Carlos Zanon, a novelist, puts it, the day is “absolutely inclusive”. Jorge Carrión, whose English-language, non-fiction work “Bookshops” includes a chapter on Sant Jordi, says that “your readers come to you in person and explain why your books are important to them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flowers allude to Sant Jordi’s legendary slaying of the dragon and liberation of a princess, which—according to local lore—took place in the Catalonian fortress town of Montblanc. In the spot where the dragon’s blood was spilt, a rose bush grew. The bookish side of the festivities has more recent, entrepreneurial roots. In 1931 publishers looking to boost sales merged an existing “day of the book” that took place each October with the “day of the roses”. The purported commemoration of Cervantes and Shakespeare now looks as much a clever marketing scheme as historical fact, with many contending that Cervantes died on April 22nd and still others pointing to conflations between the Gregorian and Julian calendars. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It has proved a compelling story nonetheless. Barcelona’s publishing houses are said to earn 5% to 8% of annual sales in a single day; new books are launched in March and April to capitalise on the event. In 2008 Carlos Ruiz Zafon sold 120,000 copies of his novel “El Juego del Ángel” (“The Angel’s Game”) in just 12 hours. Florists do even better, taking in 40% of the year’s income on Sant Jordi. One study found that rose prices peak at 8am, and then decline as demand and the quality of available flowers falls—ending the day at just one-sixth the price. A trade in second-hand roses picks up after lunch. No doubt, hearts are broken by dinner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The event has been affected by shifting political tides. It took on added significance following the death of Francisco Franco, as the Spanish dictator had censored books and curbed use of the Catalan language. As &lt;em&gt;La Vanguardia&lt;/em&gt;, a daily newspaper, described the first post-Franco event in 1976: Barcelona “lived a different atmosphere yesterday. Different, absolutely, from the Sant Jordi of other years. There was a call to democracy. To freedoms.” Now, as the region bids for independence from the rest of Spain, Catalan-language literature has become ubiquitous at the street stalls, accounting for more than a third of the books sold.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 1995 UNESCO designated April 23rd World Book Day, but in Catalonia events maintain a local feel, with flags and banners emblazoned with Sant Jordi’s cross. The day is a celebration of love, literature and the love of literature. This year, as always, Ms Santos will use the same fountain pen to sign books for readers; the only thing that changes is the colour of the ink she uses. This year she has opted for deep red with a particularly appropriate name: “Dragon’s blood”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:06:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The risks to migrants of crossing the English Channel]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/04/23/the-risks-to-migrants-of-crossing-the-english-channel]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_blp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-23T12:19:18Z&quot;&gt;Apr 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;STAND ON Britain’s southern shore, looking towards France, and your gaze will settle upon the world’s busiest shipping lane. Over 600 cargo ships pass through the English Channel each day. Many are heading to and from London or Rotterdam, separated by what amounts to a motorway-style central reservation that they may not cross (see image). Adding to the traffic are more than 60 daily cross-Channel ferry services, as well as fishermen and private recreation vessels that can number in the thousands on a summer weekend. To date, only small numbers of migrants have tried to reach Britain this way, but their numbers are rising: 539 migrants attempted the journey last year, according to figures from the Home Office, but around 80% of these attempts were made in the last three months of 2018. What are the risks and rewards of making the crossing? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The risks are clear: this is a testing crossing even for an experienced sailor with a seaworthy boat. It is not just maritime collisions that skippers have to think about. Tides in the Channel are among the biggest in the world. The island of Jersey has a maximum tidal range of over 12m (39ft). At low tide up to 3km of beach and rock can be exposed. The channel goes from 240km at its widest point to 33km at its narrowest, which is why tidal races such as the Alderney Race, a strait just off the Cotentin Peninsula of France, or the waters just off Portland Bill near Weymouth are so notorious. These can create treacherous seas even on the calmest of days. Then there are sandbanks, shoals, isolated rocks and other dangers to negotiate—and that’s before the weather plays its unpredictable part. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet for migrants and traffickers this particular route also has a definite upside. Perhaps because of longstanding assumptions about the sea’s effectiveness as a barrier, there is little in the way of security controlling the movement of pleasure craft. Many hundreds of ports along Britain’s south coast can be entered by small boats, which are greeted by little more than a poster (see image) suggesting that a phone call to the authorities or the national yachtline may be required to declare the immigrant status of certain sailors. Official ports of entry such as Portsmouth or Southampton are for ferries and commercial traffic and a world away from an unmanned wooden jetty or marina berth where people come and go at all hours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_blp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190427_blp502.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190427_blp502.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190427_blp502.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190427_blp502.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190427_blp502.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190427_blp502.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190427_blp502.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190427_blp502.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190427_blp502.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The traditional flag etiquette for those arriving from a foreign trip was to fly a yellow quarantine (Q) flag before getting the all-clear from officials who would check on travellers’ health and customs matters. The flying of the flag is still a requirement for ships coming to Britain from outside the EU (owing to concerns about disease more than migrants), but small boats do not always adhere to the rule. And a craft registered within the EU and wishing to enter another EU port need not show the Q flag at all, so there is no indication whether it has come from abroad or from just up the coast. On many occasions your correspondent has enjoyed a breezy daytime crossing, a berth in a French port, &lt;em&gt;steak frites&lt;/em&gt; on shore, and a jaunt back home the next day, with never a form filed or passport asked for. Britain’s Border Force has four cutters that are unlikely to patrol en masse in the Dover Strait. They may not be enough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2019 00:06:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Liberals need to ditch the technocratic for higher purpose]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/04/23/liberals-need-to-ditch-the-technocratic-for-higher-purpose]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190413_OPP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-23T12:43:09Z&quot;&gt;Apr 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE WORD liberalism is ambiguous. To some it evokes the generosity of the state; to others it suggests a surrender to the free market. Supporters see it as a way to guard free expression; critics consider it a means to allow noxious ideas. But this is hardly new: throughout its history, the term has meant different things to different people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Helena Rosenblatt, a historian of political thought at the City University of New York, has peered into its origins and evolution in her book, “The Lost History of Liberalism”. The concept flourished in France in the early 1800s to describe the emergence of individual rights, the rule of law and representative government. Only later was it adopted in Britain and America (and in the second half of the 20th century applied to left-of-centre politics in America).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s Open Future initiative, we are publishing an excerpt from Ms Rosenblatt’s book, on Adam Smith’s liberalism and colonial America. It is followed by a short interview with her about the need for liberals to ditch technocratic nerdery and once again embrace narrative, sentiment and higher purpose.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*     &lt;span &gt; &lt;/span&gt;*      *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From Liberal Charters to Liberal Constitutions&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Excerpt from “The Lost History of Liberalism: From Ancient Rome to the Twenty-First Century” by Helena Rosenblatt (Princeton University Press, 2018)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since medieval times, kings and emperors had granted charters conferring rights or privileges to towns, companies, or individuals. The sovereigns granting them, or the charters themselves, were called liberal when the rights they conferred were regarded as robust and, for example, involved generous economic concessions and considerable self­-government. When Englishmen left their homeland for the New World, they brought with them what they often called liberal charters establishing the colonies, and when tensions arose between England and America in the mid-­eighteenth century, much discussion revolved around whether the British government had the right to change the terms of these charters and impose new regulations and taxes on the colonies. Americans insisted that such impositions violated the charters as well as the protections accorded to them by the British constitution. They were no longer generous, not based on the principle of reciprocity; they were no longer liberal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was in this highly politicized environment that Adam Smith published his famous book, &lt;em&gt;An Inquiry into the Nature and Causes of the Wealth of Nations&lt;/em&gt; (1776). Today regarded as a foundational text of classical liberalism, it spoke directly to American concerns. Smith himself called it a “very violent attack...upon the whole commercial system of Great Britain.” Not only did he denounce English trade policies and advocate instead what he called a “liberal system of free exportation and free importation,” but he used the economy of North America to highlight the flaws of that of England. America illustrated the advantages of a system of natural liberty, in which the unimpeded investment in agriculture was causing rapid progress toward wealth and greatness. By contrast, Britain’s complicated and corrupt system of tariffs, bounties, monopolies, and other legal devices was just enriching the already wealthy while leaving the rest of the country impoverished.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190413_OPP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190413_OPP503.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190413_OPP503.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190413_OPP503.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190413_OPP503.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190413_OPP503.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190413_OPP503.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190413_OPP503.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190413_OPP503.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190413_OPP503.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Smith’s use of the word “liberal” in his &lt;em&gt;Wealth of Nations&lt;/em&gt; conjured up a centuries-­old meaning with which we are now familiar. It was a word whose moral meaning every educated gentleman of his time would have understood. In book IV, chapter 9, Smith favored “allowing every man to pursue his own interest his own way &lt;em&gt;upon the liberal plan of equality, liberty and justice&lt;/em&gt;.” Smith’s “liberal plan,” his readers would immediately have recognized, was about not only freedom but also generosity and reciprocity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is often forgotten that Smith’s first major and possibly most influential work was on ethics. In his &lt;em&gt;Theory of Moral Sentiments&lt;/em&gt; (1759), Smith wrote that “he is not a citizen who does not wish to promote, by every means in his power, the welfare of the whole society of his fellow-­citizens.” “The wise and virtuous man,” he continued, “is at all times willing that his own private interest should be sacrificed to the public interest of his own particular order or society. He is at all times willing, too, that the interest of this order or society should be sacrificed to the greater interest of the state or sovereignty of which it is only a subordinate part.” Moreover, Smith endorsed “liberality” as one of the cardinal virtues and the treatise contains a long discussion of gratitude and benevolence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The liberal principles Smith advocated in the &lt;em&gt;Wealth of Nations&lt;/em&gt; were “in the interest of the public,” while mercantile ones favored the “mean rapacity” of British merchants and manufacturers who, in league with the landowning aristocracy, con­spired against the public good. Smith defended free trade on the grounds that it would increase the welfare of “the lowest ranks of the people” and work “for the benefit of the poor and the indigent.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unsurprisingly, Americans read the &lt;em&gt;Wealth of Nations&lt;/em&gt; as a vindication of their policy of separation from England. Within a few months of its publication, the Continental Congress opened American ports to all foreign vessels and American calls for free trade grew louder. The new country’s very survival depended on it. Through the negotiation of new and liberal trade agreements with the nations of the world, Americans hoped for the advent of a new era of prosperity and peace. And on July 4, 1776, the Continental Congress adopted the Declaration of Independence by which the United States announced its secession from the British Empire and its reasons for doing so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Governments, the Americans argued, derived their authority from the consent of the governed. They were instituted to secure the unalienable rights of men. Whenever a government became destructive toward those ends, it was the right of the people to resist and even overthrow it. Men, moreover, were created equal and possessed the rights to life, liberty, and the pursuit of happiness. All thirteen new states soon provided themselves with written constitutions establishing virtually the same principle: it was to secure the unalienable rights of men that governments were instituted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, the concern for rights and their protections was not new in 1776. The British government itself recognized that it had granted charters conferring rights and privileges to the colonies. A major difference in the Declaration of Independence was that rights were now seen as natural, equal, and binding. They were no longer understood to be privileges granted by a liberal sovereign and thus subject to revocation by him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190413_OPP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190413_OPP506.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190413_OPP506.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190413_OPP506.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190413_OPP506.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190413_OPP506.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190413_OPP506.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190413_OPP506.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190413_OPP506.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190413_OPP506.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This inflection in the concept of rights involved a corresponding change in the use of the word “liberal.” While it had previously been employed to designate the generous and freedom­-loving concessions of a sovereign to his subjects, or the magnanimous and tolerant behavior of an aristocratic elite, it was now used to describe the generous and free constitution of a people who legislated themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[…]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A liberal country was not a democratic one. By any measure, the United States was not a democracy in the eighteenth century. And, in any case, to most people at the time, “democracy” was synonymous with anarchy or mob rule. But neither did the United States recognize hereditary privilege. And thus it demanded that each &lt;em&gt;citizen&lt;/em&gt; display a “truly noble liberality of sentiment and affection,” a civic commitment by each individual “to embrace the good of all.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;_____________________ &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Excerpted from “The Lost History of Liberalism: From Ancient Rome to the Twenty-First Century” by Helena Rosenblatt. Published by Princeton University Press. Copyright © 2018 by Helena Rosenblatt. All rights reserved.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;*      *     &lt;span &gt; &lt;/span&gt;*&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;An interview with Helena Rosenblatt &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Economist:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Historically speaking, are there certain social or economic conditions that tend to make liberalism popular? And if so, what factors achieve the opposite effect?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Rosenblatt:&lt;/strong&gt; Liberalism was born in a crisis that was both economic and political, namely the French Revolution. During the 19th century, however, economic and political crises also caused many to turn away from liberalism and toward socialism. In the 20th century, the Great Depression gave rise to the liberal New Deal. Today, downturns in certain sectors of the economy have attracted the electorate to populism. So, it is hard to generalise about the influence of social or economic trends on liberalism’s popularity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190413_OPP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190413_OPP504.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190413_OPP504.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190413_OPP504.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190413_OPP504.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190413_OPP504.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190413_OPP504.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190413_OPP504.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190413_OPP504.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190413_OPP504.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Personally, I believe that its prospects are greatly improved when liberals can deliver a clear message that is both hopeful and morally uplifting. History shows us that they are successful when they don’t just appeal to people’s economic needs and interests, but also to their sentiments, moral compasses and even certain needs of the soul. It seems that communicating a moral vision through inspiring leadership is more important today than ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Economist:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; Liberalism prides itself on rationality to such a degree that it seems outside the emotive, narrative-driven part of people&amp;#x27;s decisions, attitudes and values. Little wonder it&amp;#x27;s on the back-foot as populists are on the march. Can liberalism embrace sentiment and story to compete without losing its soul of reason?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Rosenblatt:&lt;/strong&gt; Of course! The majority of liberals in the past embraced sentiments at least as much as reason, and believed in values as much as they believed in policies and procedures. Benjamin Constant and Madame de Staël, whom I argue are two of the real founders of “liberalism,” wrote copiously about emotions and feelings. Constant emphasised the importance of religious sentiments in any liberal society, while Madame de Staël wrote novels to cultivate the feelings she felt were needed to support and nurture a liberal political system, particularly generosity and compassion in her readers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And of course, both liberals believed in reason, science and enlightenment too. Sentiments and reason were not seen as antithetical to each other. It is only recently that liberals have lost touch with that crucial side of liberalism and become more policy-oriented, even technocratic in outlook. They speak of interests and choices more than values and obligations. I believe that people are craving for meaning and a higher purpose to their lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; Why did France become the cradle of liberalism?  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Rosenblatt:&lt;/strong&gt; Many of your readers will undoubtedly be surprised to hear that liberalism owes its origins to France. We are so used to taking for granted that liberalism is an age-old and venerable Anglo-American tradition. But if you follow the history of the actual word, as my book does, you learn that “liberalism” was coined and first theorised in France in the early 1810s as a result of the French Revolution. It stood for a cluster of principles that the more moderate revolutionaries were fighting for: the rule of law, civil equality, constitutional and representative government and a number of individual rights. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interestingly, evidence suggests that the word “liberalism” was invented as a term of abuse by its enemies and was originally meant to stigmatise these principles as a “religio-political heresy.” For most of the nineteenth century, liberalism was widely seen as a French doctrine and was closely associated with France’s successive revolutions (1789, 1830, 1848 and 1871). “Liberalism” remained a rare word in the language of English and American politics. It only gained currency in America’s political vocabulary in the early 20th century, and by then its meaning had been utterly transformed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Economist:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; You note that liberalism originated in France in the 1800s but that the term &amp;quot;liberal&amp;quot; appeared earlier, notably by Adam Smith in the 1700s. How did the concept develop in Britain and France—and what was the interaction between the two places?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Rosenblatt:&lt;/strong&gt; The word “liberal” had been in use for centuries before “liberalism” was coined; but it was not a political or economic term. Instead it designated the ideal qualities of the member of a ruling elite. In Britain it referred to the virtues expected of a gentleman, in France those of a nobleman: magnanimity, generosity, devotion to freedom and the common good. Adam Smith used the word this way in his famous text, The Wealth of Nations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The French Revolution, while giving birth to the word “liberalism,” also added a new and political meaning to the word “liberal”. In Britain, when the word meant something political, it was often rendered in italics, or with an “e” at the end to indicate its foreignness and dangerousness. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gradually, both “liberal” and “liberalism” lost their revolutionary connotations. And with the advance of industrialisation, “liberalism” took on new meanings. It could now designate certain policies toward the economy, such as “new liberalism” and “classical liberalism,” the first favoring increased government intervention and the latter opposing it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Economist:&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Why does it look like so many Americans are ready to discard it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Rosenblatt:&lt;/strong&gt; The attraction of dictators grows in periods of uncertainty, such as the one we are living through today, when people are vulnerable to simple solutions. Charismatic leaders emerge who appeal to their emotions and often to their basest instincts. Many liberal politicians today have lost touch with people. They seem elitist, technocratic and aloof. We need leaders who can not only articulate good policies and laws, but who can also inspire people and morally uplift them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the paucity of good liberal leadership is only partly to blame. A huge problem, I believe, is our undervalued and thus underfunded public education system. Many voters today are woefully ignorant of their history and unschooled in the basic principles of citizenship. Moreover, there has been too much emphasis on vocational training and too little on the liberal arts and humanities. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 19th-century liberals knew that the survival of liberal democracies required a politically-educated citizenry. As Alexis de Tocqueville said, it is necessary to “educate democracy.” And this, he said, was “the primary duty imposed on the leaders of society today.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 22:06:33 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sri Lanka’s new threat, and more from our daily podcast]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/23/sri-lankas-new-threat-and-more-from-our-daily-podcast]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/the_intelligence_59.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-23T11:20:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AFTER CO-ORDINATED bomb attacks that killed hundreds, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/22/the-blame-game-begins-after-sri-lanka-bombings&quot;&gt;Sri Lanka is reeling&lt;/a&gt;. But if the government was so consumed by internal struggles as to miss warnings, how can it respond to the devastation? Also, we take a look at global efforts to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/04/17/alan-garcia-perus-ex-president-killed-himself-as-police-sought-to-arrest-him&quot;&gt;contain corruption&lt;/a&gt;, drawing lessons from Brazil’s sprawling &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/04/13/brazils-biggest-anti-corruption-investigation-is-at-a-turning-point&quot;&gt;Lava Jato investigation&lt;/a&gt;. And we pay a visit to what will be the precise geographic centre of the European Union—if and when Britain leaves. Runtime: 22 min.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/worryingnewthreat-tragedyinsrilanka&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2019 19:07:19 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>