<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump: foreign policy showman]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/07/04/donald-trump-foreign-policy-showman]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_USP501_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-03T16:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;JULY 4th &lt;span&gt;has not come&lt;/span&gt; a day too soon for Donald Trump. As Lexington sat down to write, the president was finalising plans for the “Salute to America” pageant he had dreamed of presiding over ever since witnessing Emmanuel Macron’s columns of armoured cars and strapping legionnaires two years ago. Tanks, planes and other things that go were promised—plus, Mr Trump teased by tweet, “an address by your favourite President, me!” Trump devotees, including the donors and other cheerleaders for whom a section of the National Mall had been cordoned off, were in for a treat.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equally delightful for the president, his critics were outraged. There were reports that $2.5m in national park receipts had been siphoned off to help foot the jamboree’s bill, and that Mr Trump’s tanks could damage the underground vaults of the Lincoln Memorial. The shame of Independence Day being so politicised was manifest. For a president who has elevated “owning the libs” from a Twitter meme to a governing strategy, this was both part of the plan and a timely distraction from more damning events. Mr Trump has issued a series of bold foreign-policy pledges for his first term: including to improve America’s trade with China, deal with the nuclear threats of North Korea and Iran, wind down the war in Afghanistan, pacify the Middle East and restore order to America’s southern border. And it has become apparent, in a recent cascade of bad news for his dealmaking ambitions, that he has a rapidly diminishing chance of honouring any of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a meeting with his Chinese counterpart at the G20 summit in Osaka he agreed to extend trade negotiations with China—but only after making concessions, including the reversal of his decision to blacklist Huawei, a Chinese telecoms firm his administration accuses of spying. President Xi Jinping also adopted a less conciliatory public tone than he had before the two leaders’ previous meeting, last year in Argentina. The prospects of a substantial China settlement appear remote. Mr Trump’s subsequently arranged trip to meet Kim Jong Un on the front-line between the two Koreas looked like an effort to divert attention from this climb-down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His Korea trip, in turn, provided a reminder that despite Mr Trump’s affectionate encouragement, Mr Kim has taken no step to denuclearise the peninsula, nor—even within the administration—is he expected to. Happily for Mr Trump, the much-criticised efforts of his daughter Ivanka to promote herself on the Korean front-line provided an additional diversion. Ms Trump’s parading for the cameras was the distraction from the main distraction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The list goes on. Iran said this week that it had stockpiled more than 300kg of enriched uranium—Mr Trump having torn up its promise to America not to do so. America’s negotiators meanwhile prepared to rejoin peace talks with the Taliban in the absence—at the militants’ insistence—of any representative of Afghanistan’s elected government. The insurgents are also stepping up attacks across the country. If Mr Trump goes ahead with the troop withdrawal he claims has already taken place, he risks triggering an explosion. As for the Middle East, better not ask. The summit in Bahrain last week at which Jared Kushner unveiled his economic blueprint for peace was a farce. The president gave it a wide berth; no plausible Palestinian attended. Which leaves the border—and this may be Mr Trump’s most damaging failure of all. Despite his effort to push Mexico into deterring border crossings, they are soaring, which is dismaying his base even as the administration’s brutal treatment of poor migrants angers everyone else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is not all Mr Trump’s fault. He has taken on major problems, some of which defeated his predecessors. And on China and Afghanistan especially his approach has been novel, good in parts and may yet form a basis for progress. The problem is his relentless divisiveness, hitherto more damaging at home than abroad, is hurting his prospects. His Iran, North Korea and Middle East polices were launched largely in an effort to repudiate his Democratic predecessor. This has encouraged the Democrats to oppose all his efforts, even—as on Afghanistan and China—where they share his aims. That partisan schism is in turn encouraging Mr Trump’s foreign counterparts to play a long-game—to think they can hold out for better terms from a future Democratic administration, or that such an administration would in any event scrap whatever deals Mr Trump might have done.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only way the president looks able to unlock the dramatic progress he craves, on any of these fronts, would be by making further concessions: for example, by agreeing to a weak trade pact with China or a replica of Mr Obama’s Iran deal. Yet he could in that case expect a backlash from within his own party. Marco Rubio, one of several Republicans senators who consider foreign policy a safe space from which to criticise the president, called the concessions on Huawei a “catastrophic mistake”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This reflects a broader dilemma for Mr Trump. Because he now has little prospect of expanding his support—beyond the large minority of Americans who are not offended by him—he must at all costs keep the Republican coalition together. He is therefore constrained by politics as well as the poor progress of his deal-making efforts: both are stuck. The daily controversies Mr Trump generates—including this week’s Trump show on the steps of the Lincoln Memorial—are meant to mask that reality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Tanks but no tanks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is depressing how well the tactic is working. By rising to the daily bait, Mr Trump’s opponents are doing as he is: whipping up their supporters, without in any way impressing the other side. To be fair, it is hard not to be thus riled; the controversies Mr Trump stirs, including over his politicising of Independence Day, are often real scandals. Yet his critics risk losing sight of his actual record. It suggests an administration that is less unstable than many believe; but one with weak support and signature policies, fully 18 months out from an election, that are mostly running into the sand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 17:40:27 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OPEC’s predictable deal cannot hide its giant problems]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/07/03/opecs-predictable-deal-cannot-hide-its-giant-problems]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_FNP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-03T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE MEETING of the Organisation of Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC) in Vienna on July 1st and 2nd was, in some respects, a snooze. The deal announced by OPEC and its allies was the continuation of one struck late last year. For at least another nine months, daily production will remain 1.2m barrels below last October’s level. But behind the predictability giant problems loom, for the oil market and OPEC itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America and Iran, an OPEC member, are flirting with war. The decline in Venezuela’s production has steepened since January, when America announced sanctions against PDVSA, its national oil company. Escalating conflict in Libya could cause production there to plummet as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, oil producers are more concerned about weakening demand than tight supply. The price of Brent crude climbed to $74 a barrel in late April, after President Donald Trump said he would not grant waivers to sanctions on Iranian exports. It then plunged in May as inventories built up, investors fretted about the trade war and government bond yields tumbled in America and Europe. The announcement on June 29th that America and China would resume trade talks has helped, but a deal is far from certain. Faced with shaky economic indicators, OPEC is keen to avoid a market awash with oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_FNC350_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But OPEC’s decision to trim output points to further uncertainties within the alliance. The first is how long it will be willing to continue losing market share to America. In 2014, as American oil flowed freely, OPEC declined to curb output, hoping that slumping prices would teach gung-ho American oilmen a lesson. The ensuing crash pained petrostates and wildcatters alike. But shale production has roared back—last year America produced more crude than any other country—and OPEC has become reluctant to let prices dive again. The result is that OPEC’s share of global production has dipped, from 42.2% in 2016 to 39.2% in March, and America’s has risen, from 10.9% to 14.5% (see chart).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second question is whether Saudi Arabia and Russia will start to feel the pain of production cuts more acutely. Sinking output in Venezuela and Iran has helped OPEC keep a lid on supply even as American output has risen. Wood Mackenzie, an energy-research group, estimates that continental America (excluding Alaska and Hawaii) will pump 1.2m more barrels of crude a day this year than in 2018. Iran will pump 1m fewer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That helps explain why, despite cutting production somewhat, Saudi Arabia accounts for almost as much of the global market as it did in 2016. Russia has been even more protected. That year it agreed to work with OPEC to stabilise the oil price. Its influence in the Middle East has grown and it has helped shape OPEC’s decisions, big and small. On June 29th Vladimir Putin, Russia’s president, said that he had agreed with Saudi Arabia to extend OPEC’s production cuts, making the imminent OPEC meeting in Vienna seem all but redundant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russia has given up relatively little in return. In most months its output has exceeded the level it had agreed with OPEC. (May was a rare—and possibly unintended—exception: an important crude pipeline suffered contamination.) In March its share of the global market was higher than in 2016. “By doing only a little, they got quite a lot,” says Martijn Rats of Morgan Stanley, a bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPEC and Russia look set to continue co-operating. The meeting in Vienna included a charter to formalise OPEC’s partnerships with non-members. But there is a limit to how much further output in Venezuela and Iran can fall. If oil prices remain low, Saudi Arabia and Russia may face an uncomfortable choice: let prices dip or cut production more steeply, thereby losing market share and propping up American shale. This month’s meeting was straightforward. Future ones may be less so. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 17:40:26 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The calm within the storm]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/07/03/donald-trump-foreign-policy-showman]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_USP501_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-03T16:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;JULY 4th &lt;span&gt;has not come&lt;/span&gt; a day too soon for Donald Trump. As Lexington sat down to write, the president was finalising plans for the “Salute to America” pageant he had dreamed of presiding over ever since witnessing Emmanuel Macron’s columns of armoured cars and strapping legionnaires two years ago. Tanks, planes and other things that go were promised—plus, Mr Trump teased by tweet, “an address by your favourite President, me!” Trump devotees, including the donors and other cheerleaders for whom a section of the National Mall had been cordoned off, were in for a treat.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Equally delightful for the president, his critics were outraged. There were reports that $2.5m in national park receipts had been siphoned off to help foot the jamboree’s bill, and that Mr Trump’s tanks could damage the underground vaults of the Lincoln Memorial. The shame of Independence Day being so politicised was manifest. For a president who has elevated “owning the libs” from a Twitter meme to a governing strategy, this was both part of the plan and a timely distraction from more damning events. Mr Trump has issued a series of bold foreign-policy pledges for his first term: including to improve America’s trade with China, deal with the nuclear threats of North Korea and Iran, wind down the war in Afghanistan, pacify the Middle East and restore order to America’s southern border. And it has become apparent, in a recent cascade of bad news for his dealmaking ambitions, that he has a rapidly diminishing chance of honouring any of them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a meeting with his Chinese counterpart at the G20 summit in Osaka he agreed to extend trade negotiations with China—but only after making concessions, including the reversal of his decision to blacklist Huawei, a Chinese telecoms firm his administration accuses of spying. President Xi Jinping also adopted a less conciliatory public tone than he had before the two leaders’ previous meeting, last year in Argentina. The prospects of a substantial China settlement appear remote. Mr Trump’s subsequently arranged trip to meet Kim Jong Un on the front-line between the two Koreas looked like an effort to divert attention from this climb-down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His Korea trip, in turn, provided a reminder that despite Mr Trump’s affectionate encouragement, Mr Kim has taken no step to denuclearise the peninsula, nor—even within the administration—is he expected to. Happily for Mr Trump, the much-criticised efforts of his daughter Ivanka to promote herself on the Korean front-line provided an additional diversion. Ms Trump’s parading for the cameras was the distraction from the main distraction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The list goes on. Iran said this week that it had stockpiled more than 300kg of enriched uranium—Mr Trump having torn up its promise to America not to do so. America’s negotiators meanwhile prepared to rejoin peace talks with the Taliban in the absence—at the militants’ insistence—of any representative of Afghanistan’s elected government. The insurgents are also stepping up attacks across the country. If Mr Trump goes ahead with the troop withdrawal he claims has already taken place, he risks triggering an explosion. As for the Middle East, better not ask. The summit in Bahrain last week at which Jared Kushner unveiled his economic blueprint for peace was a farce. The president gave it a wide berth; no plausible Palestinian attended. Which leaves the border—and this may be Mr Trump’s most damaging failure of all. Despite his effort to push Mexico into deterring border crossings, they are soaring, which is dismaying his base even as the administration’s brutal treatment of poor migrants angers everyone else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is not all Mr Trump’s fault. He has taken on major problems, some of which defeated his predecessors. And on China and Afghanistan especially his approach has been novel, good in parts and may yet form a basis for progress. The problem is his relentless divisiveness, hitherto more damaging at home than abroad, is hurting his prospects. His Iran, North Korea and Middle East polices were launched largely in an effort to repudiate his Democratic predecessor. This has encouraged the Democrats to oppose all his efforts, even—as on Afghanistan and China—where they share his aims. That partisan schism is in turn encouraging Mr Trump’s foreign counterparts to play a long-game—to think they can hold out for better terms from a future Democratic administration, or that such an administration would in any event scrap whatever deals Mr Trump might have done.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only way the president looks able to unlock the dramatic progress he craves, on any of these fronts, would be by making further concessions: for example, by agreeing to a weak trade pact with China or a replica of Mr Obama’s Iran deal. Yet he could in that case expect a backlash from within his own party. Marco Rubio, one of several Republicans senators who consider foreign policy a safe space from which to criticise the president, called the concessions on Huawei a “catastrophic mistake”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This reflects a broader dilemma for Mr Trump. Because he now has little prospect of expanding his support—beyond the large minority of Americans who are not offended by him—he must at all costs keep the Republican coalition together. He is therefore constrained by politics as well as the poor progress of his deal-making efforts: both are stuck. The daily controversies Mr Trump generates—including this week’s Trump show on the steps of the Lincoln Memorial—are meant to mask that reality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Tanks but no tanks&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is depressing how well the tactic is working. By rising to the daily bait, Mr Trump’s opponents are doing as he is: whipping up their supporters, without in any way impressing the other side. To be fair, it is hard not to be thus riled; the controversies Mr Trump stirs, including over his politicising of Independence Day, are often real scandals. Yet his critics risk losing sight of his actual record. It suggests an administration that is less unstable than many believe; but one with weak support and signature policies, fully 18 months out from an election, that are mostly running into the sand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 11:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EU leaders’ arduous deal on top jobs may yet fall apart]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/07/03/eu-leaders-arduous-deal-on-top-jobs-may-yet-fall-apart]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_EUP002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-03T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EMMANUEL MACRON is a lucky man. His rivals and opponents have a habit of shooting themselves in the foot. In the French presidential election in 2017 his main centre-right rival was consumed by a corruption scandal. Earlier this year anti-government gilets jaunes protesters surged then faded as disorganisation and public-relations mistakes took their toll. And this week Mr Macron obtained something close to a dream outcome in the allocation of big European jobs, again largely thanks to others’ mistakes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After three days of talks the EU’s leaders (minus Theresa May of Brexiting Britain) agreed to nominate Ursula von der Leyen, Germany’s defence minister, to the presidency of the European Commission, the EU’s executive. A moderate Christian Democrat close to Angela Merkel, Mrs von der Leyen shares some of Mr Macron’s federalist inclinations. Also, she did not run in the recent European election campaign as a Spitzenkandidat or “lead candidate” for the commission job—a convention that the French president wants to kill off. The presidency of the European Central Bank (ECB) goes to Christine Lagarde, the French head of the International Monetary Fund who, like Mr Macron, is on the dovish side of Europe’s economic debates. The presidency of the European Council, the group of EU heads of government, goes to Charles Michel, Belgium’s liberal prime minister and a Macron ally. The final appointment sees Josep Borrell, a veteran Spanish social democrat, as the EU’s high representative for foreign affairs and security policy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Macron is delighted with the outcome,” observes Mujtaba Rahman of the Eurasia Group, a consultancy. He points out that the result was less Mr Macron’s design than the product of others’ errors.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first took place last November, when the European People’s Party (EPP), the group of centre-right parties, picked Manfred Weber, a Bavarian member of the European Parliament, as its lead candidate. The EPP came first in the European Parliament elections that took place from May 23rd to 26th, which under the Spitzenkandidat convention would have made Mr Weber the prime candidate for the commission. But he has no executive experience, little profile outside Brussels and his native Germany and a reputation for making excuses for Hungary’s authoritarian government. Moreover, the EPP lost seats, along with its traditional partners in the centre-left Socialists and Democrats (S&amp;amp;D) group. Mr Weber was too contentious a figure for the newly fragmented parliament to settle on his candidacy, or a single alternative. Although Mrs Merkel, the EPP’s most powerful leader, backed her compatriot, other leaders objected to him at a summit on June 20th. Unable to reach a deal, the leaders postponed their talks to June 30th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was Mrs Merkel who made the second mistake. In discussions with Mr Macron and the prime ministers of Spain and the Netherlands, the German chancellor agreed to a compromise whereby Frans Timmermans, the S&amp;amp;D’s lead candidate and a Dutch vice-president of the commission, would take the commission presidency, with Mr Weber becoming president of the parliament and a liberal running the council. Mrs Merkel’s colleagues in the EPP, such as Leo Varadkar of Ireland, objected that the parliament job was too puny a prize for coming first. The leaders of eastern states and Italy, too, dislike Mr Timmermans for his record of tough action against illiberal abuses. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The summit on June 30th dragged on into July 1st. By breakfast it was clear that neither Mr Timmermans nor Mr Weber could command the necessary support. Leaders suspended the talks until the following morning, when Mr Macron floated the idea of Mrs von der Leyen. Acceptable to Mrs Merkel, the rest of the EPP, the easterners and to left-of-centre governments, she was the tolerable candidate exhausted leaders could accept. With a German heading for the commission, Mr Macron could press for a Frenchwoman at the ECB.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet the package did not inspire universal approval. Some, especially in the EPP and S&amp;amp;D, complain that Ms von der Leyen lacks a democratic mandate, having not campaigned as a Spitzenkandidat. Her struggles to modernise the armed forces cause some to question her competence: “Germany’s weakest minister”, sneered Martin Schulz, a German former president of the European Parliament. Other objections have also bubbled up. All four of the big jobs settled at the summit go to western Europeans at a time of heightened tensions between easterners and westerners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of which makes support for the package in the parliament uncertain. In votes on the parliament’s own presidency on July 3rd MEPs from the “grand coalition” of moderate pro-EU parties—the EPP, S&amp;amp;D and liberals—splintered as some social democrats backed the Green candidate and easterners in the EPP backed a Czech from a more right-wing group. David Sassoli, an Italian social democrat supposedly supported by the grand coalition, won with only 345 of its 442 votes, and no others, meaning that he does not enjoy a majority among the parliament’s 751 members.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That may suggest that Mrs von der Leyen is also not guaranteed the majority she needs to secure the commission presidency. That vote is due to take place between July 15th and 18th. If she fails, leaders will have to return to the drawing board. They might then turn to Margrethe Vestager, the liberal competition commissioner who was a Spitzenkandidat in all but name and fairly widely acceptable. Otherwise the options are few.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if she does succeed, what sort of a commission president will Mrs von der Leyen make? It is true that after five years of her as defence minister, the German armed forces are still plagued by equipment shortages and technical faults. German opposition parties are holding an investigation into her extensive and expensive use of consultancies. Yet her job is known as a graveyard of careers for good reason—the problems long predate her tenure—and Mrs von der Leyen has done well to survive in it. Multilingual and instinctively Atlanticist, she is respected by NATO colleagues for having fought for budget increases for Germany’s armed forces and presiding over expanding German military missions in places like Mali and Lithuania. She has recently warned against European complacency about China’s rise and intentions. Addressing MEPs in Strasbourg on July 3rd she struck a conciliatory tone in comments in German, French and English.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There may have been better candidates for the commission job—for example, Ms Vestager—but there were certainly much worse ones. Likewise, Ms Lagarde (see next story), Mr Michel and Mr Borrell are all competent figures. The latter will be the most heavyweight person to hold the foreign-policy role since its creation in 2009. Europe runs on compromises like this one. It could do worse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 04:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[OPEC’s predictable deal cannot conceal its long-term difficulties]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/07/03/opecs-predictable-deal-cannot-conceal-its-long-term-difficulties]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_FNP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-03T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE MEETING of the Organisation of Petroleum Exporting Countries (OPEC) in Vienna on July 1st and 2nd was, in some respects, a snooze. The deal announced by OPEC and its allies was the continuation of one struck late last year. For at least another nine months, daily production will remain 1.2m barrels below last October’s level. But behind the predictability giant problems loom, for the oil market and OPEC itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America and Iran, an OPEC member, are flirting with war. The decline in Venezuela’s production has steepened since January, when America announced sanctions against PDVSA, its national oil company. Escalating conflict in Libya could cause production there to plummet as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, oil producers are more concerned about weakening demand than tight supply. The price of Brent crude climbed to $74 a barrel in late April, after President Donald Trump said he would not grant waivers to sanctions on Iranian exports. It then plunged in May as inventories built up, investors fretted about the trade war and government bond yields tumbled in America and Europe. The announcement on June 29th that America and China would resume trade talks has helped, but a deal is far from certain. Faced with shaky economic indicators, OPEC is keen to avoid a market awash with oil.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_FNC350_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190706_FNC350_0.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But OPEC’s decision to trim output points to further uncertainties within the alliance. The first is how long it will be willing to continue losing market share to America. In 2014, as American oil flowed freely, OPEC declined to curb output, hoping that slumping prices would teach gung-ho American oilmen a lesson. The ensuing crash pained petrostates and wildcatters alike. But shale production has roared back—last year America produced more crude than any other country—and OPEC has become reluctant to let prices dive again. The result is that OPEC’s share of global production has dipped, from 42.2% in 2016 to 39.2% in March, and America’s has risen, from 10.9% to 14.5% (see chart).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second question is whether Saudi Arabia and Russia will start to feel the pain of production cuts more acutely. Sinking output in Venezuela and Iran has helped OPEC keep a lid on supply even as American output has risen. Wood Mackenzie, an energy-research group, estimates that continental America (excluding Alaska and Hawaii) will pump 1.2m more barrels of crude a day this year than in 2018. Iran will pump 1m fewer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That helps explain why, despite cutting production somewhat, Saudi Arabia accounts for almost as much of the global market as it did in 2016. Russia has been even more protected. That year it agreed to work with OPEC to stabilise the oil price. Its influence in the Middle East has grown and it has helped shape OPEC’s decisions, big and small. On June 29th Vladimir Putin, Russia’s president, said that he had agreed with Saudi Arabia to extend OPEC’s production cuts, making the imminent OPEC meeting in Vienna seem all but redundant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russia has given up relatively little in return. In most months its output has exceeded the level it had agreed with OPEC. (May was a rare—and possibly unintended—exception: an important crude pipeline suffered contamination.) In March its share of the global market was higher than in 2016. “By doing only a little, they got quite a lot,” says Martijn Rats of Morgan Stanley, a bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OPEC and Russia look set to continue co-operating. The meeting in Vienna included a charter to formalise OPEC’s partnerships with non-members. But there is a limit to how much further output in Venezuela and Iran can fall. If oil prices remain low, Saudi Arabia and Russia may face an uncomfortable choice: let prices dip or cut production more steeply, thereby losing market share and propping up American shale. This month’s meeting was straightforward. Future ones may be less so. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 04:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Boris Johnson may reverse Britain’s embrace of sin taxes]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/07/03/boris-johnson-may-reverse-britains-embrace-of-sin-taxes]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BRP003.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-03T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;CONSIDERING THEY call themselves Conservatives, Britain’s recent leaders have been unusually willing to meddle with individual choices. Plastic straws are to be banned, over concerns about pollution of the oceans. A tax on plastic bags, introduced in 2015, may double under plans currently out for consultation. The Tories have also expanded so-called sin taxes on unhealthy behaviour. Worried about bulging obesity levels, last year the government introduced a tax on sugary drinks, which led several manufacturers to change their recipes.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Some would like the nanny state to be stricter still. Jamie Oliver, a celebrity chef, wants to tax milkshakes. Professor Dame Sally Davies, England’s chief medical officer, is due to deliver in September a report that is likely to recommend more taxes on unhealthy foods. The Institute for Public Policy Research, a leftish think-tank, recently called for more food taxes and for sweets, crisps and soft drinks to be sold in plain packets, as cigarettes already are. Some environmentalists support a meat tax.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;On July 3rd Boris Johnson, the probable next prime minister, announced as part of his campaign for the Tory leadership that he would take a different approach. He promised no new sin taxes until his government had studied whether existing ones—including long-standing taxes on alcohol and tobacco—work, and whether they disproportionately hurt the poor. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Awkwardly, the answer to both questions is probably that they do. Although the Johnson campaign cites a dissenting study, on the whole there is good evidence that sin taxes change people’s behaviour. In the case of alcohol and tobacco, for example, economists tend to find that a 1% increase in prices is associated with a 0.5% decline in sales. But because poor people tend to spend a higher proportion of their income than others on things deemed sinful, such taxes hit them hardest. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Mr Johnson’s plans are likely to go down well with the Conservative Party members whose votes he is courting. Health campaigners may be less impressed. On the same day as his announcement, a report by Cancer Research UK found that obesity caused more cases of cancer than tobacco in Britain. As for targeting the poor, advocates for sin taxes sometimes argue this is in fact an advantage of the policies, because the poor will disproportionately reap the promised health benefits of having their behaviour changed.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;This ignores their associated loss of personal choice, however. It also misses a point that Mr Johnson understands very well: the thing about sinful behaviour is that it is often pleasurable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 03:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Remembering Lee Iacocca, America’s car salesman-in-chief]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/07/03/remembering-lee-iacocca-americas-car-salesman-in-chief]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_WBP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-03T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE WORLD’S carmakers can be roughly divided by specialisation. Europe’s are regarded as the best at sophisticated engineering. Japan’s are the masters of mass-production techniques. What American car firms do best is marketing their products. That reputation was acquired largely thanks to the efforts of an American business legend, Lee Iacocca, who died on July 2nd at the age of 94.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Brash, tireless and in the seclusion of the boardroom wreathed in a cloud of cigar smoke and profanities, Mr Iacocca presented a public image when boss of Chrysler as the patriotic car guy urging his countrymen to buy American. His rescue of the perennial weakling among Detroit’s “Big Three” from the brink of bankruptcy, and his regular appearance in the firm’s television adverts—once challenging customers that “if you can find a better car, buy it”—made him a celebrity boss long before such an idea became commonplace.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Public recognition in America and beyond—his autobiography, published in 1984, sold 6.5m copies worldwide—may have come through his turnaround of Chrysler, which he joined as boss in 1980, but it would not have been possible without his remarkable ability throughout his career to sell himself as much as he sold cars. The son of a hot dog vendor from Italy, he joined Ford in 1946 and grappled his way to the top using a flair for marketing ruses and a recognition that flogging Fords relied on flashy design, as much as the reliability and safety that the firm believed were its main assets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He made his name at Ford when he was in charge of the Mustang, unveiled in 1964. Sports-car looks coupled with a relatively modest price tag, and backed up by a clever promotional campaign, made the “pony car” an instant bestseller and an enduring classic. It also helped to propel Mr Iacocca to the top job at Ford in 1970. But the saleman’s pushiness and a bluntness that bordered on insubordination were distasteful to the patrician Henry Ford II, chairman and grandson of the firm’s founder. “Sometimes you just don’t like somebody,” he gave as his reason for firing Mr Iacocca, despite a successful eight-year stint at the firm’s helm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Iacocca skipped across Detroit after that to revive a dying Chrysler. Once there he used his powers of persuasion and an ad campaign that asked “Would America be better off without Chrysler?” to wrest a $1.5bn loan guarantee from the government to ensure the firm’s survival. Savage cost-cutting and a nose for the next big thing, in this case smaller cars and minivans, forerunners of the craze for SUVs, returned Chrysler to bumper profits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Iacocca’s newfound taste for lobbying the government and the American public’s shifting taste towards smaller, better equipped and fuel-efficient vehicles together laid the ground for the downsizing of Detroit. The import restrictions on foreign cars that Mr Iacocca argued for ended up encouraging Japanese and later European carmakers to set up shop in America and win a bigger share of its domestic market. By the early 1990s Chrysler was losing money again. No amount of ads featuring Mr Iacocca badmouthing foreign brands could burnish the firm’s ageing line-up. In 1992 he was shown the door.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His involvement in an attempted hostile takeover of his former firm by Kirk Kerkorian, a corporate raider, thrust him briefly back into the limelight in 1995. But his salesman’s touch was deserting him and the bid failed. Aside from cars and cigars Mr Iacocca flirted with politics. He considered running in the presidential election in 1988, but eventually got cold feet, perhaps concluding that America wasn’t ready for a businessman in the Oval Office, no matter how hard he sold the idea.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 03:40:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A familiar tune—the phonograph and music ownership]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/07/03/a-familiar-tune-the-phonograph-and-music-ownership]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/d-a9pojw4aatofi_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-03T18:58:43Z&quot;&gt;Jul 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;OUR TRANSATLANTIC podcast collaboration, &lt;strong&gt;“The Secret History of the Future”&lt;/strong&gt;, is back for a second season. Tom Standage of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; and Seth Stevenson of &lt;em&gt;Slate&lt;/em&gt; unearth curious tales hidden from the history of technology, and ask what they can tell us about the future. From the creation of the first computer program, to the quest for infallible crime-fighting forensics, to the etiquette of romance over the telegraph, these historical yarns can illuminate our present technological conundrums and offer cautionary lessons about the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Change your perception of the past, and your understanding of human nature, by discovering the secret history of the future. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first episode of season 2 considers the relationship between &lt;strong&gt;technology and music.&lt;/strong&gt; The 19th-century invention of the phonograph left composers worried they might not be paid for recordings. The 20th-century proliferation of digital sampling made old copyright laws look obsolete. Can these previous disruptions of the music business teach us how to handle a 21st-century onslaught of computers that can compose their own songs? Runtime: 39 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistallaudio/2cc33994-bfd4-4099-954c-d82540bc2ad2&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/the-secret-history-of-the-future/id1422830638?mt=2?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/2LU5CNGlh7vGy1OYW83qco&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9mZWVkcy5tZWdhcGhvbmUuZm0vaGlzdG9yeW9mdGhlZnV0dXJl&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/podcast/slate/the-secret-history-of-the-future&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/Technology-Podcasts/The-Secret-History-of-the-Future-p1150398/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 02:42:25 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[West Africa has become the world’s piracy hotspot]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/07/03/west-africa-has-become-the-worlds-piracy-hotspot]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_WOC966.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-03T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;COMPARED WITH those in Somalia, the pirates prowling the Gulf of Guinea have attracted relatively little global attention. That may now be changing. A recent report by One Earth Future, an NGO, says that the region experienced more incidents of piracy last year than anywhere else in the world. The report adds to a growing chorus of international concern about west Africa’s piracy problem. A shipowners’ association has called for the deployment of international navies to the region. India announced earlier this year that it would ban its citizens from working as sailors in the Gulf of Guinea. Maritime-security experts advise ships travelling to the region to wrap their decks in razor wire or hire local naval escorts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their concern is justified. West Africa’s pirates are much deadlier than those in Asia or Latin America. In the latter two regions, most piracy takes the form of petty theft: someone clambers aboard a ship docked at port to swipe a few items or mug a sailor. West African pirates used to specialise in stealing oil from tankers. But since 2014, when oil prices plummeted, they have copied their Somali counterparts and focused on kidnapping crews for ransom. They no longer prey exclusively on oil tankers. Last year they are believed to have kidnapped almost 200 people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;West Africa’s pirates may also be harder to stop than those elsewhere. Off Somalia, where the government controlled little of the country’s territory, international navies were given free rein and shipowners could hire private armed guards. Although pirates still occasionally probe the waters off Somalia for a vulnerable ship, they have largely been kept at bay. In South-East Asia, where the littoral states are richer and better run, governments have curbed piracy by working together and sharing intelligence. Better policing at ports has also led to a fall in petty theft in recent years.&lt;span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;West Africa lies awkwardly in between the two. Most of its pirates are from the poor and lawless Niger Delta region of Nigeria. The Nigerian government is more functional than Somalia’s and would resent foreign ships or private guards in its waters. But it has its hands full with insurgencies, banditry and local conflict on land. Its navy is thinly spread and ill equipped. Until the Delta is better governed, do not expect the pirates to disappear from the seas off west Africa.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 02:42:24 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Deepmind games—machine intelligence&#x27;s next move]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/07/03/deepmind-games-machine-intelligences-next-move]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_blm506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-03T17:34:52Z&quot;&gt;Jul 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE CHILD chess prodigy&lt;/strong&gt; who created a computer that outplays human grandmasters—&lt;strong&gt;Demis Hassabis, founder of Deepmind&lt;/strong&gt;—explains how games are a testing ground for algorithms and what real-world challenges he hopes to tackle with artificial intelligence. And, what can &lt;strong&gt;AlphaZero&lt;/strong&gt;, the chess-playing computer, teach human players? Kenneth Cukier also speaks to the &lt;strong&gt;chess players Dominic Lawson, Natasha Regan and Matthew Sadler&lt;/strong&gt; about the future of machine intelligence and its interplay with human wisdom. Runtime: 20 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistbabbage/99af5224-b955-4a3c-930c-91a68bfe6c88&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: Apple Podcasts | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/0BCUrdrOb3tvfIwazeLBUH&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWVjb25vbWlzdGJhYmJhZ2U&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=142124&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Economist-Babbage-p401958/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jul 2019 01:40:22 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>