<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Mexico rejoices after averting Donald Trump’s tariffs threat]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/06/09/mexico-rejoices-after-averting-donald-trumps-tariffs-threat]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_blp902.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-09T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 9th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;CALL IT a victory. Compared with crippling tariffs on all exports to the United States that President Donald Trump had threatened to impose, starting at 5% on June 10th and escalating to 25%, just about any deal was going to look good for Mexico. &lt;br/&gt;News of an accord reached by Marcelo Ebrard, Mexico’s foreign minister, to have the tariffs suspended indefinitely caused relief and celebration across the country—even before its contents became clear. “Ebrard deactivates Trump,” screeched the front page of El Heraldo, a newspaper, the morning after the deal on June 7th. “Mexico wins,” ran another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A saga that had threatened to hobble the still-young presidency of Andrés Manuel López Obrador became instead a crisis averted. Mexico’s president announced that a rally he had planned in central Tijuana in “defence of national dignity” would now become a celebration of Mexico’s success at the negotiating table. On June 8th governors, bishops and unionists joined the president on the stage at a traffic intersection as locals climbed atop bus stops and taco stands to glimpse the festivities. “To President Donald Trump I raise not a closed fist, but an open and honest hand,” said Mr López Obrador.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But he is not the only president doing a victory lap. Mr Trump wants to turn Mexico into the wall that he promised but has so far failed to build. He tweeted his satisfaction that Mexico would take “strong measures” towards halting the inflow of Central American migrants. In May some 144,000 people tried to cross the southern border of the United States, double the number in February. Almost all of them had travelled through Mexico rather than from it. Mr Trump’s defenders argue that using tariffs as a threat to force Mexico to get tough on migration was a masterstroke.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The accord includes the expansion of “Remain In Mexico”—a fledgling scheme that forces migrants to wait in Mexico while their claims for asylum in the United States are processed— from a few checkpoints to the entire American-Mexican border. From June 10th Mexico will also deploy 6,000 troops of its newly created national guard to two states—Chiapas, bordering Guatemala, and Oaxaca, which has a narrow isthmus—to stop migrants and people-smugglers. That will dent the number of migrants reaching the United States, though flows across the US-Mexico border tend to dip anyway in the scorching months of June and July. The sides did not set specific reduction targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The deal allows the United States to demand more from Mexico within 90 days if numbers do not fall as much as the Trump administration would like. But it is less impressive than Mr Trump claims. “Remain In Mexico” was already set for expansion. Mexican officials describe the deployment of the national guard as an “acceleration” of what they were planning to do anyway. Mr Trump tweeted that Mexico had agreed to “immediately buy large quantities of agricultural product from our great patriot farmers”. Mr Ebrard clarified that, if spared Mr Trump’s recession-inducing tariffs, Mexico would be in a better position to buy many different things.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mexico has toed a fine line in negotiations. Mr Lopez López Obrador initially responded to Mr Trump’s threat by penning an affectionate letter—a strategy for presidential seduction borrowed from Kim Jong Un. Mexico froze two-dozen bank accounts linked to people-smuggling operations and locked up two activists involved in helping so-called migrant caravans travel through Mexico. But it also rebuffed other requests, particularly pressure to accept “safe third country” status, which would, in effect, allow the United States to reject the asylum application of anyone who set foot in Mexico beforehand, and send back to Mexico those who make it into the United States. Mexicans officials say they also had to explain to their counterparts that their border with Guatemala, porous and often ignored by locals, could be strengthened but not entirely sealed. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The peso climbed upon news of the deal, but not to the level it was before Mr Trump first unsheathed his tariffs threat. That suggests that markets have priced in the chance of a return to conflict. It also suggests that investors do not believe that the USMCA, Mr Trump’s recently struck revamp of the NAFTA trade pact, provides the kind of economic certainty that free-trade deals are supposed to. From North America to North Korea, Mr Trump has made a habit of threatening to abandon his own deals even after reaching them through brinkmanship. Mexican negotiators know that Mr Trump can enrapture his fans and distract his enemies by chucking bombs at Mexico, and has every reason to do so again before his bid for re-election in 2020. “It’s like Alcoholics Anonymous, we live one day at a time,” says one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the eyes of Mr López Obrador critics, it is he, not Mr Trump, who has performed a humiliating climbdown. Mr López Obrado entered office promising to end the mass deportations of Central Americans carried out by past Mexican presidents. Indeed, the drop in the number of migrants detained during his first months in office, which American officials blame for the rise in illegal crossings, drew Mr Trump’s ire. Despite rhetoric about respecting migrants’ rights, Mexican officials concede that deportations are all but certain to rocket. &lt;br/&gt;Tijuana thus made for a bittersweet location for Mr López Obrador’s victory rally. The city is not just the cradle of Mexican-American integration, or a state that the president’s party swept in state elections on June 2nd. It is also the final destination for many of the migrants on their way to America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among those thronging Tijuana were two strolling visitors who chanced upon the president’s speech. Valerio Doctor, a Haitian migrant, had been in Tijuana for 15 days, following a three-month trip mostly by bus from Ecuador (many migrants arrive in Mexico from afar via Ecuador or Chile, the nearest countries with generous visa-free travel rules). In Port-au-Prince, Haiti’s capital, he had five children and no work. So with his friend he left to seek a path to prosperity elsewhere. In a crowd Mr Doctor watches Mr López Obrador vow to fortify the very border he and his friend had just crossed. Until that moment, the pair knew nothing of the deal. Mr Doctor still hopes to cross to the United States or, if it will not have him, to stay in Mexico. How the deal struck with so much fanfare and consequence 24 hours earlier will affect him is still unclear. The lot of poor migrants is often hard and uncertain. For those who try to follow Mr Doctor, it is likely to be harder and more uncertain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 04:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Denmark’s social democrats beat the migrant-bashers at their game]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/09/denmarks-social-democrats-beat-the-migrant-bashers-at-their-game]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_eup506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-09T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 9th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SOCIAL DEMOCRATS in much of Europe are living through torrid times. In France and the Netherlands, once-mighty centre-left parties have been reduced to bit players; in Italy and Germany they have been pushed into third place behind populists or Greens. There are many reasons for their decline, but one is the politics of immigration: centre-left parties are seen as too permissive by many of their traditional working-class voters, who have switched to supporting anti-immigrant populist parties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So the victory by Denmark’s Social Democrats (SD) in an election on June 5th is an important test case. After losing power in 2015, the SD got tough on immigration and integration. It sought to take back the initiative from the Danish People’s Party (DPP), an anti-immigrant populist outfit that has captured an increasing share of the working-class vote over the past two decades. The DPP has dragged the country’s immigration policy far in its own direction: the centre-right government of Lars Lokke Rasmussen, which has governed since 2015 through a confidence-and-supply deal with the DPP, has slowed the arrival of asylum-seekers to a trickle with tough policies such as mandating that their valuables be confiscated to pay for the costs of housing them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The SD, under its leader, Mette Frederiksen, wants to go further in some ways. It has proposed an annual cap on “non-Western” immigration, and it wants to encourage foreign retirees to leave Denmark by letting them keep their state pensions. Ms Frederiksen and other SD politicians speak of the problem of immigrants forming “parallel societies” in Denmark, and of the need to eliminate immigrant “ghettos”. Whereas the party was once seen as relatively liberal on immigration, it has by now shifted its image to a group sceptical of newcomers, which insists that those in the country integrate into the dominant culture. If the SD’s strategy succeeded, many analysts thought, Europe’s other centre-left European parties might have a model to emulate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When the result of the election came in, though, it was inconclusive. As polls predicted, the SD came first. It appears likely to return to government (pending coalition negotiations, which will start this week). But its share of the vote was 26%, down a bit from 26.3% in 2015. In contrast, the share of Venstre, Mr Rasmussen’s centre-right liberal party, rose from 19.5% to 23%. If Ms Frederiksen becomes prime minister, she will owe it to the strong performance of other parties on the left, which did not embrace tougher migration policies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The DPP was indeed devastated. It lost more than half its vote share, falling from 21% to 8%. But just 12% of its previous voters shifted to SD, according to exit polls; more went to Venstre (17%). If SD’s strategy was to win back voters from the far right, it did not seem to have worked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The equivocal results touched off a fierce debate in other countries with struggling centre-left parties, such as the Netherlands, where the Labour party’s share fell from 25% in the 2012 election to just 6% in 2017. Some analysts saw the SD’s win as proof that tough immigration policies work. “If the Dutch social democrats want to win back their original support base, they have to take on immigration,” wrote Kemal Rijken, a left-leaning political scientist, two days after the election.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Others pointed to the SD’s failure to raise its vote as evidence that the centre-left cannot hope to win such voters back. Tarik Abou-Chadi, a political scientist at the University of Zurich, argued that the paucity of DPP supporters switching to SD made it clear that even under “favourable circumstances” as in Denmark, anti-immigration politics could not be the future for social-democratic parties in countries like Germany.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some in Denmark, however, said foreign interpreters were drawing the wrong conclusions because they misunderstood the strategy. The SD failed to increase its own vote share because it lost more voters to other leftist parties than it gained from the DPP. The Socialist People’s Party (SF), a green outfit, raised its share from 4.2% to 7%, while the left-liberal Radical Liberals (RV) went from 4.6% to 8%. This, however, was part of the plan: win voters from the right, even at the cost of losing some to the left, and you have shifted the overall centre of gravity, allowing a left-leaning coalition to seize power. The point was not to win the debate on immigration, but to neutralise it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“By placing themselves where they did on immigration and integration, the SD took away a weapon from the liberals and conservatives. It took the heat out of the debate,” says Karina Kosiara-Pedersen, a political scientist. Because voters expected a tough immigration policy from whoever won the election, the contest refocused on other issues: first climate change, followed by education. Those are issues on which Danes currently trust the left more than the right. Meanwhile, the DPP was hurt by the entry of two new parties even farther to the right on immigration: the New Right party, which won 2%, and Stram Kurs (“Hard Line”), an extremist populist party that took just enough votes to damage the DPP but not enough to get into parliament.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The question is whether the SD’s strategy can be imitated by Europe’s other centre-left parties. Ms Frederiksen thinks it may be specific to Denmark. Depoliticising immigration by adopting tougher positions may work in countries—such as Sweden, Norway and Finland—with strong social-democratic parties that command loyalty on other issues. But in Germany, France, Italy and the Netherlands, voters have lost confidence in social-democratic parties for a wide range of reasons, especially economic ones. They are seen as complicit in labour-market reforms which left-wing voters dislike, and share the blame for austerity measures enacted during the euro crisis. That said, in Spain and Portugal, which have also undergone wrenching economic adjustments, the centre-left is doing well without adopting an anti-immigrant line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Danish results may thus hold lessons mainly for the rest of the Nordic countries. But elsewhere in Europe, social-democratic parties have problems which an anti-immigrant turn seems unlikely to solve.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 03:40:53 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ghost workers of the world, form a guild!]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/09/ghost-workers-of-the-world-form-a-guild]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_wbp507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-09T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 9th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE DEBATE about the future of work tends to divide commentators into two camps. The optimistic case is that technology may cause temporary disruption but will ultimately result in economic growth and thus more jobs. Combine harvesters reduced the need for agricultural labourers and personal computers eliminated the typing pool, but the displaced workers found jobs in the end.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pessimistic case is that new technology, even if it does not cause mass unemployment, will create a “digital divide”. The future will resemble a high-tech Downton Abbey, with the skilled elite lording it over the rest. Unskilled workers will be delivering pizzas to, and cleaning the bathrooms of, the likes of Elon Musk and Tim Cook.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new report* from McKinsey veers more into the optimistic camp. It predicts that men and women will be roughly equally affected by automation over the next decade, with 21% of working males and 20% of females losing their jobs by 2030. In the developed world, McKinsey estimates that men will tend to lose machine-operating jobs and women will lose clerical and service roles. But new jobs will be created, if not necessarily for the same people: women will find work in the expanding health-care industry and men in the professional, scientific and technical fields (a higher proportion of men than women have science degrees).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not all of these jobs will be well paid, especially for women, says McKinsey—just as, according to left-wing critics, the jobs boom of recent years has been in low-paid work (though data suggest that high-paying ones also rose fast). On the bright side, discouraged workers have rejoined the labour market as the economy has boomed, while technology has made it easier for employers to find workers (and vice versa).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How much of this low-paid work is the result of the gig economy? Not much so far; it only represents about 1% of American employment. But in their book, “Ghost Work”, Mary Gray and Siddharth Suri forecast that what they call “on-demand work” will reach 60% of the global workforce by 2055. They define this category to include those who work for temporary staffing agencies, have short-term contracts or who accept work from employers through websites or apps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All this makes it sound as if the future of jobs will look like the past. Before the days of the factory and the office, many workers were part of a “putting-out system”, in which merchants hired them to undertake specific tasks, such as spinning or weaving, for which they were paid a piece rate. The attraction to employers is that such work is cheap. The authors quote marketing executives as saying their company could save up to 40% by not paying benefits and saving on office space. Furthermore, in two of the main markets where on-demand workers toil, America and India, they have little access to the legal protections associated with formal employment. A digital Downton Abbey, in other words.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the new forms of employment have a plus side. Many workers in emerging markets relish the opportunity to work at home, and at times of their choosing. They are only expecting to supplement their family’s other sources of income. On some platforms, workers are identified by a sequence of letters and numbers, meaning that they are free from discrimination on the grounds or age or sex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Workers may also look to the past to find a way to organise themselves. Some have set up online forums which share information on the most reliable employers. Ms Gray and Mr Suri suggest these could be expanded to create the equivalent of medieval guilds which could enable workers to learn new skills. Such guilds could also act as a repository for employees’ work records. At the moment, it is as hard—or harder—to transfer your work rating from one online platform to another as it is to wrest your user data from Facebook. Lack of interoperability means workers have to start each contract from scratch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Responsible employers could pledge to use only workers from guilds and to apply minimum standards on issues such as prompt payment. They will benefit from a more reliable and skilful employees. That way, if workers of the world unite, everyone may gain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2019 01:18:45 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A new rendering of Christianity’s best-known supplication]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/06/08/a-new-rendering-of-christianitys-best-known-supplication]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_BLP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-08T15:39:41Z&quot;&gt;Jun 8th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN THE world of conservative Catholics, bent on proving that the current pontiff is a theologically dubious innovator, it feels as though Pope Francis has just given them a fresh ammunition. According to newspaper reports in many countries, the Argentine pontiff has just changed the Lord’s Prayer, the supplication beginning with the words “Our Father” which was taught by Jesus Christ and is used by just about all his followers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To some traditionalists, such recklessness is tantamount to changing the Declaration of Independence, in other words fiddling about with a set of words which, once delivered, was meant to stand for all time. Imagine how foolhardy this sort of tampering would look to Muslims, who believe that God’s message was revealed at a particular time, in a particular form of Arabic words, of which not one iota can be changed. For a devout Muslim, renderings of the Koran into other languages are an approximation at best; the Arabic original is the only definitive one. For a devout Jew, only the Hebrew original of the Torah has any real standing as the word of God, though slightly different versions of that text exist. Still, the fact that Christianity now accepts the idea of a spiritually inspired translation, on a par with the original, makes things more complicated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what has really happened with that Christian prayer? In 2017, Pope Francis told an Italian TV channel that he was unhappy with the standard translations of one particular line in the prayer which Christ proposed. That line is “lead us not into temptation” or in Italian “non indurci in tentazione”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He explained: “It is not a good translation because it speaks of a God who induces temptation… I am the one who falls. It is not Him pushing me into temptation to then see how far I have fallen. A father doesn’t do that, a father helps you to get up immediately. It is Satan who leads us into temptation, that’s his department.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the wake of that papal bomb-shell, it was left up to national bishops’ conferences, responsible for translation into their respective languages, to decide how to respond. In fact, well before Francis spoke, French bishops had decreed a change similar to one he recommended: Ne nous laisse pas entrer en tentation (do not let us enter into temptation) replaced Ne nous soumets pas à la tentation which could mean something like “Do not subject us to temptation.” Indeed Francis gave the French bishops credit for having blazed a new linguistic trail, and they may well have given him the idea of proposing similar changes in other tongues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Catholic prelates of Germany, and of England and Wales, considered the matter and decided to let their existing (“lead us not into..”) versions stand. The latest development, prompting the recent headlines, is that Italy’s bishops, in consultation with the Holy See, have given final approval to an Italian version which reflects the pontiff’s thinking and will be used in a forthcoming Missal or prayer-book. The new rendering is “non abbandonarci alla tentazione…” meaning something like “do not abandon us to temptation...”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So who is right? Your correspondent will not claim to sit in theological judgement over the pope but the question does have a purely linguistic dimension.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is no doubt that “lead us not into temptation” is a pretty accurate rendering of the early Greek texts from which later Bibles have been translated. “Do not bring us into temptation” might be even closer. In fact, the word whose rendering needs careful thought is not the verb but the noun, peirasmos, the term which is usually translated as “temptation”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In both ancient and modern Greek, it has a range of senses, covering many different things, trivial and grave, that might try, test or vex us or somehow throw us off course. In the context it is reasonable to assume that trials of a more serious kind are being referred to. So a loose but broadly fair translation of the contested phrase might be something like “do not test us more than we can bear…”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is what some people high up in the American Catholic hierarchy seem to think, anyway. Consult the text of the Bible as published on the website of the United States Conference of Catholic Bishops and you will find the following rather memorable, but perhaps alarming, version of the relevant verse (Matthew 6:13), taken from the New American Bible (Revised Edition) of 2011.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Do not subject us to the final test, but deliver us from the evil one…” The American rendering is a bold one but it does avert one of the potential problems posed by the new papally-blessed Italian formula. To an impious soul, being “abandoned to temptation” might sound enjoyable, indeed almost… irresistible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 00:40:23 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[James Ellroy finally has happiness in his sights]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/news/2019/06/08/james-ellroy-finally-has-happiness-in-his-sights]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_blp506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-08T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 8th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190406_OPP601_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190406_OPP601_2.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190406_OPP601_2.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190406_OPP601_2.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190406_OPP601_2.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190406_OPP601_2.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190406_OPP601_2.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190406_OPP601_2.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190406_OPP601_2.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190406_OPP601_2.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This piece is from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.1843magazine.com/&quot; data-tegid=&quot;da002gp4gh3uhauvcddhvb2mvj4mbhjf&quot;&gt;1843&lt;/a&gt;, our sister magazine of ideas, lifestyle and culture. It was published in the June/July 2019 issue.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On a dark Saturday afternoon in February James Ellroy, America’s pre-eminent crime novelist and chronicler of depravity and excess, was having problems with his central heating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It’s cold in here, isn’t it?” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I agreed that it was. Ellroy, who is tall and bald, and looks like a cross between Michel Foucault and Uncle Fester from the Addams Family, got up and spent a few moments peering and poking at the thermostat. Then he announced that he would phone his girlfriend—and former wife—Helen Knode, a writer who has her own flat in the same apartment block near Union Station in Denver, Colorado. Knode was at home making turkey chilli. “She should come over and take a look,” he said. “This is not my metier.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At bookshop readings and on TV chat-shows, Ellroy presents himself as “the Demon Dog of American fiction”, a confident huckster full of scurrilous gossip and risqué jokes. He has described this shtick as constituting about 7% of who he really is. “I like to fuck with people,” he said, by way of explanation. “Why mince words?” But as he wandered around his flat, trying to determine whether some barely audible sound was a train outside his window or a pipe stirring sluggishly to life, he seemed ungainly and boyish—even sweet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His possessions are minimal: a few pieces of stark, mid-century furniture, a wall of cellophane-covered hard­backs, some classical CDs, a hi-fi, a boom box and an exercise machine. His fridge is empty apart from shrink-wrapped sausages. For ten years, Ellroy and Knode owned a red-furred bull terrier named Margaret, after his favourite British prime minister. (“She never liked me—she’d just follow me around and bark at me and oppress me furiously as if I was a Labour Party whip.”) These days Ellroy makes do with pictures of dogs and “my Gila monster”, a life-sized artist’s model of a lizard with whom he conducts imaginary conversations. There is no television or computer, no bills, papers or bric-a-brac. The only interruption to this order was the arrival of advance copies of his new novel, “This Storm”, out this summer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s a lifestyle that is peaceful, housebound and nearly Amish in its lack of material indulgence. When I suggested that he seems quite frugal for a bestselling novelist several of whose books have been turned into movies, he replied that he likes to buy cars (he currently owns one car). On an average day, he will eat a bowl of plain oatmeal and drink several cups of black filter coffee, engage in various acts of “prayer and ponder” (he is a non-churchgoing Lutheran), check in with his assistant by fax or on the landline, and take naps. Apart from writing the occasional movie treatment or magazine piece, Ellroy’s only commitment is the monkish, monomaniacal pursuit of what he identifies as “God’s calling for me as a novelist”. “I feel like I’m the great American crime writer,” he told me one afternoon. He weighed the statement for a couple of seconds, as if scrolling through his rivals: Dashiell Hammett, Raymond Chandler and so on. Then he said, “You can make that case.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellroy’s breakthrough came in 1987 with “The Black Dahlia”, his seventh novel, which was based on a real-life murder. The novel was the first volume in his LA Quartet, a series of complex detective stories that doubled as a portrait of the city after the second world war. (In 1997, the third book, “L.A. Confidential”, was made into a film starring Guy Pearce and Russell Crowe, and won two Oscars.) In Ellroy’s hands, the crime novel became a compound of historical saga, star-crossed romance, pastiche journalism and psychological case-study. His prose heaved with period slang and the books featured a mix of real and invented characters through which Ellroy explored the roots of criminal and even psychopathic behaviour. Dennis Lehane, an American novelist, told me that the LA Quartet is “the towering achievement of American crime fiction. It’s the monolith, the one that came in and casts its shadow over everything else”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After completing the series, Ellroy wanted his next project to be a dense social portrait steeped in vice and crime but without being “beholden to a murder investigation”. The result, in 1995, was “American Tabloid”, perhaps his greatest novel and the beginning of a new sequence. The Underworld USA trilogy recounts major episodes in American history between 1958 and 1972—the Bay of Pigs, the assassinations of Martin Luther King and the Kennedys, the Vietnam war—from the perspective of various invented hit men and hangers-on. Ellroy, who has described his work as an exercise in “moral art”, told me that he found the idea of “killing for money or for dubious ideology particularly horrible and conscienceless. To humanise these characters and to live inside their heads and to connect them to the rise of someone with the inflated reputation of a John F. Kennedy was just too good to pass up.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellroy dislikes talk of prophecy or pertinence, but there are clear parallels between the worlds he created in the LA Quartet and the Underworld USA trilogy and today’s political scene. These volumes, which are being republished by Everyman’s Library this summer, offer a multi-dimensional portrait of American extremity: greasy-palmed complicity between politics and big business, rogue operatives and unchecked institutions, race hatred, police brutality, far-reaching federal investigations, corrupt land deals, lascivious and lying presidents, actress-molesting moguls and populist uprisings. As Knode said one evening at dinner, “It’s Ellroy’s world, we just live in it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was born Lee Earle Ellroy in Los Angeles in 1948. His mother was a heavy-drinking, free-living nurse from German farming stock in Wisconsin. His father, 17 years her senior, was an accountant, highly competent but idle, who worked briefly as Rita Hayworth’s business manager. When Ellroy was six, his parents divorced. Ellroy lived with his mother but felt ashamed of her behaviour. He has frequently recalled his childhood view of her as “a drunk and a whore”. In June 1958 she was found, raped and strangled, in an ivy patch next to a school playing field in El Monte, California. The case was never solved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellroy and his father didn’t talk about Geneva Hilliker Ellroy. “It was as if, after the coroner’s inquest, the shroud was dropped,” he said. Ellroy took refuge in crime fiction. His father, who was “never cheap”, would buy him at least a book a week, at Chevalier’s Books on Larchmont Boulevard. He estimates that during the summer after his mother died, he read at least 25 Hardy Boys novels. The experience was “a mediated dialogue on my mother’s death. Here I am—decidedly large and strange and prone to volatile curiosities, living with my old man, who talks to the TV and works infrequently and everyone thinks he’s my grandfather, and the un-house-broken dog urinating and defecating with abandon all over the place. And here is Everytown USA. Order is restored. The killer is identified and justice is enacted. And these nice-looking kids have nifty-looking girlfriends and a sidekick and cars and speedboats, and their widowed father is a policeman and has slick threads, and he’ll remarry sooner or later.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_BLP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190601_BLP504.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190601_BLP504.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190601_BLP504.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190601_BLP504.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190601_BLP504.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190601_BLP504.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190601_BLP504.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190601_BLP504.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190601_BLP504.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;For his 11th birthday, still in the thick of what he calls his “ambiguous bereavement”, Ellroy’s father bought him “The Badge”, a non-fiction book on crimes and law enforcement in LA. It contained a chapter on the rape and vivisection of a 22-year-old would-be starlet Elizabeth Short, the so-called Black Dahlia, a crime that Ellroy has described as “pure misogynist insanity”. That chapter “went through me like a jolt”, said Ellroy: “It was more shocking to me than my mother’s death.” He says his encounter with the case was “the formative experience of my life”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Ellroy wasn’t reading, he was acting out. “I’d do anything to get attention,” he said. In 1962 he was enrolled at Fairfax High School, a rare “white-trasher” in a swanky environment. He liked to rile his Jewish classmates and even attended American Nazi party meetings. (“You could not have imagined a more pathetic bunch of fools.”) In a mock election, he was the only kid who—partly for anti-Catholic reasons—voted for Nixon over Kennedy. Sometimes he broke into the homes of his richer neighbours to smell their underwear. But behind the bad behaviour, he felt neglected, frightened, hungry and lonely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Things came to a head in late adolescence: “1965 was pretty heady for me,” he said. “I got kicked out of high school. I joined the army. I flew to basic training, in Fort Polk, Louisiana. I had a big crack-up. I was sent home. My dad was dying. I went back to Fort Polk. Then I returned to LA, because his death was imminent.” His father’s last discernible words to Ellroy were, “Try to pick up every waitress who serves you,” which he calls “a legacy I have fulfilled, with mixed results, dare I say”. After being expelled from the army, Ellroy moved to LA and spent his time boozing, shoplifting, “peeping around” and reading potboilers. At times he lived in Robert Burns Park. To survive, he’d sell his blood plasma. For kicks he’d drink scotch, inhale Benzedrex, smoke weed and annoy hippies (“I’d say ‘Bomb Vietnam’, things like that”). On the night Bobby Kennedy was assassinated, a woman caught him on a rooftop masturbating while high on uppers. He was once beaten up by a drag queen called Peaches. One morning, he woke up in San Francisco and wondered how he’d got there. He was arrested some 40 times, for driving under the influence, public drunkenness, shoplifting, trespassing and burglary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the mid-1970s Ellroy realised that substance abuse was impeding his other appetites. “I wanted to laugh, I wanted to read, I wanted girls, I wanted to sate my curiosities, I wanted to go to the movies. I loved art. I loved great music. I loved history. I loved looking at pictures in magazines.” He also had an idea for a novel. In 1977 Ellroy joined Alcoholics Anonymous and got clean: he liked the extremity of total abstinence. He found a job as a caddy at the Bel Air Country Club and, aged 30, began to write. His idea became “Brown’s Requiem”, published in 1981 as a little-noticed paperback. Around this time Ellroy walked into the Mysterious Bookshop in New York and told the proprietor, Otto Penzler, “I’m the next big one.” Penzler replied, “Would you forgive me if I reserve judgment?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellroy wrote a series of straight genre novels before he fulfilled his own prophecy with “The Black Dahlia”. Another writer had already published a novel about the murder of Elizabeth Short, which had been turned into a film, but Ellroy realised that his own peculiar brew of experiences and sensibilities had furnished him with a unique perspective. “I’ve lived in that kind of male excess of booze, dope, girls, high-flying bullshit,” he says, but he is also a veteran of AA, a Christian, conservative, moralist and child of divorce whose mother was murdered. He is both far closer than most novelists to sinful conduct, and more willing to speak the language of moral and religious judgment. Unafraid to join the dots between his own life and his creative output, Ellroy says that his personal suffering “dogged me and informed the texts. Police officers charged with solving a series of baffling crimes, or government provocateurs and buffoons, or the authoritarian figure who needs to impose himself upon external events in order to plumb the secrets of his own identity—I’ve been able to exposit the lonely beating heart of those guys.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One evening in February Ellroy embarked on a rare outdoor excursion—dinner with his friend Jerry Ackerman, a FBI agent and a novelist. Ackerman is a compact, balding man in his late 40s who shares Ellroy’s taste for law and order, mid-century Los Angeles, traditional manners, porkpie hats and beef. Ocean Prime, a restaurant near Ellroy’s apartment, has numerous steak options and elaborately courteous waiters. As we headed out Knode whispered to me: “When people talk about the Denver food scene, this isn’t what they mean.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conversation touched on Ellroy’s current reading, the thrillers of Daniel Silva, which concern an art restorer who is an agent for Mossad, Israel’s secret service. (“It’s a preposterous combination of trades,” Ellroy said.) Noting how many historical events surface—the arrest of Adolf Eichmann, the Black September conflict—he said, “It’s like a Middle Eastern Ellroy-lite.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Is that a blurb?” Ackerman asked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Yeah, I think Daniel Silva, who outsells me about 40 to one, would really appreciate that. ‘I’m better than him’—Ellroy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ackerman had brought along material for Ellroy’s next novel—a book about the US Treasury. His books often begin with a moment of inspiration. He says that the idea for “The Big Nowhere” (1988) – a conspiracy novel from the LA Quartet that touches on homosexuality, communism, the LA Dodgers, anti-Mexican violence and the legacy of the Holocaust—came to him in a second and a half on a lonely Saturday night in the winter of 1986. Its even more intricate successor, “L.A. Confidential”, also occurred to him “in a single rush”. Then comes the graft.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With help from an assistant, Ellroy researches and then writes a detailed synopsis that’s often as long as the book itself. (Without it, he says he wouldn’t be able to “write a book worth a shit”.) Then he flies to New York to discuss the outline with his editors at Knopf, his American publisher. Finally, he says, “I execute at great length and revise in great detail.” A working day can begin as early as 1.45am. “I’ve got the outline typed up on the desk. I get up, say my prayers, have a cup of cold coffee I made the night before, get it in my system quicker.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellroy called his taste in language “very precise”. Small imperfections “leap out at me”. He avoids semi-colons and shifts indiscriminately to the present tense—“which drives copy editors crazy”. “If you want to be very good at this,” he said, “the road is consciousness. Am I repeating this motif? Is this plausible? Does this track logically? Are the paragraph breaks in the right place? Is this information exposited too early? When should this man meet this woman? That was the gradual electrifying revelation – if one has native talent of the level I possess, then it’s about consciousness.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellroy says of Knode that “There’s no one else for me but her.” They met in 1990 and they married a year later: “The aggregate of all the other women I’ve known don’t equal Helen in soul, gravity or native intellect.” The two share a tendency towards solitude and a strict morality. But whereas Ellroy failed to finish high school, Knode has a master’s from Cornell and worked for a magazine, LA Weekly, which sprang from the counterculture Ellroy detested. He is loping and saturnine, husky and housebound, with a tendency to bark, bay and growl; Knode is prone to gales of laughter and micro-bursts of surprise. She exudes an air of sensible busyness as she zips about the city in one of her many well-cut trench-coats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Ellroy and Knode met he had recently entered a period of conscious self-restraint, even self-punishment. Editing “L.A. Confidential” he had turned against flourish, metaphor and scene-setting, developing a habit of “cutting words and cutting words” that resulted in a kind of staccato shorthand. He was also growing more isolated. His behaviour was characterised, Knode told me, by “churning, compulsion, unreachability, one crazy idea after another. This was a guy who never had a moment of peace.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 1993, as he was working on “American Tabloid”, Knode took action. She felt that he needed to confront the fact of his mother’s murder more directly. That Christmas she gave Ellroy a framed copy of a newspaper photograph that depicted him in the moments after he was told his mother had been killed. Soon afterwards a journalist in California, who had access to his mother’s police file, contacted him. Ellroy’s response—not the one Knode intended – was to attempt to solve the case, more than three decades on, and write up his findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“My Dark Places”, a memoir that explored the immediate aftermath and longer legacy of his mother’s death, was published in 1996. Ellroy recognises that the book was, at best, a partial reckoning with his personal trauma. At home things carried on much as before. Ellroy has described his conduct as boorish, oblivious, callow, heedless, isolated, “preposterously male”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2001 Ellroy suffered episodes of sleeplessness and hypochondria and, eventually, a nervous breakdown. He became addicted to sedatives and sleeping pills. When I asked Ellroy what might have averted the breakdown, he said, “A different mind, a different soul. It was everything I’d suppressed in my life.” He also blames “The Cold Six Thousand”, the bestselling middle chapter of the USA trilogy, which represents the furthest extreme of his impulse to cut. Stig Abell, editor of the Times Literary Supplement, says this book is his favourite Ellroy novel but also “the logical acme point. He doesn’t give us a break, ever. There’s an element of obsession-compulsion.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_BLP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190601_BLP505.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190601_BLP505.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190601_BLP505.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190601_BLP505.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190601_BLP505.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190601_BLP505.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190601_BLP505.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190601_BLP505.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190601_BLP505.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellroy describes the style as “chaos”: “Pete rotates. Wayne rotates. Pete moves stateside. Laurent’s there. Ditto Flash. They funnel stateside. Stanton stays in-country. Ditto Mesplède. Tiger Kamp runs low-supervised. The war escalates. More troops pass through. The kadre hits Saigon half-assed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Knode, the novel reflected Ellroy’s frazzled state. She recalled thinking, “We don’t need any literary criticism here—we just need a doctor!” As things turned out, there were numerous doctors—and an actor. When Ellroy was in psychiatric lockdown, a friend put Knode in touch with Carrie Fisher. “She was a big help,” Knode says. “She knew everything. In the middle of James’s crack-up, she gave me a better picture of the modern medical landscapes and the gaps in its treatment than I’d had in two years.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellroy said that Fisher died with drugs in her system.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“She never claimed to be clean, Big Dog,” Knode said. “She just claimed to know everything about it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellroy kicked the drugs but continued to show signs of collapse. In “The Hilliker Curse” (2010), his second, more candid attempt to grapple with his mother’s legacy, he quotes a letter from Knode recalling that during this time he would drive his car too fast, dribble, wear shit-stained trousers, and audibly masturbate while her family was visiting. She got tired of waiting for him to change. Knode introduced the idea of an open marriage, but in the end it was Ellroy who met someone else—a left-wing academic named Joan. Ellroy and Knode divorced in April 2006. But they continued to talk on the phone almost every day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellroy’s relationship with Joan was short­lived. After they separated, he moved to Los Angeles—the first time he had lived there in 25 years. “So, I’m alone—I’m gassing, I’m yearning.” He was looking southbound out of his window on Rossmore Avenue when he had another “synaptic flash: forlorn-looking Japanese, in wintertime, in a bus, going up a mountain road in a snowstorm to the Manzanar internment camp in the High Sierras. Immediately I knew: four novels, World War Two.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He and Knode reunited in 2015 when he was promoting “Perfidia”, the first of his new LA Quartet. Knode was living in Denver, so Ellroy bought a flat down the hall. Knode lives more conventionally than him. Her apartment has a kitchen table, wallpaper and a comfortable-looking sofa. The art on the walls doesn’t all involve dogs or crime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One evening Ellroy and I had dinner at Knode’s place. It was Saturday night—fight night. Ellroy was excited about the boxing but also still distracted by the problems with “the fucking heat”. As we entered he turned to me. “Helen wants you to take off your shoes. I don’t go for that shit myself.” On a table in the hall was a copy of “This Storm” and a post-it note saying “Read me now”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knode and Ellroy watch boxing on two channels, Showtime and the Zone, which is run by Eddie Hearn, a boxing promoter. Knode said that Hearn had revolutionised their lives, but when the Zone stuttered on her Apple TV he was held responsible for ruining their evening. The refrain “Fuck Eddie Hearn” soon established itself. When he wasn’t yelling at the TV, Ellroy refused Knode’s offer of tea with the formula, “Fuck that shit.” He requested a cup of black coffee, and Knode frowned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I gots to have it, baby,” he said. “Just one cup.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I’m not underwriting this,” she replied.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I know—it is late.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knode told me that though Ellroy’s propensity to repeat certain jokes and riffs is unchanged, in other ways he’s grown up. He is able to “listen now in a way he wasn’t able to before. He’s burned out a lot of the bad shit.” She mentioned the dinners with Jerry Ackerman—regular meet-ups with a friend. He has a healthier relationship with the murder of Elizabeth Short. And after many years of living exclusively with his own books, he has started to read again. His current lifestyle, though oatmeal-heavy and pet-free, constitutes a loosening of the reins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And he has been adding words. Like Ellroy’s earlier books, “This Storm” has short paragraphs, single-clause sentences and heightened, at times wearying repetition. Ellroy acknowledges that he still makes “purportedly clean and direct” writers such as Dashiell Hammett and Ernest Hemingway seem “absolutely florid”. But with help from Knode and his editors he is also now convinced that, if he wants the books to have “emotional resonance”, he needs to open things up, if only a little. He calls this “a new style”—“the perfect balance” of the precise and lyrical. It’s as if, over the last decade, he has realised the need to embrace, if not equally, the two sides of his nature—wildness and control, rectitude and romanticism, “emotionality” and a spotless sideboard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On my last morning in Denver, I visited Ellroy at his flat and Knode dropped by. She asked if we were getting tired of “talking about Ellroy”. He said that we were not. Reflecting on his current circumstances, Ellroy says that he’s feeling “just outrageous good will for people”, before admitting that “I can be short-tempered and I can be rancorous and all these things, if people are pushing up against me or taking liberties”—for example, when waiters use the greeting “Hi, guys.” Then he paused, searching around for words: “I’ve just never been this happy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His new work reflects that. Without stinting on traditional Ellroy pleasures, it contains more hope and consolation. Fans of Ellroy’s earlier work may feel that he’s gone soft. Instead of evil or mercenary violence, and the “tableau of madness, hatefulness and historical dysfunction” constructed in “The Cold Six Thousand”, “This Storm” is concerned with “friendship, bravery, the ability of individuals of a wide stripe to supersede their differences and limitations and tell the truth to themselves.” Even the protagonist—“a monstrous psychopath, a fascist, a racial provocateur”—proves himself vulnerable and capable of fraternal love for a Japanese man. “This Storm” offers, says Ellroy, “the thrill of human beings changing”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You’ve taken a big breath and relaxed,” Knode told him. “It’s a lot more lucid, less internally tortured. I can just feel the oozing humanity in this one.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ellroy looked lovingly in her direction. “I’m honoured.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“You should be,” she said. “You did the work.” Ellroy gave a growl of assent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Leo Robson is a freelance journalist who has written for the &lt;/em&gt;New Yorker&lt;em&gt; and the &lt;/em&gt;New Statesman&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 20:40:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A journalist’s arrest is a worrying sign of impunity in Russia]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/07/a-journalists-arrest-is-a-worrying-sign-of-impunity-in-russia]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_eup507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-07T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE HEADLINES on Ivan Golunov’s articles make it clear that he may have made some enemies. One article pledges to explain “how officials, the security services, and bandits carve up the market for funeral services”. Others allege that the family of a vice-mayor “made billions and bought up mansions and apartments”, or promise to list “who’s making a killing on Moscow’s reconstruction”. As an investigative journalist for independent Russian media outlets, Mr Golunov developed a reputation for thorough shoe-leather reporting and scrupulous work with procurement databases to expose state corruption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the afternoon of June 6th, Moscow police detained Mr Golunov in the city centre while he was walking to meet a source. The police claimed to have found a stash of drugs in his backpack, and released photos of a small drug lab supposedly discovered in his apartment. Mr Golunov has been booked on charges of selling narcotics, carrying a potential 10- to 20-year sentence. He was prevented from contacting anyone for more than 12 hours. After a sympathetic detective tipped off a friend of Mr Golunov’s, a lawyer arrived at last. Mr Golunov alleged that police had planted the drugs and beat him up. The police refused to let medical personnel document his wounds, though they deny any misbehaviour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Golunov’s editors at Meduza, an independent news site, believe his journalism is the reason for his arrest. “We know that Ivan has received threats in recent months, and we think we know from whom,” they wrote. Colleagues and friends describe Mr Golunov as a virtual teetotaller who obeyed the law scrupulously, to avoid giving the authorities excuses to harass him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In the Russian reality, an investigative journalist even crosses the street with particular care: only on a green light, so there will be nothing to pin on him,” said Svetlana Reiter, a fellow investigative journalist. Meduza says that the handwriting on notes in police photographs does not appear to match Mr Golunov’s. Acquaintances told that site that they recognise only one of the photographs as his apartment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brazenness of the charges is not a glitch. Instead, it highlights the increasing impunity of the Russian security services. Police are known for planting drugs to meet arrest quotas. Until now such tactics have been used against political opponents only in Chechnya, where Oyub Titiev, a human-rights activist, was sentenced in March to four years in prison on drug charges that observers called fabricated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like Mr Titiev’s, Mr Golunov’s arrest is meant to send a message. “It’s a signal that they can do the same or worse with any of us,” said Pavel Kanygin of Novaya Gazeta, an independent newspaper. Journalists and supporters gathered on June 7th near the police headquarters for a series of one-man pickets, a tactic activists use to avoid a ban on protesting in groups without permission. Police detained at least seven of them—one by one—including Mr Kanygin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As police were hauling the protesters into police vans, President Vladimir Putin was striding on stage at the St Petersburg International Economic Forum, Russia’s yearly gathering of economic bigwigs. The atmosphere at this year’s forum has been marred by the arrest in February of Michael Calvey, a prominent American investor, on dubious fraud charges. Mr Putin touted Russia’s business climate and endorsed the investigation into Mr Calvey. “Just, legal decisions will be made,” Mr Putin insisted. The arrest of Mr Golunov suggests that in today’s Russia, lawlessness often masquerades as justice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 04:40:42 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to increase empathy and unite society]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/07/how-to-increase-empathy-and-unite-society]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_OPP509.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-07T17:39:53Z&quot;&gt;Jun 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IF THERE is one thing that people on both the left and right can agree, it is that expressions of our political and social differences have become markedly less cordial—and that this makes it harder to find common ground and solve common problems. The good news is that science is on the case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Empathy is not like a person’s adult height, something unalterable. Instead, it is a characteristic that can be actively encouraged or discouraged. This is the central message of a new book, “The War for Kindness: Building Empathy in a Fractured World”, by Jamil Zaki, the director of the Social Neuroscience Lab at Stanford University. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ability to structure our workplaces, schools, public spaces—and even media—to increase interactions with people from other walks of life may boost the respect that people bestow on others. This, in turn, may go some way towards helping societies to overcome political polarisation, racism, anti-immigrant anger and cultural divisions. Although Red Staters and Blue Staters, or Brexiteers and Remainers, may not lock arms—any more than the lion will lie down with the lamb—at least they will be able to talk to each other without their faces turning purple with rage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s Open Future initiative asked Mr Zaki several questions about what empathy is and how to foster it. Following that is an excerpt from his book, on the importance of contact with others to improve relations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* * *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; What is empathy and how can we measure it? Are people less empathetic today than in the past?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jamil Zaki:&lt;/strong&gt; Empathy is our ability to share and understand one another’s feelings—a psychological “superglue” that connects people and undergirds co-operation and kindness. Psychologists and neuroscientists measure empathy in numerous ways: including asking people how much they care about others, measuring how much they mimic others’ facial expressions or flinch when someone else is in pain, testing how accurately they decode others’ experiences, and examining overlap in brain activity when people experience pleasure versus seeing others happy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most common measure of empathy, a questionnaire, has been completed by hundreds of thousands of people since the late 1970s. About ten years ago, psychologists examined these data over time and found a steep drop in empathy, especially in the 21st century. Strikingly, the average American in 2009 scored as less empathic than 75% of people in 1979. We do not know the causes of this decline, though the rise of online technology and increasing polarisation seem relevant. Whatever the source, this drop in empathy should concern all of us. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; How can we harness the latest findings in neuropsychology to increase empathy?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Zaki:&lt;/strong&gt; The first step is to understand that we can increase our empathy. My least favorite phrase in neuroscience is “hard-wired,” the idea that because something resides in the brain, it is fixed and immutable. People often have that notion about empathy—that each of us has a “level” of care built in to us, which, like our adult height, will never change. But our brains are plastic, and change in response to experiences, habits and practices. The same goes for empathy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For instance, in a landmark study published two years ago, neuroscientists trained people in “loving kindness” meditation, a contemplative practice focusing on building people’s care for others. After several months of this practice, people reported greater empathy, understood others’ feelings more precisely and acted more generously to strangers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But even more strikingly, parts of their brain associated with empathy grew in volume, underscoring not only how we can increase empathy, but that we can. In fact, my colleagues and I have found that even understanding that empathy is under our control empowers people to work harder at it, especially with people who look or think differently than themselves. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; Building on that, populism, anti-immigration and anti-“other” is on the rise—how can we realistically redesign our community interactions, workplaces, schools, media, etc, to apply neuroscience and psychology to defeat this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Zaki:&lt;/strong&gt; One of our most powerful psychological instincts is to divide people into categories; for every “us” there is a “them.” This turns pernicious when mixed with competition, conflict and fear. Under these circumstances, empathy evaporates or even reverses into schadenfreude, or enjoyment of the other side’s suffering. The wreckage of America’s political climate, mixed with social media and online bullying, can seem like a schadenfreude buffet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Counteracting these trends means putting people in the position to replace “us and them” with “you and I”, as well as the incentives to see outsiders as people, rather than mere symbols of their group. One reliable way to do this is to bring people from different groups together under egalitarian circumstances and with shared goals. Another way is to encourage people to understand how empathy can be useful to them. For instance, my colleague Robb Willer has found that when people empathise with individuals on the other end of the political spectrum, they can actually argue more persuasively for their own position.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; Using your methods, won’t empathy simply develop in those who are prone to be empathetic anyway—leaving the most vile people unaffected and the world unimproved: a snowflake of kindness amid a blizzard of misanthropy? Or am I being too cynical?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Zaki:&lt;/strong&gt; I think cynicism is understandable in this cultural moment. I see it all around me, which is part of why I wrote the book. But despite appearances, even “vile” people have the capacity to become more caring under the right circumstances. In the book I tell the story of Tony McAleer, a neo Nazi whose early life was an embodiment of hatred, anger and fear. If anyone would be lost to empathy, it would be him. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And yet after meeting a Jewish man who refused to hate him back (again, moving from “us and them” to “you and I”), he reformed. Tony and his colleagues now run the group Life After Hate, which extracts others from the dark places they once inhabited. There are ample data points demonstrating that people with low empathy, even psychopaths, can turn on their care when properly motivated to do so. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; What is the most important finding from the science of empathy that people don’t know, that if they did know, the world would be a better place? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Zaki:&lt;/strong&gt; The first insight people should take with them is that we can grow our empathy if we want. Our emotions are not animalistic impulses that are out of our control. We can guide them, empathising with purpose—in ways that accord with our values. A second insight is that empathy is helpful, not just to the people around us, but to ourselves as well. It is easy to think of empathy as a squishy soft-skill in a hard world, which allows us to be nice, but also leaves us open to be trampled or left behind. But in many ways, empathic individuals finish first: experiencing greater happiness, less stress and greater professional success. Poetically, one of the best ways we can help ourselves starts with caring for each other. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* * *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hatred versus contact&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excerpted from “The War for Kindness: Building Empathy in a Fractured World” by Jamil Zaki (Crown, 2019)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 1943, a race riot seized Detroit. World War II had transformed the city into a weapons factory, and people poured in from around the country as manufacturing boomed. Housing became scarce. Black workers were excluded from housing projects and often paid triple the rent whites did. When the city earmarked a new project for black tenants only, whites burned crosses outside it. As summer arrived, racial tension boiled over. On June 20, blacks heard that a white mob had thrown a woman and her child off the Belle Isle Bridge; whites heard that blacks had raped and killed a woman on the same bridge. Neither event had actually occurred, but the imaginary mobs spawned real ones. They clashed, and in the next thirty-six hours, thirty-four people died, hundreds were injured, and thousands were arrested. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a national disgrace and a low point for American race relations. But there was a glimmer of hope: whites and blacks who had worked or studied with members of the other race were far less likely to join in the riots, and more likely to engage in peaceful behaviors, such as sheltering other-race individuals from violence. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The psychologist Gordon Allport noticed this, and saw a trend: The better people knew outsiders, the less they hated them. This was true elsewhere as well. Seventy-five percent of residents in all-white housing projects said they would dislike living alongside blacks, but only 25 percent of white residents in mixed projects actually disliked having black neighbors. Sixty-two percent of soldiers in all-white platoons opposed integrating the armed forces; among whites who had been in a mixed platoon, that number was 7 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his magnum opus, The Nature of Prejudice, Allport reasoned that bigotry often boils down to a lack of acquaintance. Its antidote was just as simple: Bring people together, and they’ll awaken to their common humanity. A similar thought led Mark Twain to quip, “Travel is fatal to prejudice, bigotry, and narrow-mindedness, and many of our people need it sorely on these accounts.” In psychology, this idea came to be known as “contact theory,” and it caught fire. Allport’s book, published in 1954, became a bestseller; he delighted in spotting it at airports and malls alongside beach novels. Thanks to him, optimists everywhere came to believe that hatred was a misunderstanding and that contact could fix it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Allport stressed that contact would not always work. In some cases it could make things worse—for instance, whites who merely saw more blacks, but didn’t get to know them, might perceive them as a threat. Time has proven Allport right. The visibility of immigrants in the United Kingdom fueled a nationalist wave that crested with Brexit. In Canada, Tony used the presence of immigrants to whip up white aggression. Even moderate people can be driven toward prejudice by the wrong type of contact. In a recent study, the political scientist Ryan Enos planted Latino passengers on a Boston commuter train at the same time each morning for ten days. White commuters who had been on a train with Latinos grew less tolerant of immigration than they had been before, or than passengers who took the very next train.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even when contact doesn’t hurt, it might not help. “Goodwill contact without concrete goals accomplishes nothing,” Allport wrote. He laid out a recipe for how to make it useful: Bring groups together and give them equal status, even if one group has more power the rest of the time. Focus on their mutual goals. Make it personal; let people learn about each other’s idiosyncrasies. And support cooperation between groups through the institutions around them. Fulfill these tenets, Allport claimed, and contact could do wonders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The theory might sound naïve—less rigorous science than Haight-Ashbury handholding. But it’s one of the most well-studied concepts in psychology. In a recent analysis of more than a quarter of a million people, the pattern was clear: The more time someone spends with outsiders, the less prejudice they express. Contact warms sentiments toward many types of outsiders. Imagine two straight, young, able white people born in the United States. Evidence suggests that the one who gets to know a diverse group will exhibit less bias toward black and Hispanic people, immigrants from Asia, Mexico, and Central America, elderly and disabled people, and the LGBTQ community than their more sheltered counterpart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact can work even when people don’t seek it out. White college freshmen randomly assigned to black roommates are less prejudiced by spring than students with same-race roommates. It doesn’t take a school year to help people warm up to new groups, either. In one recent study, trans- and cisgender canvassers went door-to-door in Florida to discuss transgender rights. After meaningful conversations with trans canvassers, residents’ transphobia dropped substantially, and they remained more tolerant three months later &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The punchline is simple: Hatred of outsiders is ancient but not inevitable. When people work, live, or play alongside each other, divisions between them melt. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To understand why, remember that empathy is a choice, and conflict gives people great reasons to avoid it. When groups compete for scarce resources, they must circle the wagons and scrap for their side. [...] Tribalism becomes natural and—from evolution’s perspective—wise. A linebacker who feels the pain of a running back would have a hard time doing his job; a soldier would find hers impossible. As a result, people in conflict don’t merely misplace their care; they actively throw it away. In one series of studies, conservative Israelis reported that they would prefer not to empathize with Palestinians. This preference, in turn, predicted their actual lack of empathy, for instance when they read about a Palestinian child with cerebral palsy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if callousness is a smart choice during war, it’s a terrible way to achieve peace. Contact remedies this by giving people reasons to care about outsiders. We crave connection and will work to keep social bonds strong. When an outsider joins the ranks of our friends or colleagues, empathizing with them aligns with that goal. The benefits compound: Empathy for one outsider can lead to caring for their entire group. Contact also makes avoiding empathy harder. The sorrow and hope of a neighbor, friend, or colleague are often impossible to block out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact can build empathy even in the toughest settings. After sectarian violence in Northern Ireland, Catholics and Protestants dehumanized each other, but they did so less if they had friends on the other side of the conflict. White Americans who work or live with blacks or Muslims express higher empathy when members of these groups are pro led by law enforcement. Empathy, in turn, promotes solidarity. After the conflict in Ireland, people who felt empathy toward outsiders were more willing to forgive them; in the United States, white Americans who empathized with minority individuals mistreated by police were more likely to join Black Lives Matter protests. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;______________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From the book “The War for Kindness: Building Empathy in a Fractured World” by Jamil Zaki. Copyright © 2019 by Jamil Zaki. Published by Crown, an imprint of Random House, a division of Penguin Random House. All rights reserved.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 03:41:11 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Climate change will be a big issue in the Democratic contest]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/07/climate-change-will-be-a-big-issue-in-the-democratic-contest]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_USP001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-07T17:15:47Z&quot;&gt;Jun 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ONE OF Elizabeth Warren’s most formative political tangles, which prompted her transition from law professor at Harvard to senator from Massachusetts, occurred in 2005 over a bankruptcy-reform bill. Ms Warren was concerned about the repercussions for middle-class Americans, especially women, who would have a harder time filing for bankruptcy as a result of the bill. A particular target of her ire was Joe Biden, then a senator from Delaware and one of the bill’s strongest backers. “Senators like Joe Biden should not be allowed to sell out women in the morning and be heralded as their friend in the evening,” she wrote at the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To this day the two are seen as ideological foes. Ms Warren appeals to a fire-breathing leftish section of the party, while Mr Biden has made a concerted effort to court moderate Democratic voters. Yet both contenders for the Democratic nomination released ambitious, detailed environmental plans within hours of one another on June 4th. The striking similarity of their plans shows how the politics of climate change has evolved from a niche issue among Democrats to one of great urgency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The American environmental activists who called for a Green New Deal, particularly Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, a freshman congresswoman from New York, can claim some credit for this change. A series of recent calamitous weather events—fires, polar vortices, hurricanes and floods—have also helped. This week, 17% of Democrats surveyed by YouGov on behalf of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; said the environment was the most important issue for them. That is second only to health care, the chief issue of last year’s mid-term elections, which captures the attention of 22%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Green New Deal has two problems. The first is that it is only skeletally sketched, with handwaving in lieu of details for the massive economic reorganisation it envisages. The second is that it includes a gratuitous list of progressive measures—including a federal jobs guarantee, a universal basic income, and universal health insurance—only tangentially related to climate policy. Many top-tier Democratic candidates, who would no doubt balk at such sweeping changes, signed on to the Green New Deal nonetheless. Yet with the release of Mr Biden’s and Ms Warren’s plans, both less quixotic and more scrupulous than the earlier sketch, the debate has been much improved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Biden had been one of the few leading presidential contenders to resist endorsing the Green New Deal. He would instead release his own climate plan, he said. An adviser’s comment that Mr Biden was seeking a “middle ground” sparked fears among activists that his would be a mishmash package that offered carbon taxes for liberals and fracking subsidies for conservatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Mr Biden’s plan is ambitious. He would like the American economy to be a net-zero emitter of carbon pollution by 2050. This would be achieved in two ways, including executive orders and actions (taking Barack Obama’s playbook for climate policy and applying it much more aggressively) that would bypass Congress. The second way, which would require legislation, is through a $1.7trn in federal funding for what Mr Biden calls, in a Sandersesque turn of phrase, a “Clean Energy Revolution”. There are other sensible proposals—finally developing the high-speed rail that America lacks, and reforming zoning to encourage denser, more efficient cities—scattered throughout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One innovation, which seems to play to Mr Biden’s strengths as a foreign-policy expert, is to threaten tariffs on countries without adequate environmental policies. America accounts for only 15% of the world’s greenhouse-gas emissions. China accounts for nearly twice that. Mr Biden’s language on this—he says he wants “strong new measures to stop other countries from cheating on their climate commitments”—sounds almost Trumpian. Given that Mr Biden is the clear front-runner for the Democratic nomination, this perhaps paves the way for a future attack on the president for focusing his trade actions on the wrong problem. Climate change is a much more serious problem for America’s future than illegal immigration or bilateral trade deficits, Mr Biden could credibly argue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Warren’s plan has a Trumpian echo, too: it was released under the banner of “economic patriotism”. It represents, according to her, “my commitment to a Green New Deal”—one that applies the analogy of wartime mobilisation during Franklin Roosevelt’s presidency to modern times. Hers is straightforward industrial policy—calling for $2trn in investments over the next 10 years for research and development—with three-quarters of that vast sum spent through federal procurement. Ms Warren thinks that all that production would generate 1m jobs, which would pay at least $15 per hour and guarantee 12 weeks of paid family and medical leave. About $100bn of the money would be spent on a “Green Marshall Plan”, dedicated to exporting the clean-energy technology developed in America to other countries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The curious thing about both proposals is that they dodge the question of a price on carbon, whether through direct taxation or a cap-and-trade scheme. Though research into more cost-effective technology for carbon capture and sequestration or solar power is helpful and necessary, a carbon price incorporating the negative externality of pollution would seem a simple first step. Mr Biden’s plan only nebulously nods towards “the principles that polluters must bear the full cost of the carbon pollution they are emitting” and says nothing more on the subject. It goes unmentioned in Ms Warren’s plan. Both candidates presumably employ clever policy staffers who know about carbon pricing—but they also employ strategists who note that carbon taxes are quite easily dismissed as energy taxes by political opponents. The lessons of 2010, when a Democratic effort to create a carbon market spectacularly collapsed despite unified control of government leading to an electoral backlash, seem to have been well-remembered. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 02:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Britain’s major parties are weaker than ever before]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/07/britains-major-parties-are-weaker-than-ever-before]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_woc221_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-07T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PREDICTING EARTHQUAKES is doomed to failure, as seismologists well know. But some political earthquakes are a different matter. In the early hours of June 7th, the Brexit Party’s candidate, Mike Greene, came close to winning the first seat in Parliament for a party that was created just two months earlier. He fell just 683 votes short of Labour’s winning candidate in a by-election in Peterborough (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/07/labour-holds-peterborough-slowing-the-brexit-partys-momentum&quot;&gt;see article&lt;/a&gt;). Even so, the result amounts to a political tremor that was much predicted, though perhaps not the Big One that some had expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;’s analysis of Westminster voting-intention polls.&lt;p&gt;The last time both parties’ support took a big simultaneous dip was in 2010, when the Liberal Democrats briefly polled in second place following an impressive televised debate by their leader, Nick Clegg. Even then, Labour and the Tories still had 65% of the vote in the election—25 percentage points higher than today’s share. The two big parties risk being overtaken by the upstart Brexit Party and the Liberal Democrats, who enjoyed a revival in last month’s local and European elections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trends in party support now look more like the wobbly lines of a seismometer than the decades-old separation between the two biggest parties and the rest. Brexit is the main cause of their instability. Historically, the Conservatives and Labour have fought elections mainly on domestic issues, such as levels of government spending and the National Health Service. But the vote to leave the European Union in a referendum in 2016 opened a new fault-line within the country and within both main parties. As Britain polarises over Brexit, a growing number of voters want parties that represent clear, stark views of EU membership: leave without a deal, or reverse the referendum and remain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the culmination of social changes that have been taking place since the 1980s, and reflect striking differences between old and young, and between university graduates and the poorly educated. But the two main parties have so been able to rely on Britain’s first-past-the-post electoral system—which penalises smaller parties—to hold on to a disproportionate share of seats in Parliament. Given the state of the polls, as well as the results from Peterborough, their supremacy is at stake. Rob Ford, a political scientist at Manchester University, says that the biggest barrier to a political realignment in Britain is in convincing voters that third parties are viable, but “If people stop believing that the major parties are the only ones that can fly, that becomes a self-fulfilling prophecy.” A great tectonic shift is underway in British politics. Whether Labour and the Tories survive the earthquake will depend on how well they can adjust to the shifting ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 02:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why spoilers are ruining storytelling]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/07/why-spoilers-are-ruining-storytelling]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_BKP512.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-07T17:09:02Z&quot;&gt;Jun 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN THE first few decades of cinema, patrons would buy a ticket that granted general admission to the theatre. Several features would be playing on a loop, and you could choose whichever you fancied. You might enter halfway through the main movie, watch it until the end, see the cartoons and the newsreel and then start from the beginning to catch what you’d missed. It functioned rather like a big public television.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, in 1960, a director decreed that no one would be permitted to enter screenings once his new film had begun: the integrity of the viewing experience was paramount. The film was “Psycho” and Alfred Hitchcock’s edict—part artistic statement, part marketing ploy—placed new emphasis on plot twists in the final act. (He also asked critics not to discuss those key details.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, writers and film-makers are obsessed with spoilers. J.K. Rowling has urged those watching “Harry Potter and the Cursed Child”, a stage play, or the new “Fantastic Beasts” films to “keep the secrets”. Anthony and Joseph Russo, the directors of Marvel films, have issued statements requesting that fans not ruin them for others. When “Once Upon a Time...in Hollywood” screened in Cannes, a similar plea from Quentin Tarantino was read to the press, to much exasperated booing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Audiences are zealous about the matter, too. Many viewers will go offline prior to episodes of a favourite television show, or mute certain words on social media so as to avoid seeing potentially spoiling posts. Writers must declare that their review contains spoilers, or face a backlash. One fan was assaulted outside a screening of “Avengers: Endgame” for “loudly revealing” the movie’s outcome. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Narratives have always had twists and unforeseen turns. “Citizen Kane” (1941) reveals a crucial detail in the last minute; whodunnits keep audiences guessing until a last gasp-inducing denouement . Yet Michael Curtiz didn’t ban viewers from entering “Mildred Pierce” (1945) late, nor did Orson Welles embargo the press on matters relating to “Rosebud”. Surprises were there to be had, certainly, but they weren’t particularly treasured or protected. (A notable exception is a production of “The Mousetrap” on the West End, which for decades has asked its patrons to keep quiet.) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In films of the 1990s such as “The Crying Game”, “Seven”, “The Usual Suspects” and “Fight Club”, the twist ending came of age; M. Night Shyamalan, a writer and director, became something of a master of the form. The ascendancy of the twist coincided with the spread of the internet, and the spoiler hysteria began. With so much analysis of films and television online, new rules of debate were inaugurated whereby warnings must be given about spoilers, or readers must be allowed to opt in to them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Film-makers realised that fans were invested in the surprise and pandered to them. Joseph McGinty Nichol released false spoilers for “Terminator: Salvation”; other directors shot multiple endings for their films. “The Last Watch”, a documentary about the making of the last season of “Game of Thrones”, shows scripts being shredded following the cast read-through and actors being flown out for needless location shoots to mislead journalists and fans. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is all rather ridiculous—and cynical. Shocking plots are what get people talking, tweeting and tuning in. In television, they help to guarantee huge ratings on the day of broadcast. The hubbub encourages fans to book their cinema tickets in advance. The Russo brothers begging viewers not to ruin the Avengers films probably helped them to secure the biggest opening weekend in film history. See it now, that seemed to say, or have someone else spoil it for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This attitude stifles proper discussion of stories by critics as much as viewers, and it inflicts damage on storytelling as a craft. By promoting one technique, the twist, and one effect, surprise, stories get bent out of shape. They try too hard to counter expectation and resist predictability. “The Lord of the Rings” is totally predictable from beginning to end, but the series does not suffer for it. William Shakespeare gave away the end of his tragedies by billing them as such and no one seemed to mind (“Romeo and Juliet” even told the audience the story in a prologue). “Columbo”, a classic crime serial, reveals who commited the murder at the beginning of each episode and succeeded in making the investigation thrilling to watch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stories that promote surprise over character end up as mere soap opera, a series of sensational shocks. That corrodes credibility, while some reveals—they were all dead! it was all a dream!—do not so much blow minds as waste time. More significant than all of this, though, is the fact that surprise is overrated. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/0956797611417007&quot;&gt;A study carried out by Jonathan Leavitt and Nicholas Christenfeld&lt;/a&gt; in 2011 found that knowing how the story ends doesn’t hamper enjoyment—it increases it. In other words, spoilers don’t spoil anything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:40:30 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>