<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[A magnificent exhibition of manga at the British Museum]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/05/a-magnificent-exhibition-of-manga-at-the-british-museum]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_BKP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-05T15:51:54Z&quot;&gt;Jun 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT IS 2019. The American president spends his “executive time” posting memes on Twitter. Video-streaming platforms are valued in the hundreds of billions of dollars. TikTok, an utterly baffling but hugely enjoyable app of very short, very weird videos, is taking the world by storm. Contemporary culture is dominated by the visual and the mass produced, and has been for years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And yet, prompted by a new exhibition of Japanese manga, newspapers are still asking whether modern visual culture has any place in museums. “I’m not knocking manga or its fans, but what has it got to do with the British Museum?” Jonathan Jones wrote in the &lt;em&gt;Guardian&lt;/em&gt;. “What’s next—Rembrandt meets Dennis the Menace?” the &lt;em&gt;Telegraph&lt;/em&gt; asked: “Is manga really as significant as Rodin and the Ancient Greeks?” The answers to these questions are, in order, everything, why not, and quite possibly. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That designated tastemakers pooh-pooh any sign of an old institution dabbling in something new is perhaps predictable. But it is precisely for that reason that the British Museum ought to be lauded for putting on this dynamic, exuberant and ambitious celebration of Japan’s comic-art narrative form. It somehow manages to strike the right balance for every type of visitor, from the utter novice to the knowledgeable fan. For the newbie there are instructions on how to read from right to left, how to decipher the codes embedded in the speech bubbles, and introductions to famous artists and important texts. For the long-time fan, original prints of canonical works will prove a big draw (pardon the pun), as will displays of the historical prints and fabrics that have influenced the modern form. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those, such as this reviewer, who fall somewhere in between—that is, with a passing acquaintance but nothing resembling expertise—it is an utter delight. The exhibition probes the historical roots of manga, with nods to Katsushika Hokusai, a famous artist and printmaker. It lays out the many genres and subgenres within the sprawling world of manga, and goes into satisfying detail on the cultural cross-pollination of American and Japanese comics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Were it all prints and information cards, the exhibition could still have been a sweet if underwhelming attempt at bringing mass culture into the museum. But it is in expanding beyond the art itself, into the experience, that it truly highlights the significance that some critics fail to see. Just as the Greeks created plays and texts and ways of thinking and seeing the world that continue to touch the lives of millions, so too has manga created a global culture that millions participate in. Some dress up as their favourite characters, buy merchandise, read fan comics and blogs (or indeed make fan-art). Others read or are touched by other things that have been influenced by manga, such as Pokémon, which started life as a video game, was adapted into manga, and later morphed into a global phenomenon that layered a virtual world over the real one. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best thing about the exhibition, however, is all the stuff that isn’t in it. Unlike an exhibition of Rembrandt, to take Mr Jones’s example, this show is an introduction, an enticement to fall down the deep rabbit hole of a different world of art and narrative and culture. That manga itself is mass-produced, inexpensive and easy to acquire on Amazon is an added bonus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Manga” continues at the British Museum until August 26th&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 23:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s visit to Britain goes well—at least for him]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/05/donald-trumps-visit-to-britain-goes-well-at-least-for-him]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_brp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-05T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;DONALD TRUMP saw only people cheering, not protests, reports of which the president branded “fake news”. They did not seem so fake on Whitehall. Placards said “Dump Trump”, “Trump: Climate Disaster” and “Keep Trump away from our NHS”. One optimistic poster proposed “Stop Brexit, stop Trump”. Most bizarre was a banner saying “Man Utd fans against apartheid”. The mood was cheerful, even carnival-like—at least until it rained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As ever, Labour’s Jeremy Corbyn came out to back the protests. But his disdain was diluted after Mr Trump revealed that he had rejected a meeting request from Mr Corbyn, whom he dubbed a “negative force”. He said the same of Sadiq Khan, London’s mayor, calling him a “stone-cold loser”. This contrasted with his enthusiasm for Brexiteers, singling out Boris Johnson as a great potential successor to Theresa May as prime minister. He also met Nigel Farage, whose new Brexit Party is eating into Tory support, suggesting he should be one of the Brexit negotiators.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The president clearly valued hobnobbing with royalty and feasting in Buckingham Palace with the queen (whom he called a “fantastic woman”) more than bilateral discussions with Mrs May. But although he said he would have negotiated Brexit differently, by suing the European Union, he also praised Mrs May’s deal. And he glossed over differences on Huawei, a Chinese telecoms giant mistrusted by America but cautiously accepted in Britain, by saying that the two countries would soon reach an agreement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trade was trickier. Mr Trump promised a “phenomenal” post-Brexit deal that would double or even triple bilateral trade. But he also echoed his ambassador by saying that everything should be on the table. That includes not just farm products but access to the NHS. When most Tory leadership candidates instantly said the NHS was not up for sale, Mr Trump backtracked. But his own trade negotiating documents make clear that the Americans will look for more NHS contracts and fairer access for drugs. What’s more, Congress has said it will not ratify any trade deal if Brexit is seen to threaten peace in Northern Ireland. A bilateral deal looks both hard and far off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The British managed to get in a few subtler digs of their own, with the queen and Mrs May going out of their way to praise the role of international institutions, which Mr Trump has criticised or in some cases abandoned. The prime minister openly admitted to differences on climate change and Iran, and she used this week’s D-day commemoration to remind the president of the value of NATO in upholding the global order. Mr Trump’s response was to repeat his demand that NATO allies spend more on defence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Besides praising Mr Johnson, with whom he spoke by phone, Mr Trump sought meetings with Jeremy Hunt, the foreign secretary, whom he said would make a good prime minister, and with Michael Gove, the environment secretary, whom he claimed not to know. The White House has clearly decided these are the three strongest candidates to succeed Mrs May. It is not obvious that Mr Trump’s support will prove helpful, any more than was Barack Obama’s backing for the Remain campaign in 2016. Yet it could weigh with some Tory party members. Certainly Mr Hunt and Mr Gove seemed pleased.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 23:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America’s vision for the Indo-Pacific gets a lukewarm reception]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/05/americas-vision-for-the-indo-pacific-gets-a-lukewarm-reception]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_asp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-05T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHAT DO YOU buy the Asian defence minister who has everything? How about a “beautiful” photo-book of North Korean ships illegally transferring oil at sea? Patrick Shanahan, America’s acting defence secretary, presented the collection of grainy aerial shots to his Chinese counterpart, General Wei Fenghe, at the Shangri-La Dialogue, an annual gathering of military bigwigs in Singapore from May 31st to June 2nd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was an emollient gesture in fractious times. When Banyan asked Mr Shanahan what he planned to say to General Wei in private, the answer was not a tirade about Huawei or the South China Sea. Instead Mr Shanahan said he was “excited” to explore areas of co-operation. North Korean sanctions-busting—which often occurs in Chinese waters—was top of the list. Such collaboration would show that America and China could “compete in a constructive way”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On June 1st the Pentagon published its plans for that competition in an Indo-Pacific strategy. At its heart was the idea of a “free and open Indo-Pacific” (FOIP), a nebulous concept conceived by Japan and enthusiastically taken up by the Trump administration. In essence, FOIP is a rules-based rejoinder to China’s vision of spheres of influence, gunboat diplomacy and murky loans. “No one nation can or should dominate the Indo-Pacific,” said the Pentagon in its report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shanahan’s notion of responsible competition—in contrast to the no-holds-barred clash of civilisations favoured by some of his head-banging colleagues—is laudable. It is also savvy. Asian states are likelier to sign up to FOIP if they are persuaded that America is not spoiling for a fight. But on both counts—stabilising the relationship with China, while rallying partners to push back against it—America has an uphill task.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start with the olive branches. General Wei did not so much ignore them as snap them into pieces. “Arise, all those who do not want be enslaved,” he thundered in his speech on June 2nd, quoting China’s national anthem. “Let us build the new Great Wall with our flesh and blood.” He warned that China’s army was “not afraid of sacrifice” and that “we make no promise to renounce the use of force” against Taiwan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One might think that such bluster would send Asians rushing to sign up to FOIP and into America’s arms. In some cases, it has. Narendra Modi will deepen defence ties with America in his second term. Japan is beefing up its armed forces and sending its navy into the South China Sea. Officials from America, Australia, India and Japan—the “Quad”—now confer routinely, most recently on May 31st.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All pay lip service to the idea that the Association of South-East Asian Nations (ASEAN), a club of ten mostly smaller powers, should be at the core of FOIP. The problem is that not all in ASEAN are sold on the idea. For one thing, many are unconvinced that America will truly stick around, as the costs of any war with China grow over time. So why risk China’s ire? “The Chinese coast guard is bigger than Malaysia’s warships,” lamented Malaysia’s defence minister.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shanahan did his best to assuage these concerns. He pointed out that the Indo-Pacific was America’s “priority theatre”, with four times as many American forces as any other American military command. America’s freedom of navigation operations in the South China Sea were also growing more routine: unusually, there were two in May alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But muscle is only half of it. The larger issue is that Donald Trump’s unpredictably incendiary foreign policy sits uneasily with the principles of FOIP. Tensions with Iran are pulling America’s attention back to the Middle East. The compulsive resort to tariffs undercuts a rules-based trading order. Mr Trump’s lack of interest in human rights hardly furthers freedom. And to many in Asia, America’s war on Huawei or its sanctions against buyers of Russian arms or Iranian oil look an awful lot like China’s “toolkit of coercion”, as Mr Shanahan put it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is unfair. An Asian order sculpted by China would be more capricious and suffocating than anything Mr Trump could devise. General Wei’s brazen defence of the Tiananmen Square massacre—he called it a “correct policy” that gave China the stability to grow richer—was a reminder of the ideological stakes. Australia, India and Japan are on board. Singapore and Vietnam’s sympathies are clear. But most ASEAN countries hate the idea of taking sides, despite widespread misgivings about China’s intentions. Mr Shanahan reckons they will eventually come round. “I think they’re building up their confidence,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 22:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“They’ve brought the violence from Darfur to the capital”—shootings in Sudan]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/05/theyve-brought-the-violence-from-darfur-to-the-capital-shootings-in-sudan]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_blm505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-05T11:10:14Z&quot;&gt;Jun 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEARLY TWO months after staging a coup, military leaders have brutally cracked down on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/03/sudans-generals-turn-their-guns-against-protesters&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;protesters in Sudan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Talks with the opposition have fallen apart—as have hopes for a resurgent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/31/with-sudans-street-fighting-women&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sudanese democracy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. We examine the rise in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/05/25/guns-from-the-united-states-are-flooding-latin-america&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;gun violence in Latin America&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; and how much of it can be pinned on American-made weapons. And, a look at the striking effects of a striker: how &lt;strong&gt;one footballer’s image is reducing hate crime&lt;/strong&gt; in Liverpool. Runtime: 20 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/sameastheoldboss-crackdowninsudan&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 20:40:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The race to become Britain’s next PM]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/04/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-31T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 31st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HERESA MAY&lt;/small&gt; has announced that she will step down as leader of the Conservative Party on June 7th. She will remain as prime minister until her successor is chosen. Nominations for the Tory leadership will close in the week beginning June 10th, followed by several rounds of voting among MPs, a process that will last until the end of the month. The MPs will then send two names to party members who will make the final choice. The result of their vote will be announced before parliament rises for summer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Betfair Exchange, a gambling website, has been tracking punters’ predictions on the next Tory leader. According to the wisdom of the betting crowd, a handful of candidates stand out. But there is only one clear frontrunner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adrian Wooldridge, our political editor, assesses the chances of the leading Conservative politicians hoping to take the top job in this short film &lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ychDrZ2QzlE&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Source: Betfair Exchange&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 20:40:18 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What it’s like to spend half a life in solitary confinement]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/06/05/what-its-like-to-spend-half-a-life-in-solitary-confinement]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_usp504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-05T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TONY MEDINA is a polite, burly man with heavily tattooed arms. Like all who are confined at the Allan B. Polunsky Unit, he is dressed in white. The prison’s squat, grey buildings hold 214 death-row inmates. Locked into a tiny booth in a visiting room, handcuffs off, he compares being “out here” to a vacation. It is quiet, save clangs of metal doors. The room is also cooled and, a rarity, he can see through Plexiglass to the face of another human.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was convicted in 1996, aged 21, for a drive-by shooting that killed two children at a New Year’s party. Since then, for 23 years, he has been awaiting execution. In Texas the death penalty is applied to those found guilty of the most heinous crimes; judges may also consider who was judged to be a threat to others. Mr Medina’s legal appeals are ongoing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A deafening wall of noise was “my clearest first memory of death row”, he says. “It’s gates slamming, the steel on steel, prisons are all concrete and steel, so it echoes, echoes, echoes. It never stops.” On his first night he was placed in a darkened wing of shouting inmates, a dumbfounding experience, “like Thunderdome-type noise, yelling and screaming and banging and everything multiplied”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early on he shared a cell. Then, after other prisoners tried an escape in 1998, all death-row inmates were shifted to solitary. He complains this is agony. “I wasn’t sentenced to solitary confinement. I was sentenced to death.” Every day since, for 19 years, he has been alone for 23 hours inside a concrete box measuring 7 feet by 11 feet. Guards pass trays of food through a slat in a door. Standing on his bed he can peer from a vent-window, a few inches high, near the ceiling. “Some guys spend all day long” doing so, he says. He never does, shunning “what is out there that I can’t touch”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He gets an hour in an enclosed yard, most days, for recreation. Again he is alone. In his cell he reads (at the moment a series about survivalists), writes or sometimes paints. Relations and volunteers, mostly European women, visit and send messages. Inmates shout to each other, cell-to-cell. But Texas, unlike some states, denies solitary prisoners any physical contact, other than frequent body inspections by guards. He says he last touched a relative, hugging his mother, on August 1st 1996. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Has a lack of human contact changed him? He describes “feeling alone, a sense of feeling abandoned”, describes himself withdrawing, growing less active, going for days without speaking, losing the urge to do recreation or to read. Other states with the death penalty, and federal prisons, have less strict conditions. In many, young inmates and those with mental-health problems are no longer isolated for long. Even Texas, with more prisoners in solitary than any other state—about 4,200 as of 2017—is reducing its numbers. A report in 2018 by the Liman Centre at Yale University estimated 61,000 inmates were kept isolated across America, of whom about 37% had endured six months or more. That tally is probably lower today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Medina believes Texas goes on isolating its death-row prisoners out of vindictiveness, not because of security. He calls the practice outright “torture”, “cruel and inhumane”, a means of “intimidation to break a person mentally” before his execution. (On average a death-row prisoner in Texas waits nearly 11 years before being put to death; the longest wait was 31 years.) It is hard to dispute his claims.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dennis Longmire, of Sam Houston State University in nearby Huntsville, says prolonged use of solitary cells is costly and needless. The UN and advocacy groups routinely condemn the practice. He has testified at 40 trials that older inmates are not especially violent to others. He recalls that his own visits to death row were deafening and unpleasant. Unsurprisingly, many guards demand to work elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many inmates suffer mental deterioration, and some turn to suicide, says Mr Medina, telling of his once “solid” immediate neighbour who broke after 15 years in his box. Prisoners grow anxious from isolation and sensory deprivation, or grow obsessed by what they see as official petty malevolence. For example, inmates in Polunsky were refused the right to buy nail clippers for 17 years. Nor are inmates supposed to decorate their cell walls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some crack while waiting for execution. When close friends are taken away—sometimes noisily resisting—for lethal injections, there is added turmoil. He counts 437 executions in Texas since he arrived on death row, including “guys that I’ve considered brothers”. It is especially distressing, he says, hearing guards chat and joke as condemned men are removed for execution. Many inmates arrive with mental difficulties. One death-row inmate in Polunsky, Andre Thomas, notoriously gouged out his own eyes and ate one. He has been moved to a psychiatric unit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In conversation Mr Medina is articulate and measured, but he says isolated confinement takes a toll. He experiences intense rage, which he calls beneficial, towards “the system—the way I hold onto my sanity is by reminding myself to be angry at the people that put me here.” The anger helped him “build a lot of walls very high in my mind”, but “it’s not very healthy” for it “can eat at you”. He has heard of inmates in Texas, released from solitary, unable to bear living among other people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His response echoes the words of Albert Woodfox, a prisoner kept in solitary confinement in Louisiana for 43 years before being released in 2016, aged 69. Mr Woodfox recently published a book, “Solitary”, in which he writes that “the fight for sanity never goes away” and he says he “shut my emotional system down” to cope with being locked away alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At issue is not whether to punish the guilty—though Mr Woodfox did eventually prove he had been wrongfully convicted. It is whether America should treat even its hardest prisoners like this. “I feel like we’re seen in the same light as places like China, Saudi Arabia and Iran. That’s the company we keep,” says Mr Medina. “Human beings are not meant to be isolated in this way.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 17:40:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Under left or right, Denmark is set to adopt ever harsher policies against migrants]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/04/under-left-or-right-denmark-will-get-ever-tougher-with-migrants]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_eup502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-04T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR A striking example of how far-right parties can change the politics of a democratic Western country, even without ever holding office, look no further than to wealthy, well-ordered Denmark. The anti-immigrant Danish People’s Party (DPP), which was first elected to the Danish parliament in 1998, has relentlessly pushed mainstream parties into adopting ever harsher policies towards immigrants, often Muslims.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The general election, which takes place on June 5th, will confirm the trend. The country of 5.7m has been ruled since 2015 by a centre-right alliance led by the Venstre party under the prime minister, Lars Løkke Rasmussen. Lacking a majority, Mr Rasmussen has had to rely on the votes of the DPP (which also supported centre-right governments between 2001 and 2011).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Venstre is polling at just 18%, and will probably lose to the Social Democrats (SD), on 29%. The SD ruled Denmark for most of the 20th century and built much of its generous welfare state. But don’t expect it to bring much change when it comes to dealing with foreigners. In the bidding war for Denmark’s increasingly strident anti-immigrant vote, the SD is promising more limits on foreigners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The DPP’s influence has helped to normalise xenophobic and Islamophobic sentiments. Last year Mr Rasmussen rolled out a plan to banish asylum-seekers to an isolated island, once used as a research centre for contagious diseases in animals, if they cannot be deported because of humanitarian concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parliament has passed laws banning women from wearing the burqa or other face coverings in public. It allows officials to confiscate cash, jewellery and other valuables from asylum-seekers, supposedly to pay for the cost of their upkeep in asylum centres. This year it approved a “paradigm shift” under which the country’s asylum policy will focus on repatriation instead of integration. This means the government can deport refugees whose countries it deems safe enough, such as Somalia (even though a Danish delegation that visited the country in 2015 to assess its security situation did not dare leave the airport).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Rasmussen also announced a policy to eradicate “ghettos” by 2030. Denmark defines these as neighbourhoods with lower income and education levels, and higher unemployment and crime rates, than the national average, and over 50% “non-Western” residents. Seeking to avoid the creation of “parallel societies”, the policy forces such areas to cut social housing to 40% of the total housing stock. For example, in Tingbjerg, a suburb of Copenhagen classified as a “hard ghetto”, all homes are social housing. Local housing associations are required to demolish buildings, build new private homes or sell property to investors. The policy also demands that children in these areas must attend publicly funded nurseries and take classes in “Danish values”, or risk losing benefits. Those who commit crimes in the “ghettos” will face harsher punishments than if they commit them elsewhere. Critics say that the policy places a stigma on immigrants; they argue that blaming foreigners ignores the underlying reasons for Denmark’s social problems, such as unemployment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In stark contrast to parties on the left in other Nordic countries, such as Sweden and Finland, the SD has proposed taking these policies even further. Even as she steers her party further to the left economically—pledging to raise taxes on the rich, for instance—the SD leader, Mette Frederiksen (pictured), is moving to the right on immigration. The SD has proposed an annual cap on “non-Western” immigration, and a limit to the share of “non-Western” students that schools are allowed to enrol at one time. Foreign senior citizens who give up their Danish residency would be allowed to take their state pensions with them if they moved back to their countries of origin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Frederiksen has even flirted with the idea of co-operating with the DPP if she wins power. If you can’t beat them, join them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 17:40:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Virginia’s governor calls for tougher gun laws]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/04/virginias-governor-calls-for-tougher-gun-laws]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_USP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-04T19:27:11Z&quot;&gt;Jun 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON MAY 31st a gunman walked into a municipal office in Virginia Beach and slaughtered 12 people, most of them colleagues he had worked with for years, before he was killed in a gun battle with police. The killer—whom the police have referred to by name only once, part of a move to strip mass shooters of their notoriety—used two semi-automatic handguns, both bought legally. He also used a silencer and extended ammunition magazines, which are also legal in Virginia. It seems likely that his presence, heavily armed, in the building, was also above board. Thanks to the state’s liberal concealed-carry laws anyone with a licence can walk into a restaurant, shop or office in Virginia carrying a gun. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Four days later, Ralph Northam, Virginia’s governor, said he would recall lawmakers to the state Capitol in June to debate a package of gun-control measures. It included, he said, a ban on silencers and high capacity ammunition magazines and new powers for local governments to limit guns in city buildings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It is wrong, it is outrageous, it is unforgivable to turn our municipal centers, our schools, our churches and synagogues and mosques, into battlefields,” he said at a news conference on June 4th. “I will be asking for votes and laws, not thoughts and prayers.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Northam, a Democrat who has long been an advocate of stricter gun controls, said he also wanted lawmakers to vote on bills to compel gun buyers to undergo universal background checks, to limit gun purchases to one a month, and to allow authorities to seize the weapons of those deemed a threat. He said that while mass shootings made headlines, far more Virginians were killed in smaller incidents—1,028 in 2017 alone. He cited the case of a little girl who was shot dead in a park last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twelve years after a student at Virginia Tech killed 32 and wounded 17 with two semi-automatic pistols in a 10-minute rampage in 2007, Virginia has yet to pass any of the stringent gun regulations that have cut gun deaths elsewhere. It is one of 17 states in which more people are killed by guns than car crashes, according to the Centre for American Progress, a think tank. In 2012 Virginia’s lawmakers repealed a law, passed in the wake of the Virginia Tech massacre, which prevented the purchase of more than one gun per person per month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Northam, a doctor who has described treating children and soldiers for bullet wounds, made gun-control a big issue in his campaign for the governorship in 2017. But his efforts have so far failed. Republicans, who hold narrow majorities in Virginia’s House and Senate, have blocked all such efforts, including a push, in January, to ban high-capacity magazines. “They have never received a fair hearing”, Mr Northam said. “I want these pieces of common sense gun safety legislation to get to the floor and let these individuals elected by you, the people, to come to the floor and cast their vote.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One Republican lawmaker did indicate that he was willing to debate gun controls. Addressing a group of protesters who had gathered outside his office to call for gun controls, Thomas Norment, the majority leader in the state Senate, said “there ought to be a meaningful discussion legislatively and in the community about gun control.” But he is also reported to have told the protestors that “nothing would have helped us at Virginia Beach”. The House Speaker, Kirk Cox, meanwhile, described Mr Northam’s announcement as “hasty and suspect when considered against the backdrop of the last few months”—apparently alluding to revelations in February that Mr Northam had donned blackface as a student. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Northam may have more luck with his gun-control push next year. Since 2016, when Hillary Clinton won Virginia, Democrats have stormed elections in the state, taking its three elective offices—governor, lieutenant-governor and attorney-general—and three congressional seats. In November, all seats in the general assembly will be up for election. With Republicans holding a two-seat majority in the House and Senate, Democrats are hoping to flip both. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 05:40:21 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Under left or right, Denmark is set to adopt ever harsher policies against migrants]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/04/under-left-or-right-denmark-is-set-to-adopt-ever-harsher-policies-against-migrants]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_eup502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-04T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR A striking example of how far-right parties can change the politics of a democratic Western country, even without ever holding office, look no further than to wealthy, well-ordered Denmark. The anti-immigrant Danish People’s Party (DPP), which was first elected to the Danish parliament in 1998, has relentlessly pushed mainstream parties into adopting ever harsher policies towards immigrants, often Muslims.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The general election, which takes place on June 5th, will confirm the trend. The country of 5.7m has been ruled since 2015 by a centre-right alliance led by the Venstre party under the prime minister, Lars Løkke Rasmussen. Lacking a majority, Mr Rasmussen has had to rely on the votes of the DPP (which also supported centre-right governments between 2001 and 2011).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Venstre is polling at just 18%, and will probably lose to the Social Democrats (SD), on 29%. The SD ruled Denmark for most of the 20th century and built much of its generous welfare state. But don’t expect it to bring much change when it comes to dealing with foreigners. In the bidding war for Denmark’s increasingly strident anti-immigrant vote, the SD is promising more limits on foreigners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The DPP’s influence has helped to normalise xenophobic and Islamophobic sentiments. Last year Mr Rasmussen rolled out a plan to banish asylum-seekers to an isolated island, once used as a research centre for contagious diseases in animals, if they cannot be deported because of humanitarian concerns.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Parliament has passed laws banning women from wearing the burqa or other face coverings in public. It allows officials to confiscate cash, jewellery and other valuables from asylum-seekers, supposedly to pay for the cost of their upkeep in asylum centres. This year it approved a “paradigm shift” under which the country’s asylum policy will focus on repatriation instead of integration. This means the government can deport refugees whose countries it deems safe enough, such as Somalia (even though a Danish delegation that visited the country in 2015 to assess its security situation did not dare leave the airport).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Rasmussen also announced a policy to eradicate “ghettos” by 2030. Denmark defines these as neighbourhoods with lower income and education levels, and higher unemployment and crime rates, than the national average, and over 50% “non-Western” residents. Seeking to avoid the creation of “parallel societies”, the policy forces such areas to cut social housing to 40% of the total housing stock. For example, in Tingbjerg, a suburb of Copenhagen classified as a “hard ghetto”, all homes are social housing. Local housing associations are required to demolish buildings, build new private homes or sell property to investors. The policy also demands that children in these areas must attend publicly funded nurseries and take classes in “Danish values”, or risk losing benefits. Those who commit crimes in the “ghettos” will face harsher punishments than if they commit them elsewhere. Critics say that the policy places a stigma on immigrants; they argue that blaming foreigners ignores the underlying reasons for Denmark’s social problems, such as unemployment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In stark contrast to parties on the left in other Nordic countries, such as Sweden and Finland, the SD has proposed taking these policies even further. Even as she steers her party further to the left economically—pledging to raise taxes on the rich, for instance—the SD leader, Mette Frederiksen (pictured), is moving to the right on immigration. The SD has proposed an annual cap on “non-Western” immigration, and a limit to the share of “non-Western” students that schools are allowed to enrol at one time. Foreign senior citizens who give up their Danish residency would be allowed to take their state pensions with them if they moved back to their countries of origin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Frederiksen has even flirted with the idea of co-operating with the DPP if she wins power. If you can’t beat them, join them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 05:40:20 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tariffs at dawn]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/04/tariffs-at-dawn]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_blm503_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-04T17:50:09Z&quot;&gt;Jun 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PRESIDENT TRUMP has started using &lt;strong&gt;import tariffs&lt;/strong&gt; to win political as well as economic battles. What will be the impact of his latest threats to impose tariffs on Mexican goods? Also, how the Federal Reserve is preparing &lt;strong&gt;for the next economic recession&lt;/strong&gt;. And, how a &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/02/charity-begins-at-work&quot;&gt;toxic working environment&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; can poison lives even among do-gooders. Simon Long hosts. Runtime: 19 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-tariffsatdawn&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2019 02:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>