<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Justin Amash calls for Donald Trump’s impeachment]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/21/justin-amash-calls-for-donald-trumps-impeachment]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_USP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-21T02:31:11Z&quot;&gt;May 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON MAY 18th, shortly after he finished reading the Mueller Report, Justin Amash, a five-term representative from Michigan, became the first Republican in Congress to call for the impeachment of President Donald Trump. In a lengthy Twitter thread Mr Amash argued that Mr Trump’s conduct had met the constitutional standard for impeachment—and that William Barr, the attorney-general, had “misled the public” about the special counsel’s findings over the president’s apparent “high Crimes and Misdemeanors.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“While impeachment should be undertaken only in extraordinary circumstances, the risk we face in an environment of extreme partisanship is not that Congress will employ it as a remedy too often but rather that Congress will employ it so rarely that it cannot deter misconduct,” wrote Mr Amash. He added that few members of Congress had read the report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Amash, who in 2010 became the youngest member of Congress when he was elected in the Tea Party wave that crashed over America, has been a rare Republican critic of Mr Trump. In 2016, shortly after Mr Trump was elected, Mr Amash accused him of having an “extra-constitutional” view of presidency. “He seems to believe that government works like a business and he is the CEO of the business, and that is not how it works,” he said. A staunch libertarian—Mr Amash co-founded the House Freedom Caucus to represent small-government Tea Partiers on the Hill—he has openly disagreed with Mr Trump on other matters, including the president’s declaration of a national emergency earlier this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Mr Trump enjoying an approval rating among Republicans of 90%, Mr Amash is unlikely to receive the backing of any of his Republican colleagues. Some quickly attacked Mr Amash. “What he wants is attention in this process,” said Kevin McCarthy, the House minority leader. “He’s not a criminal attorney. He’s never met Mueller. He’s never met Barr. And now he’s coming forward with this?” (Mr Amash is an attorney; meeting the special counsel, let alone the attorney-general, is not a precondition for taking a view of Mr Mueller’s conclusions.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump also accused Mr Amash of attention-seeking. He was “never a fan,” he tweeted, of the “total lightweight who opposes me and some of our great Republican ideas and policies just for the sake of getting his name out there through controversy”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So it was left to the Democrats (aside from a few Never Trump Republican exiles in the media) to hail Mr Amash’s courage. His move comes as a boost to those in the opposition party who are pushing, against the wishes of their party leaders, to begin impeachment proceedings against Mr Trump. Nancy Pelosi, the House majority leader, has said such a process would have to be bipartisan. Rashida Tlaib, a Democratic congresswoman from Michigan, who has formally submitted her own impeachment resolution, invited Mr Amash to join her. “You are putting country first and that is to be commended,” she tweeted. “We both took an oath to uphold the US constitution”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Absent further support from other Republicans, Mr Amash’s move is unlikely to make impeachment proceedings any more likely. Mrs Pelosi continues to believe that trying and failing to impeach Mr Trump would inflict grave electoral damage on her party in 2020. Adam Schiff, the Democratic chair of the House intelligence committee, said at the weekend that “what may be pushing us in the direction of impeachment…has less to do with Justin Amash and more to do with the fact that the administration is engaging in a maximum obstructionism campaign against Congress”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The likeliest consequence for Mr Amash is that he will lose his seat, in Michigan’s third congressional district. On May 19th, Jim Lower, a state representative, said he would challenge Mr Amash in next year’s Republican primary. “I am a Pro-Trump, Pro-Life, Pro-Jobs, Pro-2nd Amendment, Pro-Family Values Republican,” he said. “Justin Amash’s tweets yesterday calling for President Trump’s impeachment show how out of touch he is with the truth and how out of touch he is with people he represents.” He told the &lt;em&gt;Washington Post&lt;/em&gt; he had not read the Mueller report in as much detail as Mr Amash had done.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The budding primary contest could emerge as test of whether Republicans critical of Mr Trump can still win elections. Alternatively, Mr Amash may have his eye on a bigger prize. He is reportedly considering a 2020 run against Mr Trump as a Libertarian candidate. He might not need to do particularly well to create a problem for the president. As a hardline conservative, he could take the votes of disaffected Republicans. Even if he only performed well at home in Michigan, a crucial swing state that Mr Trump won by a whisker in 2016, it could undo Mr Trump’s chances of re-election.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; “I never stop thinking about these sorts of things,” Mr Amash told CNN earlier this year. “It&amp;#x27;s not because I have any immediate plans or anything like that, but I never stop thinking about those things because there is a big problem with the current two-party system we have, and someone has to shake it up.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 11:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Brooks Koepka saves his best work for a major yet again]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/05/20/brooks-koepka-saves-his-best-work-for-a-major-yet-again]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BLP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-20T21:00:01Z&quot;&gt;May 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“SOMETIMES THE majors are the easiest ones to win,” Brooks Koepka said last week. “Half the people shoot themselves out of it, and mentally I know I can beat most of them.” It sounded like a preposterous boast. The four major championships in men’s golf feature virtually all of the world’s best players, making them vastly harder to win than weekly tour events against comparatively soft competition are. But five days later, Mr Koepka proved himself right. After prevailing in the PGA Championship on May 19th, he has now won four of the past eight majors he has entered (and four of 22 overall). In contrast, outside of the majors, he has amassed just five other titles through 122 tournaments on top-tier tours.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Koepka’s victory appeared preordained for most of the event. Its organisers ensured that he would be in the spotlight from his very first shot by putting him in a playing group with Tiger Woods, still the sport’s biggest star, and Francesco Molinari. Between them, that trio held the non-calendar-year grand slam: Mr Koepka was the reigning U.S. Open and PGA Championship victor, Mr Molinari won Britain’s Open Championship in July and Mr Woods triumphed at the Masters last month. Moreover, each member of the group had suffered at least one close loss to another during those four events.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet despite the résumés of his playing partners, Mr Koepka blew them away—along with everyone else. He shot a course-record 63 in the first round on the notoriously difficult Bethpage Black Course, and followed it up with a sterling 65 in the second. With booming drives that regularly left Mr Woods’s and Mr Molinari’s balls 30 yards in the rearview mirror; pinpoint approach shots that honed in on flagsticks like laser-guided missiles; and putts whose lines never seemed to waver; Mr Koepka seemed to be playing a different game from his rivals. The last time a golfer looked that dominant may have been the heyday of Mr Woods, Mr Koepka’s playing partner, who wound up missing the cut just five weeks after he &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/04/14/tiger-woods-wins-his-fifth-masters-in-a-comeback-for-the-ages&quot;&gt;beat Mr Koepka by one stroke at the Masters&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Koepka would go on to need almost all seven strokes of the lead he had amassed at the tournament’s halfway mark. He completed the third round in a steady, even-par 70, preserving a seven-stroke advantage going into the final day. Upon reaching the back nine on Sunday, however, he came dangerously close to earning a spot on the list of golf’s most &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2016/07/28/spectacular-golfing-collapses&quot;&gt;epic collapses&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A series of errant tee shots—some captured by the fast-gusting wind, some simply mis-hit—resulted in a ghastly run of four consecutive bogeys on the 11th through 14th holes. Meanwhile, Dustin Johnson, the world’s top-ranked player at the start of the tournament, birdied the 15th after playing the front nine in three under par. For a moment, Mr Koepka’s lead had dwindled to a single stroke. At that point, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://eagle.economist.com&quot;&gt;EAGLE&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;i&gt;The Economist&lt;/i&gt;’s golf-forecasting system, gave Mr Johnson a 37% chance of completing a comeback victory—an outcome that had seemed unthinkable just an hour earlier. Had Mr Koepka’s back-nine jitters befallen anyone but a three-time major winner, fans and pundits would surely have called him a choker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Koepka never re-discovered his early-round magic after that point. He gave back another stroke with a bogey on the 17th hole, and flirted with disaster on the 18th by propelling his final tee shot into the gallery. But Mr Johnson could not sustain his momentum, over-shooting the green on the 16th hole and missing a seven-foot putt on the 17th to record back-to-back bogeys of his own. With a Houdini-like recovery to save par on the 18th, Mr Koepka staggered into the clubhouse with a four-over-par 74—and a second consecutive inscription on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.bunkered.co.uk/golf-news/us-pga-the-incredible-story-of-the-wanamaker-trophy&quot;&gt;Wanamaker Trophy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A major conundrum&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;As far as the record books are concerned, a major win is a major win is a major win. Just 19 other players can match Mr Koepka’s four titles on golf’s biggest stages. And at just 29 years of age, he has plenty of time to move further up the list. Moreover, although Mr Koepka’s near-collapse in the final hours of the PGA Championship may taint fans’ memories of his triumph, he deserves credit for his sublime play during the first two rounds, which allowed him to weather the coming storm. Overall, he beat the average score of players making the cut by a healthy 14.5 strokes, a sufficiently large margin to win a major most of the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nonetheless, Mr Koepka’s self-inflicted close call demonstrated the occasionally erratic character that caused both &lt;i&gt;The Economist&lt;/i&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.pinnacle.com/en/betting-articles/Golf/2019-pga-championship-predictions/QK92JN8HRC92GY2Q&quot;&gt;other statistical forecasters&lt;/a&gt; to preach caution on his chances. It would be an exaggeration to describe Mr Koepka as golf’s version of Dr Jekyll and Mr Hyde: he has no shortage of top-five and top-ten finishes outside of major competition. But the gap between his merely-strong work on the weekly grind and his otherworldly performances in majors remains a remarkable anomaly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since Mr Koepka first entered the top 100 of the official world rankings, the average of his 409 round scores outside of major play corresponds to a performance 0.88 strokes above par per round in a typical modern major environment. That is roughly the level one would expect from a player ranked between 20th and 25th in the world. In contrast, his average showing across 77 major rounds (after adjusting for course difficulty) comes to 0.75 strokes &lt;i&gt;below&lt;/i&gt; par per 18 holes—a threshold exceeded in modern times across majors and non-majors alike only by Mr Woods. The difference between those two figures, of 1.63 strokes per round, is the largest of any player with at least 25 rounds played in both majors and non-majors while in the top 100 since 2006.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Could such a large discrepancy really be a mere statistical fluke? It would stand to reason that some players might prepare the same way for every tournament, whereas others might devote extra effort when the biggest prizes are on the line. Moreover, quality of competition is not the only difference between majors and other events. In addition, the organisers of major tournaments typically choose and prepare the courses in order to provide an unusually difficult test. And powerful golfers, exemplified by the chiselled Mr Koepka, may have playing styles that are particularly well-suited to the souped-up challenge that major courses present. “On easier courses,” Henrik Stenson, the winner of the 2016 Open Championship, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.golf.com/news/columns/2019/05/20/brooks-koepka-no-nonsense-superstar-golf-needs&quot;&gt;told &lt;i&gt;Golf&lt;/i&gt; magazine&lt;/a&gt;, “where there is not such a penalty for bad drives and many players have wedges into greens, it is much harder for [Mr Koepka] to separate himself. A really tough setup brings out Brooks’s advantages. He’s so straight off the tee he is going to hit many more fairways than the average player. And he’s so long he’ll have less club into the green so he’ll hit it closer. If he misses the fairway he still has less club and he’s so strong he can muscle the shot onto the green when others can’t.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The ayes have it&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The evidence suggests that Mr Stenson is on to something. To test whether golfers who have performed far better or worse in majors than in other events can be expected to sustain such a discrepancy, I started with a “naïve” version of our EAGLE prediction model. This system forecasts players’ future scores based on their past ones, without taking account of whether those previous results occurred in majors or elsewhere. For every round by every player in every tournament since 2008, I then compared the player’s round score with what EAGLE would have predicted before they teed off, and recorded the difference between the expected and actual outcome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next, for each round by each player, I took the average of these differences for all previous rounds they had played, broken out into major and non-major categories. For example, before the PGA Championship began, Mr Koepka had beaten EAGLE’s forecasts in majors by exactly 100 strokes over 80 previous rounds, an average of 1.25 strokes per major round. He had also exceeded EAGLE’s predictions outside of majors by 95 strokes, nearly as large a margin. However, it took him 506 non-major rounds to amass that 95-stroke gap, resulting in a far lower average of 0.19 strokes per non-major round. The gap between these two averages, of 1.06 strokes per round, represents how much Mr Koepka has elevated his game when under the sport’s brightest spotlight, compared with his work when the stakes are lower.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, I measured whether this differential could be used to improve EAGLE’s predictions in major tournaments. The result was a resounding “yes”. After about 70 rounds’ worth of major play, golfers “carried forward” about a quarter of their historical over- or under-performance in majors to their next major round. With 200 rounds (roughly 15 years) of data, the ratio was 50-50. To make sure this apparent pattern was not driven entirely by Mr Koepka’s extreme split, I excluded him from the dataset and re-ran the analysis. Although the effect was slightly smaller, it remained significant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Relative to all of the other elements in golf forecasting, this is a fairly modest finding. In the case of Mr Koepka, who is the biggest outlier by far, it means that we should expect #MajorKoepka (as we fondly &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://twitter.com/DanRosenheck/status/1129078560499617792&quot;&gt;dubbed him on Twitter&lt;/a&gt;) to perform about a third of a stroke per round better than the mere-mortal version of Mr Koepka who shows up in non-major events. A shift of one-third of a stroke per round is closer to the difference between a major and, say, a mid-ranking captain than it is to the gap between a major and a lowly private. Nonetheless, it is enough to catapult Mr Koepka from sixth in EAGLE’s rankings to second (though not enough to overtake Mr Johnson, who also benefits somewhat from the adjustment). In contrast, Paul Casey, whom we &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/05/15/after-years-as-an-underdog-tiger-woods-is-a-favourite-once-again&quot;&gt;highlighted before the PGA Championship as under-valued by betting markets&lt;/a&gt;, loses 0.15 strokes per round from this correction, dropping him from 12th in EAGLE’s rankings to 18th. For the bulk of his career, Mr Woods has played at the same high level regardless of the stakes, and is thus unaffected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the wake of Mr Woods’s victory at the Masters, we stubbornly insisted that our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/06/our-masters-forecast-is-lukewarm-on-tiger-woods&quot;&gt;bearishness on him&lt;/a&gt; before the tournament was justified, and that we would &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/04/16/tiger-woods-made-our-golf-model-look-silly-have-we-learned-a-lesson&quot;&gt;continue to wager against him going forward&lt;/a&gt; at the prevailing betting-market odds. His poor showing when playing alongside Mr Koepka at the PGA Championship offered a small drop of vindication. This time, however, it appears we were wrong to pooh-pooh Mr Koepka’s penchant for bringing his “A” game when major titles are on the line. Look for him to shoot up our projected leaderboard when he seeks to defend his U.S. Open title at Pebble Beach next month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 07:40:32 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[On Change UK’s inadequacies, political agreements and missing Scots]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/bagehots-notebook/2019/05/20/on-change-uks-inadequacies-political-agreements-and-missing-scots]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_BRP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-20T16:03:00Z&quot;&gt;May 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I WAS much impressed by Heidi Allen’s first speech when she left the Conservative Party to join the Independent Group, now known as the Change UK Party. How could the Conservative high command have ignored such a prodigious talent? But I’m afraid I was very much underwhelmed by her performance at a Beer and Brexit debate on May 14th, organised by King’s College, London. Ms Allen is now the acting leader of Change UK. But even as her job title has grown she seems to have shrunk as a politician. Gently interrogated by Anand Menon, the reigning Brexit guru at King’s, she produced a succession of bland and vague answers that suggested that she’s not capable of either rigorous thought or vigorous organisation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Allen regurgitated a splattering of good-government platitudes about how Britain needs to be much better at harnessing expertise. Politics should be run more like a business. Parties should take an inventory of the skills and talents of each new intake of MPs. Parliament is run like an old-fashioned gentleman’s club, and so on and so forth. There’s some sense in this—particularly about the skills inventory. But isn’t calling for politics to be run more like a business a bit old hat for a party that presents itself as a change-agent? Donald Trump ran on the promise of using his skills as a businessman to shake up Washington, DC in 2016, and Silvio Berlusconi said the same about Rome in the 1990s. And isn’t the boss of Change UK rather badly placed to call for a more business-like approach to politics? The party has lurched from one disaster to another: failing to establish a brand; faffing about over its name; publicly disagreeing over policies; producing ridiculously slip-shod campaign literature; and, in every way conceivable, allowing itself to be out-performed, out-organised, and out-thought by what is supposed to be the party of out-of-touch bigots, Nigel Farage’s Brexit Party. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Change UK looks as if it will get the Palme d’Or for the most risible projects in recent political history. For a moment it looked as if Tom Watson and the Labour Party’s Social Democratic wing might stage a mass walk-out and join the Tiggers (as Change UK members were known when their nascent party was still the Independent Group). But Mr Watson chose to stay and fight and the Tiggers had to rely on the force of their personalities rather than on numbers. The trouble is that this is far from enough: the founders of the Social Democratic Party back in 1983 were big beasts who were capable of making the weather. Change UK is a collection of small beasts who will probably be swept away by the storm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TO EDINBURGH—that wonderful study in stone as poetry—to debate the future of capitalism with Stewart Wood, a Labour peer, courtesy of Reform Scotland, a think-tank. To be honest we struggled to find big things to disagree about. There is broad agreement across the political spectrum about the toughest problems facing Britain: the over-centralisation of economic and political power in London; the long-tail of low-skilled workers who are trapped in low-paying jobs; the cult of short-termism; financial engineering; the lack of respect for the manufacturing sector. And yet the British political class is instead focusing on policies that are as divisive as possible: on the right, leaving the European Union, and on the left, massive state intervention in the “commanding heights” of the economy such as re-nationalising the utilities and taking 10% of the country’s biggest public companies. While we squabble over what is contentious, we fail to address what we agree about.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SCOTLAND AND England are arguably further apart politically than they have been at any time in the history of the Union, and not just because the Scots voted to remain in the EU and the English to leave. The Labour Party once specialised in projecting Scottish politicians to the heights of power in Westminster—Tony Blair, Gordon Brown, John Smith, Ramsay MacDonald, Keir Hardie. The Liberal Party and its various off-shoots had deep roots in Scotland as well as the English provinces (think of Jo Grimond and Charles Kennedy). The aristocratic wing of the Tory Party also boasted deep Scottish connections: Alec Douglas-Home had an estate up there and even David Cameron could boast a Scottish name and Scottish shooting buddies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;British politics is now as English as it has ever been. The only Scotsman in front line politics is Michael Gove, the adopted son of a Scottish fishmonger, and a man capable of reverting from Oxbridge English to Aberdeen Scottish if need be. The people occupying the great offices of state (the prime minister, the chancellor, the foreign secretary) all seem to be in a competition to see who can be the most southern. The Scottish Labour Party has all but died from complacency and mediocrity and the national party has been captured by a clique of London MPs: Jeremy Corbyn and Emily Thornberry both have seats next door to each other in Islington and Dianne Abbott and John McDonnell both represent London seats. The Scottish Raj that once ruled over its southern neighbour is scattered to the winds: Gordon Brown and Alistair Darling have returned to Scotland and Tony Blair is in a private jet somewhere in the mid-Atlantic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Political life in Scotland is dominated by a Scottish National Party (SNP) that has no real relevance down south (though it has 35 MPs, and Ian Blackford, their leader, manfully makes the same speech at Prime Minister’s Questions every week about how Britain is taking Scotland out of the EU against its will). The liveliest issue up north at the moment is the upcoming trial of Alex Salmond on charges including sexual assault and attempted rape. (He says he is innocent of any criminality.) This is dividing the SNP—and Scottish politics in general—between admirers of Nicola Sturgeon, who began her political life as Mr Salmond’s protégé but has since turned against him, and Salmond loyalists who think he is being unjustly accused. The squabble could weaken the SNP’s (increasingly death-like) grip on Scottish politics and prepare the way for significant advances for either the Tories or the Labour Party, with profound implications for the next general election down south.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other great issue is Ruth Davidson’s re-emergence on the scene after several months on maternity leave. If things had gone well with Brexit, Ms Davidson would be re-appearing just as the Tory Party was putting Brexit behind it and turning to the question of where Britain needs to go now it is leaving the EU (Ms Davidson is a remainer who has reconciled herself to delivering the will of the people). But the Brexit problem is even more fraught today than it was when she went on leave—and the Tory brand is far more toxic. Ms Davidson resisted enormous pressure from within her party to loosen its connection with the Conservative Party south of the border. With Brexit lurching from disaster to disaster and the Tory Party increasingly associated with the likes of Jacob Rees-Mogg, she may rue her decision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 04:40:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Does carving up conglomerates create shareholder value?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/20/does-carving-up-conglomerates-create-shareholder-value]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_woc029.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-20T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Corporate fashions come and go, and this season’s is industrial break-ups. In America and Europe, once-sprawling conglomerates are being carved up into focused companies that investors hope will fare better on their own. Those banking on quick returns have mostly been disappointed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conglomerates thrived in the 1970s, and made a comeback after the merger frenzy of the late 1990s. They are beloved of megalomaniac bosses keen to prove they can run empires peddling anything from train carriages to &lt;small&gt;CT&lt;/small&gt; scanners (as Siemens currently does, albeit not, as it announced last week, for much longer). But the argument that diversity lets a firm’s healthy arms prop up temporarily frail ones is, once again, losing ground in the rich world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Private-equity funds have pots of money to buy unwanted divisions. Listing companies—or spinning them off to existing investors—is easier than it once was. Plenty of activist hedge funds are pressing firms to restructure, hoping to cash in when the sum of conglomerates’ parts fetches more than the whole (studies show this can be true in the long run).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gauging the impact of a break-up announcement is hard. Investors price in its likelihood before a company owns up to “exploring strategic options”. Splits often follow bad results that enfeeble the management, which may in turn mean worse news down the line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our chart, which takes the first detailed news reports of a spin-off as its starting-point, shows that of recent break-ups, only Honeywell, which filed listing documents for its car-parts and home-security arms last August, has subsequently outperformed the broader market. United Technologies has kept pace with it. General Electric, Thyssenkrupp, DowDuPont and &lt;small&gt;ABB&lt;/small&gt; have not. If their share prices fall any more, they will be ripe for a takeover.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 04:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Holding out on Huawei]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/20/holding-out-on-huawei]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_wbp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-20T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON MAY 20TH it became clear that some of the world’s most prominent technology companies—Google, Intel and Qualcomm—had stopped selling software, hardware and licences for intellectual property to Huawei, a Chinese manufacturer of phones and networking gear. This followed an announcement by the American government on May 15th that it was banning the export of American technology to Huawei unless companies got a special licence from the Department of Commerce.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Huawei, which sources a sixth of all its components from American companies, appears vulnerable. It has stockpiled enough components to keep its business running for several months. But reconfiguring its supply chain so that it is no longer reliant on American firms, which would be the only way to truly insulate itself from the trade wars, will be hard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google has stopped supplying Huawei with the proprietary components of Android, the search firm’s mobile operating system. That loss will have no effect on Huawei’s biggest market, mainland China, where it only uses the free, open-source components of Android. But outside China, where the firm bundles Google’s own services like Gmail and search with the tens of millions of phones it sells every year, the loss of Google’s software is crippling (and is a boon for Samsung, the South Korean market leader). Huawei is working on its own alternative, codenamed HongMeng OS according to state media, but is unlikely to be able to deploy it without significant disruption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Huawei’s hardware is threatened, too. Intel, Qualcomm and a host of other companies have stopped supplying the parts and designs that Huawei needs to build its phones and network gear. Huawei’s sales grew by 20% in 2018 to $107bn. If the supply tap is not turned back on, 2019 will be rather less rosy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Farther removed from American jurisdiction, Huawei’s Asian suppliers have been more circumspect. TSMC, the Taiwanese company which makes the semiconductors on which Huawei’s entire business (and that of most other technology companies) depends, is still supplying the firm, but says that it is examining its export-control systems to make sure that it is in compliance with American law. Other Taiwanese companies are following its lead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Huawei’s Asian suppliers must obey American law on export control, in theory at least, because it prohibits not just the direct sale of American technology by American firms, but also its transmission through non-American companies like TSMC. In reality, America has few levers to force companies like TSMC to comply with its laws. Losing TSMC as a supplier would be the final blow for Huawei. Currently, that is unlikely, but if conflict escalates TSMC could become the next battleground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Huawei says it has been preparing for an American assault on its supply chains for years. In April, Peter Zhou, a company executive, suggested that the firm had anticipated the rising tension between China and America and prepared accordingly. The firm says it has been remaking its supply chains and so will not crack under pressure as its domestic competitor, ZTE, did last year when faced with a similar ban (one ultimately lifted by President Donald Trump in response to a personal plea from the Chinese president, Xi Jinping).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the actual state of Huawei’s preparations may be better gauged by comments made by Ren Zhengfei, the boss, on May 18th. He claimed that the company would be “fine” without its American suppliers, yet conceded that he expected revenues to grow 20% more slowly as a result of the ban. If America retains the ban as Huawei’s stockpiles dwindled, the company—and indeed China’s internet ecosystem—would be more seriously damaged. More probably, America will use its ability to withhold components from Huawei as a bargaining chip in a future trade deal with China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further such action could also harm America and its allies. Beijing would probably retaliate, perhaps disrupting the supply chains of American companies within China. And although American export law is a powerful weapon in this trade war, its impact will diminish with time. Every time America lashes out at a Chinese company it hastens Chinese efforts to find suppliers elsewhere. Huawei’s semiconductor division, HiSilicon, has been designing its own versions of the chips it buys from American companies. The firm’s HongMeng OS is waiting in the wings. Next time America wants to attack the supply chain, it may find that there are fewer convenient targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 04:40:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why some American states are locking up toddlers]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/20/why-some-american-states-are-locking-up-toddlers]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_usp504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-20T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;LIKE MANY people in prison, Ada Lynn listens more than she speaks, spends most of her time with people she knows best, and is deeply wary of strangers: in fact, when she sees one she tends to burst into uncontrollable sobs, because, unlike most people in prison, she is ten months old. Natalie Myers, Ada Lynn’s 23-year-old mother, was pregnant when she was imprisoned for vehicular homicide. Washington is one of just a few states that offer residential nurseries for women who give birth while imprisoned. Ms Myers loves the programme. “This is the best thing that has ever happened to me,” she says. “I always thought I’d never be a functional person because I dug myself into such a hole. But here I’m figuring out who I am with my daughter.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not everyone shares her optimism. Carolyn Sufrin, a professor at Johns Hopkins who researches pregnancy in prisons, says that “as much as [nurseries] decorate the walls with colourful decorations, it’s still prison…What are the unspoken and unmeasurable consequences of that early environment?” Others worry that they are unconstitutional, and would not survive a court challenge brought on behalf of a baby who was imprisoned without due process. Boosters argue that they cut recidivism rates, and are the best of an array of bad options for incarcerated pregnant women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Bureau of Justice statistics, in 2017, 225,000 women were behind bars in America, with 99,000 of them in state prisons (in American parlance, jails house people awaiting trial or serving short sentences; prisons house people convicted of more serious crimes). That is around one-tenth the total number of people incarcerated, but it is nearly ten times as many women as were locked up in 1978—a rate of increase nearly twice as great as took place in the male incarceration population over the same time. And as America’s total prison population has fallen since 2008, in most states the female prison population has either continued to grow or declined more slowly than the male population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr Sufrin’s study, as of December 2016, 3.8% of newly admitted women prisoners were pregnant. A 1976 Supreme Court ruling found that the Eighth and Fourteenth amendments require states to provide health care to prisoners, but what that means in practice varies wildly, particularly for pregnant women. They are sometimes shackled while giving birth—a practice that often continues, according to Amy Fettig, a lawyer with the American Civil Liberties Union, even after states outlaw it. In most states, babies born to imprisoned mothers end up with relatives or in foster care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New York opened the first prison nursery in 1901; today 11 states have them. Criteria for eligibility vary, but generally women convicted of child-related or violent crimes are ineligible, as are women with behavioural or mental-health problems, or with a record of disciplinary problems in prison. In Washington, women accepted into the programme must be pregnant at the time of their imprisonment, and have less than 30 months to serve from the time of delivery; mothers and children are released together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Studies have found that prison nurseries are associated with lower recidivism rates, compared with women forced to give up their children, and with fewer behavioural and disciplinary problems than women in the general population. But whether that is because of the programmes themselves, or because non-violent inmates without serious behavioural, disciplinary or mental-health problems able to meet the strictures that prison-nursery programmes impose were headed down the right path anyway is unclear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conclusions about their effects on children are harder to come by. But, wonders Dr Sufrin, “if women meet these conditions, what are they doing in prison?...I think it’s essential to find ways to maintain family bonds. I just think we need to do it in ways that don’t involve barbed wire.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 04:40:11 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Rocketman” is a suitably ostentatious biopic of Elton John]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/20/rocketman-is-a-suitably-ostentatious-biopic-of-elton-john]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_BKP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-20T15:54:23Z&quot;&gt;May 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY”, a biopic of Freddie Mercury and Queen, was almost as big a money-spinner as the band itself. A notoriously troubled production, the film nevertheless went on to gross nearly $700m worldwide, making it the sixth-most-lucrative film of 2018. It was nominated for four Oscars, including Best Picture and Best Actor, an award which was won by its star, Rami Malek. The producers of “Rocketman” will be hoping that this bodes well for their film, another non-fiction drama about a theatrical and hedonistic British pop sensation, this time Elton John. Indeed, after the original director of “Bohemian Rhapsody” left the project, Dexter Fletcher was called in to supervise the last few weeks of shooting—and “Rocketman” is directed by Mr Fletcher, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite all the similarities, though, it would be astonishing if “Rocketman” sold anywhere near as many tickets as “Bohemian Rhapsody” did. That is not to suggest that it is a worse film. On the contrary, the main reason why this buoyant production may underperform is that it is bolder and less conventional, a full-blown musical rather than a biopic with songs. True, it ticks off all the usual scenes in the showbiz rise-and-fall genre—the meetings with key collaborators, the composing and recording of classic singles, triumphal concerts—but it does so with an impressionistic aplomb that “Bohemian Rhapsody” lacked. It discards realism in favour of razzmatazz, and slots in Mr John’s biggest hits as and when they suit the emotional arc of the story, whether the chronology is accurate or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Rocketman” makes its intentions clear in its opening moments when the middle-aged Elton (Taron Egerton) struts down a corridor dressed as a bright orange devil, complete with bejewelled horns and feathery wings. He looks both heroic and utterly ridiculous, which is more or less how the film portrays him throughout. He sits down in a group therapy session and lists the many, many substances to which he is addicted. A counsellor asks him about his childhood, and we’re off: with terrific confidence and flair, Mr Fletcher stages a series of fantasy-tinged flashbacks which recount how a dumpy boy from suburban Middlesex named Reginald Dwight reinvented himself as a sequinned extrovert, how he became one of the world’s top-selling musicians, how he feared that being gay would result in a life of loneliness and how he sank into what the tabloids would call a “drugs hell”. (The film’s embrace of sex, drugs and swearing, incidentally, make “Bohemian Rhapsody” seem even more coy than it did already.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Fletcher is the ideal man for the job. As well as helping out on “Bohemian Rhapsody”, he has directed one previous jukebox musical, “Sunshine on Leith”, and one comic biopic starring Mr Egerton, “Eddie The Eagle”. The film’s screenwriter, Lee Hall, is the perfect choice, too: he is best known for his “Billy Elliot” screenplay, about a young ballet dancer from the north of England, and for the subsequent stage musical he co-wrote with Mr John himself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their decision to turn Mr John’s life into what is effectively a stage musical is what makes “Rocketman” such ebullient fun, but also what stops it being as moving or as credible as it might have been. Jamie Bell (who starred in “Billy Elliot”) is restrained and soulful as Bernie Taupin, Mr Elton’s long-time lyricist and close friend, but otherwise the film is as bombastic as Mr John’s songs and as garish as his pantomime costumes. Mr Egerton, who sings all the songs himself, brings the requisite gusto, humour and vulnerability, but he isn’t exactly subtle; John Reid (Richard Madden), Mr John’s manager and lover, is evil incarnate; Mr Dwight, his domineering father (Steven Macintosh), is a parody of English reserve. And although Mr John’s bad behaviour is hardly ignored, “Rocketman”, on which the man himself is an executive producer and his husband, David Furnish, is the producer, insists that its insecure hero is more sinned against than sinning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, these objections are probably beside the point. Nobody goes to see a musical about Elton John because they want nuance. They go because they want fireworks, and the film sets off plenty of those. If it had come out two years ago, it is “Rocketman” that would have exploded, and “Bohemian Rhapsody” would have fizzled out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Rocketman” is released in Britain on May 22nd and in America on May 31st&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 23:40:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why are Indians falling out of love with gold?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/05/20/why-are-indians-falling-out-of-love-with-gold]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_BLP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-20T14:08:31Z&quot;&gt;May 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE HINDU festival of Akshaya Tritiya, celebrated on May 7th this year, is considered an auspicious time to buy gold. Queues outside Indian jewellery stores become so long that makeshift tents are set up to accommodate the rush. Cashiers hand-count wads of banknotes in conditions as noisy as those in a busy fast-food restaurant. The salesmen cater to a remarkable level of demand. As a group, Indians buy more gold than anyone apart from the Chinese (who have occupied the top spot since 2014). Indian households are reckoned to have a stockpile of gold worth $800bn. Yet the Indian market is not as healthy as it was. Purchases of the metal have fallen by around a fifth since their peak in 2010. Why is gold losing its sheen?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start with changing tastes and preferences. Around a third of Indians are 18 to 35 years old. They often prefer to spend their money on electronic gadgets, purchased in monthly instalments on zero interest rates, rather than jewellery. In 2017 consumer electronics toppled gold as the second-biggest contributor to India’s national import bill, behind oil. Moreover, the tastes of those who buy gold appear to be changing. Heavy jewellery has given way to lightweight designs, sometimes with lesser caratage. “Gold is no longer a sign of wealth but of fashion,” admits one customer at a jewellery store in Mumbai. As if to confirm this, in February the price of gold rose almost to a five-year high, dampening its allure as a store of value. This discourages those customers who would buy 22-carat bling, the purest gold suitable for jewellery, with a view to melting and reselling it at a later stage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold is no longer the go-to investment option for those whose money lies outside the formal financial system. In 2014 a state-sponsored programme opened millions of bank accounts. Mutual funds have returned 12.5% annually in the last decade. The Sensex stockmarket index has gained around 60% in the past five years. In that period, the price of gold rose, in rupee terms, by just 7% from a high base, a far cry from the 12 years until 2012 when it rose by over 500%. Its value as a hedge against inflation, at 3%, has diminished too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India’s government has long tried to wean citizens off gold, almost all of which the country imports. This burns a hole in the current-account deficit, and a depreciating rupee further weakens the balance of payments. Since 2012 officials have raised quotas on gold imports five-fold to 10%, but are wary of increasing the rate higher, lest they push the trade underground. Last year authorities seized 66kg of gold bars, worth $3m, hidden in four cars. Bootleggers will continue to seek creative ways to beat the system. But if consumers are reconsidering their love affair with gold, the government will not try to rekindle the passion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 22:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The management wisdom of Bill Campbell]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/20/the-management-wisdom-of-bill-campbell]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_wbp507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-20T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS YOGI BERRA, a legendary Yankees baseball player, coach and master of malapropisms, once said, “Baseball is 90% mental and the other half is physical.” Managers might need a better grasp of maths than Berra. But they require a similar focus on instilling the right mentality, not just in themselves but in their team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That view is held particularly strongly by three Google executives—Eric Schmidt (a former director of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;), Jonathan Rosenberg and Alan Eagle—who have written a book in praise of their mentor, Bill Campbell. His influence on Silicon Valley was so profound that they have called the book “Trillion Dollar Coach”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most outsiders will not have heard of Campbell, who began his career as a college coach of American football. Later, he worked at Apple, heading the marketing campaign for the original Macintosh, and then became chief executive at Intuit, a financial-software company. But his most effective role was in the background, as a board member at Apple (and close friend of Steve Jobs) and as a coach to companies backed by Kleiner Perkins, a venture-capital firm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google was one of Kleiner’s investments and when Mr Schmidt was appointed chief executive of the company in 2001, Kleiner’s John Doerr suggested that he recruit Campbell as his coach. Although Mr Schmidt was initially reluctant to accept the need for coaching, he learned to value Campbell’s advice. In 2004 Campbell helped to persuade the Google boss not to quit when his roles as chairman and chief executive were split.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Campbell acted as an unpaid mentor at Google until his death in 2016. He also coached executives at eBay, Facebook and Twitter, among others. In 2000 he advised the Amazon board not to replace Jeff Bezos as chief executive of the e-commerce company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a coach, Campbell’s role was not to be in charge of particular projects, or to make strategic decisions, but to make other people work better. Although he advised individuals, his focus was on ensuring that teams were able to co-operate properly. His motto was that “your title makes you a manager, your people make you a leader.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While he was happy to dish out praise in group meetings, and was a generous man in his spare time, he was not a soft touch. He simply believed in giving harsh feedback in private, and was usually adept enough to make the recipient grateful for the telling-off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When he talked to people, he gave them his undivided attention; the discussions were never interrupted and he never checked his smartphone. But coaching had to be a two-way process. Some people were temperamentally incapable of responding properly. To be coachable, Campbell believed, managers need to be honest, humble and willing to learn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A sign of his unique personality is that he has not been replaced since he died. Instead Google is attempting to incorporate his principles into the way the company is run. All managers should, in part, be coaches. The idea seems to be gaining popularity. In their book, “It’s the Manager”, Jim Clifton and Jim Harter of Gallup, a polling organisation, include a whole section called “Boss to Coach”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is linked to the importance of employee engagement. Gallup cites research showing that when managers involve employees in setting their own work goals, the latter are four times more likely to report feeling engaged. Managers are responsible for 70% of the variance in how engaged employees were.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The primary job of any manager is to help people be more effective in their job. One benefit should be that workers will stay with the company; the main reason they change jobs, according to what they tell Gallup, is for “career growth opportunities”. Workers should get regular feedback from their managers—daily if possible, surveys show. An annual performance review is of little use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this approach will only work if it comes from the top down. Middle managers tend to emulate their superiors and to respond to incentives; they will coach underlings if this behaviour is reinforced and rewarded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, even the best coaches and managers have to give their employees scope to find their own way, and make their own mistakes. As Yogi Berra put it, “I’m not going to buy my kids an encyclopedia. Let them walk to school like I did.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 21:40:17 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“They’re more legitimate than the government”—the Taliban in Afghanistan]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/20/theyre-more-legitimate-than-the-government-the-taliban-in-afghanistan]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/afghanistan.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-20T11:30:32Z&quot;&gt;May 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AFGHANISTAN&amp;#x27;S GOVERNMENT still struggles for legitimacy after 18 years and almost a trillion dollars spent fighting the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/18/why-afghanistans-government-is-losing-the-war-with-the-taliban&quot;&gt;Taliban&lt;/a&gt;; we ask why. A list of the world’s ultra-rich reveals a disproportionate number of female self-made &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/18/how-china-forged-self-made-female-billionaires&quot;&gt;billionaires&lt;/a&gt; are from China—but the trend isn’t set to continue. And we examine why presidential &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/04/25/why-presidential-libraries-are-controversial&quot;&gt;libraries&lt;/a&gt; are so controversial, and why Barack Obama’s is no exception. Runtime: 22min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/battleforlegitimacy-afghanistanvthetaliban&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 19:40:56 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>