<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[A journalist’s arrest is a worrying sign of impunity in Russia]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/07/a-journalists-arrest-is-a-worrying-sign-of-impunity-in-russia]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_eup507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-07T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE HEADLINES on Ivan Golunov’s articles make it clear that he may have made some enemies. One article pledges to explain “how officials, the security services, and bandits carve up the market for funeral services”. Others allege that the family of a vice-mayor “made billions and bought up mansions and apartments”, or promise to list “who’s making a killing on Moscow’s reconstruction”. As an investigative journalist for independent Russian media outlets, Mr Golunov developed a reputation for thorough shoe-leather reporting and scrupulous work with procurement databases to expose state corruption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the afternoon of June 6th, Moscow police detained Mr Golunov in the city centre while he was walking to meet a source. The police claimed to have found a stash of drugs in his backpack, and released photos of a small drug lab supposedly discovered in his apartment. Mr Golunov has been booked on charges of selling narcotics, carrying a potential 10- to 20-year sentence. He was prevented from contacting anyone for more than 12 hours. After a sympathetic detective tipped off a friend of Mr Golunov’s, a lawyer arrived at last. Mr Golunov alleged that police had planted the drugs and beat him up. The police refused to let medical personnel document his wounds, though they deny any misbehaviour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Golunov’s editors at Meduza, an independent news site, believe his journalism is the reason for his arrest. “We know that Ivan has received threats in recent months, and we think we know from whom,” they wrote. Colleagues and friends describe Mr Golunov as a virtual teetotaller who obeyed the law scrupulously, to avoid giving the authorities excuses to harass him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“In the Russian reality, an investigative journalist even crosses the street with particular care: only on a green light, so there will be nothing to pin on him,” said Svetlana Reiter, a fellow investigative journalist. Meduza says that the handwriting on notes in police photographs does not appear to match Mr Golunov’s. Acquaintances told that site that they recognise only one of the photographs as his apartment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brazenness of the charges is not a glitch. Instead, it highlights the increasing impunity of the Russian security services. Police are known for planting drugs to meet arrest quotas. Until now such tactics have been used against political opponents only in Chechnya, where Oyub Titiev, a human-rights activist, was sentenced in March to four years in prison on drug charges that observers called fabricated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like Mr Titiev’s, Mr Golunov’s arrest is meant to send a message. “It’s a signal that they can do the same or worse with any of us,” said Pavel Kanygin of Novaya Gazeta, an independent newspaper. Journalists and supporters gathered on June 7th near the police headquarters for a series of one-man pickets, a tactic activists use to avoid a ban on protesting in groups without permission. Police detained at least seven of them—one by one—including Mr Kanygin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As police were hauling the protesters into police vans, President Vladimir Putin was striding on stage at the St Petersburg International Economic Forum, Russia’s yearly gathering of economic bigwigs. The atmosphere at this year’s forum has been marred by the arrest in February of Michael Calvey, a prominent American investor, on dubious fraud charges. Mr Putin touted Russia’s business climate and endorsed the investigation into Mr Calvey. “Just, legal decisions will be made,” Mr Putin insisted. The arrest of Mr Golunov suggests that in today’s Russia, lawlessness often masquerades as justice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 04:40:42 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to increase empathy and unite society]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/07/how-to-increase-empathy-and-unite-society]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_OPP509.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-07T17:39:53Z&quot;&gt;Jun 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IF THERE is one thing that people on both the left and right can agree, it is that expressions of our political and social differences have become markedly less cordial—and that this makes it harder to find common ground and solve common problems. The good news is that science is on the case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Empathy is not like a person’s adult height, something unalterable. Instead, it is a characteristic that can be actively encouraged or discouraged. This is the central message of a new book, “The War for Kindness: Building Empathy in a Fractured World”, by Jamil Zaki, the director of the Social Neuroscience Lab at Stanford University. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ability to structure our workplaces, schools, public spaces—and even media—to increase interactions with people from other walks of life may boost the respect that people bestow on others. This, in turn, may go some way towards helping societies to overcome political polarisation, racism, anti-immigrant anger and cultural divisions. Although Red Staters and Blue Staters, or Brexiteers and Remainers, may not lock arms—any more than the lion will lie down with the lamb—at least they will be able to talk to each other without their faces turning purple with rage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s Open Future initiative asked Mr Zaki several questions about what empathy is and how to foster it. Following that is an excerpt from his book, on the importance of contact with others to improve relations. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* * *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp502.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; What is empathy and how can we measure it? Are people less empathetic today than in the past?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jamil Zaki:&lt;/strong&gt; Empathy is our ability to share and understand one another’s feelings—a psychological “superglue” that connects people and undergirds co-operation and kindness. Psychologists and neuroscientists measure empathy in numerous ways: including asking people how much they care about others, measuring how much they mimic others’ facial expressions or flinch when someone else is in pain, testing how accurately they decode others’ experiences, and examining overlap in brain activity when people experience pleasure versus seeing others happy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most common measure of empathy, a questionnaire, has been completed by hundreds of thousands of people since the late 1970s. About ten years ago, psychologists examined these data over time and found a steep drop in empathy, especially in the 21st century. Strikingly, the average American in 2009 scored as less empathic than 75% of people in 1979. We do not know the causes of this decline, though the rise of online technology and increasing polarisation seem relevant. Whatever the source, this drop in empathy should concern all of us. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; How can we harness the latest findings in neuropsychology to increase empathy?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Zaki:&lt;/strong&gt; The first step is to understand that we can increase our empathy. My least favorite phrase in neuroscience is “hard-wired,” the idea that because something resides in the brain, it is fixed and immutable. People often have that notion about empathy—that each of us has a “level” of care built in to us, which, like our adult height, will never change. But our brains are plastic, and change in response to experiences, habits and practices. The same goes for empathy. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For instance, in a landmark study published two years ago, neuroscientists trained people in “loving kindness” meditation, a contemplative practice focusing on building people’s care for others. After several months of this practice, people reported greater empathy, understood others’ feelings more precisely and acted more generously to strangers. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But even more strikingly, parts of their brain associated with empathy grew in volume, underscoring not only how we can increase empathy, but that we can. In fact, my colleagues and I have found that even understanding that empathy is under our control empowers people to work harder at it, especially with people who look or think differently than themselves. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; Building on that, populism, anti-immigration and anti-“other” is on the rise—how can we realistically redesign our community interactions, workplaces, schools, media, etc, to apply neuroscience and psychology to defeat this?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Zaki:&lt;/strong&gt; One of our most powerful psychological instincts is to divide people into categories; for every “us” there is a “them.” This turns pernicious when mixed with competition, conflict and fear. Under these circumstances, empathy evaporates or even reverses into schadenfreude, or enjoyment of the other side’s suffering. The wreckage of America’s political climate, mixed with social media and online bullying, can seem like a schadenfreude buffet. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Counteracting these trends means putting people in the position to replace “us and them” with “you and I”, as well as the incentives to see outsiders as people, rather than mere symbols of their group. One reliable way to do this is to bring people from different groups together under egalitarian circumstances and with shared goals. Another way is to encourage people to understand how empathy can be useful to them. For instance, my colleague Robb Willer has found that when people empathise with individuals on the other end of the political spectrum, they can actually argue more persuasively for their own position.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; Using your methods, won’t empathy simply develop in those who are prone to be empathetic anyway—leaving the most vile people unaffected and the world unimproved: a snowflake of kindness amid a blizzard of misanthropy? Or am I being too cynical?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Zaki:&lt;/strong&gt; I think cynicism is understandable in this cultural moment. I see it all around me, which is part of why I wrote the book. But despite appearances, even “vile” people have the capacity to become more caring under the right circumstances. In the book I tell the story of Tony McAleer, a neo Nazi whose early life was an embodiment of hatred, anger and fear. If anyone would be lost to empathy, it would be him. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And yet after meeting a Jewish man who refused to hate him back (again, moving from “us and them” to “you and I”), he reformed. Tony and his colleagues now run the group Life After Hate, which extracts others from the dark places they once inhabited. There are ample data points demonstrating that people with low empathy, even psychopaths, can turn on their care when properly motivated to do so. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; What is the most important finding from the science of empathy that people don’t know, that if they did know, the world would be a better place? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Zaki:&lt;/strong&gt; The first insight people should take with them is that we can grow our empathy if we want. Our emotions are not animalistic impulses that are out of our control. We can guide them, empathising with purpose—in ways that accord with our values. A second insight is that empathy is helpful, not just to the people around us, but to ourselves as well. It is easy to think of empathy as a squishy soft-skill in a hard world, which allows us to be nice, but also leaves us open to be trampled or left behind. But in many ways, empathic individuals finish first: experiencing greater happiness, less stress and greater professional success. Poetically, one of the best ways we can help ourselves starts with caring for each other. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* * *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190608_opp503.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hatred versus contact&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excerpted from “The War for Kindness: Building Empathy in a Fractured World” by Jamil Zaki (Crown, 2019)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 1943, a race riot seized Detroit. World War II had transformed the city into a weapons factory, and people poured in from around the country as manufacturing boomed. Housing became scarce. Black workers were excluded from housing projects and often paid triple the rent whites did. When the city earmarked a new project for black tenants only, whites burned crosses outside it. As summer arrived, racial tension boiled over. On June 20, blacks heard that a white mob had thrown a woman and her child off the Belle Isle Bridge; whites heard that blacks had raped and killed a woman on the same bridge. Neither event had actually occurred, but the imaginary mobs spawned real ones. They clashed, and in the next thirty-six hours, thirty-four people died, hundreds were injured, and thousands were arrested. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was a national disgrace and a low point for American race relations. But there was a glimmer of hope: whites and blacks who had worked or studied with members of the other race were far less likely to join in the riots, and more likely to engage in peaceful behaviors, such as sheltering other-race individuals from violence. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The psychologist Gordon Allport noticed this, and saw a trend: The better people knew outsiders, the less they hated them. This was true elsewhere as well. Seventy-five percent of residents in all-white housing projects said they would dislike living alongside blacks, but only 25 percent of white residents in mixed projects actually disliked having black neighbors. Sixty-two percent of soldiers in all-white platoons opposed integrating the armed forces; among whites who had been in a mixed platoon, that number was 7 percent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his magnum opus, The Nature of Prejudice, Allport reasoned that bigotry often boils down to a lack of acquaintance. Its antidote was just as simple: Bring people together, and they’ll awaken to their common humanity. A similar thought led Mark Twain to quip, “Travel is fatal to prejudice, bigotry, and narrow-mindedness, and many of our people need it sorely on these accounts.” In psychology, this idea came to be known as “contact theory,” and it caught fire. Allport’s book, published in 1954, became a bestseller; he delighted in spotting it at airports and malls alongside beach novels. Thanks to him, optimists everywhere came to believe that hatred was a misunderstanding and that contact could fix it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Allport stressed that contact would not always work. In some cases it could make things worse—for instance, whites who merely saw more blacks, but didn’t get to know them, might perceive them as a threat. Time has proven Allport right. The visibility of immigrants in the United Kingdom fueled a nationalist wave that crested with Brexit. In Canada, Tony used the presence of immigrants to whip up white aggression. Even moderate people can be driven toward prejudice by the wrong type of contact. In a recent study, the political scientist Ryan Enos planted Latino passengers on a Boston commuter train at the same time each morning for ten days. White commuters who had been on a train with Latinos grew less tolerant of immigration than they had been before, or than passengers who took the very next train.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even when contact doesn’t hurt, it might not help. “Goodwill contact without concrete goals accomplishes nothing,” Allport wrote. He laid out a recipe for how to make it useful: Bring groups together and give them equal status, even if one group has more power the rest of the time. Focus on their mutual goals. Make it personal; let people learn about each other’s idiosyncrasies. And support cooperation between groups through the institutions around them. Fulfill these tenets, Allport claimed, and contact could do wonders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The theory might sound naïve—less rigorous science than Haight-Ashbury handholding. But it’s one of the most well-studied concepts in psychology. In a recent analysis of more than a quarter of a million people, the pattern was clear: The more time someone spends with outsiders, the less prejudice they express. Contact warms sentiments toward many types of outsiders. Imagine two straight, young, able white people born in the United States. Evidence suggests that the one who gets to know a diverse group will exhibit less bias toward black and Hispanic people, immigrants from Asia, Mexico, and Central America, elderly and disabled people, and the LGBTQ community than their more sheltered counterpart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact can work even when people don’t seek it out. White college freshmen randomly assigned to black roommates are less prejudiced by spring than students with same-race roommates. It doesn’t take a school year to help people warm up to new groups, either. In one recent study, trans- and cisgender canvassers went door-to-door in Florida to discuss transgender rights. After meaningful conversations with trans canvassers, residents’ transphobia dropped substantially, and they remained more tolerant three months later &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The punchline is simple: Hatred of outsiders is ancient but not inevitable. When people work, live, or play alongside each other, divisions between them melt. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To understand why, remember that empathy is a choice, and conflict gives people great reasons to avoid it. When groups compete for scarce resources, they must circle the wagons and scrap for their side. [...] Tribalism becomes natural and—from evolution’s perspective—wise. A linebacker who feels the pain of a running back would have a hard time doing his job; a soldier would find hers impossible. As a result, people in conflict don’t merely misplace their care; they actively throw it away. In one series of studies, conservative Israelis reported that they would prefer not to empathize with Palestinians. This preference, in turn, predicted their actual lack of empathy, for instance when they read about a Palestinian child with cerebral palsy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if callousness is a smart choice during war, it’s a terrible way to achieve peace. Contact remedies this by giving people reasons to care about outsiders. We crave connection and will work to keep social bonds strong. When an outsider joins the ranks of our friends or colleagues, empathizing with them aligns with that goal. The benefits compound: Empathy for one outsider can lead to caring for their entire group. Contact also makes avoiding empathy harder. The sorrow and hope of a neighbor, friend, or colleague are often impossible to block out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contact can build empathy even in the toughest settings. After sectarian violence in Northern Ireland, Catholics and Protestants dehumanized each other, but they did so less if they had friends on the other side of the conflict. White Americans who work or live with blacks or Muslims express higher empathy when members of these groups are pro led by law enforcement. Empathy, in turn, promotes solidarity. After the conflict in Ireland, people who felt empathy toward outsiders were more willing to forgive them; in the United States, white Americans who empathized with minority individuals mistreated by police were more likely to join Black Lives Matter protests. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;______________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;From the book “The War for Kindness: Building Empathy in a Fractured World” by Jamil Zaki. Copyright © 2019 by Jamil Zaki. Published by Crown, an imprint of Random House, a division of Penguin Random House. All rights reserved.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 03:41:11 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Climate change will be a big issue in the Democratic contest]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/07/climate-change-will-be-a-big-issue-in-the-democratic-contest]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_USP001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-07T17:15:47Z&quot;&gt;Jun 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ONE OF Elizabeth Warren’s most formative political tangles, which prompted her transition from law professor at Harvard to senator from Massachusetts, occurred in 2005 over a bankruptcy-reform bill. Ms Warren was concerned about the repercussions for middle-class Americans, especially women, who would have a harder time filing for bankruptcy as a result of the bill. A particular target of her ire was Joe Biden, then a senator from Delaware and one of the bill’s strongest backers. “Senators like Joe Biden should not be allowed to sell out women in the morning and be heralded as their friend in the evening,” she wrote at the time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To this day the two are seen as ideological foes. Ms Warren appeals to a fire-breathing leftish section of the party, while Mr Biden has made a concerted effort to court moderate Democratic voters. Yet both contenders for the Democratic nomination released ambitious, detailed environmental plans within hours of one another on June 4th. The striking similarity of their plans shows how the politics of climate change has evolved from a niche issue among Democrats to one of great urgency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The American environmental activists who called for a Green New Deal, particularly Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez, a freshman congresswoman from New York, can claim some credit for this change. A series of recent calamitous weather events—fires, polar vortices, hurricanes and floods—have also helped. This week, 17% of Democrats surveyed by YouGov on behalf of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; said the environment was the most important issue for them. That is second only to health care, the chief issue of last year’s mid-term elections, which captures the attention of 22%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Green New Deal has two problems. The first is that it is only skeletally sketched, with handwaving in lieu of details for the massive economic reorganisation it envisages. The second is that it includes a gratuitous list of progressive measures—including a federal jobs guarantee, a universal basic income, and universal health insurance—only tangentially related to climate policy. Many top-tier Democratic candidates, who would no doubt balk at such sweeping changes, signed on to the Green New Deal nonetheless. Yet with the release of Mr Biden’s and Ms Warren’s plans, both less quixotic and more scrupulous than the earlier sketch, the debate has been much improved.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Biden had been one of the few leading presidential contenders to resist endorsing the Green New Deal. He would instead release his own climate plan, he said. An adviser’s comment that Mr Biden was seeking a “middle ground” sparked fears among activists that his would be a mishmash package that offered carbon taxes for liberals and fracking subsidies for conservatives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Mr Biden’s plan is ambitious. He would like the American economy to be a net-zero emitter of carbon pollution by 2050. This would be achieved in two ways, including executive orders and actions (taking Barack Obama’s playbook for climate policy and applying it much more aggressively) that would bypass Congress. The second way, which would require legislation, is through a $1.7trn in federal funding for what Mr Biden calls, in a Sandersesque turn of phrase, a “Clean Energy Revolution”. There are other sensible proposals—finally developing the high-speed rail that America lacks, and reforming zoning to encourage denser, more efficient cities—scattered throughout.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One innovation, which seems to play to Mr Biden’s strengths as a foreign-policy expert, is to threaten tariffs on countries without adequate environmental policies. America accounts for only 15% of the world’s greenhouse-gas emissions. China accounts for nearly twice that. Mr Biden’s language on this—he says he wants “strong new measures to stop other countries from cheating on their climate commitments”—sounds almost Trumpian. Given that Mr Biden is the clear front-runner for the Democratic nomination, this perhaps paves the way for a future attack on the president for focusing his trade actions on the wrong problem. Climate change is a much more serious problem for America’s future than illegal immigration or bilateral trade deficits, Mr Biden could credibly argue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Warren’s plan has a Trumpian echo, too: it was released under the banner of “economic patriotism”. It represents, according to her, “my commitment to a Green New Deal”—one that applies the analogy of wartime mobilisation during Franklin Roosevelt’s presidency to modern times. Hers is straightforward industrial policy—calling for $2trn in investments over the next 10 years for research and development—with three-quarters of that vast sum spent through federal procurement. Ms Warren thinks that all that production would generate 1m jobs, which would pay at least $15 per hour and guarantee 12 weeks of paid family and medical leave. About $100bn of the money would be spent on a “Green Marshall Plan”, dedicated to exporting the clean-energy technology developed in America to other countries. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The curious thing about both proposals is that they dodge the question of a price on carbon, whether through direct taxation or a cap-and-trade scheme. Though research into more cost-effective technology for carbon capture and sequestration or solar power is helpful and necessary, a carbon price incorporating the negative externality of pollution would seem a simple first step. Mr Biden’s plan only nebulously nods towards “the principles that polluters must bear the full cost of the carbon pollution they are emitting” and says nothing more on the subject. It goes unmentioned in Ms Warren’s plan. Both candidates presumably employ clever policy staffers who know about carbon pricing—but they also employ strategists who note that carbon taxes are quite easily dismissed as energy taxes by political opponents. The lessons of 2010, when a Democratic effort to create a carbon market spectacularly collapsed despite unified control of government leading to an electoral backlash, seem to have been well-remembered. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 02:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Britain’s major parties are weaker than ever before]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/07/britains-major-parties-are-weaker-than-ever-before]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_woc221_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-07T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PREDICTING EARTHQUAKES is doomed to failure, as seismologists well know. But some political earthquakes are a different matter. In the early hours of June 7th, the Brexit Party’s candidate, Mike Greene, came close to winning the first seat in Parliament for a party that was created just two months earlier. He fell just 683 votes short of Labour’s winning candidate in a by-election in Peterborough (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/07/labour-holds-peterborough-slowing-the-brexit-partys-momentum&quot;&gt;see article&lt;/a&gt;). Even so, the result amounts to a political tremor that was much predicted, though perhaps not the Big One that some had expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc555.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;’s analysis of Westminster voting-intention polls.&lt;p&gt;The last time both parties’ support took a big simultaneous dip was in 2010, when the Liberal Democrats briefly polled in second place following an impressive televised debate by their leader, Nick Clegg. Even then, Labour and the Tories still had 65% of the vote in the election—25 percentage points higher than today’s share. The two big parties risk being overtaken by the upstart Brexit Party and the Liberal Democrats, who enjoyed a revival in last month’s local and European elections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trends in party support now look more like the wobbly lines of a seismometer than the decades-old separation between the two biggest parties and the rest. Brexit is the main cause of their instability. Historically, the Conservatives and Labour have fought elections mainly on domestic issues, such as levels of government spending and the National Health Service. But the vote to leave the European Union in a referendum in 2016 opened a new fault-line within the country and within both main parties. As Britain polarises over Brexit, a growing number of voters want parties that represent clear, stark views of EU membership: leave without a deal, or reverse the referendum and remain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the culmination of social changes that have been taking place since the 1980s, and reflect striking differences between old and young, and between university graduates and the poorly educated. But the two main parties have so been able to rely on Britain’s first-past-the-post electoral system—which penalises smaller parties—to hold on to a disproportionate share of seats in Parliament. Given the state of the polls, as well as the results from Peterborough, their supremacy is at stake. Rob Ford, a political scientist at Manchester University, says that the biggest barrier to a political realignment in Britain is in convincing voters that third parties are viable, but “If people stop believing that the major parties are the only ones that can fly, that becomes a self-fulfilling prophecy.” A great tectonic shift is underway in British politics. Whether Labour and the Tories survive the earthquake will depend on how well they can adjust to the shifting ground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 02:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why spoilers are ruining storytelling]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/07/why-spoilers-are-ruining-storytelling]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_BKP512.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-07T17:09:02Z&quot;&gt;Jun 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN THE first few decades of cinema, patrons would buy a ticket that granted general admission to the theatre. Several features would be playing on a loop, and you could choose whichever you fancied. You might enter halfway through the main movie, watch it until the end, see the cartoons and the newsreel and then start from the beginning to catch what you’d missed. It functioned rather like a big public television.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then, in 1960, a director decreed that no one would be permitted to enter screenings once his new film had begun: the integrity of the viewing experience was paramount. The film was “Psycho” and Alfred Hitchcock’s edict—part artistic statement, part marketing ploy—placed new emphasis on plot twists in the final act. (He also asked critics not to discuss those key details.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, writers and film-makers are obsessed with spoilers. J.K. Rowling has urged those watching “Harry Potter and the Cursed Child”, a stage play, or the new “Fantastic Beasts” films to “keep the secrets”. Anthony and Joseph Russo, the directors of Marvel films, have issued statements requesting that fans not ruin them for others. When “Once Upon a Time...in Hollywood” screened in Cannes, a similar plea from Quentin Tarantino was read to the press, to much exasperated booing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Audiences are zealous about the matter, too. Many viewers will go offline prior to episodes of a favourite television show, or mute certain words on social media so as to avoid seeing potentially spoiling posts. Writers must declare that their review contains spoilers, or face a backlash. One fan was assaulted outside a screening of “Avengers: Endgame” for “loudly revealing” the movie’s outcome. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Narratives have always had twists and unforeseen turns. “Citizen Kane” (1941) reveals a crucial detail in the last minute; whodunnits keep audiences guessing until a last gasp-inducing denouement . Yet Michael Curtiz didn’t ban viewers from entering “Mildred Pierce” (1945) late, nor did Orson Welles embargo the press on matters relating to “Rosebud”. Surprises were there to be had, certainly, but they weren’t particularly treasured or protected. (A notable exception is a production of “The Mousetrap” on the West End, which for decades has asked its patrons to keep quiet.) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In films of the 1990s such as “The Crying Game”, “Seven”, “The Usual Suspects” and “Fight Club”, the twist ending came of age; M. Night Shyamalan, a writer and director, became something of a master of the form. The ascendancy of the twist coincided with the spread of the internet, and the spoiler hysteria began. With so much analysis of films and television online, new rules of debate were inaugurated whereby warnings must be given about spoilers, or readers must be allowed to opt in to them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Film-makers realised that fans were invested in the surprise and pandered to them. Joseph McGinty Nichol released false spoilers for “Terminator: Salvation”; other directors shot multiple endings for their films. “The Last Watch”, a documentary about the making of the last season of “Game of Thrones”, shows scripts being shredded following the cast read-through and actors being flown out for needless location shoots to mislead journalists and fans. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is all rather ridiculous—and cynical. Shocking plots are what get people talking, tweeting and tuning in. In television, they help to guarantee huge ratings on the day of broadcast. The hubbub encourages fans to book their cinema tickets in advance. The Russo brothers begging viewers not to ruin the Avengers films probably helped them to secure the biggest opening weekend in film history. See it now, that seemed to say, or have someone else spoil it for you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This attitude stifles proper discussion of stories by critics as much as viewers, and it inflicts damage on storytelling as a craft. By promoting one technique, the twist, and one effect, surprise, stories get bent out of shape. They try too hard to counter expectation and resist predictability. “The Lord of the Rings” is totally predictable from beginning to end, but the series does not suffer for it. William Shakespeare gave away the end of his tragedies by billing them as such and no one seemed to mind (“Romeo and Juliet” even told the audience the story in a prologue). “Columbo”, a classic crime serial, reveals who commited the murder at the beginning of each episode and succeeded in making the investigation thrilling to watch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stories that promote surprise over character end up as mere soap opera, a series of sensational shocks. That corrodes credibility, while some reveals—they were all dead! it was all a dream!—do not so much blow minds as waste time. More significant than all of this, though, is the fact that surprise is overrated. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://journals.sagepub.com/doi/abs/10.1177/0956797611417007&quot;&gt;A study carried out by Jonathan Leavitt and Nicholas Christenfeld&lt;/a&gt; in 2011 found that knowing how the story ends doesn’t hamper enjoyment—it increases it. In other words, spoilers don’t spoil anything.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:40:30 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The second half of the internet revolution, Sudan&#x27;s Tiananmen and baseball&#x27;s exceptionalism]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/07/the-second-half-of-the-internet-revolution-sudans-tiananmen-and-baseballs-exceptionalism]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_8.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-07T16:50:43Z&quot;&gt;Jun 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A SELECTION of three essential articles read aloud from the latest issue of The Economist. This week, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/08/the-second-half-of-humanity-is-joining-the-internet&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the second half of humanity is joining the internet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Citizens of the emerging world will change the web and it will change them. Next, could the slaughter of pro-democracy protesters in Khartoum be &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/06/pro-democracy-protesters-are-slaughtered-in-khartoum&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sudan’s Tiananmen?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (7:29) And, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/06/08/baseball-and-exceptionalism&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;why baseball reflects America’s desire to be different&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (14:39). Runtiome: 22 min &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-june7th2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:40:29 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Labour holds Peterborough, slowing the Brexit Party’s momentum]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/07/labour-holds-peterborough-slowing-the-brexit-partys-momentum]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_brp509.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-07T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE PETERBOROUGH by-election on June 6th has failed to cause the political earthquake that many were expecting. Lisa Forbes held onto the seat for the Labour Party, beating the Brexit Party party’s candidate, Mike Greene, into second place. The party’s leader, Nigel Farage, who briefly made an appearance at the count, retreated with his tail between his legs and a question mark hanging over his political project.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Brexit Party was registered only four months ago, born out of frustration that Britain has so far missed all its deadlines to leave the European Union. After a stunning victory in the European elections on May 23rd, winning almost one third of the popular vote, many were predicting a win for the upstarts in Peterborough. But if the Brexit Party cannot win a seat in a constituency that voted 61% for Leave in the referendum of 2016, and that had just booted out its sitting MP for criminal activity, when will it be able to win its first seat at Westminster? The Liberal Democrats failed to repeat their impressive performance in last month’s European elections and managed to come only fourth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The by-election was a triumph of old-style political loyalties. Many psephologists have taken to arguing that Leave and Remain are beginning to trump left and right as the lodestars of political loyalty. But Labour succeeded in keeping the seat, despite both the criminal antics of its previous MP (Fiona Onasanya had conspired with her brother-in-law to claim that he was driving her car in order to save her from getting points on her licence), and efforts by two challenging parties, the Brexit Party and the Liberal Democrats, to seduce its Leave and Remain supporters respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The by-election was also a triumph of old-fashioned shoe-leather politics. The Labour Party demonstrated that it is still a master of traditional get-out-the-vote politics: targeting likely voters, knocking on doors, demonstrating command of local issues, mixing national stars such as Angela Rayner with local activists and, above all, getting supporters to the polls on election day. The Brexit Party showed that its mastery of the new politics of social media and cultural polarisation that served it so well in the European elections (where people are voting for lists of candidates in giant constituencies) doesn’t translate into Westminster politics (where people are voting for particular MPs). Though Mr Farage promised that “we will be back”, his chances of winning Peterborough in a general election, where turn-out is routinely higher than yesterday’s 48%, will be slim unless he can build an old-fashioned political machine of local activists. There is a big difference between running a political party and running a glorified pressure group.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For all that it was a close-run thing. The Labour Party poured massive national resources into the constituency, something that it wouldn’t be able to replicate in a general election. Even so, it managed to defeat the Brexit Party by only 638 votes, and saw its own share of the vote share fall by 17 percentage points from the 2017 general election. Given the dismal state of Britain’s Conservative government, with Brexit undelivered and the party engaged in a bloody leadership contest, this is hardly a ringing endorsement of Jeremy Corbyn’s leadership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two biggest losers from the by-election were arguably the Conservative Party and the People’s Vote campaign. The Conservatives came a dismal third—the first time the party has failed to come in the top two in Peterborough since the introduction of the universal franchise in 1918—and saw its vote share fall by 25 percentage points from the last general election. This is perhaps a fitting political epitaph for Theresa May, who steps down as leader of the party on June 7th after three years characterised by a toxic combination of hubris, dithering and poor judgment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The party’s poor performance will reinforce the conviction that it has to push Brexit through, or see the Brexit Party syphon off many of its natural supporters, split the right-wing vote and put Mr Corbyn in Downing Street. The chairman of the Peterborough Conservative Association, Wayne Fitzgerald, said the result proved it was essential that the party commit to taking Britain out of the EU, even if it means doing so with no deal. (It is notable that, taken together, the Conservative and Brexit parties took 50% of the vote, to Labour’s 31%.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The People’s Vote campaign has been putting enormous pressure on Mr Corbyn to make Labour a Remain party that campaigns vigorously for a second referendum. But the fact that Labour has held a seat in a Leave-voting constituency against strong pressure from the Brexit Party will vindicate Mr Corbyn’s strategy of fudging on Brexit and fighting the war on Labour’s strongest fronts, public services and economic justice. Remainers may celebrate the fact that Mr Farage’s forces were defeated. But the result will also make both main parties more anxious to press on with getting Brexit out of the way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 22:40:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“It’s been a farce”—Britain’s leadership contest]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/07/its-been-a-farce-britains-leadership-contest]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_blm513.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-07T11:30:01Z&quot;&gt;Jun 7th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THERESA MAY stepped down&lt;/strong&gt; today as leader of the &lt;strong&gt;Conservative Party&lt;/strong&gt;, and would-be replacements are already &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/08/rory-stewart-odd-man-out&quot;&gt;lining up&lt;/a&gt;. There’s little hope that any would be able to arrange an elegant &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/30/britons-are-ever-more-polarised-between-no-deal-and-a-second-referendum&quot;&gt;exit from Europe&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Also, we take a look at the astonishing range of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/international/2019/06/08/magic-mushrooms-illegal-in-most-places-may-have-therapeutic-uses&quot;&gt;ailments&lt;/a&gt; that could be treated by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/08/magic-mushrooms-should-be-decriminalised&quot;&gt;magic mushrooms&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/torystory-britain-snextprimeminister&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 19:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Who can lead Britain through Brexit?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/06/who-can-lead-britain-through-brexit]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_opp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-06T19:00:46Z&quot;&gt;Jun 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ANNE MCELVOY SPEAKS to two candidates in the race to succeed Theresa May as Conservative leader and Britain&amp;#x27;s prime minister. She catches up with Rory Stewart, the international development secretary, who proposes a “citizens’ assembly” to solve Brexit. And she asks the foreign secretary, Jeremy Hunt, how he would avoid a no-deal Brexit and how he explained the National Health Service to President Donald Trump. Runtime: 36 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-whocanleadbritainthroughbrexit-&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 03:40:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Billions flee the Woodford investment group]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/06/troubles-at-the-woodford-investment-group-point-to-a-wider-trend]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_brp506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-06T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE STOCKMARKET is a risky and complicated place. For more than a century many investors have trusted financial experts to pick the best shares for them, in return for a hefty fee. But even the experts can get it badly wrong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That has been the case this week with Woodford Investment Management, which has suffered two devastating blows. The first occurred when the firm suspended trading in its flagship Equity Income fund, locking in investors’ money. The second came when St James’s Place, a wealth management group, announced that it was replacing Woodford as the manager of some £3.5bn worth of assets. That move alone reduced the amount of money managed by Woodford by around 40%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Woodford crisis illustrates a much broader trend. Investors have steadily been realising that the experts can struggle to outperform the market. Instead they have been pouring money into funds that simply seek to mimic the market, but charge low fees. Assets in exchange-traded funds (ETFs) rose from $716bn in 2008 to almost $4.7trn at the end of last year, according to Statista, an information group. The two biggest fund management groups in the world, BlackRock and Vanguard, specialise in index-tracking or passive funds. Active funds (those that try to beat the market) have struggled to perform over periods from one to 10 years. The right-hand chart shows that only a tiny proportion of funds investing in UK equities (like the Woodford fund) have beaten the market over periods from one to 10 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During the long period when he was a fund manager at Invesco Perpetual, Neil Woodford seemed to be an exception to this rule. He picked unfashionable stocks in areas like tobacco and avoided the dotcom boom. His success prompted many clients to follow him when he set up his own firm in 2014. Woodford Investment Management was managing more than £10bn at its peak.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc216.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc216.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc216.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc216.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc216.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc216.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc216.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc216.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc216.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_woc216.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this belief in “star” fund managers is not supported by the data. The left-hand chart shows the percentage of US managers in the top quartile (best performing 25%) of 2014 that repeated the feat in succeeding years. If the results were just random, then 25% of managers should repeat the feat in the first year, 12.5% in the second, 6.25% in the third and so on. As you can see, the figures become much worse than random as time goes on. Picking managers on the basis of past performance is a mug’s game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why is that so? The most obvious reason is that outperformance over a short period is down to luck more than skill and that, over time, managers revert to the mean. Since fund managers own most of the market, their performance is, on average, likely to replicate the market, before costs. Those costs can be significant (often, more than a percentage point a year) so that the average manager is doomed to underperform, after those costs are taken into account.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Star managers will, by definition, have portfolios that do not look like the overall market. Often they will have made a limited number of bets on a small number of companies. As their reputation grows, money will flood in from new investors. For a while, they might try to invest in the same shares as before. But if they are not careful, they will end up owning 20-30% of such companies. So the temptation will be to spread the portfolio over a broader range of groups. The danger is that their 50th favourite stock might not be as good a bet as their top ten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The resulting pattern can be strong performance in the early years, but a more mediocre result later on. The long-term return numbers can still look good. But most clients will have invested their money after the stellar years; the return earned by the average client will not be that great. A classic example of this phenomenon was Fidelity Magellan. When Peter Lynch took over the fund in 1977, it had just $22m in assets. He achieved a return of 29% a year on average until 1990, by which stage the fund had $14bn under management. Assets continued to pour in under his immediate successors and the fund reached more than $100bn, making it by far the biggest mutual fund in 2000. But the fund lagged the market for years afterwards; the latecomers (who invested the bulk of the money) lost out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Woodford tried to escape the rut by investing in smaller stocks, some of which were unquoted and some of which were listed on the tiny Guernsey exchange. This meant that his fund did not resemble the conventional market, and thus had the chance to outperform. But it created three problems. The first was that Mr Woodford was running an equity income fund, which meant that he needed to find companies that paid regular dividends; small, unquoted companies tend not to do this. The second problem was some of Mr Woodford’s bets went badly wrong: the fund has returned 11% since its launch, compared with the UK market’s 34%. The third problem was the greatest. Woodford Equity Income is an “open-ended” fund. When investors buy into the fund, its assets rise, and the manager must buy more shares; when they sell, the assets fall, and the manager must sell. There was thus a mismatch between Mr Woodford’s clients, who could demand instant liquidity, and his assets, a proportion of which was difficult to sell. Poor performance has been causing money to head out of the fund, with £560m flowing out in May, according to Morningstar, an investment research firm. When one big client, Kent County Council, demanded its money back, trading was suspended to give Woodford time to realise the money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of this was a big shock for Mr Woodford’s prominent backers, including Hargreaves Lansdown, a leading financial adviser. The Woodford fund was on its “Wealth 50” list of favourite funds. And Hargreaves also runs its own funds, one of which, the Multi-Manager Income &amp;amp; Growth Trust, had £405m (13.7% of its assets) in the Woodford fund. So it is not just the experts who can get it wrong; so can the experts who pick the experts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For years, those arguing that UK investors should stick to passive tracking funds have faced the comeback “What about Neil Woodford?” They won’t get that comeback any more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 02:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>