<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[In Venice, a “library of exile” reflects on displacement and language]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/15/in-venice-a-library-of-exile-reflects-on-displacement-and-language]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BKP503_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T14:55:27Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE ATENEO VENETO, a grand 16th-century palace near the Fenice Opera House, once hosted a fraternal order which cared for convicted prisoners in their final days. For the past 200 years, however, the site has been a forum for discussion, drawing together people from the city’s many communities to contemplate art, literature, science and politics. Now it is home to a different set of noisy and troubled souls. In the Aula Magna room—where scenes of conflagration adorn the ceiling—stands a porcelain box filled with 2,000 books by exiled writers, from Ovid, through Dante, Voltaire and Victor Hugo, to the present day. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the heart of this piece by Edmund de Waal, a British ceramicist and writer, is a lost library. In 1938, weeks after the Nazi invasion of Austria, his great-grandfather’s home on the Ringstrasse in Vienna was stormed and the library was seized and Aryanised. The story of the tragic dispersal of that household formed the basis of Mr de Waal’s bestselling family memoir, “The Hare with Amber Eyes” (2010). “This is a project that I have always dreamed of doing,” he says of the Venice show. “It is about exile—what it means to move to another country, to speak another language.” He reckons it will be “the most significant sculpture of [his] life”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exhibition, entitled “psalm” after a book in the Old Testament, exists in two parts. In the Jewish Museum in the Venetian Ghetto, Mr de Waal has installed ten works of porcelain, marble and gold that reflect on the cultural heritage of the area (he is the first contemporary artist to create a major project for the Ghetto). In the Ateneo Veneto, he covered the exterior of his library in gold leaf, which was then coated with white porcelain slip, a kind of slurry. On that surface he has etched the names of more than 60 lost libraries, including Alexandria, Nineveh, the Rabbinical libraries of Lvov and Odessa, Aleppo, Mosul and the classical collection of Viktor von Ephrussi, his great-grandfather. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190518_bkp504.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;Inside the library, alongside the shelves, are four glass vitrines holding small porcelain works. Mr de Waal says the layout of the space is intended to evoke the edition of the Talmud created by Daniel Bomberg, a Christian printer, in Venice in the early 16th century—around the same time the Ateneo was built. The project reflects the city’s long history “as a place of translation, a space to sit and read and be,” he says; the books are arranged chronologically by country, though most have been translated from their original language, and visitors are encouraged to seek out titles in their own tongue as well as those that have been translated from it. Readers search for the nations they know, and within them the writers they have loved and followed even as they fled abroad. Your correspondent was born in Africa, and was happy to find volumes by Patrice Nganang from Cameroon and Ngugi wa Thiong’o, a Kenyan writer who has said that “resistance is the best way of keeping alive.”&lt;p&gt;In the tumult of the Venice Biennale, there is something special about any spot that is quiet. The project encourages the visitor to reflect on returns, a theme that recurs throughout the artist’s work. Mr de Waal’s great-grandfather’s books were never recovered, probably dispersed throughout Austria or destroyed, but with this new “library of exile” he has devised his own kind of restitution. The exhibition will travel to Germany, to the Japanisches Palais in Dresden—which was operating as a public library when it was partially destroyed during the second world war—and then to the old King’s Library at the British Museum. After that, Mr de Waal aims to give the 2,000 books to the city of Mosul, which will house them in the new library the city is building to replace the one destroyed by Islamic State. He plans to add 800 books of his own, including the 18th-century edition of Voltaire that his grandmother managed to save from the Ephrussi library before she went into exile herself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“psalm”, an exhibition in two parts, continues in Venice until September 29th. The “library of exile” will be presented at the Japanisches Palais in Dresden from November 2019 to February 2020, and at the British Museum in London in 2020&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[To understand the tech lords, look to their libraries]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/15/to-understand-the-tech-lords-look-to-their-libraries]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_ldp501_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;LITERARY TYPES have long been sniffy about science fiction. Ian McEwan, a feted British novelist, has been at pains to distance his most recent book, about an intelligent android, from “sci-fi”, even though the idea is one of the most picked-over tropes in the genre. Such snobbery is misplaced. Humans are technological animals. Science fiction explores how that power might be used, what sorts of worlds might be built with it and what sublime new estrangements and transcendence may follow. It is a literature of ideas, and, as John Maynard Keynes observed (in a different context), the world is ruled by little else. To see the force of Keynes’s point, consider how the world’s richest man plans to spend his fortune.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On May 9th Jeff Bezos outlined his thoughts about the future of humanity. The founder of Amazon sells $1bn-worth of shares a year to fund his rocket company, Blue Origin, which wants to cut the cost of space flight, put tourists into space and help return humans to the moon. That is only the first part of a grander scheme to spread humanity throughout the solar system in artificial habitats. He is not alone. Elon Musk founded SpaceX with the goal of establishing a self-sufficient colony on Mars. Yuri Milner, a Russian tycoon, has promised $100m to send a robot to Alpha Centauri, the closest star system to the sun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Bezos is open about his influences. He grew up reading Isaac Asimov and Robert Heinlein, with their stories of rebellious lunar colonies, idiot-savant robots and societies founded on “psychohistory”, an amalgam of economics, history and what is now called big data. “Star Trek”, with its humane, liberal and internationalist re-imagining of the American frontier spirit, was another favourite. Decades later, Mr Bezos is using his money to help bring such a future about, rather as Heinlein’s D D Harriman did in “The Man Who Sold the Moon”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Scratch a Silicon Valley nerd and chances are you will find similar influences, and similar ideas about how the future should look. One of the tech industry’s favourite writers is Iain M Banks, a Scottish socialist whose knockabout space operas were set in and around “the Culture”, a spacefaring utopia. Amid worries about superintelligent computers and robots taking jobs, they are a tonic. In Mr Banks’s society robots have indeed taken all the jobs, but the result is inexhaustible material abundance. Sentient beings, organic or artificial, are free to flourish. Everything is run by nigh-omnipotent and mostly benevolent AI philosopher-kings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His influence runs deep. A meeting room at DeepMind, a big AI firm, is named in his honour. When Mark Zuckerberg, the boss of Facebook, ran a book club in 2015, only two of his 23 recommendations were novels. Mr Banks’s “The Player of Games” was one. (“The Three-Body Problem”, a piece of science fiction by Liu Cixin, was the other). Mr Musk named SpaceX’s rocket-recovery “droneships” after AI-animated spaceships in Mr Banks’s “Culture” books. In 2018 Mr Bezos announced plans to film those books, as well as Larry Niven’s “Ringworld” and “Snow Crash”, a cyberpunk novel by Neal Stephenson—who was, for some of Blue Origin’s early days, its only employee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many of Silicon Valley’s favourite stories feature grand, mostly benign futures. Of course, technology can change people, as well as the societies they build. Ursula le Guin has speculated about how societies might look when genetic engineering makes seemingly basic biological categories, like sex, fluid and malleable. Those who worry more about the perils of technology than its promises will find plenty to chew on, too. “1984” needs no introduction. Masayoshi Son, the boss of Softbank, worries about the “Singularity”, when machine intelligence exponentially exceeds the human sort and technological progress escapes all attempts at control. The term was popularised by Vernor Vinge, an American computer scientist and sci-fi author, and remains a popular topic in tech circles. Margaret Atwood has written of societies in the aftermath of technological apocalypses—although she, like Mr McEwan, resists the “sci-fi” label. Kim Stanley Robinson’s “New York 2140” is set in that city after it has been flooded by climate change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-ianmcewan&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One influential proponent of a less starry-eyed attitude to the future is William Gibson, who made his name by rejecting the togas-and-crystal-spires view common in mid-century sci-fi. His “high tech and low life” style of fiction, in which hacker gangs steal information for money and the rich grow ever more detached from the societies that sustain them, was prescient. Two of his aphorisms—that “the future is already here, it’s just not evenly distributed” and “the street finds its own use for things”—have become received wisdom for futurists. If you want to understand how those who are building the future think, ignore the snobs. Sci-fi is the place to start. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 22:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“It&#x27;s too much spending, not enough tax collecting”—Pakistan’s 22nd IMF loan]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/15/its-too-much-spending-not-enough-tax-collecting-pakistans-22nd-imf-loan]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/imf_pakistan.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T11:30:36Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE INTERNATIONAL Monetary Fund has struck another deal to bail out &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/13/the-imf-has-agreed-to-break-pakistans-fall-again&quot;&gt;Pakistan&lt;/a&gt;—its 22nd. How did the country’s economy end up in such a mess? Never mind rising numbers of vegetarians: the world is eating more &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/international/2019/05/04/global-meat-eating-is-on-the-rise-bringing-surprising-benefits&quot;&gt;meat&lt;/a&gt; and, in a way, that’s a good thing. And how &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/11/what-french-baby-names-say-about-the-country&quot;&gt;French names&lt;/a&gt; reveal social trends that census data cannot. Runtime: 21min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/don-tspenditallatonce-pakistanandtheimf&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 20:40:52 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China vows a “fight to the end” in trade feud with America]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/15/china-vows-a-fight-to-the-end-in-trade-feud-with-america]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_fnp001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THOUGH CHINA runs a massive trade surplus with America, over the past year it has run a massive rhetoric deficit. During that period President Donald Trump has tweeted about China 133 times; Chinese leaders, by contrast, have mostly kept mum about the trade dispute with America. But in the past few days that has begun to change. A sudden barrage of commentaries about the trade war in state media has struck a note of defiant nationalism. “If you want to talk, our door is wide open,” said an anchor on China’s most-watched news programme on May 13th, in a clip that went viral. “If you want to fight, we’ll fight you to the end.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The aggressive language comes as the two countries’ trade war heats up. Last week American negotiators alleged that China had reneged on a draft deal that was nearly complete. Chinese officials said it was the Americans who were making unreasonable demands. The breakdown in talks led to America’s decision on May 10th to raise tariffs on $200bn-worth of Chinese imports from 10% to 25%, covering products such as car parts and circuit boards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On May 13th Mr Trump tweeted, warning China not to retaliate. It will only get worse, he said. Barely an hour later China ratcheted up tariffs on $60bn-worth of imports from America, including natural gas. And it did indeed get worse, with the United States Trade Representative shortly thereafter beginning the process of implementing tariffs on “essentially all” Chinese imports. When all is said and done, China’s nearly $560bn-worth of annual exports to America could face tariffs of 25%. Much of America’s $180bn of annual exports to China could also be subject to similar levies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those already in place will hurt. Many economists estimate that China’s growth this year could be dragged down by about half a percentage point, to 6%. In America consumers will start to see higher prices: inflation could rise by half a percentage point, according to economists at Société Générale, a French bank. If Mr Trump follows through on the threat to hit all Chinese imports with duties—and few doubt his love of tariffs—the damage could be far greater. Chad Bown and Eva Zhang of the Peterson Institute for International Economics in Washington, DC, reckon that the scale of American tariffs on China would resemble the Smoot-Hawley tariff of 1930, levied just before the Great Depression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At that point China might well start making life difficult for American businesses in China. One possibility would be consumer boycotts, fanned by state media. Forecasting models scarcely capture the alarm that would spread through markets if the world’s two biggest economies engage in a full-blown trade war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is still hope that America and China will step back. A recovery in global share prices after a big sell-off on May 13th, when the tit-for-tat tariffs were announced, reflects optimism that cooler heads will prevail. Most of the latest measures are not yet in force. America’s new 25% tariffs apply only to goods that left China after they were announced. Because it takes about three weeks for ocean freighters to make the journey, it will be June before the pain is truly felt. China’s new tariffs take effect only on June 1st. So there is time to talk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In its official statements, China’s consistent message has been that, though it will not be bullied, it wants to work towards a deal with America. Mr Trump has also shown a willingness to resume talks, saying that he will hold meetings with Xi Jinping, China’s president, at a G20 summit in Japan at the end of June. The last time the two leaders met at a G20 summit, in November in Argentina, they agreed to a truce in the trade war. That might be a reason for optimism. Then again, given where the two countries are now, it could just as well be a reason for despair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 20:40:51 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A US-China game of nerves]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/14/a-us-china-game-of-nerves]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_opp501_3.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-14T19:30:59Z&quot;&gt;May 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TWO-WAY TRADE between America and China hit $2bn a day last year. But the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/11/the-us-china-trading-relationship-will-be-fraught-for-years-to-come&quot;&gt;growing mistrust&lt;/a&gt; between the two countries is turning business from a safe space into a field of contention. David Rennie, &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s Beijing bureau chief, has travelled across both countries and found that, with China’s daunting rise, making money is no longer enough to keep friendly relations. Runtime: 26 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-aus-chinagameofnerves&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 06:08:30 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Strange things are afoot in the Strait of Hormuz]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/14/strange-things-are-afoot-in-the-strait-of-hormuz]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_blp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-14T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHEN DONALD TRUMP hired John Bolton to be his national security adviser, he reportedly joked that the mustachioed hawk was “going to get us into a war”. It is easy to see why. When serving under George W. Bush, Mr Bolton embellished intelligence on Cuban and Syrian weapons and lobbied hard for the invasion of Iraq. After leaving government he argued that America should bomb Iran to set back its nuclear programme. Now that he’s back, he appears to be on the warpath once again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was Mr Bolton, not the commander-in-chief, who announced on May 5th that America had dispatched an aircraft-carrier strike group and bombers to the Persian Gulf. This was in response to undisclosed intelligence which, unnamed officials claimed, showed that Iran and its proxies were planning attacks on American forces (or its allies) in the region. On May 9th Mr Bolton reviewed war plans, updated at his request, that call for sending up to 120,000 troops to the Middle East if Iran attacks or restarts work on nuclear weapons, according to the New York Times. Such planning is not a sign of imminent conflict. But Mr Trump is reported to be telling that joke again, now with more seriousness, as Mr Bolton also ratchets up pressure on Venezuela.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some fear Mr Bolton is looking for a provocation by Iran, adding ominous undertones to recent events in the region. On May 12th four oil tankers were struck by a “sabotage attack” off Fujairah, part of the United Arab Emirates (UAE). The incident remains murky, but Emirati, Saudi and American officials claim that four ships—two Saudi, one Emirati and the other Norwegian—had 1.5-metre to 3-metre holes blown in their hull, near the waterline. Unnamed American officials were quoted fingering Iran or its proxies as the likely culprit, without presenting evidence. Fujairah lies just outside the Strait of Hormuz, a key chokepoint that Iranian officials have threatened to block if America attacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was not the only flare-up. On May 14th Saudi Arabia said two of its oil-pumping stations were attacked. The damage was limited, but the Houthis, Shia rebels who control much of Yemen, claimed responsibility and threatened more such attacks. They are fighting a Saudi-led coalition, supported by America, that backs the Yemeni government. America and Saudi Arabia accuse the Houthis of being an Iranian puppet. That is an exaggeration, though the Houthis have received arms from Iran. The facilities that came under attack lie more than 700km north of the Yemeni border. They were probably hit by long-range drones that the Houthis acquired last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two incidents taken together highlight the vulnerability of Gulf energy supplies—and thus Gulf economies. Fujairah is connected via a pipeline to Abu Dhabi&amp;#x27;s oil fields. The pumping stations hit in Saudi Arabia are part of the “east-west pipeline”, which moves crude from eastern oil fields to western ports. Both pipelines are meant to help producers bypass the Strait of Hormuz.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iran has a record of subversive action and supporting allied militias in the region—and of attacking shipping. The so-called tanker war between Iran and Iraq ravaged international shipping in the 1980s. Over 500 ships were attacked. Four years into the tanker war, after an American-flagged ship was struck by an Iranian mine, America conducted its largest ever attack on Iran, destroying two oil platforms and sinking a frigate. At least some in the White House look back fondly on that show of force.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the timing of the incident in Fujairah, and the quickness with which American officials blamed Iran, has raised eyebrows. Max Boot, a hawkish foreign-policy scholar, writes that Mr Bolton “may be trying to provoke Iran into striking first”. He and others are reminded of the Gulf of Tonkin incident—a murky naval skirmish in 1964 used by America as a pretext for expanding its involvement in Vietnam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some officials have tried to calm matters. On May 14th John Abizaid, America’s ambassador to Saudi Arabia, who previously commanded American troops in the Middle East, called for a “thorough investigation to understand what happened [and] why it happened”. Only then, he said, should America “come up with reasonable responses short of war”. Mr Abizaid insists that it is not in America’s interest to have a conflict.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even so, European officials are nervous. On May 13th Jeremy Hunt, Britain’s foreign secretary, said he was “very worried about the risk of a conflict happening by accident with an escalation that is unintended”. That was shortly before a meeting with Mike Pompeo, America’s secretary of state, who received a frosty reception from his European counterparts in Brussels. On May 14th Spain, sensing trouble ahead, withdrew its frigate from the American aircraft-carrier strike group heading towards the Gulf. Major General Christopher Ghika, the top British officer in the American-led coalition against Islamic State, said, “There’s been no increased threat from Iranian-backed forces in Iraq and Syria.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many in Europe blame America for the rising tensions. Last year Mr Trump pulled out of a deal that curbed Iran’s nuclear programme in return for economic relief. Now he seems intent on undermining what is left of the pact by imposing crippling sanctions on Iran. On May 8th President Hassan Rouhani said Iran would abrogate parts of the deal and gave the remaining signatories—Britain, China, France, Germany, Russia and the European Union—60 days to work out how to relieve the economic pressure it was under. If they cannot, Iran would feel free to enrich uranium to ever higher levels, which would shorten its path to producing fissile material for a nuclear bomb.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump, for his part, runs hot and cold on Iran. After Mr Rouhani’s announcement, he said Iran should call him for direct talks (Mr Rouhani has spurned several such offers). After the incident in Fujairah, however, Mr Trump said, “It’s going to be a bad problem for Iran if something happens.” But he said the war plans involving tens of thousands of troops are fake news: “We have not planned for that. Hopefully we’re not going to have to plan for that.” Though he added, “If we did that, we’d send a hell of a lot more troops than that.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 05:15:39 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Amazon’s boss reckons that humanity needs an HQ2]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/14/amazons-boss-reckons-that-humanity-needs-an-hq2]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_fnd000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-14T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JEFF BEZOS wants humans to live in space. On May 9th the founder and boss of Amazon, who also runs Blue Origin, a private rocketry firm, unveiled plans for a lunar lander. “Blue Moon”, as it is called, is just one phase of a bold plan to establish large off-world settlements. It is a vision ripped directly from 20th-century science fiction. Having persuaded people to take other leaps of faith, from shopping online to placing his firm’s always-on listening posts in their homes, he could be just the person to convince millions to leave Earth. But it will take a unique economic pitch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unless Mr Bezos obtains the state-like power to order masses of people around, his plans will require emigré Earthlings to leave voluntarily. Their motives need not be entirely economic. The Puritans left Britain for America in search of freedom from religious persecution. Mr Bezos might well find recruits among unhappy minorities—or deeply devoted believers in his vision for humanity. He is not an entirely implausible cult figure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Per his presentation, however, Mr Bezos imagines that his cities will be home to millions, which would require a cost-benefit proposition with mass appeal. People might line up if the costs or risks of staying on Earth were to rise—because of a deteriorating environment, say, or a looming threat of extinction. But there are two problems with the conception of space settlements as doomsday arks. Even an Earth dramatically less habitable than it is now would still be substantially more so than anywhere else in the solar system. Any technology that could conceivably be used to create massive, human-friendly environments in space or on other planets could presumably be used at less expense on Earth. The logistics would be challenging, too. Elon Musk, the boss of Tesla, who also operates a private space firm, aims to settle Mars to ensure humanity’s continuation as a species against an extinction-level event, such as an asteroid strike. But relocating a substantial number of people to a desolate planet millions of miles away is fantastically hard. He wants to build an interplanetary ship with a capacity of 100. Even one departing every minute would not keep pace with Earth’s population growth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Space cities might lure settlers by offering to make them rich. But if extraterrestrial settlements remained dependent on imports from Earth, then their cost of living would be astronomical, and the income paid by space work would need to be correspondingly high to provide residents with a generous level of welfare. That, in turn, would require export industries selling things to Earthlings that could not be made on Earth far more cheaply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Might such space niches exist? Mining extraterrestrial objects could be economical, but would provide a weak reason for colonisation, since it could be done most easily and cheaply by robots. Service industries offer more potential. If life in space were to prove therapeutic in some way, then off-world sanitariums could turn a profit. Space tourism would create a steady demand for off-world labour. The space economy might also thrive as a hub for activities banned on Earth, such as human cloning. Once a viable source of exports was found, agglomeration could drive further growth as Earthlings sought their fortunes off-world, plying goods and services to workers in the export industries. There would be obstacles, not all related to survival. Which laws might govern private enterprise in space remains an open question; an Outer Space Treaty signed in 1967 prohibits governments from asserting claims over extraterrestrial land and resources (though an American law passed in 2015 gives companies the right to own whatever useful material they can harvest in space). For tech bros who prefer asking forgiveness to begging permission, such hurdles are unlikely to delay progress for long.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Bezos appears to have in mind something other than a trade-based interplanetary economy, however. His plans take for granted speedy technological progress of the sort that would allow for large-scale mining and materials processing by autonomous robots, and construction of vast off-world habitats. The works of science fiction from which his vision borrows often assume the emergence of “fully automated luxury communism”, in which clever machines enable the emergence of a post-scarcity world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such advances might not just enable the settlement of space, but might be realisable only in space. The resource demands of a world where everyone can have everything they want would probably outstrip Earth’s material capacity. Space, however, holds a virtually unlimited supply of the raw materials needed for universal abundance. But intensive use of extra-terrestrial resources on Earth could pose environmental hazards or nuisance costs that humans would lobby to prevent. And even nearly free resources would not enable 9bn people to live where and how they want. Not everyone can have an estate on the Californian coast.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Free enterprise&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Space, on the other hand, has plenty. In addition to its countless resource-rich rocks, it offers more than enough room to build whatever habitats, with whichever climates and vistas, are needed to satisfy humanity’s demands. In the context of the finitude of Earth, insatiable resource consumption seems wasteful, even obscene. But off-world, why be stingy? Given a choice between a cheek-by-jowl existence down here and indecent luxury up there, many might accept the risks of starting a new life in the heavens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the 19th century Europeans streamed into America because wages were higher. They were high because of the continent’s extraordinary abundance—an abundance resulting from the wiping out of indigenous people, but abundance nonetheless. The living that could be made on the near-inexhaustible supply of resource-rich land forced urban firms to pay high wages, lest workers left for the frontier. Space is a forbidding place for frail humans. But the final frontier may be the only one capable of providing humankind with endless material wealth. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 01:06:40 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[After drought, famine and war, ethnic conflict now plagues Ethiopia]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/14/after-drought-famine-and-war-ethnic-conflict-now-plagues-ethiopia]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_woc007.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-14T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR MANY years Ethiopia struggled with drought and starvation, creating a population that moved frequently in search of food and water. Now it is violence that millions of Ethiopians are fleeing. Last year it topped the list of countries with displaced people, according to the Internal Displacement Monitoring Centre (IDMC), an NGO.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are nearly 70m forcibly displaced people in the world. Refugees and asylum-seekers have rights and protections, but the roughly 40m who are “internally displaced” do not. Two-thirds are in African and Middle Eastern countries. And 2018 was another awful year, with an additional 10.8m newly-displaced people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ethiopia was at the top of the list. The 2.9m people who were forced from their homes there last year amounted to a fourfold increase on the previous year; it was the fourth-biggest displacement of people in a single year in the world since 2008.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main factor, perhaps surprisingly, was Ethiopia’s move towards democracy in April last year. As the state loosened its grip, communal strife erupted and violence broke out over land and resources. More than one million Gedeo, an ethnic group from southern Ethiopia, were displaced after clashes with rival Gujis in Oromia. In Jijiga, a previously calm city in the Somali region of the country, 140,000 people were displaced in a matter of days in August. In the past, ethnic conflicts in Ethiopia were eventually pacified and many of those forced out managed to return to their homes. But if they cannot return, the IDMC says, there is a risk that large and seemingly permanent displaced populations will in turn cause friction elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile in Syria, the United Nations has called for a halt in the renewed fighting between the government and opposition in Idlib province. In addition to the 5.5m people who have fled the country, 6.2m of the country’s 18.2m population are now internally displaced because of its eight-year civil war. Not only do airstrikes destroy property and infrastructure, but unexploded bombs make it difficult for people to return to areas devastated by the war.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are some glimmers of hope in the latest data release. In 2018, there were 665,000 fewer internally displaced people than in 2017, although the total is still an appalling 6.2m. In Congo, too, the number fell, from 4.4m to 3.1m. These are small consolations in the grim accounting of misery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 01:06:39 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Erdogan needs the Kurds if he hopes to win a repeat election]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/14/why-erdogan-needs-the-kurds-if-he-hopes-to-win-a-repeat-election]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_eup501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-14T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR EIGHT years, Turkey’s public enemy number one, Abdullah Ocalan, the imprisoned leader of the outlawed Kurdistan Workers Party (PKK), had not been allowed to meet his lawyers. Hundreds of other Kurdish inmates went on hunger strike in late 2018 to demand an end to his isolation. At least eight committed suicide. The blackout ended on May 2nd, when a pair of lawyers visited Mr Ocalan in his island prison on the Marmara Sea, where he has been held for nearly two decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The news was quickly overshadowed by political drama. Only four days after the visit Turkey’s election board voted to overturn the outcome of a mayoral election in Istanbul, in which the opposition scored a remarkable upset, and ordered a repeat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two decisions, to reopen channels with Mr Ocalan and to try to overturn the mayoral vote, could not have happened without the involvement of Turkey’s president, Recep Tayyip Erdogan, analysts say. Many of them see a connection.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More than any other group, it was Kurdish voters who helped the opposition’s candidate for Istanbul mayor, Ekrem Imamoglu, score a narrow victory in late March.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Displaced from villages and towns in Turkey’s south-east by decades of war between the PKK and the army, as well as poverty, millions of Kurds have settled in the west of the country. Istanbul’s population of 15m people includes at least 2m Kurds, more than in any city in the mainly Kurdish south-east of the country. Most of them support the Peoples’ Democratic Party (HDP), an alliance of liberals and Kurdish nationalists, which did not field its own candidate in the Istanbul vote, and endorsed Mr Imamoglu instead. On election day over 80% of the HDP’s voters backed Mr Imamoglu, according to research by TEPAV, a think-tank. The remainder appear to have abstained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To win the repeat election, Mr Erdogan’s Justice and Development (AK) party might have to reel in at least some of the abstainers, as well as conservative Kurds, to secure the election of its candidate, a former prime minister, Binali Yildrim. “Erdogan’s loss has entirely to do with Kurdish dissent,” says Asli Aydintasbas, a fellow at the European Council on Foreign Relations. “He might have to pivot to the Kurds simply to keep power.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The decision to allow Mr Ocalan to meet his lawyers appears to be part of the outreach, says Ms Aydintasbas. The move comes amid rumours that Turkish spooks recently met members of the PKK’s Syrian franchise, known as the YPG, to discuss a possible “safe zone” in Syria’s north-east. Despite opposition from America, which teamed up with the YPG to crush Islamic State’s “caliphate”, Mr Erdogan’s government has repeatedly threatened to attack the YPG’s strongholds in Syria. In a statement passed on to his lawyers, Mr Ocalan called on Turkey and the Kurdish insurgents to shun violence and pursue a settlement “within the framework of a united Syria.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To make any new inroads with Kurdish voters ahead of the repeat election in Istanbul, scheduled for June 23rd, Mr Erdogan will have to do much more than put out feelers to the PKK’s leader. During his first decade in power, Turkey’s strongman offered the Kurds new cultural rights and launched peace talks with the separatists. Over the past four years, however, he has presided over ruthless army operations against PKK fighters in cities across the south-east, the arrests of thousands of Kurdish activists, an alliance with Turkish ultranationalists, plus what many Kurds consider a land grab in Syria’s Afrin province. Mr Erdogan has just over a month to chip away at that legacy. He may be too late.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 01:06:38 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Anish Kapoor’s menstrual art and the vexed question of appropriation]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/14/anish-kapoors-menstrual-art-and-the-vexed-question-of-appropriation]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190518_BKP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-14T16:54:40Z&quot;&gt;May 14th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BLOOD LEAKS and gushes from the art in Anish Kapoor’s new show at the Lisson Gallery in London. Almost literally in the case of his silicone and fibreglass reliefs: the gauze dangling beneath them is spattered with scarlet. In his oil paintings, meanwhile, blood-red spurts emanate from corporeal pinks and black cavities and orifices. Black is deathly, says Mr Kapoor, but also, like red, a colour of earth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Kapoor, a British artist who was born in Mumbai, is best known for his monumental sculptures (including a gigantic tubular installation in the Turbine Hall of the Tate Modern in 2002). His new series of paintings contemplate the idea of ritual, and the meaning of blood—which, as he puts it, is “associated with the abject and impure”. In particular, the paintings evoke menstrual blood. That motif raises another question, a version of which these days confronts artists in every genre and form. “Can a man deal with women’s issues?” Mr Kapoor muses. “Is a man allowed to?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Would that anxiety have occurred to him, say, 20 years ago? “We live in times of political correctness,” he responds, adding: “I am for it.” All the same, Mr Kapoor insists, “we have to manage it rather carefully”—in other words, being sure to safeguard artistic freedom. “Give me a break! What crap is that?” he asks of the notion that, for instance, a white artist should not explore a black person’s experience. Such leaps are the purpose of what he calls “the artistic imagination”. The only real question, he thinks, is whether the resulting work of art is good or bad. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of the shapes in his paintings—“partial objects”, Mr Kapoor calls them—are distinctly female, but the bodily references of others are more ambiguous. His white canvases suggest purity, and contamination, but also an androgynous disembodiment. In fact, while these paintings trespass on a particular “taboo” in their concern with menstruation, the curves and concavities of much of Mr Kapoor’s previous work likewise convey a preoccupation with bodies and sexuality. In his telling, the turn towards characteristically female forms goes well beyond him: he reckons that the entire history of art since Freud has involved a reorientation from phallic forms to the inward kind. In another of Mr Kapoor’s metaphors, instead of peering from the mouth of the cave up into the sky, artists have instead turned back into the shadows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The layout at the Lisson Gallery reinforces the theme of ritual. Several of the canvases hang around a pink onyx sculpture, in which twin ovoid shapes are encased in a sarcophagus or urn. As Mr Kapoor sees it, the blood in his paintings is pouring into the recesses of the stone, which to him resembles a &lt;em&gt;mikveh&lt;/em&gt; or Jewish ritual bath (he is Jewish, but also describes himself as a practising Buddhist). To this reviewer’s eye, the sculpture evokes a receptacle for the blood of a sacrifice; Mr Kapoor accepts that interpretation, too. Purity and defilement, sacrifice and cleansing: in art, as in life, contradictory things are often bound together.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Anish Kapoor” is showing at the Lisson Gallery, London, until June 22nd&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2019 00:07:29 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>