<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[British politics after Theresa May]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/24/british-politics-after-theresa-may]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_brp507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-24T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERESA MAY strode out of the door of 10 Downing Street in a crimson business suit and bowed to the inevitable. Having failed three times to get her Brexit deal through a hopelessly divided parliament, and confronted with a Tory insurrection over her proposed fourth attempt, she announced on May 24th that she would step down as leader of the Conservative Party and Britain’s prime minister.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It is and will always remain a matter of deep regret for me that I have not been able to deliver Brexit,” she declared. She then urged MPs to find the spirit of compromise. Had she left it there it might have been remembered as a dignified exit at the end of her dogged prime ministership. Instead she tried to set out her legacy—listing, among other things, measures to limit plastic waste—and only highlighted how little she managed to do. Then, as she gave thanks for the “honour of a lifetime”, a prime minister often derided as “Maybot” shed a tear and left.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She will step down as leader of the Conservative Party on June 7th. The Party will then begin the formal process for selecting a successor. Nominations will close in the week beginning June 10th, followed by several rounds of voting among MPs, a process that will last until the end of the month. The MPs will then send two names to party members who will vote on who they like most, with the result of their vote &amp;quot;announced before parliament rises for summer. Mrs May will remain as prime minister until a new leader is found. This means that she will act as host to President Donald Trump when he arrives in Britain for his state visit on June 3rd, and will attend the 75th anniversary of D-Day on June 6th, something on which she is known to put great value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leading Tories were quick to express their admiration for Mrs May—particularly for her determination and sense of duty. But there was something of a ritualistic quality to this: most Tories have been desperate to see the back of Mrs May for weeks. Thirty-six ministers resigned during her spell in office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mrs May’s resignation came after &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/23/another-british-prime-minister-is-destroyed-by-the-europe-question&quot;&gt;a surreal few days&lt;/a&gt; in British politics. On May 22nd she presented her revised EU withdrawal bill to the House of Commons, laboriously reading through the ten points that were supposed to overcome the House’s objections to the previous version. But it was clear that she had lost the confidence of both her government and party. The front bench around her was half-empty because the more pro-Brexit members of her cabinet were somewhere else discussing what to do next, and the benches behind her emptied as she spoke. This was not just a prime minister without authority but a prime minister without an audience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All this took place against the background of a European election that Britain should never have taken part in. Polls suggest that the Tories are due to come a poor fourth—one even hinted that they could get no more than 7% of the vote—and that Nigel Farage’s Brexit Party is likely to come first thanks to the votes of disillusioned Conservatives. It also took place against the background of a ticking clock. The European Union had offered Britain an extension of Article 50 (whose triggering began the Brexit process) to October 31st, so that it could find a route out of the impasse. But the government is now farther from finding that route than it was when the extension was granted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The immediate trigger for Mrs May’s departure was the failure of her revised withdrawal bill. But the bigger trigger was the general election that she called back in June 2017. Her instincts were right: increasing the Tories’ majority would have allowed her to increase her bargaining power with her party and ensure that she was not hostage to pro- or anti-Brexit factions. But the election was a debacle. The party produced a turgid manifesto that alienated voters with an ill-thought-out plan to make rich homeowners pay more for social care—a plan that was quickly dubbed the “dementia tax”. The party seriously underestimated Jeremy Corbyn’s appeal to the electorate and the quality of the Labour Party’s Momentum-powered political machine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The election campaign also underlined Mrs May’s weaknesses as a practical politician. She refused to take part in a leaders’ debate and instead sent Amber Rudd, whose father had just died, to act as her champion. Whenever she deigned to campaign she was wooden and awkward. Mrs May is an introvert in a profession that demands a willingness to mingle with people and make them feel good about themselves. She is also a rigid micro-manager in a business that is by nature fluid and open-ended. Mrs May’s instinct is to surround herself with a tiny coterie of advisers (who are completely dependent on her) and to plan everything out in detail. But this has repeatedly proven fatal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;British politics will now be consumed by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/23/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm&quot;&gt;the race to succeed Mrs May&lt;/a&gt;. Some 20 MPs have put their hats in the ring and started parading their families (and kitchens) before an exasperated public. The front-runner is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/23/choosing-boris-johnson-as-prime-minister-would-be-a-dangerous-gamble&quot;&gt;Boris Johnson&lt;/a&gt;, the former foreign secretary. Mr Johnson is the clear favourite among party members and among pro-Brexit MPs (Jacob Rees-Mogg, the head of the hardline European Research Group, has been hosting dinners for him). And he has also been doing a good job of reaching out to his party’s pro-Remain liberal wing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the rule-of-thumb in election races is that the favourite never wins the crown. Mr Johnson was also the clear favourite in the last leadership race, in 2016, but his bid imploded when his campaign manager, Michael Gove, decided that Mr Johson was not up to the job and decided to run himself. Mr Gove will hope to be a powerful contender this time. He has an impressive record of galvanising whatever departments he has run, from education to the environment, and recognises that the Conservative Party needs to do more than repeat its old mantras about unleashing market forces if it is to defeat Mr Corbyn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Messrs Johnson and Gove did more than any other Tories to win the Brexit vote for leavers. But they will have to contend with even purer Brexiteers, such as Dominic Raab and Andrea Leadsom, who will be looking for any sign of treason. They will also have to contend with senior cabinet ministers such as Jeremy Hunt, the foreign secretary who ran the health service for six years, and Sajid Javid, the home secretary. With Mr Javid fading of late, the race could end up pitching Mr Hunt as the safe pair of hands against Mr Johnson as the charismatic risk taker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/thismayhurt-britishpolitics&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Conservative Party as a whole likes nothing more than a leadership race. But whoever wins this one will face one of the most difficult situations of any prime minister in modern times. The new leader will confront a party that is bitterly divided over Brexit, with ultras determined to leave at any cost and moderates determined to prevent a no-deal Brexit. The new chief will also confront a party that is completely split about where to go in terms of broader policy: should the Conservative Party redouble its commitment to Thatcherism—the position of many hard-line Brexiteers—or should it re-embrace the One Nation tradition that was obscured by the rise of Thatcherism? One-nation Tories—who include some Brexiteers as well as Remainers—think that the Conservative Party needs to engage in a broad policy rethink if it is to address the problems revealed by the financial crisis and the subsequent rise of Mr Corbyn. Many advocate radical devolution, a more activist economic policy and a bold programme of house-building.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next leader will have to grapple with the same forces that have destroyed Mrs May: a country as well as a party that is torn over Brexit; a political system that is being pulled apart by the tension between representative and direct democracy; and a conflict with the European Union that, despite repeated statements to the contrary by Brexiteers, has most of the cards in its hand. Mrs May will not be the last prime minister to be brought to tears by Brexit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;See also:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/23/theresa-may-reaches-the-end-of-the-road&quot;&gt;Leader: Theresa May reaches the end of the road&lt;/a&gt; (May 23rd 2019)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 23:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“The Last Temptation of Boris Johnson” is a toothless satire]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/24/the-last-temptation-of-boris-johnson-is-a-toothless-satire]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_BKP514.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-24T14:31:32Z&quot;&gt;May 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FEW POLITICIANS like to be made fun of. Even fewer can stomach a character assassination. It takes a singular statesman to announce a leadership bid mere days after the premiere of a satirical play labelling him “one of the most divisive politicians of our time”. At the Park Theatre in London “The Last Temptation of Boris Johnson” dramatises the fateful dinner party in 2016 at which Mr Johnson (Will Barton), goaded by fellow Tory MP Michael Gove (Dugald Bruce-Lockhart) and Evgeny Lebedev (Tim Wallers), a media mogul, decided to campaign for Brexit. Its second act imagines the fall-out in 2029, when Johnson is weighing up his chances of gaining power on a platform of “Breentry”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Written by Jonathan Maitland, a former BBC journalist, the play’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.theguardian.com/politics/2018/jun/30/brexit-dramas-channel-four-stage-plays-facts&quot;&gt;stated aim&lt;/a&gt; is to peel back Mr Johnson’s buffoonish exterior to expose a man “substantially motivated by personal ambition”. Throughout the play the character is haunted by the ghosts of prime ministers past: Tony Blair, Margaret Thatcher and Winston Churchill (of whom Mr Johnson wrote a bestselling biography). Each of them brow-beats Boris with their own views on Brexit, and he seems to emerge from these encounters not as a scheming Machiavelli but as a man tormented by contradictory advice. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Barton uncannily replicates BoJo’s behavioural tics—the hair-ruffling, the bumbling gait, the posh speaking-voice and the ums and ahs—but he is given little else to work with. The play makes minimal effort to probe the man’s inner life, or question how affected these habits are (the hair-ruffling, it has been reported, is one of his ways of cultivating a disarming charm). Just before the interval, Johnson breaks from dinner to deliver a cod-Shakespearean soliloquy. At last he divulges a yearning for power but before his confession has had time to percolate, he distracts from it with humour. He mounts the kitchen counter, a bike helmet his crown, an orange his orb, a serving spoon his sceptre. The audience laughs, and any serious considerations of his character are forgotten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the play’s first act is toothless satire, its second is rip-roaring farce. History repeats itself—another maddening interview with the BBC, another sex scandal, another leadership bid—now with clownish exaggeration. The plot dissolves into incoherence: in one scene Johnson, Blair, Thatcher and Churchill perform the hokey-cokey; in another, Johnson gets into a televised punch-up with Gove. “The Last Temptation of Boris Johnson” ends with things crashing down, quite literally, around the titular character.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps the play disappoints because Mr Johnson is not the “perfect subject”, as the playwright claims, but rather an impossible one. Trying to skewer him is the equivalent of trying to nail jelly to a wall. The politician knows that ridicule cannot hurt you if you’re willing to laugh at yourself: from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.theguardian.com/politics/2012/aug/01/boris-johnson-zip-wire&quot;&gt;dangling on zip wires&lt;/a&gt; to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.bbc.co.uk/news/av/uk-34530932/boris-johnson-rugby-tackles-schoolboy-in-japan-his-other-sporting-slips&quot;&gt;rugby tackling ten-year-olds&lt;/a&gt;, he is always in on the joke. Mr Johnson refuses to be ashamed of his personal or professional failures. Satires only serve to boost Mr Johnson’s comedic capital and, with it, his political magnetism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Maitland has said that “if there were a leadership election during the run, I’d be jumping for joy” and it seems he will get his wish. Towards the end of “The Last Temptation of Boris Johnson”, the Conservative chief whip (Arabella Weir) assures Johnson that people would vote for him for one simple reason: they know who he is. Last week &lt;em&gt;Telegraph&lt;/em&gt; columnist Tim Stanley instructed the Tories to “send for Boris”, writing that “the fact that I don’t have to use his surname speaks volumes”; meanwhile, the &lt;em&gt;Sun&lt;/em&gt; insisted that “nobody else...is even recognisable to the voting public.” In that respect a retelling of his life and times—no matter how unsympathetic—will help, not hinder, him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“The Last Temptation of Boris Johnson” continues at the Park Theatre, London, until June 8th&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 22:40:34 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Life after Theresa May]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/24/life-after-theresa-may]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_brp507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-24T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERESA MAY strode out of the door of 10 Downing Street in a crimson business suit and bowed to the inevitable. Having failed three times to get her Brexit deal through a hopelessly divided parliament, and confronted with a Tory insurrection over her proposed fourth attempt, she announced on May 24th that she would step down as leader of the Conservative Party and Britain’s prime minister.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It is and will always remain a matter of deep regret for me that I have not been able to deliver Brexit,” she declared. She then urged MPs to find the spirit of compromise. Had she left it there it might have been remembered as a dignified exit at the end of her dogged prime ministership. Instead she tried to set out her legacy—listing, among other things, measures to limit plastic waste—and only highlighted how little she managed to do. Then, as she gave thanks for the “honour of a lifetime”, a prime minister often derided as “Maybot” shed a tear and left.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She will step down as leader of the Conservative Party on June 7th. The Party will then begin the formal process for selecting a successor. Nominations will close in the week beginning June 10th, followed by several rounds of voting among MPs, a process that will last until the end of the month. The MPs will then send two names to party members who will vote on who they like most, with the result of their vote &amp;quot;announced before parliament rises for summer. Mrs May will remain as prime minister until a new leader is found. This means that she will act as host to President Donald Trump when he arrives in Britain for his state visit on June 3rd, and will attend the 75th anniversary of D-Day on June 6th, something on which she is known to put great value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leading Tories were quick to express their admiration for Mrs May—particularly for her determination and sense of duty. But there was something of a ritualistic quality to this: most Tories have been desperate to see the back of Mrs May for weeks. Thirty-six ministers resigned during her spell in office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mrs May’s resignation came after &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/23/another-british-prime-minister-is-destroyed-by-the-europe-question&quot;&gt;a surreal few days&lt;/a&gt; in British politics. On May 22nd she presented her revised EU withdrawal bill to the House of Commons, laboriously reading through the ten points that were supposed to overcome the House’s objections to the previous version. But it was clear that she had lost the confidence of both her government and party. The front bench around her was half-empty because the more pro-Brexit members of her cabinet were somewhere else discussing what to do next, and the benches behind her emptied as she spoke. This was not just a prime minister without authority but a prime minister without an audience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All this took place against the background of a European election that Britain should never have taken part in. Polls suggest that the Tories are due to come a poor fourth—one even hinted that they could get no more than 7% of the vote—and that Nigel Farage’s Brexit Party is likely to come first thanks to the votes of disillusioned Conservatives. It also took place against the background of a ticking clock. The European Union had offered Britain an extension of Article 50 (whose triggering began the Brexit process) to October 31st, so that it could find a route out of the impasse. But the government is now farther from finding that route than it was when the extension was granted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The immediate trigger for Mrs May’s departure was the failure of her revised withdrawal bill. But the bigger trigger was the general election that she called back in June 2017. Her instincts were right: increasing the Tories’ majority would have allowed her to increase her bargaining power with her party and ensure that she was not hostage to pro- or anti-Brexit factions. But the election was a debacle. The party produced a turgid manifesto that alienated voters with an ill-thought-out plan to make rich homeowners pay more for social care—a plan that was quickly dubbed the “dementia tax”. The party seriously underestimated Jeremy Corbyn’s appeal to the electorate and the quality of the Labour Party’s Momentum-powered political machine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The election campaign also underlined Mrs May’s weaknesses as a practical politician. She refused to take part in a leaders’ debate and instead sent Amber Rudd, whose father had just died, to act as her champion. Whenever she deigned to campaign she was wooden and awkward. Mrs May is an introvert in a profession that demands a willingness to mingle with people and make them feel good about themselves. She is also a rigid micro-manager in a business that is by nature fluid and open-ended. Mrs May’s instinct is to surround herself with a tiny coterie of advisers (who are completely dependent on her) and to plan everything out in detail. But this has repeatedly proven fatal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;British politics will now be consumed by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/23/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm&quot;&gt;the race to succeed Mrs May&lt;/a&gt;. Some 20 MPs have put their hats in the ring and started parading their families (and kitchens) before an exasperated public. The front-runner is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/23/choosing-boris-johnson-as-prime-minister-would-be-a-dangerous-gamble&quot;&gt;Boris Johnson&lt;/a&gt;, the former foreign secretary. Mr Johnson is the clear favourite among party members and among pro-Brexit MPs (Jacob Rees-Mogg, the head of the hardline European Research Group, has been hosting dinners for him). And he has also been doing a good job of reaching out to his party’s pro-Remain liberal wing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the rule-of-thumb in election races is that the favourite never wins the crown. Mr Johnson was also the clear favourite in the last leadership race, in 2016, but his bid imploded when his campaign manager, Michael Gove, decided that Mr Johson was not up to the job and decided to run himself. Mr Gove will hope to be a powerful contender this time. He has an impressive record of galvanising whatever departments he has run, from education to the environment, and recognises that the Conservative Party needs to do more than repeat its old mantras about unleashing market forces if it is to defeat Mr Corbyn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Messrs Johnson and Gove did more than any other Tories to win the Brexit vote for leavers. But they will have to contend with even purer Brexiteers, such as Dominic Raab and Andrea Leadsom, who will be looking for any sign of treason. They will also have to contend with senior cabinet ministers such as Jeremy Hunt, the foreign secretary who ran the health service for six years, and Sajid Javid, the home secretary. With Mr Javid fading of late, the race could end up pitching Mr Hunt as the safe pair of hands against Mr Johnson as the charismatic risk taker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/thismayhurt-britishpolitics&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Conservative Party as a whole likes nothing more than a leadership race. But whoever wins this one will face one of the most difficult situations of any prime minister in modern times. The new leader will confront a party that is bitterly divided over Brexit, with ultras determined to leave at any cost and moderates determined to prevent a no-deal Brexit. The new chief will also confront a party that is completely split about where to go in terms of broader policy: should the Conservative Party redouble its commitment to Thatcherism—the position of many hard-line Brexiteers—or should it re-embrace the One Nation tradition that was obscured by the rise of Thatcherism? One-nation Tories—who include some Brexiteers as well as Remainers—think that the Conservative Party needs to engage in a broad policy rethink if it is to address the problems revealed by the financial crisis and the subsequent rise of Mr Corbyn. Many advocate radical devolution, a more activist economic policy and a bold programme of house-building.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next leader will have to grapple with the same forces that have destroyed Mrs May: a country as well as a party that is torn over Brexit; a political system that is being pulled apart by the tension between representative and direct democracy; and a conflict with the European Union that, despite repeated statements to the contrary by Brexiteers, has most of the cards in its hand. Mrs May will not be the last prime minister to be brought to tears by Brexit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;See also:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/23/theresa-may-reaches-the-end-of-the-road&quot;&gt;Theresa May reaches the end of the road&lt;/a&gt; (May 23rd 2019)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 22:40:33 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Judith Kerr, an extraordinary life]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/24/judith-kerr-an-extraordinary-life]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_BKP513.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-24T11:45:10Z&quot;&gt;May 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT WAS only ten days ago that Judith Kerr, at the age of 95, won Illustrator of the Year at the British Book Awards, the publishing trade’s annual celebration of the best in the business. Since Ms Kerr had been a heroine of British children’s literature from the publication of her first book, “The Tiger Who Came to Tea”, in 1968, one might reasonably say it was about time, too. But it was only the year before, in 2018, that the awards deigned to recognise illustrators at all. The first winner was Axel Scheffler, the illustrator of Julia Donaldson’s “Gruffalo” books.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, Ms Kerr never lacked for attention from her millions of adoring readers (and their parents). “The Tiger Who Came to Tea”—in which the eponymous feline arrives at the home of a girl named Sophie and proceeds to eat all the food in the house and drink all the water from the taps—had sold 1m copies by its author’s 94th year and has been the subject of a touring exhibition and a travelling stage show. Equally beloved was Ms Kerr’s stories about Mog, a family cat; the series finished with the ground-breaking “Goodbye Mog”, in which the beloved pet died. Ms Kerr was nearly 80 when the book was published in 2002 and said that she wanted to address the subject of death. At her age, she said, “you begin to think about those who are going to be left—the children, the grandchildren. I just wanted to say: Remember. Remember me. But do get on with your lives.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Kerr’s own life was an extraordinary one. Born in Berlin in 1923, her father was Alfred Kerr, a prominent theatre writer and a vocal critic of the Nazi regime. “He had a very strong sense of Jewish ethics,” Ms Kerr said in 2016. “He was brought up in the Jewish faith but he decided at about 20 that he didn’t believe in God. People used to ask us why we didn’t go to RE classes at school and, aged five, I used to say, ‘I am a freethinker!’ which is what I had been told I was.” Warned in 1933 that the Nazi regime was about to confiscate the family’s passports, they fled to Switzerland, then France, finally ending up in Great Britain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She trained at the Central School of Arts and Crafts, and while working as an art teacher met her husband, Nigel Kneale, a screenwriter. The couple had two children, Matthew and Tacy: there were a lot of visits to the zoo when the pair were young. Ms Kerr explained the genesis of her first book plainly: “I made it up to amuse my children because we were bored and because their father was away filming for very long days at a time.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 1971 she published “When Hitler Stole Pink Rabbit”, in which the Kerr family’s escape from Nazi Germany was transformed into a story of adventure rather than terror—Ms Kerr would say in later life that her parents concealed their own fear to ensure that was how she and her brother Michael perceived it at the time. It became the first volume in her “Out of Hitler Time” trilogy; in 2012 she received an OBE for services to children’s literature and Holocaust education.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children wrote to her from all over the world, a fact she found “hugely cheering”: “You feel that somebody is quite fond of you, even if you don’t know them!” She felt that her life had been an extraordinarily fortunate one. “I remember being asked when I first started trying to do books: ‘What do you want to do?’ And I said: ‘I just want to be able to do well enough that I can go on doing it.’” That is precisely what she did. Her last book, “The Curse of the School Rabbit”, will be published in June.    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 20:40:16 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[This May hurt: British politics]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/24/this-may-hurt-british-politics]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_blm508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-24T11:40:08Z&quot;&gt;May 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BRITAIN&amp;#x27;S PRIME minister has at last revealed the date she will &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/23/theresa-may-reaches-the-end-of-the-road&quot;&gt;step down&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. She had the unenviable task of delivering &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/23/another-british-prime-minister-is-destroyed-by-the-europe-question&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brexit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, which she failed to do. Her successor may fare no better. President &lt;strong&gt;Donald Trump has lost crucial legal battles over his &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/25/congress-is-winning-the-legal-battle-against-the-white-house&quot;&gt;financial records&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;, and more defeats are likely if the cases head to the Supreme Court. And, why is it that some &lt;strong&gt;music can give you &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/04/27/explaining-the-mystery-of-music&quot;&gt;chills&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;? Runtime: 20 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/thismayhurt-britishpolitics&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 20:40:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What Narendra Modi should do next, China’s pigs at risk, and confronting a history of slavery in Brazil]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/23/what-narendra-modi-should-do-next-chinas-pigs-at-risk-and-confronting-a-history-of-slavery-in-brazil]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_6.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-23T18:00:12Z&quot;&gt;May 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A SELECTION of three essential articles read aloud from the latest issue of The Economist. This week, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/25/what-narendra-modi-should-do-next&quot;&gt;India&lt;/a&gt;’s ruling Bharatiya Janata party has won a second landslide victory&lt;/strong&gt;. The prime minister, &lt;strong&gt;Narendra Modi&lt;/strong&gt;, should make better use of his latest triumph. Can &lt;strong&gt;China&lt;/strong&gt;, home to half the world’s pigs, curb the epidemic of &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/china/2019/05/25/african-swine-fever-hits-china-home-of-half-the-worlds-pigs&quot;&gt;African swine flu&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (06:28)? And&lt;strong&gt; Brazil &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;b&gt;faces painful disagreement over how to commemorate its history of &lt;/b&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/05/25/for-some-in-brazil-commemorating-slavery-is-vital&quot;&gt;slavery&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; (12:24). Runtime: 23 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-may23rd2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 02:41:28 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The race to become Britain’s next PM]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/23/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_woc777.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-23T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- data-infographic-js=&quot;/2019/tory-leadership/js/bundle.js&quot; data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/tory-leadership/css/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/tory-leadership/css/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE UNOFFICIAL &lt;/small&gt; race to succeed Theresa May as leader of the Conservative Party, and thus prime minister, has been going on ever since her disastrous election performance two years ago. On May 16th it moved up a gear when senior Tory backbenchers met Mrs May and extracted a promise that if, as expected, she fails in her fourth attempt to pass her Brexit bill in the House of Commons early next month, she will outline a timetable for her departure. The upshot is that 10 Downing Street is likely to have a new occupant this summer.
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The man most fancied to succeed her, Boris Johnson, a former foreign secretary and prominent Brexiteer, had earlier that day thrown his hat in the ring. “Of course I’m going for it,” he told an audience of insurance brokers in Manchester. Expect more candidates to break cover over the course of the next few weeks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Betfair Exchange, a gambling website, has been tracking punters’ predictions on the next Tory leader. According to the wisdom of the crowd, a handful of candidates stand out.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p &gt;Source: Betfair Exchange&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
Adrian Wooldridge, our political editor, assesses the chances of the leading Conservative politicians hoping to take the top job in this short film
&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ychDrZ2QzlE&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 23:40:11 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China is surprisingly carbon-efficient—but still the world’s biggest emitter]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/25/china-is-surprisingly-carbon-efficient-but-still-the-worlds-biggest-emitter]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_gdc901.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190525_GDC901_emissions/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;W&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;ITH ITS&lt;/small&gt; four-tiered smog warnings and lethal dumps of toxic waste, China has become Exhibit A for the environmental costs of economic development. Its growing meat consumption and reliance on fossil fuels have also made it a focus for people worried about climate change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In one sense, China’s reputation as the bellows of “hothouse Earth” is overblown. Since 1850 countries with a &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; per head of $12,000-16,000 in 2019 dollars have produced a population-weighted average of 10.6 tonnes of carbon dioxide-equivalent gases per person per year. In 2016 China’s &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; per head was $14,000, and it emitted just 9.3 tonnes per person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, China pollutes far less per person than Western countries did at the same stage of development. When America, France, Britain and Germany had incomes similar to modern China’s, they relied on inefficient power stations and cars, and spewed out 16.6 tonnes per person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The combination of China’s huge population and rapid &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; growth has nonetheless made it the world’s biggest emitter of carbon. China is predicted to produce 16bn tonnes of greenhouse gases in 2030—four times the entire world’s output in 1900.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To prevent the stock of greenhouse gases in the atmosphere from reaching levels likely to cause disastrous warming, China must do better than merely beating the past records of richer countries. Instead, it will need an unprecedented decline in emissions per head—at least to the more carbon-efficient level of similarly rich Latin American economies, and ideally onto the trajectory of poorer Asian giants like India and Indonesia, which rely less on heavy industry and manufacturing. Those countries, perched at the sweltering latitudes where farmers will be most hurt by climate change, must in turn work out how to reach upper-middle-income status without replicating China’s emissions path.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To their credit, Chinese authorities, spurred by public concern about air pollution, have prioritised green policies, such as switching from coal-fired power stations to renewable sources and setting up an emissions-trading system. China’s annual rate of emissions growth has fallen from 9.3% in 2002-11 to 0.6% in 2012-16. The waning of its cement-intensive construction boom should slow emissions further. But it will take more than incremental gains to stave off severe warming.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/source.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/source.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p &gt;Sources: Climate Action Tracker; Climate Watch; University of Groningen Growth and Development Centre; UN Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change
&lt;/p&gt;


&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/20190525_GDC901_emissions/fix.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190525_GDC901_emissions/fix.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Graphic detail&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Not-so-cold comfort&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 21:40:25 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Once Upon a Time...in Hollywood” is entertaining but empty]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/23/once-upon-a-timein-hollywood-is-entertaining-but-empty]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_BKP512.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-23T12:07:18Z&quot;&gt;May 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EVERY ONE of Quentin Tarantino’s films has been a love letter to pop culture in general and to cinema in particular, but none of those odes has been as explicit or as gushing as “Once Upon a Time...in Hollywood”. A two-and-three-quarter-hour tribute to Tinseltown, the film is a loosely bound anthology of vignettes extolling the charms of the dream factory as it was in 1969: the cars, the clothes, the on-set camaraderie. It’s a sleepy and ultimately happy comedy—too happy, perhaps, given that it stirs fact and fiction together, and features the Charles Manson cult and the murder of Sharon Tate. Mr Tarantino is so deeply in love with the movie business that he can’t peer at its dark side for long before returning to its sunlit swimming pools and studio backlots. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The film begins with a fun black-and-white clip of an actor and his stunt double being interviewed in the 1950s. The actor is Rick Dalton (Leonardo DiCaprio), the earnest, buffoonish star of a hit TV series about a sharp-shooting bounty hunter in the Wild West. The stunt double is Cliff Booth (Brad Pitt), Rick’s easy-going best friend. When the audience sees the duo again, a decade has passed—and what a difference a decade makes. Rick has been reduced to humiliating cameo appearances on variety shows. Cliff, meanwhile, hasn’t had any stunt work for a while, but he sticks by Rick as his driver, handyman and drinking buddy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their bromance is the heart of “Once Upon a Time...in Hollywood”, although it might have been more affecting if it was clearer what Cliff got out of it. After he has chauffeured Rick back to his house in the hills every evening, he gets out of the actor’s Cadillac, gets into his own battered car and drives back to his trailer to feed his dog and eat food out of a packet. He shows no sign whatsoever of resentment, and no desire for companionship that isn’t provided by a dog or an employer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is typical of the film’s mellow mood. Early on, an agent (Al Pacino) tries to persuade Rick to make spaghetti westerns in Italy, but he has to be the kindest and most honest agent who has ever been portrayed on screen. Roman Polanski (Rafal Zawierucha) moves in next door to Rick with his starlet wife, the aforementioned Tate (Margot Robbie). There is a whisper that Tate’s ex, Jay Sebring (Emile Hirsch), is planning to steal her away, but Mr Tarantino doesn’t elaborate: the director prefers simply to gaze at Tate as she strolls around in her white mini-skirt and boots. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The film’s most interesting and unsettling conceit is that the ranch where Rick and Cliff once shot their TV show is now occupied by Charles Manson and his brainwashed acolytes, and Cliff suspects the ranch’s owner (Bruce Dern) has been kidnapped—or worse—by the interlopers. But, again, Mr Tarantino prefers to see the funny side of the situation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He has no truck with the pitch-black cynicism of “Mulholland Drive”, “The Player” and all of the other great films about the scandals, exploitation and sheer craziness of La La Land. Indulging in dewy-eyed nostalgia with all of his usual obsessive attention to detail, Mr Tarantino lets the good times roll instead. And when the inevitable orgy of gory violence finally begins, even that is nowhere near as horrifying as you might fear. Mr Tarantino’s film is entertaining, of course, in its rambling, jokey way, but it doesn’t have much to say except that things often work out better in the movies than they do in real life. An escapist homage to the escapism industry, “Once Upon a Time...in Hollywood” is as much of a fairytale as its title implies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Once Upon a Time...in Hollywood” will be released in America on July 26th and in Britain on August 14th&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 21:40:24 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“A re-election of a kind that no one has won in India before”—Narendra Modi&#x27;s landslide]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/23/a-re-election-of-a-kind-that-no-one-has-won-in-india-before-narendra-modis-landslide]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/bjp1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-23T11:30:51Z&quot;&gt;May 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;NARENDRA MODI&amp;#x27;S &lt;/strong&gt;BJP party appears to have secured a convincing re-election victory. What will that mean for India and the region? Also, we look back on &lt;strong&gt;the life of Bob Hawke, a former Australian prime minister&lt;/strong&gt; who convinced the world that his country deserved a prominent place in global politics. And, why &lt;strong&gt;Silicon Valley’s latest obsession is optimising &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/18/sleepless-in-silicon-valley&quot;&gt;sleepy time&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Runtime: 21min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/repeatperformance-india-selection&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 21:40:23 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>