<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Populists fall short of expectations in the European elections]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/charlemagnes-notebook/2019/05/26/populists-fall-short-of-expectations-in-the-european-elections]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_blp903.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-26T22:26:45Z&quot;&gt;May 26th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THAT right-wing populism has gained ground in Europe in recent years is a well-established fact. A glance at the continent&amp;#x27;s recent electoral history shows that much: the Lega dominates Italy’s politics, Marine Le Pen made it to the run-off of the French presidential election in 2017, Law and Justice (PiS) runs Poland and elsewhere smaller parties from Alternative for Germany to the Danish People’s Party and Vox in Spain are shaping their countries’ politics. All of which is a far cry from the settled European party landscape of 15 or 20 years ago. But that much is known. The question now is: in what direction is European politics moving and at what pace?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This evening’s result in the European elections provides some answers to that, and caveat the more excitable commentaries about the rise of nationalists in Europe. Turnout is up for the first time ever, and at 51% higher than in any European election since 1994. And yes, the right-populists have done well again. The Lega is first in Italy, Ms Le Pen’s National Rally has narrowly beaten Emmanuel Macron to first place in France, PiS came first in Poland despite running against a mostly unified opposition ticket. But it is also clear that the mighty, breakneck populist surge of a couple of years ago—with Britain voting to leave the EU, populists topping polls all over the continent and a cataclysmic nationalist takeover threatening—is over. Nationalists are now consolidating their gains and settling into a much broader pattern: that of fragmentation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consider the numbers. Ms Le Pen’s result is down on 2014, the previous European election. So is the Austrian Freedom Party and, more drastically, the Danish People’s Party and the Party for Freedom in the Netherlands. It is true that some of the latter’s support has switched to Forum for Democracy, a rival right-populist outfit. But this too underperformed expectations and the overall seat-share of Dutch Eurosceptics has halved. Alternative for Germany also disappointed its boosters: on 10.8% it only modestly increased its support on 2014 and did less well than in the 2017 Bundestag election. The Lega has made big gains, but it too seems to have done worse than was generally expected and its wins only just make up for losses elsewhere. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall the three Eurosceptic or hard-right groups in the European Parliament have, according to the parliament’s own projection, increased their seat share from 21% to 23%. Hardly a surge and oddly static after five years that have seen Europe face a migration crisis, the Brexit vote, terror attacks and the wholesale fragmentation of the continent’s politics. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of that fragmentation there was much more evidence. The Green group is projected to swell in size from 52 seats to 70 seats, thanks especially to the German Green party’s 21% showing (taking second place and overtaking the doughty Social Democrats to become the largest party on the German left). The centrist Alliance of Liberals and Democrats for Europe will grow from 69 to a projected 101 seats, with Mr Macron’s Renaissance joining and immediately becoming its largest member. Meanwhile the two big losers are the big-tent party families that have together run Europe as an informal “grand coalition”: the centre-right European People’s Party (EPP) and the centre-left Socialists and Democrats (S&amp;amp;D). Their joint tally falls from 401 seats (54%) to a projected 325 seats (43%).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This fact will shape the next European Parliament. For one thing, the EPP and S&amp;amp;D have lost their majority. Expect more ad hoc coalitions around case-by-case issues. And where a “grand coalition” of the centre is needed—on the upcoming approval of a new European Commission president, for example—it will have to be much broader than before and draw in liberals and even greens. The old two-party establishment has become at least a three-and-a-half-party establishment. And it is looking much less established, in any case. European politics is churning, splitting and recombining in new ways and directions. The long-term rise of the right-wing populists is part of that but not, in this election, a particularly new or dynamic one. Tonight’s crucial trend is not a populist surge but the revelation of the full scale of Europe’s political fragmentation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2019 07:18:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The case for Margrethe Vestager]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/charlemagnes-notebook/2019/05/25/the-case-for-margrethe-vestager]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-25T20:09:25Z&quot;&gt;May 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPEAN POLITICS is a febrile place. The old centre-right European People’s Party (EPP) and the old centre-left Party of European Socialists (PES) have long dominated the continent’s politics but are now ceding their dominance. Tomorrow’s European election results will probably show that the two are the big losers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Who should replace them? Matteo Salvini, Italy’s far-right leader, will marshal a nationalist right-wing party. Emmanuel Macron, France’s president, will try to found a liberal pro-European force. Neither will succeed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mainstream national leaders will want a figure who can get things done, who is acceptable to the centre-right European People’s Party; to the centre-left Party of European Socialists and possibly to liberal and green camps. They will look for someone who crosses old ideological boundaries and who can make Europe relevant at a time when the continent is declining in global significance. They will stumble upon Margrethe Vestager.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Vestager has served as education, interior and economy minister of Denmark despite belonging to a tiny left-liberal party. As European Commissioner since 2014 she has applied both a liberal sense of consumer rights and a centre-left commitment to defending the little guy to the task of regulating technology giants. She has taken on tax dodgers, infringers of personal privacy and market distorters and defeated them all. Thrusting machos from Silicon Valley have turned up in her office, berated her and come off the worse.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The EU in 2019 faces an array of security and economic threats. It needs a powerful, efficient leader with experience of the Commission and a sense of how the world is changing. It needs a leader who can stand up for Europe and initiate legislation defending its citizens. It needs someone acceptable to left and right, north and south. Many candidates will put their names forward. Ms Vestager ticks all the boxes. Europe would be foolish to overlook her.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 05:40:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Onward Christian soldiers]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/05/25/onward-christian-soldiers]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_BLP508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-25T20:30:00Z&quot;&gt;May 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IF ALL THE people involved were civilians, there would be nothing especially controversial about a popular website, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://prayatlunch.us/&quot;&gt;PLUS&lt;/a&gt;, which invites American Christians to “pray at lunchtime for the United States”. But the site’s main author, John Teichert, describes himself as an “active duty brigadier-general who has served in the United States Air Force” since 1994.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For critics like Mikey Weinstein, president of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.militaryreligiousfreedom.org/&quot;&gt;Military Religious Freedom Foundation&lt;/a&gt; (MRFF), which campaigns for church-state separation in the armed forces, this sort of thing epitomises an ever-escalating trend. In the era of Donald Trump, they allege, fundamentalist Christians in uniform have felt freer than ever to test the boundaries set by the constitution and take advantage of their rank when disseminating their own reading of their faith and of American history. The MRFF is not alone in this complaint: last year, at least two other secularist groups formally protested to the Pentagon over the fact that service personnel were being bamboozled into attending religious ceremonies, compromising their own religious freedom.    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In several ways, the PLUS website is carefully crafted. It offers the disclaimer that “the views presented are those of the author and do not necessarily represent the views of the Department of Defence or its components.” The reference to lunch suggests that people are not being asked to give up professional time. The author’s surname is not given, although it is an open secret. The Pentagon has defended the website as a legitimate use of spare time by the officer. On the other hand, as commander of fighter-aircraft testing at Edwards Air Force Base, a giant facility in California, the brigadier-general enjoys huge personal authority and charisma. The MRFF says it is continuing to complain about his site, despite repeated rebuffs from the Pentagon, at the urging of at least 40 service personnel, including believing Christians who say they feel intimidated by the knowledge that one of their commanders is propagating one particular version of the faith.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Weinstein describes this version as “dominionist” Christianity, the idea that earthly institutions should be harnessed to spread the Christian cause. This often goes hand in hand with a particular interpretation of America’s earliest years, which insists that the founding fathers planned to establish a Christian nation, not a religiously neutral one. (Secularist historians disagree.) The PLUS website urges followers to pray for America &amp;quot;to return to its biblical foundation&amp;quot;. It also advocates prayers for &amp;quot;Bible-preaching churches, pastors and missionaries&amp;quot;, in language often used by non-conformist Christians to differentiate themselves from, say, Catholics who stress the authority of the church as opposed to the Bible alone. Further supplications are proposed for the unborn and for Israel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In years past, Mr Weinstein says, this way of thinking was especially prevalent in the Air Force, but now he says he observes it in all branches of the American services. He finds it widespread in elite special-forces units, such as the Navy Seals. “The closer you get to the tip of the spear, the more dominionist thinking there is.”  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As he uses the term, dominionist Christians should be distinguished carefully from evangelicals, although the two categories do overlap. Many evangelical Christians fully respect the principle of church-state separation and correspondingly keep their faith and its propagation within boundaries that are designed to respect the freedom of others. Among the 60,000 or so supporters of the MRFF, there are many evangelicals, according to Mr Weinstein. Some turn to the MRFF because they feel bullied over religious matters by commanders or chaplains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About 3,000 chaplains serve the American forces. The overwhelming majority are Protestant, and only a handful cater to minority faiths such as Judaism, Hinduism and Islam. Within the Protestant contingent, a vocal subset make no secret of the fact that they regard chaplaincy as an opportunity for missionary work, rather than for catering to those who already profess their faith.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As in many areas of American life, managing religious affairs in the armed forces will always involve a careful equilibrium between two principles enshrined in the constitution’s First Amendment: the free exercise of faith, and a bar on the state establishment of any particular religion. In that spirit, an official instruction to Air Force officers tells them to:  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;…balance constitutional protections, for their own free exercise of religion, including individual expressions of religious beliefs, and the constitutional prohibition against governmental establishment of religion…They must ensure their words and actions cannot reasonably be construed to be official endorsing or disapproving of, or extending preferential treatment for any faith, belief, or absence of belief.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;This seems to imply that officers should never use their professional time, their work e-mail accounts or the authority of their rank to spread one particular idea about religion. But in practice this principle is widely violated, complains Mr Weinstein, himself a retired Air Force officer.         &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As one example he offers, a recent legal determination by the Pentagon, winkled out by the MRFF, lays down what officers can say at change-of-command ceremonies or personal promotion celebrations. In rather surreal language, it says that in the former kind of ritual, commanders may “briefly thank a Supreme Being (either generally, such as Providence, that Almighty Being, our Lord, or the Supreme Author of All Good; or specifically, such as Allah, Brahman, Christ, Ganesh, God, Yahweh, or even Beelzebub)”. A celebrant may also be invited to offer a prayer to one of these beings.    &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Weinstein and his supporters believe that these concessions to expressions of faith by commanders are mistaken. The promotion ceremony, while regarded as an individual milestone, is nonetheless conducted in uniform, he observes.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, whatever the successes chalked up by the perceived dominionists, there are some countervailing trends in the armed forces. One is the increasing acceptance of LGBT service personnel and same-sex relationships. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2015 it was announced that the armed forces&amp;#x27; equal-opportunity policies applied to gays and lesbians. Two years ago a married lesbian woman, Kristin Goodwin, was named as commandant of cadets at the US Air Force Academy. Religious conservatives grumbled that to have got so far, she could not have been honest about her sexual orientation during her early career. (In fact, the “don’t ask, don’t tell” policy, which military authorities applied in relation to sexuality between 1994 and 2011, would have spared her any difficult questions.)  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last month it was announced that Brigadier-General Goodwin had been removed from her post, pending the investigation of a complaint about which no details have been disclosed. There is no suggestion whatever that her sexual orientation was the basis of that complaint, but her removal was announced prominently on religious conservative websites. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As America prepares for Memorial Day commemorations of its war dead on May 27th, it is fair to say that battles over religion and culture are raging deep inside the armed forces, as in so many other arenas. And for what it may be worth, Brigadier-General Teichert has added Mr Weinstein to the list of people in need of those lunch-time prayers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 03:40:43 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[American history in black and white]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/news/2019/05/25/american-history-in-black-and-white]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_opp507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-25T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 25th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FEW COUNTRIES erect monuments to their failed secessionist movements, particularly those premised on the right to enslave people. But, then, America is an exceptional country. Many American cities and states are debating the propriety of monuments to the Confederacy—the band of southern states that fought a civil war over the right to maintain slaves. In few places is the controversy so searing as in Montgomery, the state capital of Alabama. This had served as the confederate capital before it was moved to Richmond, Virginia, a few months later.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;I visited Montgomery to report on poverty in the Black Belt—the fertile region just south and west of the city once filled with vast cotton plantations worked by slaves. After the civil war, which the South lost, things improved only marginally for rural blacks. New forms of subjugation took the place of slavery: sharecropping; the indentured labour of prisoners; lynching; the suppression of black voters; and racial segregation. Alabama was at the forefront of all these. In the Black Belt I interviewed descendants of slaves who were living without proper sanitation, with untreated sewage draining into their backyards.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;It is no accident that Montgomery was a focal point of the civil-rights movement in the 1960s. It is where Martin Luther King Jr preached, where Rosa Parks refused to give up her bus seat and one of the places where Freedom Riders were viciously attacked when they challenged segregation on buses.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;The National Memorial for Peace and Justice, known as the national lynching memorial, is a powerful testament to the racial brutality endured by blacks well after the civil war. Lynching was tolerated and sometimes abetted by local officials, and watched by crowds of thousands for sheer entertainment.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;The memorial documents 4,400 people killed. Their names are etched on large iron steles, some suspended from a roof, others laid on the ground stretching far into the distance. The identities of many more victims are unknown. The site’s museum traces the journey of blacks towards racial equality, often distressingly plagued by setbacks.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;So to move on to the First White House of the Confederacy, just a 20-minute walk away, is bewildering. It stands just off the capitol grounds, a few blocks from the church at which King preached. Jefferson Davis, the first and only president of the Confederacy, used this as his White House for four months.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;It is, in effect, a monument to &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;white victimhood&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span&gt;. There is scarcely a mention of slavery to be found among its displays. One room features the Davis family Bible, which was found by a Northern soldier during the “war between the states” (a euphemism for the civil war), and later returned to the family. A docent tells visitors about the conditions of Davis’s imprisonment after the war, describing it as tantamount to “torture”. Two women listening to him coo in sympathy. The elegant armchair sent to him while in captivity sits on display.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;An approving full-length obituary from a Mississippi newspaper sits on the wall, subtitled “An American Patriot”. It declares that “No man laboured harder to preserve the union than did Davis. Only when it became obvious that the terrible schism was inevitable did he consent reluctantly to accept the presidency of the confederacy.” The idea of the Lost Cause—that the war was over northern aggression, states’ rights or chivalric duty, not the preservation of slavery—is widely believed. It is given official succour by places such as the Confederate Memorial Monument, on the grounds of the state capitol. Beneath the statue of a Confederate soldier an inscription declares: “The knightliest of the knightly race/who since the lamps of old/have kept the lamp of chivalry/alight in the hearts of gold”.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;The memorial had been adorned with four Confederate flags until the massacre of black churchgoers in Charleston, South Carolina, in 2015. Thereafter several states, including Alabama, took down the flags from official sites because of their association with white supremacism.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Still, it is surreal for a city to commemorate both the achievements of the civil-rights movement—documenting the white-supremacist rhetoric and violence that attempted to arrest it—while also preserving Confederate memorials that whitewash the underlying cause of the conflict. Some will plead that these Confederate monuments should stand as they are for the sake of historical preservation. But they do not honestly preserve history. They distort it by omitting any mention of slavery and transmogrifying those who fought to preserve it into men of Arthurian virtue.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Other acts seem hard to justify, too. Alabama, along with Mississippi, still jointly celebrates Martin Luther King Jr Day, a federal holiday, at the same time as Robert E Lee Day, a state holiday that commemorates the birthday of the commander of the Confederate army. To this day, there remains a Jefferson Davis high school in Montgomery, even though &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.publicschoolreview.com/jefferson-davis-high-school-profile&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;94% of its pupils are black&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;I am not the first to notice this jarring juxtaposition. But having just witnessed at first hand the long and mournful legacy of slavery—in which poverty, bad schooling and dire job prospects are transmitted from one generation to the next—the contrast struck me all the harder.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot;&gt;&lt;span&gt;Fifty-five years after the passage of landmark civil-rights and anti-poverty legislation, it has become easy and even popular to describe the poverty of black Americans as a consequence of their own bad decisions. Their poverty is a complicated phenomenon—too complicated to reduce to determinism of the historical kind (which blames it entirely on slavery) or of the present-day variety (which blames it on sloth). Even so, for the state to sponsor uncritical and ahistorical Confederate memorials is to deny entirely the historical roots of black deprivation—thereby making it conveniently easy to ignore.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 May 2019 01:40:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why we should embrace big business]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/05/24/why-we-should-embrace-big-business]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_OPP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-24T17:59:12Z&quot;&gt;May 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IF THERE is one truth that millennials hold to be self-evident, it is that big business is bad. Soulless corporations pollute the planet, overpay their bosses and gouge consumers. Big tech turns us into screen addicts. Big Pharma makes life-saving drugs unaffordable. Big banks sell us dodgy mortgages. One cannot help wondering, listening to the chatter on social media, whether corporations ever do anything right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actually, they do, says Tyler Cowen, an economist at George Mason University in Virginia. In his latest book “Big Business: A Love Letter to an American Anti-Hero,” he argues that many of the gripes about business are ill-informed. And where there are real concerns, such as fraud or excessive concentrations of power, he believes that wise regulation can minimise the harm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Cowen has earned a reputation as a shrewd and iconoclastic thinker. In his blog Marginal Revolution he relishes debunking junk economics with data. &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s Open Future initiative is publishing an excerpt from “Big Business” that presents the arc of his argument. We probe it further in a short interview that follows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*       *      *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp504.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp504.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp504.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp504.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp504.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp504.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp504.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp504.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp504.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;From “Big Business: A Love Letter to an American Anti-Hero” by Tyler Cowen (St. Martin&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;b&gt;’&lt;/b&gt;&lt;strong&gt;s Press, 2019)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We live in an age when the reputation of business is under siege. Among Democrats, for instance, the word “socialism” now polls better than does “capitalism.” But Republicans, while they pay greater lip service to some business ideals, are not in practice much better. Many of them have quite readily followed President Donald Trump into his attacks on free trade, immigration, outsourcing, and the American media (which is labeled “the enemy of the people”)—all fundamentally anti-business stances.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Business, quite simply, has become underrated, and thus I am writing a contrarian book that ought not to be contrarian at all. All of the criticisms one might mount against the corporate form—some of which are valid—pale in contrast to two straightforward and indeed essential virtues. First, business makes most of the stuff we enjoy and consume. Second, business is what gives most of us jobs. The two words that follow most immediately from the world of business are “prosperity” and “opportunity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Without business we would not have:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* Ships, trains, and cars&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* Electricity, lighting, and heating equipment&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* Most of our food supply&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* Most of our lifesaving pharmaceuticals&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* Clothes for our children&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* Our telephones and smartphones&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* The books we love to read&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* The ability to access, more or less immediately, so much of the world’s online information&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And let’s not forget your paycheck. “Meeting payroll,” to invoke a now old-fashioned phrase, is nothing less than a heroic act. Someone or some group put in the hard work and thought up the innovations required to create a company from scratch—I know it’s easy enough to take this for granted if you aren’t the one who did it. On top of the paycheck, jobs are among our biggest sources of pride and a significant way to meet friends and establish social networks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[...]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We can all admit that we are a nation sorely in need of virtue, specifically in our political realm. The growing polarization of today’s politics has made our government at best hopelessly sclerotic and at worst prone to unpredictable lurches. This polarization has also spurred out-of-control political correctness and censorship, rampant racism and injustice, new waves of violent marches and shootings, and an array of indictments and corruption charges. Many features of contemporary America are wonderful, including the high level of trust in the corporate sector, but the weirdness in our government has been rising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, the world of American business has never been more productive, more tolerant, and more cooperative. It is not just a source of GDP and prosperity; it is a ray of normalcy and predictability in its steady focus on producing what can be profitably sold to customers. Successful businesses grow dynamically, but they also try to create oases of stability and tolerance in which they can perfect their production methods. These oases help to attract and retain talent and make it possible for businesses to offer consumers a steady stream of “comfort products.” Business helps carve out spaces for love, friendship, creativity, and human caring by producing the resources that make our lives not just tolerable but comfortable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;American big business in particular has led the way toward making America more socially inclusive. McDonald’s, General Electric, Procter &amp;amp; Gamble, and many of the major tech companies, among others, were defining health and other legal benefits for same-sex partners before the Supreme Court legalized gay marriage. Apple, Pfizer, Microsoft, Deutsche Bank, PayPal, and Marriott, among others, spoke out or protested the North Carolina law that sought to specify which restrooms transgender people had to use; the outcry led to the eventual repeal of that law. This push for tolerance shouldn’t come as any surprise. Big business has lots of customers and relies on the value of brand names. It doesn’t want any group of those customers to feel put out or discriminated against or to have cause for complaint, not least because we live in an age of social media. Profit maximization alone—not to mention the consciences of some CEOs—puts big business these days on the side of inclusion and tolerance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Larger firms, in particular, which you can think of as wildly successful businesses and thus embodiments of the logic of business, tend to be more tolerant of employee personal tastes than smaller firms. A local baker might be reluctant to make a wedding cake for a gay couple, but Sara Lee, which tries to build very broadly based national markets for its products, is happy to sell to all. The bigger companies need to protect their broader reputations and recruit large numbers of talented workers, including those from minority groups. They can’t survive and grow just by cultivating a few narrow networks of local white men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have a complaint about America today, and it is simple: we don’t love business enough.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[...]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’m here to speak up for business, to persuade you that it deserves more of your love and less hate. Perhaps, like you, I am not entirely comfortable with ceding so much of the daily human realm to apparently selfish, profit-maximizing, and even sometimes corrupt entities, but on closer examination this is a better bargain than it might seem at first. Indeed, at its best, business gives our lives more scope for the heroic and the noble, as we can use the outputs of business to satisfy our own creative desires and to better our lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ll argue that a lot of the most common criticisms of American business don’t stand up to scrutiny. For instance, it’s often claimed that American business is too focused on quarterly earnings statements, at the expense of a longer-run perspective. But in fact there is plenty of evidence that companies can think long-term when appropriate. Sometimes short-run problems are easier or more important to solve, or they are the bridge to longer-run success, and the evidence at hand indicates that American business does a pretty good job of looking to the future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then there’s the question of American CEO pay, which Edward Luce, a Financial Times columnist (and a friend of mine), described on Twitter as “unconscionable.” American CEOs are paid much more than they used to be, but these pay hikes have pretty much moved in tandem with the size and valuations of the firms they manage. Contrary to common claims, it is hard to establish that CEOs as a whole are ripping off their shareholders with manipulated pay packages, as a look at the numbers will show that high compensation is the price of attracting top talent. Running a large corporation involves taking on more roles than ever before, including media, government, and public relations, formulating a vision, understanding consumers and communicating to them, building cross-cultural global strategies, working with governments, and keeping the company out of trouble, in addition to having a lot of sector-specific expertise. That limits the number of eligible candidates who might succeed at the job and thus it boosts their pay, according to basic principles of supply and demand. Today’s CEOs are literally superachievers, and it should come as no surprise that they are compensated accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the most frequently cited whipping boys is the financial sector, which is portrayed as too large and out of control. The reality is that the financial sector has held to a fairly constant 2 percent share of American wealth, though of course that wealth has grown and so has finance with it. The ability of American finance to mobilize savings into riskier forms of equity and venture capital has brought Americans hundreds of billions of dollars in value each year, and those gains significantly outweigh the costs typically attributed to the financial sector. Nor is the financial sector draining the American economy of all its talent for other endeavors, as evidenced by the rise of American manufacturing output to ever higher levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most of all, business is criticized for being fraudulent and ripping us off. While there is plenty of fraud in business, the commercial sector isn’t any more fraudulent than individuals in other capacities, and it may even be somewhat less fraudulent. Business can make us better people—for example, by teaching us how to cooperate better—and the best evidence indicates that, on net, businesses do not make us worse compared with our participation in other institutions. A lot of us were somewhat dishonest to begin with, and if you have doubts, just look at the individual lies and misrepresentations in online dating profiles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So many of the problems with business are in fact problems with us, and they reflect the underlying and fairly universal imperfections of human nature. Yet we respond to this truth somewhat irrationally. While we suspect business of wrongdoing, at the same time we expect corporations to give us jobs and take care of us, to give us a network of friends, to solve our social problems, and to give us risk-free consumption experiences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[...]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Particularly now in the age of social media, which allows direct connections with consumers and offers them the chance to provide direct feedback when things go wrong, the most successful businesses have a kind of messianic view of their role in society—venerating the delivery of goods and services to the consumer, or perhaps promoting a particular vision of how society ought to be. Workers wish to believe their toil is saving the environment, fighting poverty, and strengthening America as a nation. A business that instills in its workers and managers a sincere belief in such goals has a better chance of building a durable competitive advantage than a business that does not. It will attract more consumer loyalty and better and more cooperative partners at the business-to-business level. Think of it this way: Who wants to marry someone who is always selfishly seeking to optimize happiness from the marriage?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ayn Rand showed a deep insight into the character of successful business when she emphasized that it can be a vehicle for the achievement of heroic goals. The character of Hank Rearden in Rand’s novel Atlas Shrugged stressed the dignity, honor, and reason involved in good productive work, and he came to see it as the very foundation of America’s greatness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is often those business leaders who are religious or have strong ideologies of another kind who grasp most clearly the relevance of a business having a mission above and beyond profit. They understand that the business and religious or ideological sides of their lives are by no means totally separate. They understand they can do best by their shareholders—and the broader society—by tying together the business, religious, ethical, and ideological perspectives in one bundle. […]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other words, business at its best is a fundamentally ethical enterprise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;__________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Excerpted from “Big Business: A Love Letter to an American Anti-Hero” by Tyler Cowen. Copyright © 2019 by the author and reprinted with permission of St. Martin&lt;/em&gt;&lt;i&gt;’&lt;/i&gt;&lt;em&gt;s Press.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*       *      *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;An interview with Tyler Cowen&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;The concentration of power of business seems intense. Do we need to make capitalism more competitive, and if so, how?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp505.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp505.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp505.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp505.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp505.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp505.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp505.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp505.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190525_opp505.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tyler Cowen:&lt;/strong&gt; I see concentration of business in some sectors as a problem, but by no means all. For most goods and services, Americans have far more choice, choice of supplier and diversity of product than ever before. Consumers know this intuitively and it has turned out that recent claims about increased concentration in the American economy are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.nber.org/papers/w25066.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;largely wrong&lt;/a&gt; on a factual basis. In most sectors there is more actual competition, and the dominant players we do have, such as Amazon and Walmart, typically are lowering rather than raising prices when they enter markets. For the tech sector, there are dominant product suppliers such as Google and Facebook, but they are hardly following the old monopolist playbook of higher prices and restricted output.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is too much concentration in the hospital sector, and in K-12 education: it’s a government semi-monopoly, and it’s hard to compete with the free government product unless you are selling to wealthy families. We also have some outrageously high prices for real estate and higher education, but those are due to supply constraints and excess regulation, rather than private monopoly. In all of these cases I would consider legal remedies to give consumers a better deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; What do you fear most about the effects of the anti-business sentiment?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Cowen:&lt;/strong&gt; For a start, I fear we will split up our big tech companies, or at the very least severely distract senior management with antitrust suits. An alternative route we might go down is to enact severe privacy legislation which raises costs to new market entrants, and cements in the power of the incumbents. Either of those two paths would be a mistake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most generally, I fear that the status of going into business will fall, as it already has in much of Europe. It would hurt America greatly to lose its genius and distinct preference for business activity. Culture really does matter, and America stands at risk of losing its pro-business, pro-entrepreneurship leanings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; What do businesses need to do to improve their image, other than PR?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Cowen:&lt;/strong&gt; Business has to realise it always will be held to a higher standard, perhaps unjustly so, but still that is a reality. That means business ought to opt for less fraud, less lobbying for crony capitalism, more social conscience when it comes to pollution and climate change, and also bolder, less bureaucratic decision-making procedures. We are pretty far from that world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I stress in the book, a lot of business is pretty fraudulent. The thing is, human beings are fraudulent too; maybe more so outside of a business context. Ask a simple question: who lies more, the company Match.com, or the online daters filling out their profiles? The answer is both obvious and sad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; What can individuals and groups do to hold businesses to account?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Cowen:&lt;/strong&gt; Search for the best price; it benefits the whole market. Speak up when you are unhappy, noting that the internet makes the monitoring of business quality easier than ever before. When it comes to health care, educate yourself. So much of the waste in the American economy is in that sector. And, if you really see persistent business failures in a particular area, consider starting a business yourself to fix them. Or recommend the business idea to someone else. All of the best businesses today were at some point in the past unrealised dreams.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; If we can&amp;#x27;t look to the political sphere for leadership to address global challenges, are we right to turn to business for that leadership? Ought they to rise to that mission, even if it strays from their central remit of making and selling their widgets?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr Cowen:&lt;/strong&gt; Most of the biggest global challenges will require contributions from both government and business. Take climate change. Yes, governments need to regulate more and tax carbon emissions. But we also need businesses to step up and innovate. We’re seeing a systematic tendency to villainise the role of business in carbon emissions and pollution. Yes, business has had a major role in this, but so have consumers, so have voters, so have all of us. The reality is that we will need the help of business to solve the problem, and we should not make this a question of us versus them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 03:41:05 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The race to become Britain’s next PM]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/24/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_woc777.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-24T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- data-infographic-js=&quot;/2019/tory-leadership/js/bundle.js&quot; data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/tory-leadership/css/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/tory-leadership/css/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;
  &lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HERESA MAY&lt;/small&gt; has announced that she will step down as leader of the Conservative Party on June 7th. She will remain as prime minister until her successor is chosen. Nominations for the Tory leadership will close in the week beginning June 10th, followed by several rounds of voting among MPs, a process that will last until the end of the month. The MPs will then send two names to party members who will make the final choice. The result of their vote will be announced before parliament rises for summer. 
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Betfair Exchange, a gambling website, has been tracking punters’ predictions on the next Tory leader. According to the wisdom of the betting crowd, a handful of candidates stand out. But there is only one clear frontrunner.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic- &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;p &gt;Source: Betfair Exchange&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; &gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Adrian Wooldridge, our political editor, assesses the chances of the leading Conservative politicians hoping to take the top job in this short film
&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ychDrZ2QzlE&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 03:41:04 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China’s $10bn annual spending on soft power has bought little of it]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/24/chinas-10bn-annual-spending-on-soft-power-has-bought-little-of-it]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_woc087.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-24T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;CHINA WANTS the world to love it. In 2007 Hu Jintao, its leader at the time, announced to a congress of the Communist Party that acquiring soft power, or ruan shili, was essential for the country to become a global force. Xi Jinping, who succeeded Mr Hu in 2012, has zealously continued his mission to expand China’s cultural appeal as quickly as its economic heft and military strength. Today the party spends about &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/china/2017/03/23/china-is-spending-billions-to-make-the-world-love-it&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;$10bn a year on soft power&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Its most notable strategy has been to build Confucius Institutes on foreign university campuses. These offer instruction in Mandarin, cooking and dancing, among other cultural pursuits. According to Joshua Nederhood of Development Reimagined, a consultancy based in Beijing, the party has opened more than 500 of these institutes in the past 15 years, along with nearly 1,200 Confucius Classrooms, which offer language courses at schools. This rapid growth means that China, which had almost no foreign cultural outposts in 2000, now has more than any other country.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_WOC089.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190525_WOC089.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190525_WOC089.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190525_WOC089.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190525_WOC089.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190525_WOC089.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190525_WOC089.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190525_WOC089.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190525_WOC089.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190525_WOC089.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;But despite this gigantic public-relations campaign, the world’s esteem for China—or at the very least, for its Communist Party—has fallen sharply. Since 2006 Gallup, a pollster, has asked people around the globe whether they approve or disapprove of China’s leadership. The Economist has looked at the annual figures for 123 countries and found that, in 2007, the average country gave the Chinese government a net approval rating of +11% (measured as the percentage who approve minus the percentage of those who disapprove). A decade later, that number had dwindled to just +1%. Africans tend to think of China most highly, with a net rating of +34%, and Europeans are most wary, with a tally of -14%. But in every continent Gallup recorded a decline of at least five percentage points between 2007 and 2017.&lt;p&gt;The Confucius Institutes are unlikely to be the cause of this change in global opinion, since few people outside universities have encountered them. However, they do offer clues as to why China might have gained more foes than friends. Many academics have complained that the institutes spread propaganda and suppress discussion of sensitive topics, such as Taiwanese independence. A few Western universities have shut them down. A clumsy attempt to impress foreigners, it seems, might be worse than none at all. Perhaps some people have also been spooked by claims that China’s Belt and Road Initiative, a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/briefing/2018/07/26/china-has-a-vastly-ambitious-plan-to-connect-the-world&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;global infrastructure-building project&lt;/a&gt;, is really a way to exert political influence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Xi seems to have realised the need for an even softer touch. He is now intent on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/china/2019/02/07/the-communist-party-capitalises-on-foreign-interest-in-chinese-culture&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;building Chinese Cultural Centres&lt;/a&gt;. These are not located on campuses and so avoid being seen as interfering with liberal institutions. And Chinese news agencies have turned their sights to Facebook, where they have acquired &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/20/china-is-using-facebook-to-build-a-huge-audience-around-the-world&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;hundreds of millions of followers&lt;/a&gt; who receive fluffy articles about the country. The Communist Party’s net approval rating got its first noticeable boost in 2018, rising from +1% to +4%, although the reason is not clear. It might take China a long time to recover the support that it has lost in the past decade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 02:41:10 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Are the Victorians a model for Brexit Britain?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/24/are-the-victorians-a-model-for-brexit-britain]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_blp507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-24T17:17:56Z&quot;&gt;May 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WITH THERESA May on her way out of 10 Downing Street and Britain no closer to achieving the Brexit she promised, Anne McElvoy takes the long view. She asks Jacob Rees-Mogg, a Conservative MP, and Tristram Hunt, director of the Victoria and Albert Museum, to debate how the titans of the 19th century shaped modern Britain. What would Queen Victoria do? And who in the Conservative party do they tip to take over the leadership? Runtime: 34 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-arethevictoriansamodelforbrexitbritain-&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 01:40:36 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Keeping children safe on the internet]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/24/keeping-children-safe-on-the-internet]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_ldp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-24T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FEW PARENTS, confronted with grumpy toddlers or bored ten-year-olds, are strong-minded enough to resist the peace that comes from sticking their darlings in front of a tablet or a smartphone. But the relief is tinged with guilt. One minute toddlers can be watching Peppa Pig, and the next learning that the Moon landings were faked or that Earth is flat. YouTube and Netflix are designed to keep their audience hooked in ways that are creepy when used on adults; but when they involve children they are downright disturbing. Data are being collected from individuals too young to dress themselves, let alone consent to the myriad of uses to which the data are put.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The problem is not new. Rules have long governed children’s exposure to older forms of media—think of watersheds in television schedules, age-ratings in cinemas or restrictions on buying pornography. Yet for many years, both governments and tech firms have treated the web as a domain where those rules are so laxly enforced that they hardly apply at all. The industry hides behind the skimpiest of figleaves. Facebook’s terms of service forbid those under 13 from signing up, as do those of WhatsApp, a messaging service that Facebook owns. Both provisions are blithely ignored by millions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The platforms themselves are not well policed. According to one survey, 61% of parents who let their children watch YouTube report that their offspring have come across unsuitable content. Some videos purporting to be children’s cartoons have been found spiked with violence, or with predatory comments below the line. Now, though, propelled by worries about everything from religious radicalisation to exploitative content and grooming by paedophiles, governments are at last beginning to pay attention (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/25/how-to-make-social-media-safe-for-children&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;). In America Congress is drafting several bills. India may forbid data-collection from anyone who is under 18. Britain wants to force porn sites to implement robust age checks, or face being blocked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Broadly, this is welcome. Many liberals, like this newspaper, think that censorship laws are easily abused, and that too much mollycoddling is not just unnecessary but harmful. Yet it is hard to defend the idea that there should be one set of rules for old media and another—or none—for newer kinds. The argument that it is up to parents to control their children’s media consumption has much to recommend it. It would have even more if tech firms were not using every design trick they could think of—from push notifications to recommendation engines—to undermine that control, or if they were taking the initiative in rooting out harmful content.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The risk is that new rules cost a fortune to enforce and become obsolete as technology marches on. Hence governments should apply two principles. First, online rules should reflect the broad standards that are already in place for offline media. Obviously, these standards need to be adapted to suit a new generation of technology in which interaction is enabled, individual preferences can be catered for and viewing is on demand. But they apply to the same children and are a good foundation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second principle is that governments should not get bogged down trying to specify precisely how platforms should solve problems—setting out, for example, the details of what it means to identify when a child is using a site. That is a task for the tech firms, which can innovate and which understand their platforms better than anyone. Instead, regulators should demand results, and impose large sanctions for firms that fall short. The sorts of fines imposed by the GDPR, which are based on percentages of a firm’s global revenue, are a starting-point. Tech firms would be well advised to co-operate. Some are trying—YouTube’s “Kids” app is a start, but it should be aggressively promoted as the company’s default option for children. But even the most mercenary should see the way the wind is blowing. If they do not respond they will find their bad behaviour ends with tantrums and tears.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 01:40:35 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[British politics after Theresa May]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/24/british-politics-after-theresa-may]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_brp507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-24T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERESA MAY strode out of the door of 10 Downing Street in a crimson business suit and bowed to the inevitable. Having failed three times to get her Brexit deal through a hopelessly divided parliament, and confronted with a Tory insurrection over her proposed fourth attempt, she announced on May 24th that she would step down as leader of the Conservative Party and Britain’s prime minister.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“It is and will always remain a matter of deep regret for me that I have not been able to deliver Brexit,” she declared. She then urged MPs to find the spirit of compromise. Had she left it there it might have been remembered as a dignified exit at the end of her dogged prime ministership. Instead she tried to set out her legacy—listing, among other things, measures to limit plastic waste—and only highlighted how little she managed to do. Then, as she gave thanks for the “honour of a lifetime”, a prime minister often derided as “Maybot” shed a tear and left.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She will step down as leader of the Conservative Party on June 7th. The Party will then begin the formal process for selecting a successor. Nominations will close in the week beginning June 10th, followed by several rounds of voting among MPs, a process that will last until the end of the month. The MPs will then send two names to party members who will vote on who they like most, with the result of their vote &amp;quot;announced before parliament rises for summer. Mrs May will remain as prime minister until a new leader is found. This means that she will act as host to President Donald Trump when he arrives in Britain for his state visit on June 3rd, and will attend the 75th anniversary of D-Day on June 6th, something on which she is known to put great value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leading Tories were quick to express their admiration for Mrs May—particularly for her determination and sense of duty. But there was something of a ritualistic quality to this: most Tories have been desperate to see the back of Mrs May for weeks. Thirty-six ministers resigned during her spell in office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mrs May’s resignation came after &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/23/another-british-prime-minister-is-destroyed-by-the-europe-question&quot;&gt;a surreal few days&lt;/a&gt; in British politics. On May 22nd she presented her revised EU withdrawal bill to the House of Commons, laboriously reading through the ten points that were supposed to overcome the House’s objections to the previous version. But it was clear that she had lost the confidence of both her government and party. The front bench around her was half-empty because the more pro-Brexit members of her cabinet were somewhere else discussing what to do next, and the benches behind her emptied as she spoke. This was not just a prime minister without authority but a prime minister without an audience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All this took place against the background of a European election that Britain should never have taken part in. Polls suggest that the Tories are due to come a poor fourth—one even hinted that they could get no more than 7% of the vote—and that Nigel Farage’s Brexit Party is likely to come first thanks to the votes of disillusioned Conservatives. It also took place against the background of a ticking clock. The European Union had offered Britain an extension of Article 50 (whose triggering began the Brexit process) to October 31st, so that it could find a route out of the impasse. But the government is now farther from finding that route than it was when the extension was granted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The immediate trigger for Mrs May’s departure was the failure of her revised withdrawal bill. But the bigger trigger was the general election that she called back in June 2017. Her instincts were right: increasing the Tories’ majority would have allowed her to increase her bargaining power with her party and ensure that she was not hostage to pro- or anti-Brexit factions. But the election was a debacle. The party produced a turgid manifesto that alienated voters with an ill-thought-out plan to make rich homeowners pay more for social care—a plan that was quickly dubbed the “dementia tax”. The party seriously underestimated Jeremy Corbyn’s appeal to the electorate and the quality of the Labour Party’s Momentum-powered political machine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The election campaign also underlined Mrs May’s weaknesses as a practical politician. She refused to take part in a leaders’ debate and instead sent Amber Rudd, whose father had just died, to act as her champion. Whenever she deigned to campaign she was wooden and awkward. Mrs May is an introvert in a profession that demands a willingness to mingle with people and make them feel good about themselves. She is also a rigid micro-manager in a business that is by nature fluid and open-ended. Mrs May’s instinct is to surround herself with a tiny coterie of advisers (who are completely dependent on her) and to plan everything out in detail. But this has repeatedly proven fatal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;British politics will now be consumed by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/23/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm&quot;&gt;the race to succeed Mrs May&lt;/a&gt;. Some 20 MPs have put their hats in the ring and started parading their families (and kitchens) before an exasperated public. The front-runner is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/23/choosing-boris-johnson-as-prime-minister-would-be-a-dangerous-gamble&quot;&gt;Boris Johnson&lt;/a&gt;, the former foreign secretary. Mr Johnson is the clear favourite among party members and among pro-Brexit MPs (Jacob Rees-Mogg, the head of the hardline European Research Group, has been hosting dinners for him). And he has also been doing a good job of reaching out to his party’s pro-Remain liberal wing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the rule-of-thumb in election races is that the favourite never wins the crown. Mr Johnson was also the clear favourite in the last leadership race, in 2016, but his bid imploded when his campaign manager, Michael Gove, decided that Mr Johson was not up to the job and decided to run himself. Mr Gove will hope to be a powerful contender this time. He has an impressive record of galvanising whatever departments he has run, from education to the environment, and recognises that the Conservative Party needs to do more than repeat its old mantras about unleashing market forces if it is to defeat Mr Corbyn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Messrs Johnson and Gove did more than any other Tories to win the Brexit vote for leavers. But they will have to contend with even purer Brexiteers, such as Dominic Raab and Andrea Leadsom, who will be looking for any sign of treason. They will also have to contend with senior cabinet ministers such as Jeremy Hunt, the foreign secretary who ran the health service for six years, and Sajid Javid, the home secretary. With Mr Javid fading of late, the race could end up pitching Mr Hunt as the safe pair of hands against Mr Johnson as the charismatic risk taker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/thismayhurt-britishpolitics&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Conservative Party as a whole likes nothing more than a leadership race. But whoever wins this one will face one of the most difficult situations of any prime minister in modern times. The new leader will confront a party that is bitterly divided over Brexit, with ultras determined to leave at any cost and moderates determined to prevent a no-deal Brexit. The new chief will also confront a party that is completely split about where to go in terms of broader policy: should the Conservative Party redouble its commitment to Thatcherism—the position of many hard-line Brexiteers—or should it re-embrace the One Nation tradition that was obscured by the rise of Thatcherism? One-nation Tories—who include some Brexiteers as well as Remainers—think that the Conservative Party needs to engage in a broad policy rethink if it is to address the problems revealed by the financial crisis and the subsequent rise of Mr Corbyn. Many advocate radical devolution, a more activist economic policy and a bold programme of house-building.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next leader will have to grapple with the same forces that have destroyed Mrs May: a country as well as a party that is torn over Brexit; a political system that is being pulled apart by the tension between representative and direct democracy; and a conflict with the European Union that, despite repeated statements to the contrary by Brexiteers, has most of the cards in its hand. Mrs May will not be the last prime minister to be brought to tears by Brexit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;See also:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/23/theresa-may-reaches-the-end-of-the-road&quot;&gt;Leader: Theresa May reaches the end of the road&lt;/a&gt; (May 23rd 2019)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 23:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>