<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[What is China’s “one country, two systems” policy?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/06/30/what-is-chinas-one-country-two-systems-policy]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_CNP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-30T10:38:53Z&quot;&gt;Jun 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS of demonstrators repeatedly took to the streets of Hong Kong in June to protest against a proposed law that would allow the extradition of criminal suspects to mainland China. Their demonstrations, some of the largest in Hong Kong’s history, were instrumental in persuading the territory’s chief executive, Carrie Lam, to suspend the bill. In agitating against closer ties, Hong Kongers made use of freedoms that are denied in mainland China. What is their origin?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the late 20th century three historically Chinese territories remained beyond the control of the Chinese Communist Party: Taiwan, Macau and Hong Kong. Shortly after emerging as China’s paramount leader in 1978, Deng Xiaoping declared his ambition of achieving “reunification” with Taiwan. The island is technically the last stronghold of a government that once ruled all of China until a civil war ended in victory for the Communists in 1949, sending the defeated nationalist army into exile on Taiwan. Since then it has become a democracy, and its people increasingly identify as “Taiwanese”. Rulers in Beijing are sworn to unify the island with the mainland, if needs be by force.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deng promised Taiwan a “high degree of autonomy”, describing his proposal as “one country, two systems”. Taiwan would be allowed to retain its separate administration, capitalist way of life and even its own armed forces as long as it recognised the Communist government in Beijing as legitimate in all of China, including Taiwan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Taiwanese did not take the bait, but China used the “one country, two systems” idea when it took back Hong Kong from Britain and Macau from Portugal. Britain had secured the heart of Hong Kong in perpetuity as spoils of the 19th-century Opium Wars but the final part, the New Territories, was acquired on a 99-year lease in 1898. The Portuguese had ruled Macau since the 1500s, but eventually started withdrawing troops in 1975. With Britain’s lease expiring and Portugal abandoning Macau, China began talks with both countries in the mid-1980s to make arrangements for the return of the two territories and to decide their future political arrangements. Hong Kong and Macau were to become parts of China again in 1997 and 1999, respectively.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All parties, including China, recognised that imposing China’s political system on the two colonies would create panic and cause economic mayhem. “One country, two systems” would allow the territories to remain much as they were, with independent legal systems and police forces. Their political structures would change little, except that local “chief executives” would replace governors sent by the colonial powers. In Hong Kong, the chief executive would be elected by a 1,200-member electoral college from a pool of candidates approved by the Chinese government and would preside over a system modelled roughly on Britain’s, though with a single legislative chamber. China even promised that the chief executives would eventually be elected by “universal suffrage”, though its exact meaning in this context is unclear. The government in Beijing would be responsible for defence and diplomacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These arrangements are to last for 50 years. It is unclear what happens after 2047. In the meantime, democracy activists have been growing despondent as pro-establishment forces, some funded by Beijing, secured majorities in local councils and the territory’s legislature, and new loyalty tests were imposed on candidates for office. Frustration led to the so-called Umbrella Movement of 2014, a series of protests and sit-ins aimed at securing a promise of genuine democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In response, the central authorities doubled down on the “one country” side of the deal. In 2016 and 2017 they secured the disbarring of six legislators for disrespecting China by mangling their oaths of loyalty. This year they have changed Hong Kong’s constitution to require the passage of a law that would punish people for insulting the national anthem, mirroring a law China passed in 2017. And they have pushed to change the current, colonial-era law that specifically bars extraditions to China. The proposed bill does not cover political offences, but many fear that the Communist Party could use it to secure the extradition of people deemed offensive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though Ms Lam has suspended the extradition bill, political veterans expect the Communist Party to tighten its grip in myriad, less visible ways. The central government still praises “one country, two systems” as a great innovation. In January China’s leader, Xi Jinping, stressed the policy’s importance for securing what he called the “inevitable” unification of the mainland and Taiwan. Few in Taiwan are convinced. Recent events in Hong Kong have only increased their suspicions. Deng’s innovative solution to the problem of reunification has never faced greater scepticism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 21:26:28 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Microsoft’s transformation required a change of culture]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/30/microsofts-transformation-required-a-change-of-culture]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_wbp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-30T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;LIKE AN NFL changing room, the technology industry is littered with the bodies of fallen champions, from AOL to Yahoo to Blackberry, in urgent need of rehabilitation. Ten years ago many might have expected Microsoft to end up in the same state. But the software giant has made a startling comeback, regularly vying for the title of the most valuable company on global stockmarkets, with a market capitalisation above $1trn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The story of this revival is the subject of a new case study by Hermania Ibarra and Adam Jones of London Business School (LBS). In large part, the success has resulted from a shift away from a focus on the Windows operating system and towards Azure, Microsoft’s cloud-based services offering. It involved a willingness to let Microsoft programs run on Apple and Android smartphones, something the company had previously avoided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the turnaround also required a change to the company’s culture and that is the main subject of the LBS study. The shift to cloud-based services meant that revenues would be generated in a different way. Under the old system, clients bought software under a fixed-term contract; once the sale was made, the revenue was guaranteed. Cloud services are paid for on a metered basis; revenue comes in only when customers use them. That required a new approach by the company’s sales team, led by Jean-Philippe Courtois.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shift was enormous. Around 40,000 people had to change how they did their jobs. Three elements were important. First, staff had to understand how customers were using cloud-based services, so that they could be encouraged to use them more. This required 5,000 specialist hires.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second, to permit existing sales staff to concentrate on attracting and retaining customers, they had to be relieved of some duties, such as preparing sales forecasts. Internal review meetings were reduced, including an intimidating ordeal known as the mid-year review in which senior executives grilled employees—and for which workers spent lots of time cramming like students for a test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Finally, salespeople needed an incentive to put in the work to flog the new products, which were potentially less lucrative for them than the traditional fixed-term contracts. This involved a greater use of performance bonuses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This being Microsoft, technology chivvied the process along. A new productivity tool helped workers analyse how much time they spent in meetings or writing emails and whether they were interacting with fellow Microsoft employees or with clients. Among other things, it allowed the usefulness of meetings to be gauged: if staff were fiddling with their work smartphones, they were not listening to their colleagues and probably had better things to do than loiter in a conference room. (The test could be usefully applied to meetings at a lot more places than Microsoft.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Managers have had to change too. Microsoft is introducing a programme called “Reimagine Managers” which aims to foster an approach of coaching and caring for the staff. Technology has made some routine management tasks (like organising rotas) easier, leaving more time for more time-consuming non-routine ones, such as talking to employees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Changing a corporate culture is an enormous task, and Mr Courtois admits that it is a work in progress. Microsoft, he says, has shifted from a “fixed mindset” to a “growth mindset”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what is interesting about the Microsoft case study (which is mostly free of such management jargon) is that it highlights the practical changes needed to transform a company. Microsoft could have been a classic victim of “creative disruption”, so dependent on an existing technology (personal computers) that it failed to manage the shift to a world dominated by mobile devices. But the shift has only been successful (so far) because it has involved not just a strategic insight, but a change in approach across the workforce.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft can still trip up. Tech companies are like the Red Queen in Lewis Carroll’s “Through the Looking Glass”—constantly running to stay in the same place. IBM performed a successful shift from hardware to services in the 1990s, but has struggled to grow its revenues or lift its share price in recent years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the long run Microsoft’s fortunes may depend on whether acquisitions like LinkedIn, the career site, or GitHub, a software-development startup, prove wiser than its failed bet on Nokia’s mobile-phone business earlier in the decade. But it has already shown that, even in a big organisation, cultural change is possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 21:26:27 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump meets Kim Jong Un on the border between South and North Korea]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/30/donald-trump-meets-kim-jong-un-on-the-border-between-south-and-north-korea]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190706_blp902.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-30T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON THE morning of June 29th Donald Trump, America’s president, extended the most casual of invitations from his hotel room in Osaka, where he was attending a meeting of the G20 hosted by Japan. “If Chairman Kim of North Korea sees this, I would meet him at the Border/DMZ just to shake his hand and say Hello(?)!,” Mr Trump wrote on Twitter. After all, Mr Trump was already scheduled to visit the “demilitarised zone” between the two Koreas the next day, after a meeting with Moon Jae-in, South Korea’s president. Why not throw in a meeting with North Korea’s dictator, whom he had met twice before in an effort to get North Korea to abandon its nuclear weapons. Mere hours later, North Korea pronounced Mr Trump’s suggestion “very interesting”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Interesting enough that, on the afternoon of June 30th, Mr Kim and Mr Trump met for the third time in just over a year. Following a tour of the South Korean side of the DMZ, which also took in a windswept guard post and a canteen where troops presented the president with a golfing outfit, Mr Trump strolled towards the dividing line in the truce village of Panmunjom. He shook hands with Mr Kim, who was waiting for him on the northern side, before stepping across the line into North Korea. The moment was heavy with symbolism: it was the first time a sitting American president had set foot in North Korea, and it came 69 years, nearly to the day, after American troops had entered the Korean war on the South’s side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During a brief chat on the northern side, Mr Trump said it was an “honour” to visit North Korea. Mr Kim appeared chuffed: “I never expected to see you in this place,” he told Mr Trump, who then invited the North’s dictator to visit the White House. Afterwards, the two stepped back across the line into South Korea, where they posed briefly for a photo with Mr Moon before retiring for talks to “Freedom House” on the southern side. Mr Moon, who needs negotiations between America and North Korea to restart in order to advance his ambitious agenda of inter-Korean economic cooperation, was effusive throughout. “The flower of peace is blossoming on the Korean peninsula,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As well as being a gift for Mr Moon, the summit was also a boon for Messrs Trump and Kim. The president’s comments during and around the meeting will have pleased Mr Kim. Mr Trump downplayed North Korea’s recent tests of short-range missiles, claiming America did not consider them missile tests. Mr Kim’s nuclear programme barely got a mention: for all the world, it looked as though Mr Trump was perfectly happy to engage with North Korea on its own terms, implicitly acknowledging the regime’s nuclear-armed status as legitimate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These comments, along with the pictures of Mr Trump stepping into North Korea and saying that he was honoured to be received by Mr Kim, are gold for the North’s domestic propaganda machine, which is bound to use them to demonstrate the great leader’s diplomatic acumen. They may go some way towards brushing up Mr Kim’s domestic image following the collapse of the pair’s previous summit, in Vietnam in February. North Korea’s failure to win relief from sanctions at that meeting seems to have so infuriated Mr Kim that he demoted his chief negotiator and is rumoured to have punished other aides. But the decision to meet Mr Trump again suggests that he still holds out hope of benefitting from continued negotiations. Mr Trump’s effusiveness about his friendship with Mr Kim is also likely to burnish the dictator’s image internationally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump, for his part, used the occasion to congratulate himself for saving the region from the devastating conflict that he claimed would be racking it had it not been for his efforts. “We are in a much different place than we were two and a half years ago,” he said. He complained repeatedly and at length about the media, whose lack of appreciation for his efforts he deemed “insulting”. He also seemed to enjoy the theatricality of the meeting, which was enhanced by its supposedly impromptu nature. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It remains unclear whether the encounter really was arranged in just 24 hours. On the one hand, the chaotic scenes at Panmunjom (including the White House press secretary getting into a fight with North Korean security officers) did not suggest extensive planning. On the other, the two leaders had been exchanging letters in the weeks leading up to the meeting, and Mr Trump had brought his entire team of nuclear negotiators along with him on his long-planned visit to Seoul. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If peace-making is taken to mean improving relations with a rogue dictatorship, the meeting certainly had some value. But it contributed very little to America’s aim to persuade North Korea to give up its nuclear weapons. In a press conference following his encounter with Mr Kim, Mr Trump told reporters that the two sides’ negotiating teams would get together in the coming weeks to arrange working-level talks. “They’ll start a process, and we’ll see what happens,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Arms-control experts have been hoping for the start of that process ever since Mr Trump announced his meeting with Mr Kim in Singapore more than 13 months ago. The failure to get down to nitty-gritty talks had been taken as a sign that North Korea was not really serious about disarmament. Even if negotiators do finally start chewing over details, there is little reason to imagine that Mr Kim is ready at last to surrender his nuclear weapons. But he and Mr Trump do like a photo-op.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2019 21:26:26 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America and China resume talks in a bid to end their trade war]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/29/america-and-china-resume-talks-in-a-bid-to-end-their-trade-war]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190706_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;XI JINPING and Donald Trump claim to be fond of each other. After a year of spiralling disputes between America and China, their professions of friendship are hard to believe. But it is true that whenever they get together, they usually succeed in stabilising their countries’ relationship, at least for a time. Their meeting on June 29th, on the sidelines of the G20 summit in Osaka, appears to have delivered again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The two superpowers agreed to resume their on-again, off-again trade negotiations, and America desisted from applying further tariffs. That is a welcome respite for global markets and companies, and indeed for anyone who hopes that China and America can find a way to avoid a new cold war. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, it is also true that the periods of calm after previous Xi-Trump meetings have only lasted so long, and have ultimately been followed by a progressive escalation of the trade war. Whether that happens this time will hinge on the negotiations that are set to begin anew. There are many reasons for pessimism and one for guarded optimism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Details of what the leaders agreed during their 80-minute meeting are still scant. The biggest surprise was Mr Trump’s statement at a subsequent press conference that America would permit its tech companies to continue selling components to Huawei, a Chinese telecoms giant, an apparent reversal of an earlier decision to blacklist it. That is a big reprieve for Huawei, and a victory for Mr Xi. But Mr Trump also suggested that a final decision on how to handle Huawei would rest on the fate of the trade talks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America’s decision to hold off on further tariffs had been expected, because China had made that a precondition for the resumption of talks. But it is important all the same. America has so far levied tariffs of 25% on $250bn-worth of Chinese imports, about half of what China sells to America. Mr Trump had threatened to slap tariffs on almost all remaining Chinese imports if the talks with Mr Xi went badly. Chinese officials, for their part, emphasised the leaders’ agreement that talks would proceed “on the basis of equality and mutual respect”, wording that helps address their complaint that America was making one-sided demands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet one obvious lesson from the past year is that it will be exceedingly tough to reach a true deal. The longer the dispute goes on, the more intractable it seems to get. At the outset Mr Trump dwelled on China’s gaping trade surplus with America. But it soon became clear that his combative approach had uncorked a range of long-held American grievances. Among the issues to have figured in the talks: restrictions on foreign firms’ access to the Chinese market, China’s shoddy protection of intellectual property and the range of subsidies that underpin China’s economic model.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The commercial conflict has also laid bare a rivalry over technology that is destined only to get more intense. Even if America and China manage to roll back tariffs, these are just one part of their increasingly sprawling confrontation. Chinese investors and researchers in America face more restrictions and scrutiny. China has said it will blacklist foreign companies that cut off supplies to its firms. Both countries are developing plans specifically aimed at curbing technological reliance on the other.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In some ways, too, the political dynamics have become worse. Mr Trump is heading into an election year and does not want to appear soft on China. In China itself the field has tilted in favour of those advocating a more unyielding stance. Since the breakdown in trade talks in early May, state media have unleashed a bombardment of commentaries that are highly critical of America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many assume that as the cost of the trade war rises—whether in the form of slower growth or sputtering markets—cooler heads will prevail. But Mr Trump so far likes what he sees. American stocks just notched up their best first-half performance in more than two decades (largely thanks to the Federal Reserve’s signalling that it will cut interest rates). China has felt more pain from the trade war, but its fiscal and monetary policies are also shifting in a pro-growth direction. So for the time being, both countries may feel emboldened rather than constrained by their economies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The one reason for cautious optimism is that the new round of talks should be grounded in greater realism. The breakdown in early May occurred when Chinese negotiators insisted on major revisions to a deal that the Americans thought was nearly done. It is not known whether there had been a change of heart on the Chinese side—a feeling that they had given away too much—or whether it was a negotiating tactic, a last-minute rollback of promises.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In either case the deep freeze in talks over the past two months has not been a total waste. China has laid out its position more explicitly than before, making three core demands: America must scrap all tariffs imposed on China since the start of the trade war; commitments to buy more American goods must be “realistic”; and the text of the final deal must be balanced, not just a list of Chinese concessions. The American side has long been clear about what it wants from China: credible commitments both to reduce its trade surplus and reform its economic policies, backed up by enforcement mechanisms if it fails to do so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chinese and American officials should have a good idea by now of the scope of an eventual agreement. That they are ready to resume talks suggests they think a deal is possible. But if the result is yet another breakdown, no one should be surprised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 19:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Join us for a day of ideas, debate and inspiration]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/28/join-us-for-a-day-of-ideas-debate-and-inspiration]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_OPP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T21:14:10Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join journalists from &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; for the second annual Open Future Festival on Saturday, October 5th 2019. Held in three cities simultaneously—Hong Kong, Manchester and Chicago—it is a chance for people from across the ideological spectrum to meet and debate vital issues on the future of open societies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hear talks and panels by prominent figures from politics, business, civil society and the arts. The festival themes include free speech and free trade; the environment and inequality; the rise of populism and anxiety over the algorithmic society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Come and share your ideas during a day of exciting discussions, curated content and exhibitions, immersive experiences and the chance to make connections with hundreds of festival attendees. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More information for the festivals by region:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://events.economist.com/events-conferences/asia/open-future-festival-hong-kong?utm_source=EM8172_Web_OFHUB&amp;amp;RefID=EM8172_Web_OFHUB&quot;&gt;Hong Kong event details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://events.economist.com/events-conferences/emea/open-future-festival-manchester/?utm_source=EM1696_Web_OFHUB&amp;amp;RefID=EM1696_Web_OFHUB&quot;&gt;Manchester event details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://events.economist.com/events-conferences/americas/open-future-festival-chicago/?utm_source=EM2355_Web_OFHUB&amp;amp;RefID=EM2355_Web_OFHUB&quot;&gt;Chicago event details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn more about Open Future&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Open Future &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/openfuture&quot;&gt;content hub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Take part in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/26/our-essay-competition-for-young-people&quot;&gt;Open Future essay contest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Letter from the editor: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2018/04/16/a-letter-to-readers-from-the-editor&quot;&gt;Open Future explained&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Watch &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s editor-in-chief Zanny Minton Beddoes interview &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NAfm5L_DOLM&quot; data-tegid=&quot;ub0s0birid6siht0j726ov5houcptr88&quot;&gt;Steve Bannon&lt;/a&gt; at last year’s festival&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Is capitalism rigged in favour of the elites? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://debates.economist.com/debate/capitalism&quot;&gt;Read the online debate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Read &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/01/21/we-need-to-own-our-data-as-a-human-right-and-be-compensated-for-it&quot;&gt;“We need to own our data as a human right—and be compensated for it”&lt;/a&gt;, an Open Future essay by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://will.i.am/&quot;&gt;will.i.am&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 07:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[In their first primary debate Democrats focused on the issues]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/28/in-their-first-primary-debate-democrats-focused-on-the-issues]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic- data-infographic-js=&quot;/2019/debate-night-interactive/js/bundle.js&quot; data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/debate-night-interactive/css/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/debate-night-interactive/css/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;“America does&lt;/small&gt; not want to witness a food fight, they want to know how we’re going to put food on their table.” So said Kamala Harris, the junior senator from California, on the second night of this week’s Democratic primary debate on June 27th. The line, while clearly scripted, provoked raucous applause, suggesting that the assembled audience was more interested in policy disagreements than bickering and personal attacks. That is, for the most part, what the candidates gave them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to an analysis of the first Democratic debate by &lt;i&gt;The Economist&lt;/i&gt;, the vast majority of the candidates’ time—more than 70%—was spent discussing specific policies. Elizabeth Warren, a senator from Massachusetts, and Julián Castro, a former housing secretary, impressed with their command of health-care and immigration policy. These issues took up 10% and 9% of the debate, respectively. Bernie Sanders and Pete Buttigieg, meanwhile, spoke at length about economic and foreign policy, which each represented about 10% of debate time. Other topics, such as climate change and gun control, received less attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such issues may be of little concern to primary voters. According to YouGov, a pollster, America’s biggest political divides run along demographic, not policy lines. Nonetheless, this week’s debate may still prove consequential. During Thursday’s tussle, Ms Harris pressed Mr Biden, the front-runner, over his civil rights record, including his opposition to school busing ordered by America’s Department of Education in the 1970s. The exchange may damage his standing among his core supporters. Prior to the debate, punters on PredictIt, a political-betting market, gave Ms Harris a 14% chance of winning the primary in South Carolina, where most Democratic primary voters are black. After her performance on Thursday, her chances jumped to 43%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 03:40:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why did the justices rule that courts cannot curb partisan redistricting?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/28/why-did-the-justices-rule-that-courts-cannot-curb-partisan-redistricting]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_USP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T11:29:13Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR JOHN LOCKE, the 17th-century political philosopher, anarchy was when a leader “has the liberty to be judge in his own case”. In a properly constituted society, disputes between contending parties are turned over to a third party for adjudication—an independent judge who can apply the law and issue a fair judgement. America’s judiciary generally fills this role. But on June 27th, a bare majority of the Supreme Court declared a crucial issue—partisan gerrymandering—outside its portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The court told state legislators they are their own bosses when it comes to drawing electoral maps for their legislatures and for Congress. No matter how blatantly or egregiously the lines are skewed, the federal judiciary will remain studiously above the fray. Legislators may choose their voters, rather than the other way around, and nobody will blink. The decision will give a bigger boost to Republicans, because they control more state houses and governor mansions. While it closes the door to claims of political gerrymandering, race-based gerrymandering remains subject to judicial review. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/18pdf/18-422_9ol1.pdf&quot;&gt;opinions&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;em&gt;Rucho v Common Cause&lt;/em&gt; were penned by the court’s best writers: Chief Justice John Roberts for the five-man conservative majority, Justice Elena Kagan for the four liberal dissenters. But the opinions offer starkly different visions of the courts’ role in preserving democratic norms and institutions. Whereas the chief summoned a raft of arguments to explain why there is simply no manageable way for judges to determine when a gerrymander goes too far, the dissent characterised the ruling as abrogating a “duty to declare the law” on a matter that is fundamental to the very functioning of American elections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The districting plans at issue here are highly partisan, by any measure”, Chief Justice Roberts began, but the lower courts that struck them down inappropriately “exercised judicial power” by declaring them “unconstitutional as well”. In dutifully laying out the facts of cases from North Carolina and Maryland, the chief expressed no alarm and said little about the bigger picture. He did, however, note some of the most alarming details, including a comment in 2016 from an architect of North Carolina’s congressional map securing a 10-3 Republican advantage in the House of Representatives. The legislator stopped at 10-3—in a state that is fairly evenly split between Republicans and Democrats—because he did “not believe it [would be] possible to draw a map with 11 Republicans and 2 Democrats”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Judges cannot stop stunts like this, even those that may “reasonably seem unjust”, Chief Justice Roberts wrote, because challenges to engineered maps “present political questions beyond the reach of the federal courts”. Objections to partisan gerrymandering are, in technical terms, “non-justiciable”. Federal courts “have no license to reallocate political power between the two major political parties”, the chief justice wrote, because there are “no legal standards to limit and direct their decisions”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In dissent, Justice Kagan replied with a truism: what the court says “can’t be done &lt;em&gt;has&lt;/em&gt; been done”. In recent years, “federal courts across the country...have largely converged on a standard for adjudicating partisan gerrymandering claims” and struck down maps drafted by both parties that are extreme outliers. The same advances in technology that permit modern gerrymanderers to carve precise maps to entrench their power afford challengers a tool to demonstrate just how engineered the lines are. In North Carolina, the Republican Party&amp;#x27;s map was, according to software analysis, “the absolute worst of 3,001 possible maps” for Democrats, the “only one that could produce a 10–3 partisan split even as Republicans got a bare majority of the state-wide vote”. The chief may fret over how much partisanship is too much, and declare that there is nowhere to draw a line, but, the dissent argues, surely the courts could agree that such a map is unfair to voters of the state’s minority party.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a rather feeble attempt to soften the blow of his decision, Chief Justice Roberts wrote that the majority’s “conclusion does not condone excessive partisan gerrymandering” and points to reform measures in Congress and in the states that could ease redistricting concerns. Several states have, indeed, turned line-drawing over to independent commissions in an attempt to push toward fairer maps. But curiously, in 2015, Chief Justice Roberts wrote a strong dissent in a case &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2015/07/02/one-for-the-people&quot;&gt;narrowly upholding&lt;/a&gt; the constitutionality of just such a commission in Arizona. That solution may not survive another challenge in the hands of the Supreme Court’s strengthened conservative majority. And the chief set himself up for ridicule when observing that a redistricting reform bill, first drafted in 2005, “has been reintroduced in every Congress since”. Well, Justice Kagan quipped, it “might be reintroduced until the end of time”. What all the proposals “have in common”, she wrote, “is that they are not laws”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which brings us back to Locke. There is an obvious reason why legislative fixes are not on the horizon. “The politicians who benefit from partisan gerrymandering”, like judges in their own cases, have no incentive to deal fairly with rivals. These legislators “are unlikely to change partisan gerrymandering” and because they “maintain themselves in office through partisan gerrymandering, the chances for legislative reform are slight”. With no one watching over them, and with increasingly sophisticated methods of identifying optimal maps to warp elections, legislators are now empowered to gerrymander at will. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Partisan redistricting has already “debased and dishonoured our democracy”, Justice Kagan wrote, “turning upside-down the core American idea that all governmental power derives from the people”. But with the door now shut on lawsuits and assurances that no one in the federal judiciary will meddle in their plans, gerrymandering legislators have a green light to skew electoral maps exactly as they please—a regime that could “irreparably damage our system of government”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 01:40:28 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Containing Iran, reparations for slavery and Europe’s problem with veggie burgers]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/28/containing-iran-reparations-for-slavery-and-europes-problem-with-veggie-burgers]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T17:00:34Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A SELECTION of three essential articles read aloud from the latest issue of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;. This week: how t&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/29/as-america-and-iran-inch-closer-to-war-new-talks-are-needed&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;he world should contain &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/29/as-america-and-iran-inch-closer-to-war-new-talks-are-needed&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Iran&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;; the debate around &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/06/29/the-idea-of-reparations-for-slavery-is-morally-appealing-but-flawed&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;reparations for slavery&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (09:08); and Europe heroically defends itself against &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/29/europe-heroically-defends-itself-against-veggie-burgers&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;veggie burgers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (16:30). Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-june28th2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 00:40:29 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Who are the members of the Conservative Party?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/06/28/who-are-the-members-of-the-conservative-party]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_BLP515.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T14:24:02Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JEREMY HUNT and Boris Johnson are on the hustings, travelling through Britain to seek support for their bids to succeed Theresa May as leader of the Conservative Party, and thus as prime minister. They are not trying to charm millions of voters, just the considerably more exclusive franchise of the Conservative Party’s membership. Whoever polls highest will be declared the winner on July 22nd and move into Downing Street the next day. To some this may seem an eccentric, even undemocratic way to pick the leader of an advanced democracy. But by precedent, the sole criterion to be prime minister is that he or she must command a majority in the House of Commons. So who are the members of the Conservative Party, and whom are they likely to pick?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All Britain’s main political parties have suffered a decline in membership in recent decades, but none more so than the Tories (see chart). In the 1950s they had nearly 3m members. Now they have about 160,000. They are unrepresentative of Britain: according to research from Queen Mary University of London, 86% of Tory members are middle class and 97% are white, whereas only 54% of Britons are middle class and 87% white. Fully 71% of Tory party members are men and 44% are over 65 years old, compared with 18% of the population as a whole. They are disproportionately concentrated in London and the south of England. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These characteristics help to explain the political attitudes of the membership, particularly when it comes to Brexit. About 60% of those over 65 voted to leave the EU in the referendum of 2016, as did about two-thirds of Tory party members. Now, the overwhelming majority of members oppose holding a second referendum. According to a recent YouGov poll, the Tory membership is so dedicated to Brexit that 54% would be willing to destroy the party itself in order to achieve it. Equally, a majority would be happy to break up the United Kingdom to get Brexit—even though the official name of the Tories is the Conservative and Unionist Party. Members are more socially conservative than the average Tory voter and, on the economy, are more likely to be against any government redistribution. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are the leanings that Messrs Hunt and Johnson have to take into account. They may choose to tack to the political centre at a general election, but to get into Downing Street in the first place they will have to throw some very red meat to the activists. Thus Mr Johnson’s recent declaration Britain would leave the EU on October 31st, “do or die”, might horrify many voters, but the evidence suggests that it is exactly what party members want to hear. A no-deal Brexit holds no fear for many of them: according to the YouGov survey, 44% believe that such an outcome will win the Tories at least the next election. Little wonder, then, that Mr Johnson, who fronted the Leave campaign in 2016, remains the favourite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 00:40:28 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[For women, running is still an act of defiance]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/news/2019/06/28/for-women-running-is-still-an-act-of-defiance]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_efd_001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AT AROUND 5pm on October 28th 2018, the day the clocks went back in Britain, I pulled on my running shoes and left the house. My usual route follows a seven-mile (11km) loop. It starts in the medieval walled city of York, going south on good, firm cycle paths, then on to boggier trails and through a small wood to the nearby village of Bishopthorpe, returning via a few suburban alleys, across a race-course and a paved riverside path. It is flat and untroubled by cars, and I do it once or twice each week, taking one hour and one, two, sometimes even three minutes. As long as it’s not my turn to put my children to bed and I get changed the minute I stop work, I can run and be home before sunset. But on the day the clocks changed, I misjudged things and at 5pm it was already dark. No matter. I shrugged myself into a high-viz vest, donned reflective arm- and ankle-bands, stretched my new head-torch around my forehead, and left the house.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve run for over a decade, since my mid-20s. When I started it brought me little pleasure. I had been running for only a couple of weeks—short bursts, on treadmills—when I decided to jog eight miles along the road from a holiday cottage in the Yorkshire Dales to the nearest town. I wore an ancient pair of Converse and arrived in Pateley Bridge with acute achilles tendonitis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But I kept running. It fed my tendency to link worth with quantification. I valued things that could be enumerated and their progress measured. I relished the data: the distances, personal bests, calories burnt. But I found running physically unpleasant. My hip and knee would hurt. I would take ever more ibuprofen to get through a half-mara­thon, until I could no longer run through the pain and had to stop. I ran because I felt like I should be a runner. But because it hurt and I was never as fast as I wanted to be, my runs were suffused with a sense of failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Only after having children in my mid-30s did running become something else. Unexpectedly, seven months of enforced rest during pregnancy, and physiotherapy for pelvic misalignment and pain, dealt with my niggles. Running again, I felt good as new. I swapped road running for softer paths to protect my pelvis. At first I ran around the muddy perimeter of our local London park, then delved into Epping Forest. When we moved up to York, I discovered the North York Moors and the delights of longer distances across flowering purple heather, through ancient woodlands, and along cliffs cascading down to apricot beaches. And running offered freedom. A day in the hills was rare, precious time in charge of my body and mind, when I could be alone without a child clamouring for sweets or bum-wiping or “Paw Patrol”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I discovered that running up and down hills, vaulting tree roots and crunching along forest paths come with genuine, unquantifiable physical pleasures: clean, sharp air in hard-working lungs. A sudden downpour on parched salty skin. A cold pint in a lakeside pub after a summer run, and a cup of tea and toasted teacake in a village café in winter. The miraculous release from gravity’s pull at the top of a hill, followed by a childlike caper down the other side, with arms outstretched like a plane.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On October 28th the first mile took me along cycle paths, yellow in the glare of street lamps. It was the perfect temperature, just cold enough to slice through the torpor left by a day spent in a centrally heated, fluorescent-lit office. Running brought me back to my body, as if I possessed the liquid soul which the Greek Stoics called pneuma and it was trickling back into me, pushing up against the inside of my skin and inflating me with life. It felt wonderful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the first mile, my route diverged onto a track that banked onto empty fields below. A small aperture ahead turned silver in the light of my headtorch, but all around was unvariegated charcoal. My stomach lurched and my heart rate increased. I kicked up my heels faster, hurd­ling clods and tussocks to the next stile. “Am I an idiot”, I wondered, “to have come out here, in the dark, alone?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I run, I tend to meditate on uncomplicated things (paint colours for a room I’m decorating) or I work over mathematical puzzles (the time it will take me to finish an upcoming race, say). Sometimes these transmute into more fearful wonderings, like whether I will get home safely. I know that women are much more vulnerable to assault in their own homes than in dark alleys or parks. I know that by far the majority of rapes, assaults and murders of women are perpetrated by men known to them. I know that not all men are violent, but I also know that in 2017-18 in Britain 93% of those prosecuted for violence against women and girls were men. And I know of women attacked or murdered while running: among them Karina Vetrano, Mollie Tibbetts, Wendy Martinez, all since 2016. Women may be more at risk in the home, but they aren’t necessarily safe outside it, either.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My fear is not all in my head. I have twice been chased by men as I ran. One jogged beside me with a cigarette for nearly a mile, falling away when I sped off. The second was more sinister, and I had to duck into a stranger’s driveway and pretend to knock at the door. I’ve been surrounded by men on mopeds chanting “Cunt! Cunt! Cunt!” I’ve had cigarette smoke deliberately blown into my face, been spat at, tripped up, lunged at, and received heckles, cat-calls and honks: “You look like a paedophile in those leggings!”; “Can’t you run faster than that?”; “Give us a smile, love!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am not alone. “Female runners,” I tweeted not long ago, “would you run alone in the dark?” Stories flooded in: a woman who runs at night only if her neighbours are home to watch for her return. Women who stopped running in the dark after being grabbed or followed or encouraged to get into strangers’ cars, then stopped running alone in the day after facing similar intimidation, and then stopped running altogether. Women who run alone only if accom­panied by a dog or rape alarm or, in America, mace or even a gun carried in a sporty holster under a running skirt. Running’s emotional windfalls couple a sense of profound freedom with moments of euphoric joy. But for me they are always cut through with the fear that as I run alone, a man will abduct, rape, attack or murder me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, as the dark path spilled onto a nearby village’s high street, and propelled me through squares of light from pubs and fish-and-chip shops, I sighed, relieved. But soon I was back in the blackness, running through an alley onto an unlit cycle path bordering deep fields. In the distance, a small bright light swooped closer: a cyclist. “Thank god,” I thought, “a chaperone.” But then I doubled back: “Oh shit, no, maybe he’s a rapist?” Panicky, I tried to rationalise away my fear. From a distance, perhaps I was not distinguishable as a woman? But I’m not tall and the height of my head-torch probably gave me away. Perhaps I could outrun him? But I could not outrun a bike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we passed one another, I kept my gaze down, reluctant to make eye contact. My fear was disproportionate, but not groundless. How do you calibrate fear to a small but nonetheless existent risk? What is the appropriate level of fear to feel that you probably, but not certainly, won’t be attacked? How do you make yourself less afraid anyway?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The freedom that running promises is complicated for many women. It is often hard-won, limited in scope, perhaps squeezed into brief chinks in a week dominated by the second shift of child care or housework, or tinged with the guilt of temporarily abandoning those duties. The freedom of leaving the house unburdened by anything more than a key in the zip-pocket of your leggings is particularly meaningful for women used to the weight of handbags, buggies, changing bags stuffed with snacks and spare pants. And, as I had found when I was younger, running can be allied to social and psychological forces that inhibit and control us—anorexia, orthorexia, OCD—as much as it has the potential to free us from those forces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On that particular run, I began to fantasise about a night-time male curfew. Without this fear, what would I do at night? Nothing very dramatic: simply allow my life to unfold into the full 24 hours of day and night. I’d run, anxiety-free, alone in a forest after dark. After a night out, I’d go straight to bed, without waiting up to hear that the female friends I’d been with were home safely. I wouldn’t double- and triple-check the locks on my windows and doors, as I’ve done every evening since I woke one night in my 20s to find an unknown man leaning over my bed, half-suspended through an unlocked window. I wouldn’t endlessly revisit memories of a childhood neighbour—a woman who lived alone—who was raped on the hottest night of the summer by a man who climbed onto her balcony and through her French windows. And I wouldn’t walk home with a makeshift weapon of keys wedged between my fingers, as I’ve done ever since, aged 14, we girls were taken aside at school and solemnly warned of the need to protect ourselves against rape—as if rape were an inevitable natural force, like black ice, and not the result of men’s decisions. (The boys were not subjected to cautionary sessions advising them not to rape women.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In similar conversations on Twitter recently women have pondered what they would do if men disappeared for 24 hours. Thousands took part. Like me, many fantasised about wearing headphones or heels at night, leaving windows open, travelling home alone from gigs, forgoing bras under their clothes, booking Airbnbs in cheaper, less salu­brious locations. But most often, women’s dreams were variations of being able to “walk alone at night, anywhere I wanted, and not be afraid” or “go for a run really late at night”. Their imaginings are striking in their banality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After 12 more minutes running, the path I was on joined up with a road and then, home, safe! I stopped my watch: my average pace had been 15 seconds a kilometre faster than usual. I unlocked the front door. My heartbeat slowed and I sank on to the staircase’s bottom step. I thought that I probably wouldn’t run again off-road at night, on my own. Running, or rather not running, had become yet another adjustment that women make all year long in an attempt to avoid becoming victims of assault, adjustments that become more urgent in winter when our lives are constrained by the ever-shortening daylight hours. And look how I’m talking about this, as if what is wrong here is the shifting of the seasons, or the tilt of the Earth’s axis, or the decision in 1916 to move the clocks back in autumn to increase productivity in the morning—anything but the fact that some men deliberately intimidate and assault and kill women, and that one of the more minor but not insignificant outcomes of that fact is that so very many women do not run alone in the dark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Men have long tried to control women’s running. In the 18th century thousands of spectators gawped at women running in “smock-races” (the prize was often a smock) at village fairs. In the 19th century men bet on female speed-walkers traipsing around tracks in pub gardens. Some running women—such as Greek mythology’s Atalanta, who killed the male suitors she outran—rejected the trappings of femininity. They challenged everything that kept them sexually submissive, physically dependent and domestically servile. No wonder men tried to control and limit them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some men would try to sabotage the female athletes’ feats. At a pub in Bradford in 1864, Emma Sharp, who was attempting to cover 1,000 miles in 1,000 hours, defended herself with pistols against men trying to win their bets by pressing chloroform-soaked cloths into her face. Others fared even worse. In 1874 a Wolverhampton farmer called James Alcock was convicted of assaulting Rebecca Richards, a competitive female runner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Criticism came from other quarters too but the intent was the same: to stop women in their tracks. Journalists derided women’s foot-racing as “unnatural” and “dangerous”. This mirrored the rise of pseudo-scientific medical claims about women’s physiological and psychological frailty. As early as 1827, a medic warned that vigorous “exertion” in post-pubescent women threatened their reproductive health “by wearing out the powers of the body”. In 1928 newspapers reported the apparent collapse of female athletes on the finish line of the 800 metres at the Amsterdam Olympics: one journalist concluded that “women are not built physically to undergo the strain of races. Nature made them to bear children”—as if childbirth were a walk in the park. Women were then banned from Olympic events longer than 100 metres, roughly the length of a football pitch. As late as the 1970s, officials justified this exclusion on the basis that “women are too weak and fragile” and their “reproductive organs would get damaged.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 1967 Kathrine Switzer entered the male-only Boston Marathon under her initials, K.V. Switzer. Once the starting gun had been fired, race official Jock Semple realised that a woman was running and tried to manhandle her off the course, bellowing “Get the hell out of my race,” before Switzer’s male running partner shoved him aside. Switzer completed the run in 4 hours 20 minutes, disproving claims that women were too frail to run long distances. Boston Athletic Association director Will Cloney reacted by threatening “if that girl were my daughter, I would spank her.” But in 1972 the Boston Marathon directors capitulated and formally permitted women to run. Other marathons followed suit but change has been slow. Women’s distance-running events—those longer than 1,500 metres—were not included in the Olympics until 1984.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The history of women’s exclusion still hangs over the running world. Books on running typically feature a silhouette of a single, sleek male physique on the cover. Women are mostly invisible in the stories of bestsellers such as Christopher McDougall’s “Born to Run”, a macho account of ultra-runners in Mexico and America. Those who do appear are scrutinised with the male gaze. In his memoir, “What I Talk About When I Talk About Running”, novelist Haruki Murakami depicts long-distance running as a serious test of mental and physical endurance closely aligned with novel writing. But only the men in his book are up to the task. Its women, with their “blonde hair in a ponytail, and brand-new iPods” are “more mentally cut out for brief runs at high speed.” “Still,” Murakami consoles himself, “it’s pretty wonderful to watch these pretty girls run.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women’s exclusion from running played on my mind in July last year in the Ultimate Trails race, a 55km route around England’s Lake District. Compared with other races in which I’ve participated, the number of women on the start line was unusually high. Female participation in running has steadily risen at all distances and levels since the 1980s. Women’s presence in ultra-distance trail races increased from about 5% of all contestants in the 1990s to around 20-25% today, but it is still well short of parity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cause and consequence of this imbalance is that most races are designed with men in mind. Rules and regulations are often based on the assumption that runners have male bodies. The 106-mile Ultra-Trail du Mont Blanc (UTMB) is one of the most famous and popular trail races in the world. Runners who achieve a rare, hard-won place and then develop an injury can defer to a later year. But female competitors who become pregnant or give birth are not offered a deferral and can obtain a refund only if the race occurs within 15 days of giving birth, after which women are considered to have returned to race form.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A photograph of a runner called Sophie Power at a checkpoint during the 2018 race, breast-feeding her three-month-old son while also expressing milk, went viral as a “powerful and positive” image of a mother’s autonomous identity and strength. Yet it also encapsulated the sexist inconsistency of the UTMB’s deferral policy. Power went to extraordinary lengths to compete: she put aside extra time for expressing; arranged to meet and feed her son during a long, often remote event; and raced that distance in the wake of a lighter training load during pregnancy, the physical exertion of childbirth, and the sleep deprivation that follows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Long-distance races usually set “cut-offs”, deadlines by which runners must have passed certain points or finished. Cut-offs allow organisers and marshalls to pack up and re-open roads, but they also filter slower runners from the competition. At all levels, from amateur to elite, and at all distances, from 100 metres to 1,000 miles, men’s higher aerobic capacity, lower body fat, greater haemoglobin content and muscle mass, bigger hearts and larger proportion of fast-twitch muscles, make the average male runner around 10% quicker than the average female competitor (although this varies according to distance). So the more stringent the cut-off, the more disproportionately will female competitors be timed out or deterred from entering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This phenomenon is visible in the annual Lakeland Trails marathon around Coniston in the Lake District. There are two versions: both are the same length, but one, the Challenge, has a liberal cut-off of eight hours, and the other, the Race, ends after only six. Female participation in the Challenge is high at around 50%. But it is only 25% in the Race, even though around half of female Challenge finishers typically complete in under six hours anyway. Sports-science studies confirm the obvious implication: men tend to overestimate their speediness but women do the opposite and underestimate their own abilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When women are included in competitions, it’s often grudging. Women’s races are frequently accorded less time and space than men’s. The English Cross Country Association—the governing body of cross-country running in England—still allows women in the national championships to run only 8km, two-thirds of the length of the men’s race. In the South of England Championships, men run almost twice as far as women. The World Mountain Running Association had the same rules—senior women raced 8km compared with men’s 12km—until January 2017, when they responded positively to a campaign to equalise men’s and women’s distances to 10km each.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preventing women from running as far as men is partly the legacy of Victorian anxiety about women’s lack of endurance, and partly based on “traditionalists’” argument that “women are not as fast” and require a shorter race “so that it takes the same amount of time”. But, as campaigner Maud Hodson points out, women are not a third or half as slow as men, as the cropping of their races might suggest. And, in any case, the South of England Championship doesn’t actually equalise the time spent on the men’s and women’s races. Male runners are granted twice the time women are—90 minutes to women’s 45—which assumes that they are in fact running at the same speed. With double the time and almost double the distance of the women, are men considered “twice as important”?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This matters. It’s important that women are included in running events, that the specificities of our bodies and lives are considered. The presence of other women in a run can offer a kind of solidarity, a diminished embarrassment derived from shared bodily experience, especially when it comes to the more intimate aspects of ultra-running, such as going to the toilet out in the open. Most importantly, running offers specific joys that are often missing from women’s lives: a focus on strength and health and pleasure rather than thinness and acquiescence. We should not be denied these opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the morning of the Ultimate Trails race, the unusually hot weather forecast led the race directors to revise the mandatory kit list. Warm hats and waterproof trousers were struck off. Instead we were advised to carry two litres of water. I was conscious of the extra weight in my running pack as soon as we left Ambleside. The burning ache in my lower back gradually bore down into my thighs. By the time we reached a short section of road that rises steeply—aptly named “The Struggle”—each lift of a leg was immediately suckered back down again by gravity, and my pack was starting to rub against the edges of my breasts. The bag had been advertised as unisex. In reality it was cut for the planes of a man’s body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women’s running kit has been improving steadily since the 1980s. Shoes, for example, are now fitted to women’s physiology. But women still have far less choice than men. The Ultramarathon Running Store currently sells four times as many unisex—that is to say, male—running packs, as those cut for women. I have never found a running cap or pair of gloves tight enough to fit my only-slightly-smaller-than-average female body. At races, the smallest size of finishers’ T-shirt is often still way too big.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lack of specific provision undoubtedly reflects women’s lesser participation in running. But it works both ways. Bras with insufficient support, running packs chafing our breasts, hats and head-torches slipping down over our eyes are all irritants that disfigure our pleasure and discourage women from taking part. This discomfort starts young. Sports clothing advertised for girls is consistently less durable, less waterproof and less accommodating of movement than the equivalent for young boys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Things are slowly changing. The standard approach to designing women’s garments has been to “shrink and pink” the male version, says Helen Stuart, a designer at Inov-8, which makes running gear. Stuart starts with the women’s design, then adapts it for men. Making products for female bodies is harder so it makes sense to begin with them, she argues. Innovative firms such as EVB Sport are producing active wear specifically to support women’s perineum, pelvic floor and core muscles. But they are still the exception.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the race’s first checkpoint, at the top of Kirkstone Pass, I needed to ease the pain caused by my poorly fitting hydration pack. I decided to reduce its weight, by emptying the reservoir and relying on the water in my flasks. Relieved of a kilo, my feet began to accelerate happily down the path towards Brothers Water, a long downhill trail, peppered with large unstable stones that require nimble legs to sail over without injury. Within a mile, I was not only returned to mental and physical wellbeing, but leapt beyond it to what is often called “runner’s high”: the joy of efficiently working muscles and lungs, oblivion to pain or fatigue and sensory bliss; sun on my face, mountains mirrored in still water, shady paths quenching the skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teetering down a rocky, ankle-imperilling descent into Grasmere, I had to brake suddenly and veer behind a hedge. Since giving birth to twins in 2014, my pelvic floor—the sling of muscles running from the back to the front of the body—has been shot to pieces. I’m one of around 35% of women in Britain who are affected by pelvic-floor disorders (compared with around 4% of men), a propensity that is hugely increased by pregnancy and birth, especially instrumental deliveries, and exacerbated by a lack of post-natal care. In France, pelvic-floor physiotherapy is offered to post-partum women as standard; not so in Britain. Many go back to high-impact sports, such as running, that strain the pelvic floor, without adequate physical checks or advice, resulting in even greater damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Childbirth has left me with a cystocele and rectocele (when the bladder and rectum respectively collapse into the vaginal wall) and a uterine prolapse (when the uterus drops into the vagina). These affect my running in different ways. The uterine prolapse is painful; an aching sensation, like a ball of descending pressure. But I wear a vaginal pessary, a sturdy silicone ring, slightly smaller than my palm, which sits neatly under my cervix as a crutch for my sagging uterus. Because of the cystocele, I also need to wear incontinence pads when I run. They need changing frequently, and during the Ultimate Trails race, I carried five, which took up more than half of my running pack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s embarrassing, too. Trail races rarely pass public toilets, and many are unusable anyway. In Britain, since 2010 councils have given up the maintenance of 13% of public facilities, and as many as a third have closed entirely. When I’m out running, I have to duck behind a bush or wall to change my pad every 12km or so. I’m particularly leaky running downhill. If I don’t stop in time, my pad overflows, shadowing my shorts with urine, and it chafes too, rubbing my thighs sore. During my period, the whole procedure becomes even messier and I carry a small pack of wet-wipes to clean my hands of blood. It’s no surprise that a survey of female runners showed that many are deterred from long-distance running by the lack of toilet provision. The paucity of loos on a mountain or moor is unavoidable, and to an extent one becomes inured to pulling down your pants in the countryside. But city races present a much higher level of exposure and embarrassment. There is some hope, though. Louise Greenwood, race director of the Canalathon ultra in Rochdale, has secured permission from pubs en route for competitors to use their toilets. Nevertheless, there’s scope for urban races—where most runners start, and many consequently stop—to make much better provision for women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trail-running is as much about caring for your body as it is about revelling in the scenery. Every runner’s body has a series of eloquent “tells”. I’ve learned that I’m adequately hydrated, salted and fed when my inner voice exclaims with pleasant surprise, “I feel fine. I really do.” Or when I’m able to greet marshalls and other runners with chirpiness. Or when I can sigh happily at the top of a steep ascent, as gravity shifts from encumbrance to emancipation. But I know I’m getting closer to hitting the wall when I panic about mild physical niggles; when I feel bored or obsessed with the finish line; or when I’m grumpy and suffused with nausea. It has taken me years not only to develop this listening habit but to learn to act on it. Women are not supposed to care for our bodies. We’re supposed to beat them into submission instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I approached the final two miles of the race, I knew I’d got it right. I had enough energy to speed up, hurtling down the final paved slope, swooping over the footbridge and around the cricket pitch, and over the finish line in 10 hours 12 minutes. The finish-line photograph shows me sweaty, dusty, spots emerging across my face after spending a day doused in salt, hair matted against my head, and utterly triumphant and proud and strong and happy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Rachel Hewittis a lecturer in creative writing at Newcastle University. She is working on a book, “In Her Nature”, about women’s relationships with the natural world&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 00:40:27 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>