<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[“Late Night Feelings”, Mark Ronson’s new album, is a delight]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/24/late-night-feelings-mark-ronsons-new-album-is-a-delight]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_BKP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-24T13:17:24Z&quot;&gt;Jun 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE FIRST single from “Late Night Feelings”, Mark Ronson’s new album, was released back in November. “Nothing Breaks Like a Heart”, a terrific, Dolly Parton-esque track featuring Miley Cyrus, was an instant hit, and has scored nearly 250m plays on Spotify to date. A number of interviews followed in which Mr Ronson talked about the album: with the BBC in November, the &lt;em&gt;Sunday Times&lt;/em&gt; in December, the &lt;em&gt;Guardian&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Interview&lt;/em&gt; magazine in February. One of the themes of those pieces was his discontent with a world in which artists were forced by their paymasters to churn out hits of diminishing quality, making records to appeal to algorithms rather than to satisfy their own artistic urges.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It seemed an odd thing to say as “Nothing Breaks Like a Heart” racked up the streams. Then the four subsequent singles did not come close to matching that success—the second most popular, “Find U Again”, has 225m fewer streams on Spotify—and “Late Night Feelings” did not appear. The official line from the Ronson camp is that the album was always scheduled for June, and that it wasn’t announced until April. Yet all those interviews talked about the album in some depth, and the interviewers had clearly heard it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Ronson became a superstar in 2015 with the release of “Uptown Funk”, a catchy funk-pop song featuring Bruno Mars, and one of the best-selling singles of all time. It turned Mr Ronson into the kind of artist on whom major record labels rely to generate revenue, and to prove to other artists that they know how to sell music by the truckload. Labels want their superstars to carry on being superstars: if someone makes them a great deal of money making party hits, they tend to want more of the same. So while the official line is that “Late Night Feelings” was always meant to be coming out now, it wouldn’t be a huge surprise if at some point in the future Sony reveals that it had wanted more obvious hits on one of their marquee albums for 2019, and had offered Mr Ronson more time to make them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Luckily “Late Night Feelings” is worth the wait. It is both very old-fashioned and very modern. Mr Ronson has said that it is an album of “sad bangers”—meaning songs both heartbroken and catchy—which happens to be one of pop’s more notable trends (Robyn, the current critical darling, is a queen of the sad banger). It is also a notion that is at the heart of some of the very best pop music of the 1970s: ABBA, especially, and huge tranches of disco (see “I Will Survive”).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It might seem a curious move for Mr Ronson, who is best known for party music: “Valerie”, with Amy Winehouse, from 2007; the all-conquering “Uptown Funk”; “Electricity”, the single he and his friend Diplo made in 2018 with the singer Dua Lipa. The one word you wouldn’t have used to describe Mr Ronson’s past work is “personal”, but this time it is inspired by his own despair after the breakdown of his marriage (even if he is just one of scores of writers on each track, and as ever, it is guests—Lykke Li, Camila Cabello, King Princess, Yebba, Alicia Keys, Ms Cyrus, Angel Olsen, Diana Gordon, Ilsey—doing the singing).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, this is a rather lovely album. In theory putting a number of very good writers, musicians and singers together on one record will produce something worthwhile, but in reality that is not always the case. Mr Ronson, though, has a gift for synthesising the contributions of others into something coherent, and he clearly sticks with people he trusts. “Late Night Feelings” features members of the Dap-Kings, a soul group which played on Winehouse’s “Back to Black” (produced by Mr Ronson), Kevin Parker of Tame Impala, and the Parisian production duo The Picard Brothers. Between them, they’ve made a gorgeous, lush, melodic record, the kind that—and this is meant as praise—you can imagine popping up in bar scenes and montages in decent romantic comedies for years to come.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shame is that “Late Night Feelings” deserved all those big interviews this month, to give it the biggest push. Its big hit single should have come out two weeks before release, rather than seven months before, to maximise momentum. It is a terrific album—even if it doesn’t include another “Uptown Funk”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 20:40:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“It&#x27;s frankly sent us all a bit crazy”—how Brexit divided Britons]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/24/its-frankly-sent-us-all-a-bit-crazy-how-brexit-divided-britons]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_blm520.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-24T09:48:54Z&quot;&gt;Jun 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EXACTLY THREE years after the referendum result, it’s clear: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/briefing/2019/06/20/how-brexit-made-britain-a-country-of-remainers-and-leavers&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brexit&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; has driven Britain a bit batty. We look into the grand societal divides that the vote exposed. In &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/22/a-re-election-in-istanbul-tests-president-erdogans-power&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Istanbul&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, a repeat mayoral election reaches the same result: the ruling party lost. President Recep Tayyip Erdogan no longer seems so invincible. And, in Kenya, an “Uber for ambulances” saves time and lives. Runtime: 22 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/dc2ac083-d9e5-41de-9a6c-ad98c204e180&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 20:40:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How Americans became workaholics]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/23/how-americans-became-workaholics]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_wbd001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-23T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMERICANS LIKE to work hard whereas Europeans prefer a more leisurely life. That is the widely held perception of the continental divide in business culture. But it has not always been the case; 40 years ago, there was precious little difference between the two.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his new book, “Spending Time: The Most Valuable Resource”, Daniel Hamermesh, an economist, examines how work and leisure patterns in America differ from those in the rest of the developed world. In the first half of the 20th century the American working week fell sharply from nearly 60 hours to around 40. By 1979 the average worker in America put in around 38.2 hours a week, similar to the number in Europe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is where the figures started to diverge. For a while, the American workweek got longer, reaching 39.4 hours in 2000, before falling back to 38.6 in 2016. The main difference, however, is holidays. In the 1980s Europeans began to take more annual leave but Americans did not. Over the year as a whole, Americans average 34 hours a week, six more than the French and eight more than the Germans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What explains this gap? Some point to cultural reasons but, as Mr Hamermesh points out, it is hard to see why American culture suddenly diverged from that of the rest of the world in the last 40 years. Others point to lower taxes, which raise the value of putting in the extra hour. Yet American taxes were lower than European rates back in the 1960s, when working hours were similar. Another potential explanation is a decline in trade union membership has weakened American workers’ bargaining power—except that unionisation rates in France and America are not far apart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A more plausible reason is policy. There is no legal requirement to offer paid vacations in America, whereas France mandates a minimum of 25 days, and Germany, 24. Famously, France also limits the working week to 35 hours. Mr Hamermesh finds similar examples in Asia. In the 1980s and 1990s, Japan passed laws reducing the standard working week from 48 hours to 40. Beyond that, workers were entitled to overtime pay. A similar process occurred in South Korea between 2004 and 2008. Employers responded by cutting hours; workers earned less as a result but surveys found they were happier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In America, by contrast, champions of workers’ rights have recently focused on raising the minimum wage (so far to little avail at the federal level, though some states have enacted more generous wage floors). Wage gains have certainly skewed toward the better-off. The median American worker makes about $20 an hour while the worker at the 95th percentile makes $62. That is a ratio of 3.1. Back in 1979, the ratio was 2.2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These higher wages do seem to have had an incentive effect. High-paid employees work 8-9 more hours a week than the lowest-paid. In part, this may reflect the low earnings of part-time workers, who have grown as a share of the workforce. Either way, the gap has widened since the late 1970s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But don’t shed too many tears for the wealthy. They may work more hours, but the poor often work more inconvenient ones. It is a myth to say that well-paid workers put in more hours at the weekends or at night, Mr Hamermesh says. It is cleaners and food delivery people who work when it is dark, not bankers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what is going on? John Maynard Keynes dreamed that his grandchildren would be working only 15 hours a week. But the decline in hours which the economist predicted slowed after the 1970s. This may hint that 35-40 hours is close to the most efficient working period. Any more and workers become too stressed; any less and companies lose too much production. But it is also a sign that Keynes was wrong to think that society would place a high value on extra leisure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the developed world most workers have more than enough to feed themselves and their families. But they still want &amp;quot;positional&amp;quot; goods—homes in a good location, holidays in sun-drenched resorts and possessions that demonstrate their social status. Prices of these goods will be pushed higher, driving status-seeking employees to work more hours to earn them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So whatever labour-saving gadgets Silicon Valley dreams up, future generations will probably still have to put in a long shift. But Americans could enjoy a bit more holiday. Those who feel the same ought to ask their politicians why Europeans should get more rest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 20:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The opposition’s new star deals Turkey’s president a stinging blow]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/24/the-oppositions-new-star-deals-turkeys-president-a-stinging-blow]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_blp903.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-24T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 24th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THIS TIME around, there was no room for doubt. In late March Ekrem Imamoglu had won the Istanbul mayoral election by a fraction of a percentage point. On June 23rd he won the re-run by a landslide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Imamoglu’s victory in the rerun was the best showing for any opposition politician in decades, and Turkey’s biggest city celebrated in style. Street parties erupted in some neighbourhoods. “Sunny days will come,” sang a crowd of young people by the Bosphorus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Given the scale of Mr Imamoglu’s success, there was no room for the antics that Turkey’s president, Recep Tayyip Erdogan, pulled last time to deny the new mayor his first victory. Then, after Mr Imamoglu prevailed by just 13,000 votes, Mr Erdogan and his ruling Justice and Development (AK) party challenged the outcome, accused the opposition of stealing the vote and leaned heavily on the country’s election board to order a repeat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The move turned out to be one of the worst gambits of Mr Erdogan’s career. In the new election, Mr Imamoglu received a solid 54% of the vote to 45% for AK’s candidate, Binali Yildirim, a former prime minister—a margin of over 800,000. Turnout reached 85%, boosted by thousands of Istanbul residents who cancelled or interrupted their holidays to be home on election day. Mr Yildrim conceded in front of the cameras as soon as the first results were made public. In a written statement, Mr Erdogan congratulated the new mayor shortly thereafter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Imamoglu forged a coalition that included his secular Republican People’s Party (CHP), Kurdish voters, a breakaway nationalist group and some Islamists. But he has also earned the sympathy and the votes of a growing number of disenchanted ruling-party supporters. A street vendor in one conservative Istanbul neighborhood said he was so appalled by the re-run decision that he chose to stop voting AK. “What they did to Imamoglu was an injustice,” he said. “There’s been too much corruption,” another former AK voter said. “They made too many mistakes.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Imamoglu’s success should be a lesson for his party, says Fehmi Koru, a newspaper columnist. By running a relentlessly positive campaign and refusing to play by the rules of Turkey’s identity politics, he was able to make inroads with conservative voters, something the CHP has not managed for decades. Assuming that Mr Imamoglu can reshape the party in his own image, it might finally broaden its reach. The CHP has long been unable to attract more than 25% or so of the electorate. Mr Imamoglu may soon shine on the national stage, says Mr Koru, though he needs to prove he can run Istanbul. Success in Turkey’s largest city as mayor was exactly how Mr Erdogan himself rose to prominence in the 1990s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now, however, Mr Erdogan remains in charge of the country. Turkey’s leader enjoys sweeping executive powers, which he can use to undermine Mr Imamoglu. He also retains the support of the Nationalist Movement Party (MHP), which gives him control of the parliament. At least in theory, Mr Erdogan does not have to face another election for four years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the ground beneath his feet is starting to shake. Emboldened by Mr Imamoglu’s success, some estranged AK politicians, already poised to launch a rival conservative party, might do so sooner rather than later. The economy, which clawed its way out of recession a few months ago, faces the risk of another downturn later this year. Possible American sanctions over Mr Erdogan’s purchase of a Russian missile-defence system would compound the damage severely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The opposition at last has the wind at its back, with an inspiring new leader. Together with Istanbul, the CHP and its allies now control municipalities that account for roughly 70% of Turkey’s economy, says Sinan Ulgen of Carnegie Europe, a think-tank. “They now have the means to fund their political activities, and to eliminate AK’s network of patronage,” he says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Imamoglu, meanwhile, has the country’s attention, a mandate to shake up his own party and a chance to heal a divided society. “The era of partisanship is over,” he said in a victory speech in front of a crowd of elated supporters. “The era of rights, law and justice is here.” Elsewhere, the same words might sound bland. In today’s Turkey, as Mr Erdogan knows, they are nothing short of revolutionary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 18:40:01 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The American exception]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/23/the-american-exception]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_wbd001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-23T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMERICANS LIKE to work hard whereas Europeans prefer a more leisurely life. That is the widely held perception of the continental divide in business culture. But it has not always been the case; 40 years ago, there was precious little difference between the two.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In his new book, “Spending Time: The Most Valuable Resource”, Daniel Hamermesh, an economist, examines how work and leisure patterns in America differ from those in the rest of the developed world. In the first half of the 20th century the American working week fell sharply from nearly 60 hours to around 40. By 1979 the average worker in America put in around 38.2 hours a week, similar to the number in Europe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is where the figures started to diverge. For a while, the American workweek got longer, reaching 39.4 hours in 2000, before falling back to 38.6 in 2016. The main difference, however, is holidays. In the 1980s Europeans began to take more annual leave but Americans did not. Over the year as a whole, Americans average 34 hours a week, six more than the French and eight more than the Germans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What explains this gap? Some point to cultural reasons but, as Mr Hamermesh points out, it is hard to see why American culture suddenly diverged from that of the rest of the world in the last 40 years. Others point to lower taxes, which raise the value of putting in the extra hour. Yet American taxes were lower than European rates back in the 1960s, when working hours were similar. Another potential explanation is a decline in trade union membership has weakened American workers’ bargaining power—except that unionisation rates in France and America are not far apart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A more plausible reason is policy. There is no legal requirement to offer paid vacations in America, whereas France mandates a minimum of 25 days, and Germany, 24. Famously, France also limits the working week to 35 hours. Mr Hamermesh finds similar examples in Asia. In the 1980s and 1990s, Japan passed laws reducing the standard working week from 48 hours to 40. Beyond that, workers were entitled to overtime pay. A similar process occurred in South Korea between 2004 and 2008. Employers responded by cutting hours; workers earned less as a result but surveys found they were happier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In America, by contrast, champions of workers’ rights have recently focused on raising the minimum wage (so far to little avail at the federal level, though some states have enacted more generous wage floors). Wage gains have certainly skewed toward the better-off. The median American worker makes about $20 an hour while the worker at the 95th percentile makes $62. That is a ratio of 3.1. Back in 1979, the ratio was 2.2.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These higher wages do seem to have had an incentive effect. High-paid employees work 8-9 more hours a week than the lowest-paid. In part, this may reflect the low earnings of part-time workers, who have grown as a share of the workforce. Either way, the gap has widened since the late 1970s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But don’t shed too may tears for the wealthy. They may work more hours, but the poor often work more inconvenient ones. It is a myth to say that well-paid workers put in more hours at the weekends or at night, Mr Hamermesh says. It is cleaners and food delivery people who work when it is dark, not bankers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what is going on? John Maynard Keynes dreamed that his grandchildren would be working only 15 hours a week. But the decline in hours which the economist predicted slowed after the 1970s. This may hint that 35-40 hours is close to the most efficient working period. Any more and workers become too stressed; any less and companies lose too much production. But it is also a sign that Keynes was wrong to think that society would place a high value on extra leisure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the developed world most workers have more than enough to feed themselves and their families. But they still want &amp;quot;positional&amp;quot; goods—homes in a good location, holidays in sun-drenched resorts and possessions that demonstrate their social status. Prices of these goods will be pushed higher, driving status-seeking employees to work more hours to earn them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So whatever labour-saving gadgets Silicon Valley dreams up, future generations will probably still have to put in a long shift. But Americans could enjoy a bit more holiday. Those who feel the same ought to ask their politicians why Europeans should get more rest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 20:17:05 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Ebola response in Congo is running short of money]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/23/the-ebola-response-in-congo-is-running-short-of-money]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_map504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-23T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 23rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SINCE LAST August, when the Ebola outbreak in the Democratic Republic of Congo began, the World Health Organisation (WHO) has published regular reports that make for grim reading. With 2,204 cases and 1,479 deaths as of June 19th, this is the second-largest outbreak of Ebola in history. The failure to eliminate Ebola has been complicated by conflict, politics and the weakness of the country’s health system. Money should not be an issue in this sort of internationally led emergency response. Yet it is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After all, if the Ebola outbreak gets out of control, it will quickly become a multi-billion dollar headache for the world, just as it did in West Africa. But the WHO’s resources are stretched thin for its response in Congo. Since February, it has received donations for less than half of the money it has needed to fight the outbreak, and has now all but used up an emergency fund. The WHO warns that operations could grind to a halt during a critical stage of the outbreak. Member states are being urged to meet the funding gap in order to prevent the response from suffering a “potentially devastating setback”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In February, the projected costs until July were $98m. Of this, the WHO has received from donors only $44m. To stay solvent, the WHO has dipped into a pot of money called the contingency fund for emergencies, or CFE. Since the beginning of the outbreak, it has taken about $73m from the kitty. The CFE is supposed to be there to release money quickly, during a sudden emergency, for example when plague struck Madagascar. It has been used 44 times in the past year. This fast-moving pot of cash can be mobilised in as little as 24 hours and can be critical in life-threatening situations. But the CFE is now “running on fumes” says one spokesperson and is down to less than $4m.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The WHO says it will have to scour its reserves to see if more money can be found. But the scale of the shortfall means that for its next planning period, which starts in July, the WHO may have to restrict its operations. Mike Ryan, head of the WHO’s health emergencies, is reluctant to say the organisation will cut any of its core funding for Ebola. This seems to mean that the WHO will, somehow, find the money for the most mission-critical aspects of the response. However, Mr Ryan also concedes that money has become an “obstacle” to completing the job of eradicating Ebola. Either way, the organisation is clearly facing a challenge finding enough cash. Mr Ryan says the WHO is constantly reprioritising, moving money around, “sometimes robbing Peter to pay Paul”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In recent weeks, pressure has mounted on the WHO to declare an official health emergency in Congo. Some, such as Jeremy Farrar, head of the Wellcome Trust, a charity that supports international health, feel that declaring what is known as a Public Health Emergency of International Concern (PHEIC) would raise awareness about the outbreak and with it more international funding.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Declaring a PHEIC is, strictly speaking, a technical designation that commits the WHO to issuing formal recommendations to countries on how to handle the outbreak. However, declaring a PHEIC does focus attention and might have been expected to help drum up extra money. But the WHO feels that there is moral hazard in declaring an emergency simply to raise money. It also weakens the argument for having money available to deal with outbreaks, so that there is no need to call a PHEIC.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The situation is sufficiently serious that Britain’s international development secretary, Rory Stewart, is planning a number of trips in the next few weeks to persuade other donors among the G7 to stump up more cash as soon as possible. He may also want to raise the issue of the funding gap for preparing neighbouring countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is vital work. According to Tarik Jasarevic, a spokesperson for the WHO, health workers have been trained in infection control, the use of protective gear and creating isolation facilities. Seth Berkley, boss of Gavi, an international vaccine finance agency that has been helping to provide Ebola vaccine, says that close to 5,000 health workers have been vaccinated in 165 facilities in Uganda. Workers in South Sudan and Rwanda have also been jabbed. Already, three cases of Ebola have been confirmed in Uganda. More efforts will be needed to prevent a crisis in one country from becoming a regional disaster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2019 20:17:04 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mark Esper looks set to be America’s next defence secretary]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/22/mark-esper-looks-set-to-be-americas-next-defence-secretary]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-22T06:20:14Z&quot;&gt;Jun 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN THE circumstances, President Donald Trump’s announcement on the evening of June 21st that he intended to nominate Mark Esper to be his defence secretary was as good as could be expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Esper, the current army secretary, would not be a distinguished occupant of the office held by Robert McNamara and Robert Gates. Aside from some odd jobs as a congressional staffer and in the Pentagon, the 55-year-old is best known as a successful former defence industry lobbyist. He has no significant foreign policy experience. Yet he has some credentials lacked by Patrick Shanahan, the acting secretary who will shortly leave the Pentagon: including a decade of active duty service in the army and influential admirers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump had previously announced his intention to nominate Mr Shanahan, a former Boeing executive, to become secretary permanently. Yet he refrained from doing so, as doubts about Mr Shanahan mounted. Though accommodating to the president (including in his support for siphoning billions off his own department’s budget in order to pay for some border fencing) he made no significant mark on the government during six months as acting successor to James Mattis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was a relative non-entity in security discussions on Iran, North Korea and elsewhere, even as Mr Trump contemplated launching military strikes on the former. He resigned from the government this week after the &lt;em&gt;Washington Post&lt;/em&gt; revealed serious incidents of domestic violence in Mr Shanahan’s family (His son beat up his ex-wife with a baseball bat). He was to be replaced, on the same acting basis, by Mr Esper.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This will now complicate Mr Esper’s nomination. He cannot go through a Senate confirmation process for a job he is holding temporarily. He is therefore expected to be replaced as acting secretary of defence by the navy secretary, Richard Spencer. That would mean Mr Trump is set to have four defence secretaries in three years, a record rate of turnover. The administration’s current length of time without a defence secretary, over six months, is another record. (It also has no ambassador to the United Nations or secretary of the Department of Homeland Security, among other security-related jobs). Yet Mr Esper does at least look able to secure Senate confirmation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was confirmed as army secretary by the Senate with a large majority and has admirers there, including Jim Inhofe, chairman of the Senate Armed Services Committee. Whether Mr Esper could restore the primacy that the Pentagon, the federal government’s biggest department, has traditionally enjoyed in security decision-making is another matter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since Mr Mattis resigned, in protest at Mr Trump, the Pentagon has been increasingly sidelined by the National Security Council, under John Bolton, and Secretary of State Mike Pompeo. Mr Trump was &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/21/donald-trump-orders-air-strikes-on-iran-then-cancels-them&quot;&gt;briefly persuaded&lt;/a&gt; to order an air strike on Iran under their belligerent guidance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fact that Mr Esper graduated from West Point in the same class as Mr Pompeo suggests he might have a firm ally in the secretary of state. He might in that case also be expected to support him in Mr Pompeo’s emerging rivalry with Mr Bolton. Given the national security adviser’s particularly extreme bellicosity, that would probably be for the best. Yet the notion that the secretary of defence could play such as secondary role in cabinet politics is also indicative of how far the Pentagon has fallen in the pecking order since Mr Mattis left it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 18:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Which Democrats can challenge Trump in 2020?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/21/which-democrats-can-challenge-donald-trump]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_blp509.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T17:07:04Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ANNE MCELVOY and John Prideaux, &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s US editor, interview two distinctive hopefuls &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/06/20/donald-trump-launches-a-familiar-sounding-re-election-campaign&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;running to replace Donald Trump&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. &lt;strong&gt;Pete Buttigieg&lt;/strong&gt;, the 37-year-old mayor of South Bend, Indiana, assesses America’s role in the world and sets out his plan to redress racial inequality. He also reflects on what he has learned both from Mr Trump and from Leslie Knope, a character in the TV comedy, “Parks and Recreation”. And &lt;strong&gt;Andrew Yang&lt;/strong&gt;, an entrepreneur, champions universal basic income as a way to restore the American Dream. Runtime: 30 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/56ac4e4c-1e63-4337-944a-7f022c054491&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 14:40:25 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How much trouble does Airbus’s new plane pose to Boeing?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/gulliver/2019/06/21/how-much-trouble-does-airbuss-new-plane-pose-to-boeing]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_WBP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T20:38:56Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BOEING, AN American aerospace giant, had once hoped that it would have a good week at this year’s Paris Air Show, which ends on June 23rd. It was expected to launch the 797, a new mid-sized jet to fill the gap in its range between its smaller 737 narrow-body airliner and its much larger 787 and 777 wide-body jets. But instead it was Airbus, its European arch-rival, that launched a plane that fitted this criteria. The A321XLR (the XLR stands for “extra long range”) is a version of the planemaker’s popular narrow-body adapted to boost its range to 5,400 miles (8,700 km). This is made possible by enlarging the aircraft’s centre fuel tank. It is a move that could spell trouble for Boeing’s own plans to fill the middle of the market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The A321XLR is a plane “that is of interest to the entire world,” says Francois Caudron, a marketing boss at Airbus. He says the demand for the proposed jet came from airlines flying previous A321 models, which had a range of about 4,000 miles. “The market, asked us, ‘With the A321 now, we can fly from the East Coast of the United States into Europe, but we can’t really go deep into Europe. We can’t go to Rome. So Airbus, can you do something to give us another 500 nautical miles?’” The company responded, he says, with a new fuel tank configuration that added an extra 700 nautical miles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Boeing had hoped to answer that same question with its proposed Boeing 797. The American firm had hoped that it would serve as a replacement for the Boeing 757 and 767, two older mid-sized jets. But Mr Caudron says that Airbus also sees the new model as a replacement for Boeing’s 757. Both are narrow-body jets and they offer the same range and similar seating capacities. The XLR also burns 30% less fuel than the 757. Boeing’s proposed New Midsize Airplane (NMA) is instead a wide-body aircraft with two instead of one aisle. It has a slightly larger seating capacity and has more range than the XLR. So it seems much more like a replacement for the Boeing 767 in terms of size and design. All the extra space would certainly make it a more comfortable plane than the XLR for flyers. But it would also be more costly plane to fly, as the wider fuselage increases the amount of drag on the plane. And as passengers increasingly choose the cheapest tickets whatever the service on board an airline is like, that could harm sales.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much has been made of Boeing’s other troubles for the postponement of the 797’s launch. It is true that the continued grounding of its 737 MAX planes, due to safety worried following two crashes of the type in Ethiopia and Indonesia that killed 346 people, does not help. But even before the 737 MAX’s problems, the business case for the 797 was already weak. Analysts have long said that the business plan only made sense if the profits from aftermarket services, such as maintenance checks and spare parts, were enough to make up the losses produced by designing and building the planes. With the XLR eating into the bottom of that market, it has become weaker still.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 06:40:29 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The justices side with a death-row inmate over race and juries]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/21/a-prosecutor-excluded-black-jurors-from-a-murder-trial]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_USP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-21T22:17:02Z&quot;&gt;Jun 21st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 1986, the Supreme Court ruled 7-2 in &lt;em&gt;Batson v Kentucky&lt;/em&gt; that racial bias in jury selection violates the Sixth and Fourteenth Amendments. A lawyer cannot strike a potential juror from a case without a &amp;quot;neutral&amp;quot; reason, &lt;em&gt;Batson&lt;/em&gt; held, and defendants who suspect racial bias may raise an objection. More than three decades later, on June 21st, the justices &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/18pdf/17-9572_k536.pdf&quot;&gt;again split 7-2&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;em&gt;Flowers v Mississippi,&lt;/em&gt; a case involving a prosecutor who consistently excluded black prospective jurors from the six murder trials of Curtis Flowers, a black Mississippian. Mr Flowers was charged following the murder of four furniture-store employees in 1996. He was charged with each individual murder in the first four trials and for all four deaths in the fifth and sixth trials. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The majority opinion in &lt;em&gt;Flowers&lt;/em&gt;, penned by Justice Brett Kavanaugh, stretched to 31 pages but, as it said, broke “no new legal ground”. The ruling “simply enforce[s] and reinforce[s] &lt;em&gt;Batson&lt;/em&gt; by applying it to the extraordinary facts of this case”. The facts are, indeed, striking. In the six trials, Doug Evans, the prosecutor, used peremptory challenges (for which a lawyer need offer no reason, as opposed to a strike &amp;quot;for cause&amp;quot; that does cite a justification) to eliminate 41 of the 42 black prospective jurors. In the sixth trial, the one at issue in &lt;em&gt;Flowers&lt;/em&gt;, he excluded five of six. In the apparent hope of finding “pretexual reasons to strike” them, Justice Kavanaugh wrote, Mr Evans “engaged in dramatically disparate questioning of black and white prospective jurors”. And he excluded one black potential juror, Carolyn Wright, for reasons that should have resulted in a challenge to white jurors for whom the only relevant difference seemed to be their race. Prosecutors said Ms Wright was struck because she knew a few witnesses and worked at the same WalMart as Mr Flowers&amp;#x27;s father. But several white potential jurors were also familiar with players in the trial and faced less questioning and no challenge. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the first three trials, the Mississippi Supreme Court chastised Mr Evans for violating Mr Flowers’s right to an impartial jury and reversed the convictions. The fourth and fifth trials ended in hung juries, with no verdict. But Mississippi’s high court found no problem with Mr Evans’ behaviour the sixth time. In the latest trial, there were 26 potential jurors, six black and 20 white. The prosecution used five of its six peremptory strikes against black prospective jurors, resulting in 11 white jurors and one black juror. When Mr Flowers raised a challenge to the fairness of his trial under &lt;em&gt;Batson&lt;/em&gt;, the Mississippi Supreme Court rejected it. The United States Supreme Court then told the state court to take another look at the matter in light of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2016/05/24/the-supreme-court-cracks-down-on-racist-prosecutors&quot;&gt;its 2016 decision&lt;/a&gt; in&lt;em&gt; Foster v Chatman, &lt;/em&gt;another jury-discrimination decision. After a second examination, the Mississippi Supreme Court again sided with the prosecution. But the vote was 5-4, and a dissenting judge said he believed the majority had badly erred. “I cannot conclude that Flowers received a fair trial”, he wrote.The five-judge majority “completely disregard[ed] the constitutional right of prospective jurors to be free from a racially discriminatory selection process”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After walking through the justification and implications of &lt;em&gt;Batson&lt;/em&gt; and the facts of Mr Flowers’s case, Justice Kavanaugh concluded the four dissenting judges on the Mississippi Supreme Court had it right. The state’s case against Mr Flowers was “motivated in substantial part by discriminatory intent”. “Equal justice under law”—the words carved into marble above the familiar pillars of the Supreme Court’s main entrance—”requires a criminal trial free of racial discrimination in the jury selection process”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justice Kavanaugh’s thorough opinion attracted the votes of Chief Justice John Roberts and the four liberal-leaning justices. Justice Samuel Alito joined the judgment but wrote separately to emphasise that &lt;em&gt;Flowers&lt;/em&gt; is “a highly unusual case” and “likely one of a kind”. If not for the “unique combinations of circumstances present here”, Justice Alito would have affirmed the Mississippi Supreme Court’s ruling. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Justices Clarence Thomas and Neil Gorsuch did not find any circumstances worthy of vindicating Mr Flowers’s constitutional rights. In a biting 42-page dissent, Justice Thomas recounted the 1996 killings in detail and blamed his seven colleagues for “needlessly prolong[ing] the suffering of four victims’ families” and disrespecting Mississippi’s state courts. (The majority may have sided with Mr Flowers, the dissent speculates, to “boost its self-esteem”.) Looking through the record, Justice Thomas finds no evidence of racist prosecutorial intent. “Any competent prosecutor would have exercised the same strikes as the state did in this trial”, he wrote. In a section of the dissent Justice Gorsuch did not join, Justice Thomas attacked &lt;em&gt;Batson&lt;/em&gt; itself: the ruling “was suspect when it was announced, and I am even less confident of it today”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 05:40:34 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>