<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Chevron is buying Anadarko for $33bn]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/04/13/chevron-is-buying-anadarko-for-33bn]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-13T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN RECENT MONTHS a question has been hanging over the plains of Texas: what would be the next big shale deal? The logic for consolidation seemed clear. Texas’s Permian basin is America’s most productive oilfield, despite a patchwork of plots with hundreds of owners. Shale companies looked cheap, with investors sceptical about firms’ ability to produce both oil and profits. On April 12th the curious got their answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chevron, a giant oil company, will pay $33bn in cash and shares to buy Anadarko, an independent producer with rich holdings in the Permian. It will also assume Anadarko’s $16bn debt. The deal transforms Chevron into the world’s second-biggest publicly traded oil-producer, behind only ExxonMobil. It is the latest sign of shale’s growing importance to the world’s biggest energy firms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oil majors have arrived relatively late to fracking. Small, independent companies were first to set about coaxing oil from shale. They developed ways to drill not just down but horizontally, then assault shale with water and sand until the rock gave up its hydrocarbon riches. But the industry titans have warmed to the idea. Unlike, say, a complex deepwater project in a distant jurisdiction, shale offers quick drilling times, predictable cashflow and favourable American regulation. Smaller companies have often fracked frenetically, eager to reinvest proceeds and chase growth. Too frenetically at times; some took on more debt than they could handle. Giant companies have less experience with the technique. But their diversified revenue and larger balance-sheets allow them to accumulate acreage even as they drill at a more measured pace. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year &lt;span&gt;BP&lt;/span&gt;, a British firm, paid $10.5bn to acquire the shale assets of BHP, a giant miner. ExxonMobil and Chevron have placed the biggest bets. Chevron’s shale holdings were vast even before the Anadarko deal. The company controlled 1.7m acres (690,000 hectares) in two of the Permian’s most productive regions. In March ExxonMobil said it expects production in the Permian to exceed 1m barrels a day within five years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Anadarko, Chevron’s Permian production may be 60% higher than ExxonMobil’s, according to Rystad Energy, a research firm. Anadarko gives Chevron more than just shale. Its assets include a liquefied-natural-gas project in Mozambique and holdings in the Gulf of Mexico. Still, Anadarko’s Permian plots would have been the main lure. With them, Chevron can drill more wells, more efficiently. Adjacent plots will let the company move farther sideways through the rock and simplify the transport of equipment and other inputs, such as the millions of gallons of water required to wrest oil from each well. Chevron reckons that the deal will bring $2bn in savings, all told. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some investors hope that, as shale companies consolidate, they will mature and their performance will improve. Independent producers may now bulk up, following the lead of Concho Resources. Last year it bought RSP&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Permian, a rival, for $9.5bn. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, the supermajors’ holdings look poised to expand. ExxonMobil has said it would consider additional shale acquisitions. Royal Dutch Shell is rumoured to be weighing the purchase of Endeavor Energy, whose headquarters sit in the heart of the Permian. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not all investors are sold on the attractions of shale. Follow This, a group of them concerned about climate change, expressed disappointment that Chevron would spend $33bn on Anadarko, rather than on renewable energy. At its annual meeting next month, Chevron’s shareholders will vote on a resolution that would compel the company to disclose how it can reduce its carbon footprint in line with the Paris climate agreement. Chevron insists that it is “positioned to win in any environment”. An environmentally friendlier one may be an exception. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 23:42:17 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pete Buttigieg is emerging as a serious contender for the Democratic nomination]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/04/12/pete-buttigieg-is-emerging-as-a-serious-contender-for-the-democratic-nomination]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190413_USP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-12T17:11:47Z&quot;&gt;Apr 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETE BUTTIGIEG does a good line in self-deprecation. He knows that many voters do not know who he is. On the stump he describes how a woman at an airport asked if he was a reporter covering a political campaign. He jokes about his lack of physical height. He speaks of the “audacity of someone like me”, meaning a 37-year-old mayor of a smallish city joining the 2020 race for the presidency. He also tells crowds he is not a “prototypical candidate”, saying his youth is a virtue that makes him focus on long-term concerns, like climate change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a man with a hard-to-pronounce Maltese name and little experience of national politics, Mr Buttigieg is enjoying an extraordinarily good start to his campaign. His political memoir is selling fast. Television news shows and other media are following him closely. That interest is driven in part by the novelty of his having a husband, Chasten. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Buttigieg has been on the road and fundraising for weeks but will formally launch his campaign on April 14th in South Bend, the city in Indiana where has been mayor since 2012. On April 11th he received his first serious endorsement, from Steve Grossman, a former chairman of the national Democratic Party and a well-known political figure in Massachusetts. Mr Grossman will no doubt encourage more donors to give to the campaign. Mr Buttigieg has already raised a decent $7m, a figure that includes many small donations, a hallmark of a serious candidate. He mentions, over a beer in a New Hampshire brewery, that he now has the means to expand his campaign team across several states, and notes that everything is moving faster than he had expected a few weeks ago. He says he is braced for a “marathon, not a sprint”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Polls show voters warming to him. Bernie Sanders and Joe Biden (who has not yet declared) are consistently ranked in the lead in the Democratic race, but Mr Buttigieg seems to be jostling for the third spot in a crowded field. A poll in Iowa, published on April 11th, gave him 9% overall support. That rises to 12% among voters who are under 50 and 12% among respondents with a college degree. That is a big shift: three months ago Mr Buttigieg did not register among pollsters at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The veteran, who served in Afghanistan, is proving to be a capable campaigner and a strong orator. With his measured speaking style he can sound a bit like Barack Obama (who, he sometimes reminds his audiences, described him once as a future prospect for the party). As a participant in televised debates between Democratic candidates later this year he is likely to perform well. Much of the recent interest in him was sparked when he spoke eloquently at a town-hall meeting broadcast by CNN in early March. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At recent events in New Hampshire the crowds were large. When an art gallery in Manchester overfilled with 300 guests, he addressed the roughly equal number that had gathered outside. Standing on a bench he spoke about freedom, security and democracy. He also touched some emotional notes, mentioning his father’s recent death and the loving support of his husband. He repeated the performance inside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rise of long-shot candidates from outside Washington has a long tradition. Bill Clinton’s jump from governor of Arkansas to Democratic nominee in 1992 surprised many. Jimmy Carter, who had been governor of Georgia, was little known before his successful run in 1976.  His clean-cut, God-fearing, small-town, virtuous persona appealed to many after the Nixon presidency.  Mr Buttigieg also emphasises his Christian faith and small-town virtues, playing up his distance from Washington. He talks, earnestly, of a public yearning for moral national leadership, saying “people are ready for something different” and it is time for “decency, honesty”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How far can this carry him? The fact that Mr Buttigieg is openly gay is, on balance, an asset—progressive Democrats can less easily shun him as a white man who studied at Harvard and Oxford before working as a consultant for McKinsey. At the same time, his identity as a Christian, married, with business and military experience, all suggest he could be popular among more centrist Democrats. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He has weaknesses. Just over a quarter of South Bend’s population is African-American, but he has so far said little about their needs as unusually poor community. In his memoir he describes a battle to rename one avenue after Martin Luther King Junior, but mentions little else about African-Americans there. He has tried reaching out to black voters, for example by saying he would support the study of reparations for descendants of slaves. But it is unlikely African-Americans would see him as their most powerful champion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He has also been a bit shy about which policies he would make his own. He suggests there is little variation between Democrats on policy, saying it matters more to talk of values and aspirations rather than offer up a “14-point plan” for every policy area. He mentions issues—such as cyber security and climate change—that matter to him. But he is not ready to spell out in detail how he would address them. Before long he will have to do so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 02:06:21 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Do people become happier after 40?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/12/do-people-become-happier-after-40]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190413_WOC710.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“LIFE BEGINS at forty”, according to an old saying popularised by a self-help book from the 1930s. The theory goes that years of hard work are rewarded with less stress and better pay; children begin to fly the nest; and with luck, a decent period of good health remains. A quick glance at self-reported happiness across the world appears to corroborate this view.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People in their teens and early 20s start out reasonably cheerful. Gallup, a pollster, asked a representative sample of people in 158 countries to rate their life satisfaction on a scale from zero to ten. The data reported by the authors of the World Happiness Report, an academic study backed by the UN, show that happiness among people across the world aged 15-19 was 5.35 on average in 2016-18. A slow depression then appears to set in. By the age of 35-39 average self-reported happiness falls to 5.09 points. Once people hit 40 their depression gradually lifts. At the age of 70 an individual’s self-reported happiness rises to 5.58 points, on average. On this basis happiness during a person’s lifetime follows a gentle U-shape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Life satisfaction does not follow this pattern in all countries. Self-reported happiness in former Soviet states declines markedly with a respondent’s age. Among males in India it is an inverted U: happiness rises to middle-age before declining into old age. Generally, Indians are among the gloomiest in the world, their average life satisfaction has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/03/21/economic-growth-does-not-guarantee-rising-happiness&quot;&gt;fallen by 1.2 points&lt;/a&gt; over the past decade. When Indian men reach their 70s they are among the least happy in the world, reporting average life satisfaction of just 3.6 points. In contrast women aged 70 and over in America appear to be the world’s happiest group of people, with life satisfaction of some 7.5 points. The reasons for these differences are not well understood, but the idea of a U shape has been discussed by sociologists for decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One difficulty is that the data provide just a snapshot, so may simply be measuring cohorts of people rather than changes in individuals’ happiness as they age. By using longitudinal data, which tracks the same people over a long period of time, several studies have tried to find out whether happiness really is U-shaped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0167268112000601&quot;&gt;2012 study&lt;/a&gt; of happiness among Australians, Britons and Germans between 1980 and 2010 found that after controlling for income, relationships, health and the fact that longitudinal panels may be biased, self-reported happiness was flat between the ages of 20 and 55. It then rose through to the age of 75 as people enjoyed a stress-free life before declining sharply as their health deteriorated. Another &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1111/ecoj.12256&quot;&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published in 2015 used the same data but employed a different methodology and found evidence for a U-bend in life. It posits that happiness is a simple function of vitality and emotional maturity: the latter rises with age, while vitality deteriorates with age, but in concert they combine to minimise happiness at around middle age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children play a part, too. A recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.nber.org/papers/w25597&quot;&gt;working paper&lt;/a&gt; published by NBER finds that children increase the happiness of European parents, especially for the first ten years. Parents become less happy, however, if having children causes them to encounter financial difficulties. It follows, then, that happiness bounces back for financially-stretched parents once those children become financially independent, but decreases for those parents that enjoyed their children in financial comfort. Evidence for the U-bend of life might be mixed but if life does begin at 40 then it might be down to the matter of money and kids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 02:06:20 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Julian Assange: journalistic hero or enemy agent?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/04/12/julian-assange-journalistic-hero-or-enemy-agent]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190413_BLP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JULIAN ASSANGE, hauled out of the Ecuadorian embassy in London on April 11th after nearly seven years of self-imposed confinement, pale and hirsute, was not a pleasant house-guest. He is alleged to have smeared faeces on the wall of the embassy and neglected his cat, among other uncouth behaviour, according to Ecuador’s exasperated foreign minister. Even so, claim his supporters, his expulsion and arrest was a grave assault on press freedom. Others think it a long-overdue reckoning with justice for a man who had unleashed information anarchy upon the West, culminating in the destabilisation of American democracy. Is Mr Assange a heroic journalist, reckless activist or even an enemy agent?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is no doubt that Mr Assange and his organisation, WikiLeaks, have published some of the most dramatic leaks of the past decade. These include documents exposing American wrong-doing in Iraq and Afghanistan (including larger estimates of civilian casualties in Afghanistan than previously reported, and video footage of an indiscriminate attack by an American helicopter in Iraq) in 2010. The same year it released a trove of over 250,000 juicy American diplomatic cables, stolen with the help of Chelsea Manning, then a junior soldier. Perhaps most seriously, in 2016 WikiLeaks was the conduit for Russian-hacked emails from the Democratic Party that may have swayed the course of America’s presidential election.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Assange’s admirers ask: what distinguishes him from the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt;, which published the leaked Pentagon Papers in 1971, exposing damning details of the Vietnam war? In some ways, Mr Assange was doing no more than following in the footsteps of such illustrious news organisations, which had long given a platform to anti-government leakers–and enjoyed First Amendment protections while doing so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet there are several reasons why Mr Assange’s conduct puts him in a different category. The American charges against him point to one notable difference. They accuse Mr Assange not only of publishing leaked information—that is something that journalists do all the time–but also of helping Ms Manning to crack the password to a secret Pentagon network, making him a “co-conspirator” in illegal hacking. Many journalists egg on their sources to provide more information, as Mr Assange is alleged to have done; most do not help their sources pick physical or digital locks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Barack Obama’s justice department acknowledged that it could not prosecute Mr Assange’s leaking without criminalising the quotidian work of the media. But it warned, reasonably, that journalists did not have carte blanche: if they were believed to be agents of a foreign power, or conspiring in crimes with one, they could be legitimately booked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of WikiLeaks’ behaviour may have come close to crossing this line (though the extent of Mr Assange’s personal role in its activity is unknown). According to an indictment published by the special counsel, Robert Mueller, in 2016 WikiLeaks urged Russian spies—operating under a flimsy pseudonym—to send it emails relating to the then Democratic candidate, Hillary Clinton. Its aim was to sway the election in favour of her Democratic rival, Bernie Sanders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump was the real beneficiary. “Boy, I love reading WikiLeaks,” he declared in 2016 (now, as president, he says WikiLeaks is “not my thing”). Mike Pompeo, then a Republican congressman, gleefully tweeted about WikiLeaks during the campaign. But in April 2017, having become director of the CIA, he called WikiLeaks “a non-state hostile intelligence service often abetted by state actors like Russia”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This points to a second difference between Mr Assange and ordinary reporters. Most responsible journalists would not implore an authoritarian country’s spies to send them secrets for the purpose of disrupting a democratic election; nor would they fail to inform readers about the dubious provenance of the information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WikiLeaks’ willingness to serve as an uncritical and enthusiastic laundromat for Russian intelligence reflects the group’s longer history of publishing material with little or no newsworthiness, but calculated to undermine American interests. A cache of CIA hacking tools published in 2017 was one example. In contrast, WikiLeaks almost never publishes leaks that might undermine America’s autocratic rivals. Mr Assange may not be an enemy agent, but he has at least been a useful idiot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Assange’s commitment to dumping information, rather than reporting it, has put him directly at odds with real journalists. In 2011 he published the unredacted version of the American diplomatic cables, having disagreed with the decision of several newspapers to publish only redacted ones the previous year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His five partners—the &lt;em&gt;Guardian&lt;/em&gt;, the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;El País&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Der Spiegel&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Le Monde&lt;/em&gt;—condemned the move, pointing out that Mr Assange had revealed sensitive personal information and national-security details with little news value. Some named sources, such as an Ethiopian journalist, were forced to flee their countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is right to be sceptical of the motives of Donald Trump’s administration. Britain should be wary of extraditing a high-profile suspect to a country whose justice department is in a state of political flux, and where details of the central offence of hacking are still sketchy—not least whether it was successful and what information, if anything, was stolen. But that does not mean the freedom of the press rests on the fate of Mr Assange. If Mr Assange deems himself to be a journalist, he is in desperate need of a remedial course on the basic ethics of the profession. Whether in Britain or America, he is likely to have plenty of time for that in the months ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 02:06:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Michael Nesmith’s back catalogue is a long-hidden treasure trove]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/04/12/michael-nesmiths-back-catalogue-is-a-long-hidden-treasure-trove]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190413_BKP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-12T16:10:19Z&quot;&gt;Apr 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE COUNTERCULTURE of the 1960s produced a number of musicians who were simultaneously nourished by its spirit of change yet deeply rooted in, and fascinated by, America’s past. It would be mistaken to call this a movement; it was more an attitude. Its standard-bearers were The Band, whose mix of ramshackle rock’n’roll and old-timey aesthetics would form the basis of the Americana genre. Folk and country music were its principal sources, but such diverse figures as Van Dyke Parks, Harry Nilsson and Randy Newman would draw on more metropolitan sounds, including ragtime, vaudeville, musicals and American classical, as well as those of the American Gulf coast and the Caribbean.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A key figure is often left out of this story. The omission might seem odd, given that he was a member of one of the decade’s most successful bands: the Monkees, assembled by television producers for the comedy show of the same name. It made no odds that Michael Nesmith, like fellow Monkee Peter Tork (who died in February), was a product of the folk-music scene. His five-year tenure as a teen idol in a “manufactured” pop group (a dismissive phrase which overlooks how all groups are manufactured in one way or another, as well as Mr Nesmith’s revolt against that interference) would define him in the mind of the public, while his subsequent recording career would go overlooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new box set, “Songs”, contains the first 11 of Mr Nesmith’s 14 (thus far) solo albums, along with a compilation from 1989. It offers an opportunity to reassess his body of work, and discover why he is so influential among musicians—acts as varied as the Breeders, the Jayhawks, Susanna Hoffs and Run-DMC have covered his songs—and cherished by a small but ardent following which at last has easy access to the bulk of his catalogue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The set divides neatly into two parts. The first six discs cover a creative flurry between 1970, when Mr Nesmith took a hefty financial hit to be released from his Monkees contract, and 1973. These are the country-rock albums he recorded with his short-lived backing group, the First National Band, its successor of even briefer tenure, the Second National Band, and finally as the sole credited artist (now going by Michael, to distinguish him from the woolly-hatted television character “Mike”). The first of these albums, “Magnetic South”, would yield the only top-40 single of his solo career, “Joanne”—a reversal of fortune for the former member of an act which had scored five top-three singles and four number-one albums in a two-year period. Mr Nesmith’s fifth solo LP, in 1972, would bear the sardonic title “The Hits Just Keep On Coming”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was not that Mr Nesmith wished to be obscure or uncommercial, and there was nothing about his solo material that determined it should be. His composition “Different Drum” had five years before been a substantial hit for Linda Ronstadt’s group, the Stone Poneys, whose version stands as a minor classic. It is Mr Nesmith’s most celebrated song, and it says a great deal that many who enjoy it will have no idea he wrote it. His own, folksy take—strikingly different from the chiming, driving Stone Poneys number—underlines his distinctive qualities as a writer and performer: his way with a melody, his phrasing of concise narrative detail and his capacity to be at once wry and rueful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Timing and circumstance condemned those first six records to obscurity. Mr Nesmith signed to Nashville’s leading label, RCA, but the burgeoning hip country-rock scene—for which his music would have been a natural fit—was suspicious at best of the ex-bubblegum pop star. Monkees fans, meanwhile, had already abandoned that group as it strove for artistic independence; they would have been bewildered by what they heard, if they heard it at all. Today, those albums make up a treasure trove, liable to delight the first-time listener.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Nesmith became notably less prolific as other interests intervened: it took him two decades to issue as much music as he did in those first three years. The video clip he made for “Rio”, one of his better-known songs, led him to devise a show called “PopClips” for Nickelodeon, a children’s cable channel. Acquired by TimeWarner, “PopClips” became the basis for MTV, the standalone channel that transformed music, and the music business, in the 1980s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Rio”, with its Latin lilt, demonstrated how Mr Nesmith’s palette expanded from the mid-1970s onwards, as he released music on his own Pacific Arts label. The second half of “Songs” shows him becoming ever more experimental, with such pieces as the soundtrack to a book (“The Prison”, 1975) and its chiefly instrumental companion album, “The Garden” (1994). His more overtly pop albums utilise the sounds of the Americas in a way that prefigures the work of David Byrne. Never compromising, never anything other than amiably inventive, never sounding—no matter what form he works in—like anyone other than himself, Mr Nesmith has lived up to the pseudonym he once used in the 1960s: Michael Blessing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(此域名已被污染，谢谢大家一直以来的支持)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 00:06:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can the law still do justice in America?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/12/can-the-law-still-do-justice-in-america]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190413_blp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-12T16:08:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ANNE MCELVOY talks to Preet Bharara, a former federal attorney in New York, who successfully took on some of the biggest crimes in America involving corruption, organised crime and terrorism. He explains why Wall Street executives were not prosecuted for the financial crisis. He also expresses his concern about how politicised the Mueller report has become. And, Mr Bharara reveals what crime he would be tempted to commit and why he loves mafia movies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-preetbharara&quot; width=&quot;500&amp;amp;quot;&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com&amp;amp;gt;Apple Podcasts | &amp;amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com https:=&quot;&quot; spotify=&quot;&quot; com=&quot;&quot; show=&quot;&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWVjb25vbWlzdGFza3M&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=142125&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/Business--Economics-Podcasts/The-Economist-Asks-p999213/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 00:06:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why the NHL’s best team in decades is unlikely to win the Stanley Cup]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/04/12/why-the-nhls-best-team-in-decades-is-unlikely-to-win-the-stanley-cup]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190413_BLP509.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-12T13:21:44Z&quot;&gt;Apr 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THIS YEAR’S edition of the Tampa Bay Lightning are the best team to take to the ice in the National Hockey League (NHL) for decades. On April 6th they concluded regular-season play with a typically convincing 6-3 victory over the Boston Bruins, the second-best team in the NHL’s Eastern Conference. It was the Lightning’s 62nd win this season, matching the league record set by the Detroit Red Wings in 1995-96, a squad that featured seven future members of the Hall of Fame. Tampa Bay had never before accumulated more than 54 victories in a season, and no NHL franchise in the last decade had won more than 56 games in a single campaign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a team to win more than three-quarters of its 82-game regular season fixtures, almost everything has to go right. For Tampa Bay this season, it did. Steven Stamkos, the veteran centre and captain, justified his annual $9.5m salary by commanding the league’s best offence. Meanwhile Nikita Kucherov, a winger, led the NHL in points (goals plus assists) and matched the all-time record for assists from his position. Andrei Vasilevskiy, the goaltender, remained one of the top puck-stoppers in the league, backing up a stellar defence which was led by Victor Hedman. Best of all, the Lightning remained largely injury-free. They scored 103 more goals than they allowed, while the next-best team, the Calgary Flames, managed a differential of only 62.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every season features a leader in the wins column, but the structure of the NHL limits the likelihood that a team would dominate to such a degree. The league’s hard salary cap, introduced after a protracted labour dispute that wiped out the 2004-05 season, ensures that no team can simply spend its way to glory. A modest payroll limit, tied to league-wide revenues and set at $79.5m in 2018-19, keeps most free-agent salaries within reach of small-market clubs. When Detroit recorded their 62-win season 23 years ago, their $28.5m payroll was more than double that of four other teams, including the Lightning, who were still floundering as a recent expansion franchise. This year, all but two NHL teams &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.nhlnumbers.com/team-salaries&quot;&gt;spent at least $67m&lt;/a&gt;, within $11m of Tampa Bay’s $78m outlay.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Taking home the Presidents’ Trophy, the silverware given to the NHL team with the best record in the regular season, requires that those limited millions are spent wisely. Tampa Bay’s roster includes only one of the 25 highest-paid players in the league, Mr Stamkos, whose paycheck was tied for 15th place. Yet according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.hockey-reference.com/about/point_shares.html&quot;&gt;Point Shares&lt;/a&gt; (PS), a metric that apportions a team’s results among its players, the Lightning’s lineup is studded with skaters who were worth just as much. Leading the pack is Mr Kucherov, a 25-year-old right winger earning $5.5m, who posted one of the best offensive performances of the decade. His 14.6 PS set him comfortably ahead of Connor McDavid, Edmonton’s 22-year-old superstar, whose 13.0 PS was exchanged for a $15m paycheck. Wringing 62 wins out of $78m also requires that some production should come at next to no cost, such as the 11.4 PS earned by Brayden Point, the Lightning’s 23-year-old second-line centre. As a third-year player yet to qualify for free agency, Mr Point handed his team an all-star level performance for $650,000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the salary cap helps maintain regular-season parity, then the NHL playoff system has long served a similar purpose by preventing a runaway winner. To secure the Stanley Cup, the sport’s most coveted prize, a team must win four playoff rounds, each involving a best-of-seven-game series. In the 13 years of the salary cap era, the Presidents’ Trophy winners have emerged as overall champions only twice. None of the regular-season winners in the past three years—the Washington Capitals in 2015-16 and 2016-17 and the Nashville Predators in 2017-18—has even advanced past the second round. Using a simple model based on each team’s goals scored and allowed, the average favourite in a playoff head-to-head has a mere 63% chance of advancing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 2018-19 Lightning are no average team. Yet the first day of the playoffs, on April 10th, served as a reminder that a short series in a low-scoring sport is never a sure thing. Tampa Bay’s path to the championship began with a 4-3 loss in their first game against the Columbus Blue Jackets, who squeaked into the playoffs as the second wild card in the Eastern Conference. In three head-to-head meetings this year, the Lightning not only won the lot, but also trounced the Blue Jackets by a combined score of 17 goals to 3. Nonetheless, Columbus, like every Eastern Conference team in the playoffs, is no pushover. The Blue Jackets added Matt Duchene and Ryan Dzingel, two veteran forwards, at the February trade deadline, and they boast one of the league’s strongest goaltenders in Sergei Bobrovsky. One &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://theathletic.com/910662/2019/04/08/2019-nhl-playoff-preview-lightning-vs-blue-jackets/&quot;&gt;series forecast&lt;/a&gt; that incorporated these roster additions, calculated before the surprising first-game result, gave the underdogs a one-in-four chance of progressing to the next round.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if there were a 75% probability that the Lightning would win each of their four rounds, that would give them less than a one-in-three chance of lifting the Stanley Cup. Betting markets are harsher still, giving them just a one-in-four shot. Two analytics-based models, published by Dom Luszczyszyn of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://theathletic.com/565136/2019/04/06/2018-19-nhl-point-projections-and-playoff-probabilities-updated-daily/&quot;&gt;The Athletic&lt;/a&gt; and Neil Greenberg of the &lt;em&gt;Washington Post&lt;/em&gt;, push that number down to one-in-five. Mr Greenberg’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.washingtonpost.com/sports/2019/04/08/expect-wild-nhl-postseason-with-flames-not-lightning-stanley-cup-favorites/?noredirect=on&amp;amp;amp;utm_term=.960d87ffeb8c&quot;&gt;forecast&lt;/a&gt; goes so far as to slightly favor the Calgary Flames to win the championship, as their Western Conference path to the final is likely to pit them against weaker opponents than the ones the Lightning must face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The salary cap limits the effect of market size on team performance, and the NHL playoff structure counter-balances talent with a hefty dose of luck. The Lightning may not hoist the Stanley Cup this year, but most of the squad’s core is under contract well into the next decade, with Mr Kucherov signed until 2025 and Mr Stamkos until 2024. Should they falter in this year’s playoffs, they can take heart from the fate of the Red Wings 1995-96, who fell to the Colorado Avalanche in the conference finals. Neither the 1996-97 and 1997-98 editions of the Red Wings even won their regular-season division, but both accomplished what the 62-win squad could not, by winning the Stanley Cup. Next year’s post-season will offer its own share of obstacles, but Tampa Bay is well positioned to qualify for another bite at the cherry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 23:06:48 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A former pope blames the swinging sixties for clerical crimes]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/04/12/a-former-pope-blames-the-swinging-sixties-for-clerical-crimes]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190413_BLP508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-12T08:32:24Z&quot;&gt;Apr 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUST AS Pope Francis struggles to stop his well-regarded papacy being overshadowed by charges of laxity over child abuse, his predecessor has emerged from retirement to make an unexpected intervention. Benedict, the pope emeritus who turns 92 next week, has blamed a surge of criminal acts against children by clerics on the sexual revolution of the 1960s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He offered this diagnosis in an essay of nearly 6,000 words that was published in a German monthly, &lt;em&gt;Klerusblatt&lt;/em&gt;, and rapidly retransmitted across the Catholic media. The stated purpose of this contentious piece of writing, which varies from personal reminiscence to dense theological argument, was to assist the deliberations of the current pontiff, who convened a global meeting on child abuse in February after reports of dreadful crimes and cover-ups in countries ranging from Ireland to the United States, and from Chile to Australia. But many supporters of Francis, as well as those who observe the church from outside, will find the older cleric’s analysis far from helpful. Benedict resigned unexpectedly in 2013, becoming the first pontiff to step down for 600 years, and he has lived quietly in Rome since then. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pope Benedict, formerly Cardinal Joseph Ratzinger, opens his essay by recalling how he, as a young cleric, experienced the permissiveness that suddenly swept over his native Germany, like all other Western countries, half a century ago. He describes how: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sexual and pornographic movies became a common occurrence...I still remember seeing, as I was walking through the city of Regensburg one day, crowds of people lining up in front of a large cinema, something we had previously only seen in times of war...I also remember arriving in the city on Good Friday in 1970 and seeing all the billboards plastered with a large poster of two completely naked people in a close embrace.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;This anything-goes attitude had an effect on the atmosphere in which Catholic priests were trained, and “in various seminaries homosexual cliques were established,” according to Benedict. He links this to a liberal trend in theology which tried to argue that there was no action which could unconditionally, and in all circumstances, be described as evil. Pope John Paul II, taking office in 1978, had done good work to stem that movement and re-affirm absolute standards in morality, in the retired pope’s view. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Benedict writes that the child-abuse scandal was a reflection of collapsing ethical norms which in turn flowed from a collapse of private and public faith in God. “Why did pedophilia reach such proportions? Ultimately, the reason is the absence of God...After the upheaval of the second world war, we in Germany had still expressly placed our constitution under the [principle] of responsibility to God. Half a century later it was no longer possible to include responsibility to God as a guiding principle in the European constitution.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the places where clerical abuse has been most extensively investigated, such as the American state of Pennsylvania or the Dublin area, this analysis will be received sceptically. Reports have emerged of awful abuse occurring well before the 1960s, indeed as far back as anyone now alive can recall. The Pennsylvania report published last summer goes back 80 years. If there is a common theme in the whole story, it is that abuse can occur in any situation where representatives of the church (or any other powerful institution) feel they are immune from scrutiny or accountability. One of the ways in which clerics developed that sense of impunity was by presenting themselves as emissaries of God.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Benedict’s argument does contain serious points which would be worth deliberating in a different context, for example a cultural-studies debate. It is perfectly true that in the 1960s and 1970s, public opinion in the Western world was far too inclined (from a 2019 perspective) to turn a blind eye to the sexual manipulation of children. It seems extra-ordinary now that a so-called Pedophile Information Exchange (PIE) was allowed to operate openly, and campaign for the lowering of the age of consent, in Britain from 1974 onwards. What looks obvious now is that the PIE was cynically trying to conflate the campaign for sexual freedom between consenting adults with the exploitation of minors. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, one of the conclusions of the child-abuse summit in Rome in February was precisely that homosexual relations between adults, and child abuse, are two different things which should not be confused. So the existence of “homosexual cliques” in seminaries is off the point for anyone who is trying to understand the root causes of sexual violence against the young.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What the world, and many rank-and-file Catholics, wants to know now is whether the church has the humility and honesty to acknowledge the ghastliness of child abuse, punish the perpetrators and regain public trust. Whatever the rights and wrongs of history, blaming some malign external influence will not do much to inspire fresh confidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 21:06:24 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sudan’s despot is deposed, and more from our daily podcast]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/12/sudans-despot-is-deposed-and-more-from-our-daily-podcast]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/the_intelligence_52.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-12T11:39:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;OMAR AL-BASHIR, the president of Sudan since 1989, has stepped down after months of protests against his rule. What happens next? Also, Bitcoin has turned ten, but its promise to upend the financial system is still a far way off. And the discovery of a new species of human complicates the picture of our evolution. Runtime: TK min.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/bashirandpresentdanger-sudan-scoup&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(此域名已被污染，谢谢大家一直以来的支持)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 18:57:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A new push for the Equal Rights Amendment]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/04/11/a-new-push-for-the-equal-rights-amendment]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190413_USP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-11T18:00:33Z&quot;&gt;Apr 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE ENERGY generated by the #MeToo movement has revived a much older crusade: the push to ratify the Equal Rights Amendment. The full text of the ERA, which was passed in a storm of controversy in the 1970s, seems unprovocative today: “Equality of rights under the law shall not be denied or abridged by the United States or by any state on account of sex”. Yet a renewed push to ratify the amendment looks likely to spark fresh discord.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ERA was first proposed by Alice Paul, a leader of the campaign for women’s suffrage, in 1923. With overwhelming majorities in the House and Senate—and support from President Richard Nixon—Congress passed the ERA in 1972. When the measure went to the states (the constitution says that three-fourths must ratify an amendment), its prospects looked good. Within five years, 35 of the required 38 states had signed up. Then nothing happened. The original seven-year deadline for ratification that Congress had placed in the preamble of the amendment was extended to 1982—and still, the remaining three states failed to ratify it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nearly a century after its introduction, campaigners think they are on the verge of a breakthrough. On March 27th, a group of 22 Senate Democrats, including six presidential hopefuls, reintroduced the ERA in the upper chamber. They have been encouraged by the fact that in 2017 and 2018 Nevada and Illinois became the 36th and 37th states to ratify. Campaigners across the country are taking bets on which state might be the next, and last. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of the 13 states that have not ratified the amendment, many activists see Virginia as the ERA’s best hope. The amendment had previously passed the state Senate, but floundered in the House of Delegates, where it failed in committee again this January. When Democrats proposed a change to House rules to bring the resolution to the floor in February, the measure failed by one vote. Eleanor Smeal, a former president of the National Organisation for Women and a leader of the campaign to pass the ERA in the 1970s and 80s, says proponents of the amendment should not be disappointed. If Democrats win a majority of seats in Virginia’s House elections in November, Mrs Smeal says, they will have the votes. ERA campaigners cherish similar hopes in Arizona and North Carolina. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the ERA can clear the 38-state hurdle, what will happen next? In a recent op-ed for the &lt;em&gt;Washington Post&lt;/em&gt;, Senators Ben Cardin and Lisa Murkowski, a Democrat and a Republican, argued that the 1982 deadline was arbitrary, and that Congress “handcuffed itself” by including it in the amendment’s introduction. They have introduced a bill that would remove the deadline, theoretically clearing the way for ratification of the ERA upon passage by a final state. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But some states have come to regret their ratification. In the 1970s—thanks in large part to an anti-ERA campaign led by Phyllis Schlafly, a firebrand critic of feminism—five states voted to rescind their approval. It is not clear that states have the authority to rescind ratification of a pending amendment. The question made it to the Supreme Court in 1982 with &lt;em&gt;National Organisation for Women v Idaho&lt;/em&gt;, which concerned one of those five states, but as the 10-year deadline for ratification had just expired, the court dismissed the case as unsettled. How would today’s judiciary handle such squabbles? If campaigners call for the ERA’s adoption upon ratification by a 38th state, those five states may mount a legal challenge. “No one really knows how to handle that situation,” says David Strauss, a constitutional law professor at the University of Chicago. “It’s all a great unknown and it’s not clear the Supreme Court would touch that”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The question that looms largest over this latest push is whether America still needs the amendment at all. Around half of the states already have some version of the Equal Rights Amendment written into their constitutions. Women in the rest of the country may stand to benefit from a federal standard. However, the legal landscape changed significantly in recent decades. As a lawyer arguing in front of the Supreme Court in the 1970s, Ruth Bader Ginsburg helped broaden the scope of the 14th Amendment’s equal-protection clause to include discrimination on the basis of sex. Women can now attend what were once all-male military institutes and may not be struck from juries on the basis of their sex, for example. The ERA may not add much to this list.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Activist groups on both sides of the ERA debate see larger-stakes issues on the horizon. Many pro-life groups view the amendment as a pernicious attempt by the left to entrench more permissive abortion requirements in the constitution. They quote Jerrold Nadler, a congressman from New York, who in June 2018 pitched the ERA as a bulwark against the possible erosion of Roe v Wade, the 1973 ruling recognising a woman’s right to access abortion in the first trimester. “What the Supreme Court giveth, the Supreme Court can taketh away”, he said. That is true. But there is little reason to believe that the ERA, by itself, would stand in for Roe and save abortion rights should the Supreme Court one day dispatch the long-standing precedent. There are, however, other reproductive-rights concerns for which the ERA may provide a constitutional hook in litigation. For example, some ask whether paying childbirth expenses under Medicaid obliges the government to provide funds for medically necessary abortions as well. Another concern involves access to contraceptive care under the Affordable Care Act, which the Supreme Court decided in &lt;em&gt;Burwell v Hobby Lobby&lt;/em&gt; could be denied to women by employers with religious objections.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever the legal implications, women’s rights activists and legal scholars seem to agree that ratifying the ERA would have symbolic and cultural value. Justice Ginsburg is sceptical that the amendment would make a huge difference to the lives of American women. But she has said that she “would like to be able to take out my pocket constitution and say that the equal citizenship stature of men and women is a fundamental tenet of our society, like free speech”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(此域名已被污染，谢谢大家一直以来的支持)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 03:07:27 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>