<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[The market believes the Fed will cut rates by September. Should it?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/12/the-market-believes-the-fed-will-cut-rates-by-september-should-it]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_fnp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE FEDERAL RESERVE is changing direction. In December it predicted it would raise the federal funds rate twice in 2019, to 2.75-3.0%. In March it thought it would hold rates steady instead. Investors now think there is a one-in-five chance that it will cut rates at its meeting on June 19th, and a better-than-evens chance that it will do so by September (see chart). Jerome Powell, the Fed’s chairman, has said it is “ready to act”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190615_fnc246.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190615_fnc246.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190615_fnc246.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190615_fnc246.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190615_fnc246.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190615_fnc246.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190615_fnc246.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190615_fnc246.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190615_fnc246.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190615_fnc246.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reason for the change is a darkening world economy, caused primarily by the failure of America and China to strike a deal to bring their trade war to an end. Yet for all the ructions, the visible impact on America’s hard economic data has so far been relatively small. True, American firms hired only 75,000 workers in May, on first estimate, well below the recent monthly average. But jobs data are volatile, and the unemployment rate is a very low 3.6%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Where the pain of the trade war has shown up is mainly in financial markets. The ten-year Treasury yield, for instance, was 2.5% in early May but has since fallen to 2.1% as investors have rushed to safety and anticipated rate cuts. Large moves like these raise an uncomfortable question for the Fed. Should it yield to the market, and risk the appearance that monetary policy is set by traders? Or should it consider only backward-looking economic data, which move slowly?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Markets provide the aggregated wisdom of a crowd of individuals with money on the line. In most contexts their forecasts will outperform those of a financially disinterested committee, even of experts. But there are other reasons why an apparent discrepancy between the two may endure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first is that there is not really a discrepancy at all. Suppose the Fed and the market make the same judgment about the risk of an economic shock such as a trade war. “The Fed has the luxury of more time,” says Torsten Slok, an economist at Deutsche Bank. It can wait to see what happens before changing policy, whereas investors must hedge their bets immediately to account for even unlikely events.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second is that markets agree with the central bank about the economic outlook, but are confused about how it will act. “The Fed might have failed to communicate well,” says Frederic Mishkin, a former rate-setter.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Only if these possibilities can be ruled out can central bankers conclude that markets are telling them something they need to hear about growth and inflation. Discerning this signal becomes trickier the more the Fed appears to respond to the market. To see why, suppose that the Fed ignores market movements completely, and instead sets policy in an entirely predictable way, responding only to hard data on growth and inflation. Any change in market expectations about Fed policy would then reflect only changes in investors’ perception of the outlook for those variables. “If Fed policy is clear and systematic”, says Charles Calomiris of Columbia University, “policymakers can glean useful information from markets.” The more the Fed responds to the market, however, the more it is “looking in the mirror”, as Alan Greenspan, a former Fed chairman, supposedly once quipped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if monetary policy were entirely automated, the information embodied in markets would be useful but unused. What is more, reacting only to real data is like driving while looking only in the rear-view mirror. Central bankers often say that monetary policy works only with a lag of 18 months or two years. Many economists believe that flat-footedness at the Fed has been to blame for numerous post-war American recessions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the Fed wants to glean useful information from markets, it cannot pander to them. “The Fed needs to be the dog that wags the tail,” says Mr Mishkin. But when market movements have a fairly clear cause—in today’s case, the trade war—and the reaction is severe, it is likely that a rate cut will eventually be necessary. The short-term risk of moving in anticipation of events is that the outlook brightens and the rate cut then sparks inflation. Yet to the extent that economic data are telling a clear story, it is that inflation is contained. Consumer-price inflation, for example, slowed to 1.8% in May. That suggests it would be better for the Fed to get on with the rate cuts that the market expects.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 05:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“They chose to come and fight for the freedom of Hong Kong”]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/china/2019/06/12/they-chose-to-come-and-fight-for-the-freedom-of-hong-kong]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_asp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“THEY FIRED plastic bullets at us!” Breathless from running, a young man holding a white flannel over his face shakes his head in disbelief at the response of the police. Other youngsters lie on the floor washing the residues of pepper spray from their faces. Similar scenes have played out throughout Hong Kong on June 12th, after violent confrontations between riot police and mainly young protesters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tensions had been rising for days over plans by the Legislative Council (Legco) to pass a law allowing Hong Kong to send suspected criminals to mainland China, where many fear they would not get a fair trial. Before 9am, with little resistance from the police, protesters closed large roads surrounding the government district. Cars were abandoned where they sat in traffic jams. Outside Legco a line of priests led the crowd in a chorus of “Sing Hallelujah to the Lord”. Others berated policemen for turning against their fellow citizens.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The protesters’ intention had been to prevent legislators from joining a meeting to speed up the passage of the bill. In that, they succeeded. Just after 11am, when the meeting was due to start, its postponement was announced. But the crowds were not appeased. Calls from the government asking them to disperse went unheeded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many were veterans of past Hong Kong protests, having joined student demonstrations in 2012 and pro-democracy ones in 2014. Experience had shown them what they needed, and most came suitably equipped: masks, goggles and scarves for protecting mouths, eyes and bodies from pepper spray and tear gas; and the ubiquitous umbrellas, symbols of Hong Kong’s protest movement since 2014. One protester, Ricky, spoiling for a fight, said: “Unless you come down and are prepared to take risks, don’t come.” Shouts of “ga yau!”, a call of encouragement literally translating as “add oil!”, or “keep it up!”, rang out as spare umbrellas and yellow construction helmets were passed up to the front line of protesters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hong Kong’s riot police are a fearsome sight. All wear thick arm-length gloves and carry batons and plastic shields. Some carry weapons to fire rubber bullets. For most of the morning they seemed intent only on forming a tight circle to protect the offices of the chief executive, the civil service and Legco. Around 4pm, however, as protesters barged their way past police lines into the Legco building, police lost their patience. Some fired tear-gas canisters. Soon afterwards they fired rubber bullets and small bean-bags filled with birdshot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A running battle continued up and down the flyovers and roadways of the Admiralty district. Clouds of stinging gas could be felt blocks away. As hundreds of demonstrators fled in every direction, many took shelter in shopping malls and office buildings, scrambling over the makeshift barricades they had erected earlier in the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although they came prepared for trouble, protesters were surprised at the level of aggression shown by the police. Though nobody was killed, one young woman on the front line was moved to draw a comparison with the Chinese Communist Party’s massacre of protesters around Tiananmen Square 30 years ago—an event widely commemorated in Hong Kong last week. “We can’t believe that this kind of thing can happen in Hong Kong,” she said. “Citizens try to fight back but we have nothing.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the police had cleared and sealed off the area around Legco, apparently taking group selfies to celebrate, protesters gathered in huge groups elsewhere, disrupting traffic. Office workers joined the throng. One demonstrator, Zoe, argued that “Most people here... their parents wouldn’t want them to be fighting with the police. But they choose to come anyway and fight for the democracy of Hong Kong.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 04:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What Ivan Golunov’s ordeal reveals about Russia]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/12/what-ivan-golunovs-ordeal-reveals-about-russia]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_eup002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A WEEK AGO few people had heard of Ivan Golunov, a freelance journalist who reports on corruption in Moscow. His work was published by Meduza, an independent news website that operates out of Latvia. Police and prosecutors ignored him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That changed on June 6th, when police arrested Mr Golunov in central Moscow, beat him up and charged him with the possession and distribution of drugs. They denied him access to his lawyer, and refused to conduct forensic tests. The case was clearly fabricated. Photos purporting to show a drugs lab in Mr Golunov’s flat were taken elsewhere, the police later admitted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Russian social media exploded. Hundreds of journalists and citizens queued up in front of police headquarters to stage “single pickets”, the only permitted form of protest, demanding Mr Golunov’s immediate release. Some were promptly bundled into police vans, further increasing the general outrage. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Kremlin had spent millions of dollars staging a summit in St Petersburg with Xi Jinping, the Chinese president, on the day of Mr Golunov’s arrest. In the event, the formerly obscure journalist overshadowed the powwow. The story of his arrest circulated widely; international and Russian media ran pictures and posted videos of him in tears inside a cage in a courtroom. Actors, singers and other public figures joined in the denunciation of the case.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On June 10th three mainstream business dailies, none of them radical, came out with identical front pages, spelling out in large print: “We Are Ivan Golunov.” By 10am that day newsagents had sold out. Journalists announced a mass protest for June 12th, a holiday that marks Russia’s independence from the Soviet Union. But 24 hours before the march was supposed to start, something changed. The police abruptly dropped the case and cleared Mr Golunov of all charges. Almost simultaneously, and surely not coincidentally, a court in Chechnya released another victim of the police’s drug-planting tactics, Oyub Titiev, a human-rights campaigner. There is no doubt that the order to release both men came from the Kremlin. Mr Putin is better known for encouraging rather than restraining his security services. So why the reversal?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;First, the release of Mr Golunov shows that the Kremlin is worried about losing its monopoly on force. An investigation by activists and supporters concluded that the journalist was nabbed by members of a corrupt group of FSB officers who work with the criminal underground, connections that Mr Golunov has exposed. Mr Titiev was arrested and jailed for crossing Ramzan Kadyrov, a strongman in Chechnya who commands a small army. But although neither arrest was sanctioned by the Kremlin, the gangs were only following the Kremlin’s example. Having observed their ultimate bosses act with impunity against their opponents, the police and local FSB men decided there was nothing stopping them from doing the same. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;By slapping them down, the Kremlin has tried to portray Mr Putin as the only true source of justice, a good Tsar who can pardon and punish as he sees fit. This is no thaw. On June 12th the police brutally disbanded a peaceful rally against their tactics, detaining some 200 protesters including some of the very journalists who had helped to get Mr Golunov freed. Alexei Navalny, Russia’s most prominent opposition leader, was also arrested. He said that the Kremlin’s actions only seemed illogical: “They are fantastically scared of consolidation in Golunov’s case, so they first need to break up the solidarity and then intimidate and jail those who persevere.” &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The outpouring of support for Mr Golunov shows the power of online media and a growing mood for protest. Five years of declining incomes, mixed with brazen corruption and injustice, make a combustible mix; the Kremlin is keen not to add a spark. But it is also keen not to let protesters seize the initiative. As Mr Putin prepares for his annual televised phone-in show on June 20th, and contemplates ways of retaining power after the end of his final presidential term under the constitution, he needs quiet on the streets. Mr Golunov’s case suggests he is unlikely to get it. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 04:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Global carbon emissions hit another record]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/12/global-carbon-emissions-hit-another-record]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_woc411.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN “ICE ON FIRE”, a documentary narrated by Leonardo DiCaprio which premiered last night on HBO, the actor and environmental activist highlights the magnitude of the climate crisis and some of the tools available to fight it, from renewable energy to advanced batteries to carbon capture. A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.bp.com/en/global/corporate/energy-economics/statistical-review-of-world-energy.html&quot;&gt;new report&lt;/a&gt; from BP suggests that recent progress on this front has been slow. In its annual statistical review of world energy, the British oil firm finds that the world’s power sector is spewing out ever more CO2. Overall emissions of greenhouse gases increased by 2% in 2018. In the power industry, emissions rose by 2.7%, the biggest increase in seven years. This was driven by a high number of days that were either unusually hot or cold, which boosted energy demand. Without a more sustainable energy mix, the low-carbon future Mr DiCaprio envisions will be a thing of Hollywood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are some grounds for optimism. Data from the International Energy Agency (IEA), an intergovernmental group, show that the carbon intensity of the power sector—the amount of carbon dioxide emitted for each unit of electricity generated—has fallen by 10% since 2010. That is in part because the use of renewable energy, including solar and wind, is up. Of the 78 countries tracked by BP, three-quarters have some form of renewable power, up from just a third twenty years ago. To make meaningful progress, however, renewable electricity production will have to keep pace with global energy demand, which jumped by 3.7% in 2018. Producers will also have to do more to remove coal, easily the dirtiest of the fossil fuels, from the electricity grid. Coal-fired power plants still supply more than a third of the world’s power (see map). In 2018, coal-based output increased for the second consecutive year, following three years of declines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To clean up the industry, a variety of fuels and technologies will be needed. For the power sector to keep its carbon emissions steady at 2015 levels, BP estimates it could have added some 1,000 terawatt-hours of renewable energy to the mix (equivalent to the renewable output of China and America combined). Alternatively, it could have swapped out 10% of its coal capacity with natural gas. BP, itself a major producer of natural gas, argues that renewables alone will not achieve the goals laid out in the Paris climate agreement of 2018, in which signatories committed themselves to keeping the rise in global temperature “well below” 2°C above pre-industrial levels. There is much debate on the relative merits of gas and renewables, but the report makes one point indisputable: current trends set the world on a dangerous path.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 02:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Space invaders—the business of small satellites]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/12/space-invaders-the-business-of-small-satellites]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_blm506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-12T17:00:05Z&quot;&gt;Jun 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BUSINESS OPPORTUNITIES from &lt;strong&gt;small-satellite technology&lt;/strong&gt; are infinite: from an “ambulance” which rescues malfunctioning spacecraft to devices that can measure the oil level in a tanker from space. Also, are we on the verge of making &lt;strong&gt;gene-editing technology&lt;/strong&gt; safer? And 50 years after man set foot on the moon, Oliver Morton, The Economist&amp;#x27;s senior editor and author, predicts the future of humans’ relationship with &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/05/28/casting-light-on-the-moon&quot;&gt;lunar exploration&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Kenn Cukier hosts. Runtime: 23 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistbabbage/babbage-spaceinvaders&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 01:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Supreme Court refuses to hear a Guantánamo detainee’s appeal]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/12/the-supreme-court-refuses-to-hear-a-guantanamo-detainees-appeal]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_USP503_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-12T09:00:59Z&quot;&gt;Jun 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN JANUARY 2002, Moath al-Alwi, a Yemeni, was one of the first 20 men dispatched to the Guantánamo Bay Naval Base in Cuba and detained as an enemy combatant. Some 780 men have passed through Guantánamo over the past 17 years, and Mr al-Alwi is one of only 40 prisoners remaining. On June 10th, the Supreme Court refused to entertain Mr al-Alwi’s latest legal challenge to his detainment. There were no published dissents from that demurral. But Justice Stephen Breyer penned a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/orders/courtorders/061019zor_3dq4.pdf&quot;&gt;statement&lt;/a&gt; imploring his colleagues to take up a future case asking whether the Supreme Court decision from 2004 permitting Mr al-Alwi’s confinement should apply indefinitely. Justice Breyer wants the court to revisit the question of whether “Congress has authorised and the Constitution permits” the detention of enemy combatants in a war on terror launched two decades ago. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr al-Alwi is, according to the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.nytimes.com/interactive/projects/guantanamo/detainees/28-moath-hamza-ahmed-al-alwi&quot;&gt;Department of Defence&lt;/a&gt;, a “veteran jihadist” who “admitted fighting for the Taliban” in al-Qaeda’s former 55th Arab Brigade. In 2008, Mr al-Alwi’s habeas corpus plea—disclaiming ties to al-Qaeda and asserting he never took up arms against America—was rebuffed in a federal district court. Three years later, the District of Columbia Circuit Court of Appeals affirmed the lower court’s ruling. In 2015, Mr al-Alwi tried another tack. Rather than question the government’s account of his actions, he attacked the legal justification for his detention. In the days after the September 11th attacks, Congress passed an “Authorisation for the Use of Military Force” (AUMF), licence for the president to “use all necessary and appropriate force” against people who may have “planned, authorised, committed or aided the terrorist attacks”. But that was 2001. Reflecting on the changed circumstances in Afghanistan and the passage of time, Mr al-Alwi &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/DocketPDF/18/18-740/74187/20181205150643166_2018-12-05%20Petition%20for%20Writ%20of%20Certiorari.pdf&quot;&gt;argued&lt;/a&gt; that “the government’s statutory authority to detain” him “has unravelled”—or, alternatively, “has expired” because the war during which he was apprehended “has ended”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This latest plea draws from language in &lt;em&gt;Hamdi v Rumsfeld,&lt;/em&gt; the case from 2004 in which the Supreme Court (with Justice Breyer joining the plurality) gave the president the power to detain enemy combatants as a “fundamental incident of waging war”. But Justice Sandra Day O’Connor, who wrote the opinion, noted that the justification for detaining men without trial “may unravel” if evolving facts on the ground “are entirely unlike those of the conflicts that informed the development of the law of war”. Justice Breyer &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://sblog.s3.amazonaws.com/wp-content/uploads/2014/04/13-638-denial-hussain.pdf&quot;&gt;picked up&lt;/a&gt; on that idea five years ago when the Supreme Court refused to hear another detainee’s appeal in &lt;em&gt;Hussain v Obama.&lt;/em&gt; There are “unanswered questions” from Hamdi, he wrote, that the justices will eventually need to resolve. This week in &lt;em&gt;al-Alwi v. Trump,&lt;/em&gt; Justice Breyer showed more impatience. The prospect of “perpetual detention” for the remaining Guantánamo prisoners is alarming, he wrote, and “it is past time to confront the difficult question” of how long an AUMF can continue to provide the legal foundation for holding detainees without trial.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr al-Alwi had found no relief in the lower courts, with both the district and appellate courts rejecting his arguments. In March, the District of Columbia Circuit Court of Appeals noted that the National Defence Authorisation Act of 2012 permitted the government to detain enemy combatants until the end of hostilities in the Afghan theatre. With “active combat” still underway—the Air Force has already conducted over 1000 sorties there this year, about a third of those involving weapon fire—there is no doubt that hostilities continue. In any case, it would take a “political act” to bring the war to a close, the court noted, not a judicial declaration. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So Mr al-Alwi and some three dozen fellow detainees languish at Guantánamo with little hope of release, barring an unlikely vote in Congress to rescind the aging AUMF. Relief from the judiciary remains elusive. Two other pending cases at the DC Circuit Court involve “forever prisoners” Khalid Ahmed Qassim, another Yemeni citizen, and Abdul Razak Ali, an Algerian. Both requested an initial hearing &amp;quot;en banc&amp;quot; (as a full court) at the appeals court—a rare move &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.cadc.uscourts.gov/internet/home.nsf/Content/VL%20-%20RPP%20-%20Circuit%20Rules/$FILE/RulesFRAP20181201.pdf&quot;&gt;reserved&lt;/a&gt; for “a question of exceptional importance”— and were turned down. Instead, Mr Qassim’s case was argued on January 15th before a regular three-judge panel; Mr Ali’s day in court is coming. There is little reason to believe either detainee will fare better than Mr al-Alwi did. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But there are at least two Breyeresque judges on the DC Circuit who would like their colleagues to resolve the mess. In an opinion concurring with the decision not to hear Mr Ali’s challenge en banc from the outset, Judge David Tatel (joined by Judge Cornelia Pillard) wrote that the court has never clarified the “Due Process Clause’s reach into Guantánamo Bay”. The DC Circuit issued a ruling called &lt;em&gt;Kiyemba v. Obama&lt;/em&gt; in 2009 involving a group of Uighur Muslims from China who had been detained at Guantánamo but who had been declassified as enemy combatants. The question in &lt;em&gt;Kiyemba&lt;/em&gt; was whether the men—who feared arrest, torture, or execution if they were returned to China—could be released into American territory. The district court had said yes, but the DC Circuit disagreed: only Congress and the president had the authority to admit the Uighurs to America.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Judge Tatel, this ruling implies only that Guantánamo detainees lack a substantive right to enter the United States. It does not rule out the clumsily named right of “procedural due process”—a guarantee of fair dealing using standard legal procedures that was partially vindicated for enemy combatants in &lt;em&gt;Boudemine v Bush&lt;/em&gt; (2008). Mr Ali’s claim that “the Due Process Clause has something to say about the length of his confinement”, Judge Tatel wrote, “is serious—and deserves to be taken seriously”. Guantánamo’s prisoners have not been charged with a crime, much less tried for one, yet their detainments are “lengthening into decades, with no end in sight”. The conundrum “requires this court’s careful consideration”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will the men at Guantánamo ever be able to challenge their imprisonment? Justice Breyer, for one, would like the Supreme Court to address the quandary. Mr al-Alwi “faces the real prospect that he will spend the rest of his life in detention”, Justice Breyer notes, “even though today’s conflict may differ substantially from the one Congress anticipated”. Stephen Vladeck, a law professor at the University of Texas, suspects Justice Breyer voted against hearing &lt;em&gt;al-Alwi v Trump&lt;/em&gt; because Justice Brett Kavanaugh’s recusal could have foretold a 4-4 tie, leaving the DC Circuit court’s ruling in place. But while the court awaits “an appropriate case” to take up, uncertainty reigns. It is “remarkable”, Mr Vladeck says, “just how little has been settled” since 2002. “Nearly 18 years in, we still don&amp;#x27;t know if the Guantánamo detainees even have due process rights”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 01:39:55 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Girish Karnad was one of India’s foremost storytellers]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/12/girish-karnad-was-one-of-indias-foremost-storytellers]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_BKP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-12T14:57:53Z&quot;&gt;Jun 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SIRSI, A sleepy town in the southern Indian state of Karnataka, was infamous for its power cuts. With little else to do, a favourite pastime of its denizens was to share stories. At home, grandparents would spin yarns; at school, if a teacher failed to turn up, students were instructed to regale each other with tales. As a child Girish Karnad partook of this tradition, and would accompany his father, a physician, on free trips to performances at the local theatre, too. (The area was affected by malaria and actors could need treatment at short notice.) “I saw play after play after play,” he said, “and theatre got into my blood without my realising it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a teenager, Mr Karnad dreamt of being a poet—though he knew his verse was clunky and awkward—and fantasised about winning the Nobel prize. He would spend hours drawing sketches of famous writers such as Agatha Christie and T.S. Eliot, sending these portraits with pleas to sign and return them to him. One of his idols, Sean O’Casey, a great Irish dramatist, advised him to stop wasting his time with autographs and write something of his own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was sage advice. Mr Karnad’s first play, “Yayati”, was published in 1961 when he was 23 years old. It drew on a story in the “Bhagavata Purana”, a Hindu text, about a lustful king cursed with premature old age who orders his son to sacrifice his youth for him. With no formal training in script-writing, and working in Kannada, his native tongue, the play “just poured out,” Mr Karnad recalled. “I was like a steno-typist writing down whatever [the characters] were saying. It was an ecstatic process.” It was a hit, and was translated into several Indian languages. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The work popularised the idea of the “Yayati complex” or “reverse Oedipal complex”, where children forsake their freedom to submit to their parents’ demands. It was hardly a coincidence that Mr Karnad had written the play just weeks before taking up a Rhodes Scholarship to study philosophy, politics and economics at Oxford, against his parents’ wishes—they wanted him to be a bureaucrat in the Indian Administrative Service. (They also worried that he would marry a white woman without seeking their blessing.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His writing often combined contemporary concerns with history and mythology. “Tughlaq”, a play which had its premiere in 1964, retold the story of Muhammad bin Tughlaq, a 13th-century Mughal king who banned public prayers and introduced madcap economic schemes. It was an instant success at a time when India was growing impatient with its own leader, Jawaharlal Nehru, and his ideals. “Taledanda” or “Death by Beheading”, first staged in 1990, charted the rise of radical protest and reform movements in 12th-century Karnataka. Mr Karnad probed ancient, but persistent, problems in the caste structure and tensions between the Hindu and Muslim communities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet for all his accomplishments as a playwright, Mr Karnad was best known as an actor. “I got into Hindi films to make money and pursued money quite single-mindedly,” he said. In more than 100 movies, he played corrupt cricket officials, dance teachers, professors, lawyers and ministers. He was brilliant on the small screen, too. In “Malgudi Days”, a cult television series broadcast in the 1980s, he played a strict father: the actor who played his child often said that a cold stare from Mr Karnad was enough to put him in a catatonic state. He directed many award-winning movies in Hindi and Kannada, and his contribution to the arts earned him India’s third- and fourth-highest civilian awards, the Padma Bhushan and Padma Shri, as well as the Jnanpith award, the country’s highest literary honour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Off-screen, Mr Karnad was a scathing critic of political leaders who stoked communal tensions. “I really feel that secularism is the great legacy that we have and we need to fight for it. There are forces that have eaten away at it and made the country a dangerous place,” he once declared on national television. During the recent elections he was among 200 writers who appealed to Indians not to fall prey to the sectarian campaign run by the ruling Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP), and urged people to vote for a “diverse and equal India”. The BJP, led by Narendra Modi, won with a thumping majority. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking his mind had consequences. His home in Bangalore was frequently pelted with stones. Sometimes the threats warranted police protection. A special investigation found that Mr Karnad was a target of a far-right militant group that in 2017 had shot dead Gauri Lankesh, a journalist. At a memorial of Lankesh’s death last September, he declared that he was “proud to be part of the hit list”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He derived his life force from storytelling and speaking out, even in ill health. In his penultimate film, “Tiger Zinda Hain” (“Tiger is Alive”, 2017), he acted with a tube in his nose, tethered to an oxygen cylinder. He played his part, of a suave secret service officer, with a flourish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 22:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Hong Kong’s protesters are braving tear gas and rubber bullets]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/china/2019/06/12/why-hong-kongs-protesters-are-braving-tear-gas-and-rubber-bullets]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_cnp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A POWERFUL INSIGHT of modern psychology is that humans are hard-wired to fear loss, and will take greater risks to avoid it than to realise a gain. Such insights help to explain protests that have paralysed central Hong Kong in recent days. On June 9th hundreds of thousands of people—over a million, organisers say—peacefully marched in opposition to a government bill that would allow extraditions from Hong Kong to mainland China. Things turned nastier on June 12th, when protesters surrounded the Legislative Council building and forced a delay in the debate on the bill, scoring a temporary victory. As protesters blocked streets with metal barriers and hurled water bottles, police fired tear gas and rubber bullets, and threatened to use more force to disperse the crowds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hong Kong’s chief executive, Carrie Lam, appointed by a panel of local loyalists of the Communist Party in Beijing, talks of “plugging a loophole” with the bill. She says opponents will leave the territory a refuge for fugitives. That is to suggest that previous leaders somehow forgot to draft rules for sending criminal suspects to China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, there was no omission, says Margaret Ng, a barrister who represented the legal profession in Hong Kong’s legislature from 1995 to 2012, under first British then Chinese rule. When drafting an extradition law before the handover in 1997 officials took a deliberate decision to maintain a firewall between Hong Kong’s justice system and that of the mainland, “to protect the rule of law in Hong Kong and confidence in Hong Kong as an international hub free from China’s much mistrusted system.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China’s law courts explicitly serve as instruments of party control, rather than as any check on state power. Hong Kong authorities note that the extradition bill excludes those accused of political crimes. That offers no reassurance, retort opponents: Chinese dissidents routinely face trumped-up charges like bribery or blackmail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prospect of losing the legal firewall between Hong Kong and China, in a bill that is being rushed with minimal debate, is what brought out vast crowds, many dressed in white, the colour of mourning. Several confided that this was their first time at a political demonstration. Such scenes are a surprise. By now, 22 years after the British colony became a Special Administrative Region of China, its people were supposed to have accepted the fate envisioned for them by rulers in Beijing: a life of well-fed but politically neutered domestication, like so many golden-egg laying geese. Rewards are on offer for those who comply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Communist leaders pledged that Hong Kong’s capitalist system, independent courts and Western-style freedoms of speech and assembly would be preserved for 50 years, under the slogan “one country, two systems”. There were ambiguous promises that Hong Kong might move towards democratic elections for its legislature and for the post of chief executive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Increasingly, though, that emphasis on autonomy has been being replaced by proposals that would leave Hong Kong merely the wealthiest and most international city in China. Hong Kong remains valuable as a global financial centre. But Communist bosses increasingly expect Hong Kong to know its place. The territory represented over 18% of China’s GDP when British rule ended in 1997, but less than 3% in 2018. Ms Lam has promoted integration with the “Greater Bay Area”, a region spanning Hong Kong, Macau and the mainland province of Guangdong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The costs of defiance, meanwhile, have risen. In 2003 authorities shelved an anti-sedition law that Beijing wanted to impose on Hong Kong, after large street marches. Since then the central government has grown less patient, notably after Xi Jinping became party leader in 2012. In April this year several leaders of Occupy Central (also known as the Umbrella Movement), a pro-democracy campaign of civil disobedience that blocked streets for weeks in 2014, were jailed for up to 16 months for causing “excessive inconvenience” during those protests, in the words of a Hong Kong judge. Politicians have been barred from running for office unless they pledge loyalty to China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Chaguan last year met Benny Tai, a rumpled law professor from Hong Kong University and an Occupy Central leader, he sadly wondered when his city might witness large demonstrations again. “People are concerned that it is not safe to protest, especially in the business sector,” he sighed. He talked of “holding the line” while waiting for democracy in mainland China. It would be interesting to hear Mr Tai’s views now, but he is currently in prison.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An American newspaper this week asked if China had created a million new dissidents in Hong Kong. That is to mistake the mood. The protesters are not marching to gain new freedoms, but to avoid losing those that they still have. Anson Chan, who served as chief secretary of the Hong Kong government under the British and for the first four years of Chinese rule, spent four and half hours among the marchers on Sunday. Many probably “held out very slim hope that the government will change these proposals”, she says. “But they wanted to stand up and be counted.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fighting without hope of winning&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;In commentaries intended for overseas consumption, Chinese state media accuse “foreign forces” of trying to create “havoc” in Hong Kong. Actually, though the British and American governments have expressed concern about the extradition bill, and Congress could revoke trade and visa privileges granted to Hong Kong, this movement’s backers include prominent, local lawyers, priests and entrepreneurs. Politicians and scholars have drafted moderate compromise proposals, including a one-off arrangement to send to Taiwan a murder suspect whose case is the ostensible pretext for amending extradition laws.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a clarifying rebuke for China’s rulers. Exposure to their version of the rule of law feels like an unbearable loss to many in Hong Kong, outweighing the rewards of integration with a faster-growing China. Assuming that the extradition law is rammed through anyway, it will be a win for fear and resignation, not love. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 20:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The EU must keep its promise to North Macedonia]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/12/the-eu-must-keep-its-promise-to-north-macedonia]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_eup504_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ENLARGING the European Union long ago fell out of fashion. No country has joined since Croatia, in 2013. As Hungary and Poland attack their judiciaries and clamp down on media it seems quaint to argue, as many once did, that negotiating membership could instil democratic habits in countries with memories of dictatorship. How much harder to make the case in the Balkans, the EU’s inner courtyard of unfinished business. Kosovo and Serbia are permanently at daggers drawn. Bosnia is an ungovernable mess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But these problems should not distract from the extraordinary progress in the country known, since February, as North Macedonia. After years of authoritarian misrule the new government, led by Zoran Zaev, has started tackling corruption and reforming the judiciary. In a region riven by ethnic strife, the country’s Slavic majority and Albanian minority enjoy good relations. Most of all, last year Mr Zaev’s government signed the Prespa agreement with Greece, ending an absurd but destabilising dispute over the country’s name by adding a geographical signifier to it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is why the European Commission wants the EU’s governments to open membership talks with North Macedonia, along with Albania. It was the promise of accession to the EU (and NATO, which is forthcoming) that gave Mr Zaev space to push through Prespa at home. Yet in June 2018 his bid to start talks was kicked down the road for a year. Now further delay is likely. Such treatment is not only shabby, it is dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To start membership talks with a candidate country, every EU government must agree. Until now France and the Netherlands were the stumbling blocks. Emmanuel Macron’s argument that Europe must deepen before broadening concealed his fear that encouraging enlargement would help Marine Le Pen, his nationalist opponent. Now, just as Mr Macron is softening, a fresh obstacle has emerged in Germany. Angela Merkel’s government needs backing from the Bundestag to approve EU bids, and MPs from her Christian Democratic Union are resisting. They claim they need more time for debate. But that is a fig-leaf for opponents of enlargement. Some distrust Albania’s judicial system, but the two countries’ bids can be decoupled. Others simply want to give Mrs Merkel a black eye. And the chancellor’s authority is dwindling as the sun sets on her political career.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The original plan was to greenlight the two candidates’ EU bids at a meeting on June 18th. That now looks impossible. A special summit of leaders could be convened in July were North Macedonia’s bid sure to pass. But the Bundestag will soon begin its summer break. Another opportunity will not arise until October, and by then the habit of delay may have become ingrained.&lt;br/&gt;Every day lost is perilous for Mr Zaev’s government. Having already suffered one delay, voters are sceptical. The opposition, still smarting at its ejection from office, will pounce at the first sign of failure. Moreover, by autumn Greece is likely to have a new centre-right government that will face pressure from anti-Prespa voters to veto the talks. More broadly, for the EU so brazenly to break its promise to one Balkan state will boost leaders in others who say the Europeans cannot be trusted. Other powers sniffing around, from Russia to China to Turkey, will nod sagely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conversely, opening talks with North Macedonia will strengthen the hand of pro-European reformers throughout the Balkans. (A delay for Albania, which remains politically unstable, is on balance justified.) Starting talks is no guarantee of successfully concluding them, as Turkey—which began negotiating in 2005 and is going backwards—demonstrates so depressingly. Croatia’s accession lasted eight years. The EU should not lose confidence in its most potent foreign-policy weapon. To reject North Macedonia would be cruel, self-defeating and wrong. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 20:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“A profound improvement in humanity’s aggregate happiness”—the internet’s second half]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/12/a-profound-improvement-in-humanitys-aggregate-happiness-the-internets-second-half]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_blm505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-12T11:20:32Z&quot;&gt;Jun 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HALF OF humanity is now &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/08/the-second-half-of-humanity-is-joining-the-internet&quot;&gt;online.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; What will the second half do when it logs on? The same as the first: friendly chat, personal expression and a lot of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/briefing/2019/06/08/how-the-pursuit-of-leisure-drives-internet-use&quot;&gt;cat videos&lt;/a&gt;. Despite appearances, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/09/race-plays-an-ever-more-important-role-in-voting&quot;&gt;racism&lt;/a&gt; in America&lt;/strong&gt; is actually going down; the problem is that America’s politics is increasingly fractured along racial lines. And, why is it that &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/04/25/a-brief-cultural-history-of-the-scream&quot;&gt;screams&lt;/a&gt; are so prevalent in popular culture?&lt;/strong&gt; Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/oncemore-withfelines-halftheworldgetsonline&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 19:23:37 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>