<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Joe Biden launches himself as a fighter for the working class]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/04/30/joe-biden-launches-himself-as-a-fighter-for-the-working-class]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_USP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-30T01:31:56Z&quot;&gt;Apr 30th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT IS NOT always a mistake to refight the last battle. Joe Biden, addressing the first crowd of his official campaign on April 29th, in Pittsburgh, promised to overcome the mistakes made by the Democrats in 2016. Three years ago his party failed to fire up blue-collar workers, especially in the Midwest. Mr Biden said he would focus on the power of organised labour and ordinary, middle-class folk—the backbone of America, he said, from teachers to health-workers to plumbers—who do extraordinary things. “I am a union man, period”, he vowed, earning cheers of “We want Joe!” He stood in a union hall, before a “Biden Workers for America” poster, amid members of a firefighters’ union that had just endorsed him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also said his campaign would focus on the small towns and struggling parts of Pennsylvania that Democrats neglected so badly in 2016. Democrats tend to do well in cities and suburbs, but Mr Trump fired up large numbers of rural voters, turning Pennsylvania Republican in the first presidential race since 1988. Mr Biden had chosen Pittsburgh to launch his campaign, he said, because: “If I’m gonna beat Donald Trump in 2020, it’s going to happen here”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His map-reading is spot on. No Democratic presidential candidate since Harry Truman in 1948 has reached the White House without taking Pennsylvania. Mr Trump’s path to a second term almost certainly depends on his holding on to the state’s 20 electoral college votes. Along with Michigan and Wisconsin, which Mr Trump also narrowly won, the state will serve as the centre of the 2020 campaign. Mr Biden’s big advantage is that he can cast himself as a local boy. He was born in the state, was a senator next door in Delaware and has long been claimed by Pennsylvania Democrats as their own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nothing in Mr Biden’s cautious speech in Pittsburgh was surprising, including his failure to mention immigration (he knows that more than a few blue-collar voters in the Midwest agree with Mr Trump’s position on that). He has borrowed a slogan—“the dignity of work”—that was previously deployed this year to good effect by another Midwestern presidential-aspirant, Sherrod Brown. In early March Mr Brown, a 66-year-old senator from Ohio, said he would not enter the race. That disappointed many who saw him as an affable younger version of 76-year-old Mr Biden. But it cleared Mr Biden’s path to stand as the representative for America&amp;#x27;s ordinary, hard-working folk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The approach is calculated to undermine a president during a time of prolonged economic growth. By saying “the dignity of work is my measure”, Mr Biden brushes aside statistics about low unemployment and high GDP, pointing instead to how ordinary workers feel. His talk of higher wages and more respect could resonate well with some of the president’s wavering supporters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What does the start of Mr Biden’s campaign mean for his Democratic rivals? Polls suggest he is the solid frontrunner, with 25% or more support in a crowded field. After eight years as vice-president to Barack Obama, who remains enormously popular, Mr Biden starts with a big advantage. Most people already know who he is. Last week he raised more money—$6.3m—in the first 24 hours of his campaign than any other candidate had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He also instantly attracted Mr Trump’s attention. Ahead of his first rally the president posted a tweet about “sleepy Joe Biden” and the leaders of the fire fighters’ union who endorsed him. At times during his rally Mr Biden sounded like a less angry, more upbeat version of Mr Trump—at one point he chastised the bosses of GM, a carmaker, for closing factories in America and opening a new plant in Mexico.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Biden’s greatest strength is his ability to be a voice for the sort of angry, blue-collar worker who drifted away from the Democrats in 2016, while also promising to be a more civil, hopeful and upbeat sort of leader. More than once during his speech he emphasised his optimism, telling voters to choose “hope over fear” and “truth over lies”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Biden will be vulnerable, however, is if primary voters reject the idea of refighting the battle of 2016. He might make amends for Hillary Clinton’s failure to excite blue-collar supporters. He might, by virtue of his association with Mr Obama, win the backing of many African-Americans. But other parts of the Democrats’ broad coalition—including urban, youthful voters, or people who want make history by electing a female president or a gay one—do not want to vote for an elderly white man.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On policy, meanwhile, Mr Biden can appear cautious—he is anxious not to scare away swing voters, even if that means failing to inspire those to his left. Though he criticised Mr Trump’s tax cut, for example, he did not propose reinstating higher taxes on the rich. Instead he promised to close “tax loopholes” that supposedly let the rich evade $1.6 trillion in taxes. That is a big number, but it is a long way from the grand promises made by some of his rivals. Mr Biden is a cautious man. But for now he appears to be the Democrat most likely to take on Mr Trump next year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 10:07:29 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The past decade has brought a compliance boom in banking]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/04/29/the-past-decade-has-brought-a-compliance-boom-in-banking]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_FNP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;COMPLIANCE OFFICERS are the killjoys of finance. To bankers and traders keen to let rip, they are the po-faced types who, while generating no revenue themselves, frown at any transaction that might breach this rule or contravene that regulation. A recent episode of “Billions”, a television drama about Wall Street, captured the rainmakers’ frustration: so fed up is “Dollar” Bill Stern with having his wings clipped by Ari Spyros that the veteran trader rams the side of the compliance chief’s Porsche (pictured above) when he pulls out of the car park of their hedge fund, Axe Capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But pity not finance’s in-house policemen, for they have had a golden decade since the crisis. While swathes of banking has laboured under cutbacks and stiff capital requirements, compliance departments’ headcount and clout have grown. Banks clobbered by fines for aiding corruption, money-laundering and sanctions-busting have beefed up their compliance, risk, legal and internal-audit teams. Compliance officers will never be the rock stars of finance, but they have moved from drums to rhythm guitar. And though some banks hint at having reached “Peak Compliance”, staffing and investment are likely to remain well above pre-crisis levels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Combating financial crime is central to the compliance effort. Enforcement has been ratcheted up since America passed the Patriot Act, which targeted money flowing to terrorists and other bad actors, after the September 11th attacks. Regulators have fined financial firms at least $28.4bn for money-laundering and sanctions violations since 2008; BNP Paribas alone coughed up $8.9bn for sanctions shenanigans. Aiding tax evaders has cost banks at least another $9.5bn. There is more to come: Scandinavian banks embroiled in scandals involving laundered Russian money, including Danske Bank and Swedbank, are bracing for penalties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Corrupt money is only part of the picture. Compliance is about keeping on top of a plethora of regulations, covering everything from capital and corporate governance to disclosure and diversity. Compliance teams even have to fret about diversions like “office pools”—sweepstakes on sports events—in case they fall foul of gambling laws. Thomson Reuters, which tracks regulatory alerts, reckons that 56,321 were issued by 900 bodies in 2017. “You have to build an industrial-scale operation just to digest all the regulatory changes,” says Colin Bell, HSBC’s chief compliance officer (CCO).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keen to show that compliance is a priority, banks highlight it much more in filings than they used to (see chart 1). They seem to have backed up talk with action—though its extent is hard to gauge because disclosure is patchy and banks define compliance and related functions in varying ways. Disclosures, such as they are, suggest that it accounts for 10% or more of the workforce at large banks these days, up from perhaps half that in the mid-2000s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the end of 2018, some 30,000 (or 15%) of the 204,000 employees of Citi, an American bank, worked in compliance, risk and other control functions—enough to fill more than two-thirds of the seats at Citi Field, the New York Mets’ baseball stadium. At the end of 2008 it was just over 4% of employees. JPMorgan Chase could just about fill it with the 43,000 it claims to employ in “fortress controls” (a category that is probably broader).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HSBC, which was fined $1.9bn in 2012 for banking Mexican drug money and other lapses, has around 5,000 employees in anti-money-laundering (AML) compliance. Standard Chartered, which has coughed up $1.8bn for breaches of sanctions, has 3,500. Both banks spend $500m a year on AML alone—for Standard Chartered, the equivalent of a fifth of its pre-tax profit for 2018. British banks’ annual AML spend is £5bn ($6.5bn), according to the Financial Conduct Authority.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since BNP Paribas was hit with its mega-fine in 2014, it has nearly doubled headcount in compliance and other control functions, to almost 13,000. Growing demand for AML sleuths has been a boon for those who certify them, too. The Association of Certified Anti-Money-Laundering Specialists, based in Miami, has seen worldwide membership grow from 5,600 to 70,000 since 2007.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Banks caught up in dirty-money scandals are not only rushing to hire, but keen to advertise the fact in order to calm market nerves. Danske Bank has said it will hire 600 new compliance staff this year; it has already quadrupled the number since 2015, to 1,200. ABN Amro, which is under scrutiny because an operation that it used to own may have been connected with the Troika Laundromat, a Russian money-washing scheme, has disclosed details of its investment in AML (including a tripling of staff engaged in “client due diligence”). Banks are also throwing money at staff training—and policing it more assiduously. Gone are the days when traders could get interns to take their computer-based compliance tests for them while they popped out for a pint. Such ruses are now a sacking offence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Compliance is gaining not just investment, but clout. In the past it was often buried in the legal or risk department, and compliance chiefs reported to chief risk officers or general counsels. Now they are more likely to have a direct line to the top: for instance, HSBC’s Mr Bell reports directly to the chief executive and attends meetings of the board’s risk committee. The CCO’s role now involves much more than ensuring the firm is within the law: liaising with the boss and the board, ensuring investors and regulators have the information they need, and helping shape the bank’s risk culture. “It has become a much more influential position,” says Mark Jackson of Heidrick &amp;amp; Struggles, a recruitment firm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the financial crisis, the market for compliance jobs became one of the hottest in finance. CCOs earn nothing like banks’ rainmakers, but the best-paid can expect basic annual salaries of over $1m. (Compliance also weighs heavily in pay for top dogs: at HSBC, “risk and compliance” is the biggest component the board considers when assessing the CEO, weighted at 25%. Profit counts for 20% and revenue growth 10%.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consequently, compliance is attracting more big names than it used to. Jennifer Calvery, HSBC’s head of financial-crime threat mitigation, was previously head of FinCEN, America’s AML regulator, a role that strikes fear into bankers’ hearts the world over. Recruiters say talented lawyers who would previously have shunned compliance roles are now more interested.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So too are banks’ profit generators. In recent years BNP Paribas has encouraged employees to move between the business side and compliance to “disseminate the compliance and conduct culture”, says Nathalie Hartmann, its compliance chief—and previously head of portfolio management. Under BNP’s post-fine compliance framework, “conduct and control officers” wander trading floors and sales desks, spotting wayward behaviour earlier than would previously have been possible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Banks such as BNP and HSBC, which are now several years into compliance-boosting efforts, have entered a “stabilisation” phase, says a consultant. Having started by throwing people at the problem, they are now seeking to increase efficiency and lower costs. Some, including UBS, have even suggested it may be time to pare back after the boom. Spending on compliance at HSBC peaked in 2017, says Mr Bell. “As in any cycle of transformation, there is a settling-in phase, when you can, for instance, do without some of those who did the initial training or initiated technology projects that are now up and running.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some financial firms, particularly small ones, are outsourcing compliance functions or specific projects. Compliance Risk Concepts, an American firm that takes on such work, has seen demand for its services grow by over 30% a year, says Mitch Avnet, its managing partner. And in America, which strengthened controls earlier than Europe did, the market for jobs in compliance has eased a bit. Jack Kelly of Compliance Search Group, a recruiter, attributes this partly to regulatory forbearance: not so much actual deregulation (the Trump administration has cut less red tape than promised) as “winks and nods” from regulators to signal they will enforce rules less stringently. John Gilmore of BarkerGilmore, another recruiter, says that while the market remains strong, “we’re no longer seeing amazing bidding wars for well-qualified compliance officers where there would be two other offers on the table and you couldn’t be sure the guy would start until he actually walked through the door.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, the biggest question for bank controllers is how many humans they can replace with bots without compromising compliance. HSBC is looking at the possibility of using big data to assign a financial-crime-risk score to each customer. Banks are partnering with some of the hundreds of “regtechs” that have sprouted in recent years: startups with names like Regbot and Arachnys that tout cutting-edge compliance solutions. According to HTF, a market-research firm, global regtech market revenue was $1.4bn in 2018 and is forecast to reach $6.4bn by 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most mature part is AML screening, which is dominated by bigger firms such as Refinitiv and Dow Jones that help banks and companies vet clients and potential trading partners for money-laundering, sanctions and terrorist-finance risks. It continues to grow at quite a clip: sales increased 18% in 2018, reckons Burton-Taylor, another research firm. Some big hitters are backing the robot revolution. “Over time, AI willdramatically improve [AML processes] as well as other complex compliance requirements,” wrote Jamie Dimon, the chief executive of JPMorgan Chase, in his latest letter to shareholders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now, though, many banks struggle to choose between the myriad products hustling for attention, says Stacey English of Thomson Reuters. “AI carries risks we don’t understand,” says a large bank’s compliance chief. Regulators will need convincing, too. In December a group of American regulators issued a statement urging banks to use “innovative approaches”, including AI, to enhance money-laundering compliance. But banks remain nervous that regulators will penalise banks if techno-experiments fail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The idea of compliance algorithms replacing warm-blooded sleuths is fanciful, say experts. Sujata Dasgupta, the head of financial-crimes compliance at Tata Consultancy Services, sees compliance staff moving into “higher-quality investigations”, with bots used for “more rule-based, repetitive screening tasks”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, bankers expect no let-up in either financial-crime enforcement or new regulation. America’s increased use of sanctions as a foreign-policy tool under Donald Trump means banks must be more vigilant than ever (see chart 2). Demand is growing for people who can help banks negotiate new data-protection and privacy rules, such as the EU’s GDPR. Tougher enforcement is increasing compliance risks, too. Britain, for instance, has increased personal liability for senior executives at financial firms caught behaving badly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also rewarding more vigorous compliance efforts is the growing tendency of regulators, including America’s Department of Justice, to offer big reductions in penalties to firms that self-report violations in financial-crime and corruption cases. Hardly surprising, then, that a global study of risk and compliance officers at 800 financial firms in 2018 found that 43% expected their team to grow over the next 12 months, with only 5% expecting a reduction. If the Russian laundromat scandal claims more victims, another hiring spree may be around the corner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A picture of Eliot Spitzer hangs on a wall at Mr Kelly’s compliance-recruitment firm. As New York’s attorney-general from 1999 to 2006, Mr Spitzer was a scourge of Wall Street, tilting at banks for various alleged transgressions and sparking an earlier compliance hiring spree. “He’s one of my heroes,” chuckles Mr Kelly, “and scandals are my friend.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 05:06:31 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The release of “PM Narendra Modi” has been delayed until after the election]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/04/29/the-release-of-pm-narendra-modi-has-been-delayed-until-after-the-election]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_BKP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-29T19:01:43Z&quot;&gt;Apr 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE TRAILER for “PM Narendra Modi” is intended to be stirring. Supporters chant the prime minister’s name, and throng around him, trying to shake his hand. There is emotive music as he addresses a crowd stood atop a car, or strides across a plain to stare into the sun. There are sweeping shots of snow-clad mountains and azure waters as well as flashes of guns, motorbikes and marches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those two and a half minutes are all that Indian audiences have been able to see so far. The film was due to be released on April 11th, the first day of voting in the general election, but has been mired in legal disputes. The Delhi High Court approved the release of the film, and the Central Board of Film Certification had few complaints. But the Election Commission (EC) watched the biopic and declared that it had “several scenes depicting a major opposition party as corrupt and showing them in poor light”, and that any film “which has the potential to disturb the level playing field during the elections should not be displayed”. A web series, called “Modi: Journey of a Common Man”, has also been banned, along with “Lakshmi’s NTR” and “Udyama Simham”, two biopics of founders of regional political parties. The EC recommended delaying the release of the film until May 19th, when &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/04/11/why-do-indias-elections-take-so-long&quot;&gt;voting concludes&lt;/a&gt;. The Supreme Court upheld that recommendation last week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“PM Narendra Modi” has proven controversial for its hagiographic tone and its apparent willingness to tinker with the truth. It is a depiction of a man who rose from humble tea-seller (there are no official records to support this) to hold India’s top job. The trailer shows Modi (played by Vivek Oberoi, a popular actor), in helpless despair during the rioting in Gujarat in 2002, when at least 1,000 people were killed, most of them Muslims. Mr Modi was chief minister of the state at the time, and his critics have argued that he did not do enough to stop the massacre. He has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2017/06/24/indias-prime-minister-is-not-as-much-of-a-reformer-as-he-seems&quot;&gt;never condemned the events or apologised for them&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, if the short reel is any indication, “PM Narendra Modi” shows its subject to be entirely flawless. It is billed as a celebration of Mr Modi’s “remarkable courage, wisdom, patience, dedication to his people, his acumen as a political strategist [and] his leadership that inspired a thousand social changes in Gujarat and later India”. Mr Oberoi rarely does anything other than strive to appear pensive behind his white beard, and utter such clichés as “if you wish to change the country’s fate, first, you will have to face your own destiny.” One absurd sequence shows a young Modi inexplicably caught in an exchange of gunfire between the Indian army and some kind of terrorist group. He risks his life to raise the Indian flag.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ban on “PM Narendra Modi” will do nothing to damage the cult surrounding the leader, and Mr Modi needs little help with publicity. In one interview, when asked about a cross-border air strike conducted by the Indian army in February, he claimed that he “went to Pakistan and killed the terrorists” himself. Last week, in a filmed chat with Akshay Kumar, a Bollywood superstar, both men stressed how “non-political” the conversation was (that it took place during election season was entirely coincidental). It was an attempt to bring out the lighter side of the chest-thumping leader, and Mr Modi responded genially to scripted questions about mangoes (he loves them) and sleep (never more than three and a half hours a night). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“PM Narendra Modi” fits into a larger self-aggrandising narrative. That will matter little to audiences: movies that favour the ruling party have found viewers of late. “The Accidental Prime Minister” (2019), a film satirising Manmohan Singh, a former leader from the opposition Congress party, performed reasonably well at the box office. “Uri” dramatised the so-called “surgical strike” by the Indian army on Pakistan-controlled Kashmir in 2016, and is the highest-grossing Bollywood film this year. “My Name is RaGa” is currently in production, a film that, judging from its trailer, seems to mock the Congress party’s president, Rahul Gandhi. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For all its cinematic flaws, “PM Narendra Modi” promises to be a hit among “Modi &lt;em&gt;bhakts&lt;/em&gt;”, fans of the prime minister who support him unquestioningly. When it is finally released, viewers will no doubt erupt into cheers, whistles and standing ovations. The true story of one of India’s most powerful, colourful and divisive personalities is yet to be told. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 03:11:10 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Avengers: Endgame” is already the year’s highest-grossing film]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/29/avengers-endgame-is-already-the-years-highest-grossing-film]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_WOC351.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;DISNEY’S EXECUTIVE boardroom may be the happiest place on Earth right now. Three days after its release, “Avengers: Endgame” was already the highest-grossing film of 2019. It has broken the record for best-ever opening weekend, thanks in no small part to its phenomenal &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/04/24/avengers-endgame-is-just-the-beginning&quot;&gt;box-office takings in China&lt;/a&gt;. But the latest Avengers blockbuster is no one-off. Of the ten most lucrative opening weekends in the United States and Canada, five were for Disney-owned Marvel superhero movies, and two for episodes of the “Star Wars” series, which is also owned by Disney.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In some respects, the list vindicates time-honoured Hollywood wisdom: sequels have a ready-made audience; viewers want slick, action-packed escapism and retina-burning visual effects. But a more salient point is the genius of Marvel’s “shared universe” concept. Beginning with “Iron Man” (2008), every one of the studio’s superhero films has been set in the same fictional world, the so-called Marvel Cinematic Universe, so that characters from one story can drop into other ones. What this means is that even if a film such as “Black Panther” is not a direct sequel to any film in particular, it is connected to numerous others. Thus, every Marvel release is an advertisement for the ones which came before and the ones which are coming afterwards—and “Avengers: Endgame” is the climactic 22nd entry in the franchise. Don’t expect other studios to copy this winning formula easily. Some have already tried. Warner launched DC’s superhero universe; Universal launched a shared universe populated by its classic monsters. Neither was exactly marvellous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another lesson taught by the top-ten list is that we now pay to see characters rather than movie stars. Cinema-goers may love Robert Downey Jr. as Iron Man, but they won’t necessarily queue to catch him in any other role. None of the actors in the recently revived “Star Wars” saga is an A-lister. It is the intellectual property that counts. And that is another reason for Disney executives to be cheerful. Actors may come and go, but if you have the rights to Captain America and Black Panther, you can always make another hit film, and another. The “Endgame” need not be the end.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 03:11:09 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What the change of emperor means for Japan]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/04/29/what-the-change-of-emperor-means-for-japan]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_ASP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-29T14:42:11Z&quot;&gt;Apr 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON APRIL 30TH Emperor Akihito (pictured, right) will step down as the head of Japan’s royal family after 30 years on the throne. The 85-year-old monarch’s decision came as a shock, as it is the first imperial abdication since 1817. Akihito’s eldest son, Crown Prince Naruhito (pictured, left), will duly become the 126th emperor of the world’s oldest monarchy, which according to Japanese myth traces its origins directly back to the Shinto sun goddess, Amaterasu. What does the change of emperor mean for Japan?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The postwar constitution changed the emperor from a living god with political powers, including the right to declare war, to a symbol of Japan. Akihito, who ascended the throne in 1989, has interpreted this role differently from his father. Rather than sitting in the palace and praying, he made the emperor more approachable. He married a commoner, the first monarch to do so in nearly 2,680 years of imperial history, visited sanatoriums that house leprosy patients, and championed the Paralympics. After the Tohoku earthquake of 2011, which devastated much of north-eastern Japan, he and his wife, Empress Michiko, went to talk with survivors, kneeling on the floor and holding their hands. He has done much to atone for Japan’s wartime history, visiting battlefields such as Saipan and Palau to pay tribute to those who lost their lives. And he has refrained from visiting Yasukuni, a controversial shrine in Tokyo that enshrines the souls of 14 high-ranking war criminals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most obvious change that Naruhito’s succession brings to Japan is the beginning of a new era, Reiwa, which means “beautiful harmony”. Naruhito will have his own ideas about what it means to be a symbol. The Oxford-educated crown prince and the empress-to-be—a Harvard graduate and multilingual diplomat before she joined the imperial family—may be more visible on the international stage than Akihito and Michiko, who tended to focus on supporting Japan’s vulnerable groups. But it is unlikely that Naruhito will deviate far from the path that his father trod over the past three decades. Akihito’s approval rating hovers around 80%. Naruhito will continue to visit disaster-affected areas and advocate for the disabled. He will carry on Akihito’s legacy, revisiting Japan’s wartime past and shunning Yasukuni.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Akihito’s efforts to bridge the gap between the monarchy and the public have ensured his family’s popularity. But imperial crises loom that not even a popular monarch can fix. Under Japan’s Imperial Household Law, the family cannot be headed by a female, so on Naruhito’s accession, the next in line of succession will be his brother, followed by his 12-year-old nephew. The family will diminish further from its current 18 members, since women must leave the imperial household when they marry commoners. Ideas for addressing these problems, such as welcoming female monarchs, have been met with fierce opposition from traditionalists, who represent a support base for the prime minister, Shinzo Abe. Royal rituals, which often have strong Shinto elements, have also been embroiled in controversy. Critics argue that the use of public funds for imperial ceremonies violates the constitutional principle of separation of religion and state. But for now,  a new emperor means a fresh start. After an era marked by economic downturn and natural disasters, the country is ready to embrace a new age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 02:06:26 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What happens when antibiotics no longer work?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/29/what-happens-when-antibiotics-no-longer-work]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/the_world_ahead_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-29T16:40:13Z&quot;&gt;Apr 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN THIS edition of “The world ahead” podcast we examine a possible future where antibiotics no longer work. What causes antimicrobial resistance and what can be done to remedy it? And in a related scenario, we examine technology&amp;#x27;s potential to address the global shortage of medical staff. Anne McElvoy hosts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theworldahead/theworldahead-whenthedrugsdontwork&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1409838532?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/77TqNrVfHv2kK633eQPk4t&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZXdvcmxkYWhlYWQ&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=208475&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Economist-The-world-ahead-p1143184/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:06:33 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The genomics revolution for good and ill]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/04/29/the-genomics-revolution-for-good-and-ill]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190427_OPP510.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-29T14:52:28Z&quot;&gt;Apr 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SEX IS how humans propagate. But developments in genetic engineering might change this one day. “We are, in the future, going to have sex for most of the wonderful reasons that we have sex now: for fun, for pair-bonding, to connect with other people, to give meaning to our lives. But increasingly we are going to do it less and less for procreation,” says Jamie Metzl, the author of a new book on genetics, “Hacking Darwin.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Metzl was speaking on &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s Babbage podcast on technology and science. Today, during in vitro fertilisation, it is possible to screen embryos for genetic disorders. Tomorrow it may be feasible to look for—or even add—new traits. (An excerpt from Mr Metzl’s book is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/04/25/how-genetic-engineering-will-reshape-humanity&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.) The podcast raised questions of technology, ethics and society. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistbabbage/babbage-thegeneticrevolution&quot; width=&quot;500&amp;amp;quot;&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Listen on: &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id508376907?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/0BCUrdrOb3tvfIwazeLBUH&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWVjb25vbWlzdGJhYmJhZ2U&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=142124&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Economist-Babbage-p401958/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Genomic technologies are going from research lab to commercial service quickly, notably in America, which has permissive regulations. Steven Hsu, the cofounder of Genomic Prediction, discusses how his company already screens for Down’s Syndrome and is planning to test for other disorders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet this may just be the start. As more traits are detectable through genetic testing, parents may be able to choose among traits in their natural embryos. But some would go further, and tinker with DNA to produce certain traits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gulzaar Barn, a philosopher at King’s College, London, is uneasy with this. On the podcast, she argued that society should be cautious before accepting genetic enhancement as a good thing, since it undermines the idea that we are all equal despite our genetic or individual differences (be it looks or intelligence, and so on).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Less controversially, basic genomic technologies are used to cure disease. Eric Topol is a doctor and author of several books on technology and health care (including “Deep Medicine,” recently &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/03/23/a-doctors-hopes-for-digital-medicine&quot;&gt;reviewed&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;em&gt;The Economis&lt;/em&gt;t). He looks forward to using genomics to tailor therapies around individual needs. “Instead of this kind of dumbed-down approach, where we treat people without knowing much more about them, we will have a far greater handle at many levels,” he tells us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After talking to scientists, businesspeople, philosophers and doctors, the Babbage programme turned to the world of the arts and culture for the final word. We spoke to Ella Road, the 27-year-old playwright of “The Phlebotomist” (ie, someone who takes blood for medical testing). It recently concluded a run in London. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the play, people are rated for their genetic makeup. She argues on the podcast that her futuristic play isn’t far from the world of today, where people are rated on social media all the time and society accepts wide inequalities. You can read a scene from the play &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/04/26/the-genetic-data-dystopia-we-may-face?fsrc=gp_en&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This episode of Babbage was produced as part of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s Open Future initiative, which makes the case for freedom, rights, technology and diversity in the 21st century. You can read more on the topics at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/openfuture&quot;&gt;Economist.com/openfuture&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And if you enjoy the Babbage podcast, please subscribe to the show or rate us (&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://podcasts.apple.com/gb/podcast/babbage-from-economist-radio/id508376907&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;) and share it on social media.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:06:32 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why do some airports hide their buses?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/gulliver/2019/04/28/why-do-some-airports-hide-their-buses]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190330_WBP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-28T14:39:34Z&quot;&gt;Apr 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;ALWAYS ON THE lookout for a bargain, Gulliver takes great pride in using public transport when he travels abroad. Journeys between airports and city centres are no exception. Most of the time finding the cheapest route takes no more effort than logging onto an airport’s websites or opening a navigation app such as Google Maps. Sometimes, however, airports are not co-operative, trying their best to shove visitors onto convenient but overpriced transport links. Arlanda Airport near Stockholm, the capital of Sweden, is by far the worst offender Gulliver has encountered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Passengers arriving at Terminal 5, which handles most of Arlanda’s international flights, are presented with clear signage to its train and bus stations. The train station is served by the Arlanda Express, a high-speed rail link that covers the 40km stretch to Stockholm Central Station in just 20 minutes. Many business travellers swear by the service for its speed and convenience. But with standard one-way fares costing 295 SEK ($31), those paying for their own ticket may feel less happy about the price. An alternative is offered by Flygbussarna, a private bus company, which does the journey by road in 40 minutes. One-way tickets purchased from its drivers cost 119 SEK–by no means an exorbitant amount, but not exactly a steal either.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;A quick visit to Arlanda’s website gives the strong impression that these are the only two options. But there are in fact more than that. Three commuter buses also connect the airport with Märsta Station, 20 minutes from Arlanda. From there you can take a 40-minute train to Stockholm Central. Because the entire journey can be made within a 75-minute window, passengers only need to buy a single ticket. That costs just 32 SEK if you invest in a prepaid swipe card, or 45 SEK if you do not.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;That one can reach Stockholm city centre for nearly one-tenth the price of the Arlanda Express is nothing exceptional. The price difference is roughly comparable to that at London’s Heathrow Airport between the Heathrow Express, an overground rail service which is Britain’s most expensive train per mile, and the cheap-as-chips London Underground system. Local buses are also well signposted at its terminals. What is exceptional at Arlanda, however, is the lengths to which it has gone to hide the very existence of the cheaper commuter bus services. As well as excluding them from its website, the airport diverts passengers away from its own bus station.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Instead, people arriving at Terminal 5 must ignore the signage and go upstairs to the departures level before waiting at an unmarked stop. (The actual signpost has been placed so far away from the doors of the terminal that bus drivers pay no attention to it and hardly stop there.) Alternatively, local buses also stop at a nearby office complex—another option that requires passengers to ignore all the airport’s signage to find the buses there.&lt;o:p&gt;&lt;/o:p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Gulliver appreciates that the public-private partnership which built the Arlanda Express in the 1990s–at a mind-blowing cost of 6bn SEK–wants to recover at least part of its investment. That is why passengers are also hit with a 120 SEK “station access fee” if they attempt to take slower commuter trains to Stockholm. But free competition between different modes of transport is good for travellers as it spurs efficiency and helps keep a lid on fare levels. Both Arlanda and the City of Stockholm risk losing footfall to other cities if their visitors feel ripped off every time they arrive at the airport.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:06:31 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China-America trade talks, and more from our daily podcast]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/29/china-america-trade-talks-and-more-from-our-daily-podcast]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/the_intelligence_62.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-29T11:23:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMERICAN NEGOTIATORS will be in Beijing this week to finalise a trade deal. What’s left to be agreed, and what are the sticking points? Also, America’s shale boom has given it leverage in international oil markets. How will it use its power? And we look at a foul-smelling Egyptian delicacy that has the potential to kill. Runtime: 21 min.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/thestraininspain-anelectionlooms&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 19:07:48 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Spain’s Socialists win the election, but need to find allies]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/29/spains-socialists-win-the-election-but-need-to-find-allies]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_EUP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BACK LAST May when he filed the censure motion that brought him into office, Pedro Sánchez brushed off demands for an immediate election. With less than a quarter of the seats in Congress, he governed for ten months through a mix of significant gestures—in particular a big rise in the minimum wage—and symbolic acts, such as starting the process of moving the remains of Franco, the former dictator, to a less prominent location.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His reward came on April 28th when his Socialist party won a general election with 123 seats, gaining 2m more votes and 38 more seats compared with the last ballot in 2016. That is well short of a majority, however, so the Socialists will need allies to govern in the 350-seat Congress. But on paper at least, Mr Sánchez may be able to find them on either left or centre-right.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The election increased the fragmentation of what was once a two-party system in Spain. The right paid a price in lost seats for its splintering into three. The formerly dominant conservative People’s Party (PP) lost more than half of its seats. Ciudadanos, a formerly liberal but now more right-of-centre party, came within 220,000 votes of the PP. The hard right, in the shape of Vox, a newish ultra-nationalist party, entered Congress for the first time since 1982. But with only 24 seats and 10.3% of the vote, it fell short of many forecasts. The spectre of Vox, indeed, probably helped Mr Sánchez to mobilise his voters. A high turnout of 76% on a warm spring day helped the Catalan separatists too, who won 22 seats, up from 17.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“We’ve sent a message to Europe and the world that you can defeat reaction [and] authoritarianism,” Mr Sánchez told a cheering crowd outside the Socialist headquarters in Madrid. He will now face two big tasks: to fulfil his promise of a fairer society when economic recovery is slowing, and to try to defuse Catalan separatism. First he will have to marshall a majority in Congress. “From our ideas on the left, we will extend our hand to all political forces [who operate] within the constitution,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One option, and perhaps the likeliest, is to join forces with Podemos, a further-left outfit with 42 seats (down from 71), the moderate Basque nationalists and assorted regional parties. Pablo Iglesias, Podemos’s leader, has been pressing for a formal coalition—a first in Spain’s post-Franco era. This would echo Portugal’s largely successful government. But such an assemblage will be able to govern only if it can rely on the abstention of Catalan separatists on big votes. Catalan opposition was the reason why Mr Sanchez’s failed to pass his budget in February, leading to the early election. And forming such a coalition may be tricky anyway. Many Socialist voters will recoil at Podemos’s commitment to an independence referendum in Catalonia. The Socialists do favour dialogue with the separatists, but a referendum is not currently on offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A stronger, but politically even more difficult, option would be a coalition with Ciudadanos. Albert Rivera, the party’s leader, explicitly ruled that out during the campaign and did so again on election night, saying that he would lead the opposition. Mr Rivera wants a hard-line approach to Catalan separatism, not dialogue as Mr Sánchez advocates; he also sees an opportunity to displace the PP as the dominant force on the centre-right. For their part, Socialist activists listening to Mr Sánchez outside party headquarters chanted “Not with Rivera”. The private sector and many centrists will urge both men to reconsider. But Mr Sánchez is unlikely to announce any decision until after municipal, regional and European elections on May 26th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the entry of Vox and a stronger Catalan separatist contingent, the new Congress is likely to be a rowdy and ill-tempered body, when Spain needs the moderation and concord Mr Sánchez is pledged to seek. The election leaves the Spanish right with a difficult task of rebuilding. Unless the PP does much better next month, its new leader, Pablo Casado, is likely to be forced out. He chose to tack right, trying to echo rather than challenge Vox.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the Socialists, whatever happens next, this was their first victory since 2008 and a personal triumph for Mr Sánchez, who was briefly ejected as party leader in 2016-17. The days of absolute majorities in Spain are over for the time being. But Spain’s prime minister has delivered a rare good result for European social democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 29 Apr 2019 19:07:47 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>