<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Terms and Conditions for Young People’s Essay Contests]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/19/terms-and-conditions-for-young-peoples-essay-contests]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190617_OFD100_google_now.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-19T11:54:02Z&quot;&gt;Jun 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Terms and Conditions of Participation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This competition (the “Competition”) is operated and promoted by The Economist Newspaper Limited (“The Economist”), a company registered in England at 1-11 John Adam Street, London WC2N 6HT, United Kingdom (registered number: 236383). By entering the Competition, you agree to these terms and conditions and confirm that you are telling us your real name.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Competition&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;• There is one essay contest, associated with an Open Future theme (ie, the environment). The contest has a specific question and description to be answered. Details of the contest will be published by The Economist on the Open Future online hub at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/19/our-essay-competition-for-young-people&quot;&gt;www.economist.com/openfuture/essay-contest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Essays should take a side, analyse the situation and build a case based on argument and facts. Elegant writing is important but the judges will make allowances for those for whom English is not their native language. The winner will be based on the subjective decision of the judging panel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• There will be one winner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Entries should be no more than 1,000 words in length, and must be written in English.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• The winning entry will be published online by The Economist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Prizes&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;• The prize for the winner will be an invitation to one of The Economist’s Open Future events to be held on October 5th 2019 and at venues in Hong Kong, Manchester and Chicago. This will include an economy-class flight for the winner, if required to get to the relevant event, and hotel accommodation for at least two nights. The Economist will determine in its sole discretion which Open Future event location to award to the winner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Please note that if you win and you are under 18 at the time of the relevant Open Future event, a person with parental responsibility or some other responsible adult must accompany you. The Economist will also provide an economy-class ticket and hotel accommodation for this person.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• The prizes do not include any items other than those expressly stated. They do not include, for example, insurance costs, the costs of transfers to and from airports, food and drink other than meals provided by The Economist, taxes or personal expenses. Any such costs, or other costs incidental to the fulfilment of the prize, are the responsibility of the winner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• You will be responsible for ensuring that you are available to travel and hold valid passports, any necessary visas and other travel documents for the prize in question on the travel dates specified.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How to enter&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;• All entries must be received by 11:59 pm (UK) on July 31st 2019, the closing date of the Competition. Only entries that are duly received by us by the closing date will be eligible for the Competition. We cannot accept responsibility for entries that are lost, delayed or damaged and proof of sending an online entry is not proof that we received it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Entries must be submitted as plaintext in the body of an email addressed to OpenFuture@Economist.com, with the subject line: “Open Future essay competition”. Note: File attachments are not allowed and will not be opened.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Entries cannot be returned so please remember to retain a copy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• All entries must be the original work of the entrant and must not infringe the rights of any other party. The Economist accepts no responsibility if entrants ignore these terms and conditions and entrants agree to indemnify The Economist against any claim by any third party from any breach of these terms and conditions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Entries must not contain defamatory, obscene, offensive, or any other unsuitable material; The Economist reserves the right to disqualify entries containing such matter. Entries must be suitable to be published by The Economist for audiences of all ages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Intellectual property&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;• Each entrant retains the copyright in his or her entry but grants to The Economist a perpetual non-exclusive royalty-free licence to publish, broadcast (across all media) and post the entry online and on any other platforms yet to be envisaged, together with his or her name, age and country of residence. This licence will be deemed to include all the necessary rights and permissions to enable such use by The Economist, to fulfil the prizes and to complete the administration of this Competition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• By submitting an entry, you agree that The Economist may at its sole discretion edit, adapt, abridge or translate the entry for the purposes listed in these terms and conditions (even if you don’t win we may, for example, publish your essay or excerpts from it as a runner-up in the Competition). You grant permission to The Economist, and to those acting under The Economist&amp;#x27;s authority, to use your name, picture, likeness, voice, biographical information and statements for promotional purposes without additional compensation, in all media now known or hereafter discovered, worldwide and on the Internet and World Wide Web, without notice, review or approval. You agree that The Economist may use your entry for the creation of derivative products and that The Economist shall own the copyright in such derivative products, shall accordingly be free to use them as it wishes and not be obliged to acknowledge you as a source or author of such products or of underlying elements thereof.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;span&gt;Eligibility&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;• The Competition is open to persons &lt;strong&gt;between the ages of 16 and 25 inclusive&lt;/strong&gt;, except for employees of The Economist or its affiliated companies and professional advisors, their immediate families, and anyone professionally connected with the Competition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• If you are under the age of 18 or are classed as a minor wherever you reside, you must obtain written parental or guardian consent to enter and to claim your prize. The Economist may ask the winner to provide proof of age and/or parental consent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• In entering the Competition, you confirm that you are eligible to do so and eligible to claim any prize you may win. The Economist may require you to provide proof that you are eligible to enter the competition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Only one entry per person is permitted. Entries via third parties and automated entries are not permitted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• No purchase is necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Entries not submitted in accordance with these terms and all other rules and directions given by The Economist, or entries that are incomplete or illegible (as determined in our sole discretion) will not be eligible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Prize and judging&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;• A judging panel of at least five people will be established, comprising a number of Economist journalists as well as other persons. A subset of that panel will be responsible for shortlisting what it judges in its discretion to be the best entries, and the panel will then choose the winner from that shortlist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• There is no alternative prize or cash alternative and prizes cannot be transferred to any other person. We may alter arrangements or prizes should this be deemed necessary by us. Prizes are not transferable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• The decision of the judging panel is final, and at its sole discretion. No correspondence or discussion will be entered into by us in relation to that decision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Winners will be announced on or about September 15th, 2019.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• The winners will be notified (by email, post or phone, using contact details provided with the entry) within 45 days of the closing date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• We will make all reasonable efforts to contact the winners. If any winner cannot be contacted or is not available, or has not claimed his or her prize within 10 days of the announcement date, The Economist reserves the right to offer the prize to the next eligible entrant selected from the correct entries that were received before the closing date.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• We may ask you to provide documentary proof or your identity and/or address before award of the prize. The use of a false name or address will disqualify you from receiving any prize.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Use of your information&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;• We will use any personal information that you give us in accordance with the law and our privacy policy at: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economistgroup.com/results_and_governance/governance/privacy/&quot;&gt;http://www.economistgroup.com/privacy&lt;/a&gt;, for the purposes of the Competition, in the ways described in these terms and conditions, and for any marketing or other purposes you may indicate your consent to. We may also share your details with our service providers and agents for the purposes of providing prizes on our behalf, and any sponsors or Competition partners involved in this Competition.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• We will disclose the names and countries of the winners on request from a third party. Their names, counties and countries will be available from The Economist at the address provided above on receipt of a stamped, addressed envelope for a period of three months after the date the winners are first announced.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• If you have any questions or concerns about the use of your personal information please contact us by email at dataprivacy@economist.com.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;General&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;• We are not liable for any damage, loss or disappointment suffered by you taking part or not being able to take part in this Competition, or from being unable to claim your prize or otherwise participate in the relevant Open Future event.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• Insofar as is permitted by law, The Economist, its agents or distributors will not in any circumstances be responsible or liable to compensate the winner or accept any liability for any loss, damage, personal injury or death occurring as a result of taking up a prize except where it is caused by the negligence of The Economist, its agents or distributors or that of their employees. Your statutory rights are not affected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• In the event of unforeseen circumstances, we may alter, amend or foreclose the Competition without prior notice. We reserve the right to change these terms at any time. The Competition is void wherever prohibited by law.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;• These terms are governed by English law you submit to the jurisdiction of the English courts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 22:40:16 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Our essay competition for young people]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/19/our-essay-competition-for-young-people]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190617_OFD100_facebook.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-19T11:45:31Z&quot;&gt;Jun 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;THE ECONOMIST&lt;/em&gt;’s Open Future initiative was begun last year to make the case for political, economic and social freedoms at a time when these values are under assault. We want this exploration of ideas to involve our critics as well as our supporters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of the initiative we are holding an essay contest. It is open to people between 16 and 25 years old. Essays should be no longer than 1,000 words. The deadline for submissions is July 31st 2019. Please read the formal &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/19/terms-and-conditions-for-young-peoples-essay-contests&quot;&gt;terms of the competition&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The winning essay will be published on &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s Open Future website and the winner will be invited to attend one of the three Open Future Festival events, to be held simultaneously in Hong Kong, Manchester and Chicago on Saturday October 5th 2019. &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; will pay for travel and accommodation; if the winner is under 18, we will pay for a guardian to accompany the winner as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Essays should answer the question by taking a stance and making a case based on arguments and facts. We will select the best essays based on the quality of their arguments, not the extent to which they align with our views. Though good writing is important, judges will make allowances for those for whom English is not their first language.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Essayists should email their submissions by &lt;strong&gt;July 31st 2019&lt;/strong&gt;, with the subject “Open Future essay contest” to: OpenFuture@Economist.com. Please send only one, final submission, and place the text in the body of the email: we cannot accept attachments. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The essay question is:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What fundamental economic and political change, if any, is needed for an effective response to climate change?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Description: For decades the world has been aware that human activity is heating up the planet to dangerous levels, with potentially calamitous consequences. Despite efforts by government, business and individuals to curtail the trend, carbon emissions are still rising. Perhaps new thinking is needed, since previous attempts to deal with the problem have failed. So what might be done?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Again, please do read the terms of the competition. We are a global organisation and we operate a strict privacy policy around the world. How we will use your personal data is spelled out in the terms of the competition, and how we handle personal data more generally is in our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economistgroup.com/results_and_governance/governance/privacy/&quot;&gt;privacy policy&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By entering the competition, you agree to the terms of the competition, and you agree to us processing and using your personal data for the purposes described in the terms—including to administer the contest, to attribute winning entries and runners-up publicly and for promotional purposes. We will not use your details to market other services to you unless you specifically give us permission to do so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We encourage you to read last year’s winning essays &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2018/09/10/fresh-ideas-on-how-to-fix-the-world&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good luck!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 22:40:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Madonna remains scandalous, but for the wrong reason]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/19/madonna-remains-scandalous-but-for-the-wrong-reason]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_BKP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-19T11:51:58Z&quot;&gt;Jun 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 2016 Madonna was honoured at a music industry awards ceremony. In her speech, she reflected on her 34 years in the business, her extraordinary success as the best-selling female artist of all time and her talent for shocking people. She said something that was, true to form, startling. “People say I’m controversial. But I think the most controversial thing I have ever done is to stick around.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Asked to identify Madonna’s most scandalous moment, this is not the answer that most people would give. Foremost among her many provocations are the music video for “Like a Prayer” (1989), which the Vatican condemned as blasphemous, her simulation of masturbation during her Blond Ambition tour in 1990, and “Sex” (1992), an erotic photo-book chronicling her sexual adventures with both men and women. The idea that these events could be eclipsed by the mere longevity of Madonna’s career seems odd, until you remember how sexist and ageist the music industry is. In her speech she said that a woman who continues to make music even as she gets older is treated as guilty of a kind of sin. Well, here I am, Madonna seemed to say. Guilty. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She remains unrepentant. Madonna, who turned 60 last August, is back with a new album. Released on June 14th, “Madame X” finds her in her darkest mood since “American Life” (2003). “Things have got to change,” she sings on the hypnotic “Batuka”, “there’s a storm ahead”. Enter Madonna’s alter-ego, Madame X. A spy working undercover as a teacher, nun and cha-cha-cha instructor—but who nonetheless never removes her conspicuous crystal-encrusted eye patch—Madame X is on a mission to cast off the chains of the oppressed. Who the oppressors are is never entirely certain, but they must be located in Brazil, Colombia, Portugal and Atlanta, Georgia, because it is the sounds of those places that supply the soundtrack to her quest. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much of “Madame X” seems calculated to appeal to younger listeners. Her persona is on-trend: it’s cool to care about the issues, and Madame X cares. “God Control” laments the fact that nothing is being done to stop mass shootings in American high schools; “I Rise” starts with a clip from an impassioned speech by Emma González, one of the teenage survivors of the shooting in Parkland, Florida, in 2018. “Madame X” is woke—sometimes a little too woke. On “Killers Who Are Partying”, she sings about identifying with the downtrodden (“I will be gay, if the gay are burned / I will be Africa, if Africa is shut down”). On “Come Alive”, she sings “All I want is peace, peace, peace”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the years, Madonna has hired producers to help her weave the genres &lt;em&gt;du jour&lt;/em&gt; into her music, and sometimes those producers have gone overboard. If you didn’t already know that “Hard Candy” (2008), produced by R’n’B hitmakers Timbaland and the Neptunes, was a Madonna record, you might have thought the singer was Britney Spears. By contrast, the producers of “Madame X”—among them Mirwais and Diplo—understand how to update her sound. On “Crave”, Madonna sings over the skittering high hats and big bass of trap, smoothing the edges of this spare, flinty style of hip-hop until it becomes a wistful lullaby. On the sweaty, sultry “Medellín”, Madonna’s melancholy lyrics give new depth to reggaeton, a genre of Latin dance music as seductive as it is superficial. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Madame X” is no “Erotica”—there are no controversies on this album—but that is not to say that Madonna isn’t experimenting. Since she moved to Portugal in 2017, she has been exploring the sounds of the Lusophone diaspora, as is audible on the most intriguing tracks on “Madame X”. “Batuka” riffs on batuque, a traditional dance music from Cape Verde notable for its call-and-response structure, but adds syncopated handclaps and crescendoing drums to hypnotic effect. With its sirens, whistles and chirrups, “Faz Gostoso” is a carnivalesque take on Brazilian funk on which Madonna and Anitta, a Brazilian singer, rap in Portuguese.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All the same, this reviewer could not help longing for a glimpse of Madonna the provocateur. She is right to argue that she is taking a stand against the music industry merely by making records at her age, but she could be more ambitious. During the height of her career, in the 1980s and 1990s, Madonna presented society with a new model of femininity: the woman who was unafraid to brazenly flaunt her sexuality. She inspired a slew of imitators from Ms Spears to Miley Cyrus. Now that Madonna is 60, and still backed by millions of fans, the opportunity has arisen for her to scandalise the public once again. She could show listeners what it is like to be an older woman, one who embraces her sensuality yet is not afraid to reveal her wrinkles and talk about menopause. That would be truly surprising.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 19:40:42 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“We have become almost unable to make peace”—the UN’s refugee report]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/19/we-have-become-almost-unable-to-make-peace-the-uns-refugee-report]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_blm505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-19T11:30:33Z&quot;&gt;Jun 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE WORLDWIDE count of people forced from their homelands has increased sharply, again. What’s driving these movements, and what are governments doing about incoming &lt;strong&gt;refugees?&lt;/strong&gt; The Democratic Republic of Congo is suffering the world’s second-largest outbreak of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/04/28/the-ebola-outbreak-in-congo-is-getting-worse&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ebola&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;—we ask why it hasn’t been declared an international &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://espresso.economist.com/20e169b48c8f869887e2bbe1c5c3ea65&quot; data-tegid=&quot;ir39ag2e5pgu8acau30edf89h07tpuuj&quot;&gt;emergency&lt;/a&gt;. And, why Thailand is getting into the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/04/27/the-sky-high-costs-of-thailands-first-medical-marijuana-farm&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;weed business&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Runtime: 20 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/205f4563-9a2c-47ed-95c5-92dbf0ab007a&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 19:40:41 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Pope Francis may open the door to married priests]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/06/18/why-pope-francis-may-open-the-door-to-married-priests]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_BLP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T18:12:32Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NOT FOR the first time, Pope Francis—or, to be more precise, his aides in the Vatican—have raised eyebrows. On June 17th, in a document that sets the agenda for a meeting in October to discuss the problems of the Amazon basin, they declared that the Catholic church should consider ordaining married men. The problems of Amazon communities range from the destruction of the natural environment to the persecution of its indigenous peoples. For the Catholic church, however, there is another pressing issue—it does not have anywhere near enough priests to minister to the existing Catholic population, let alone proselytise or fend off a growing challenge from Evangelical Christianity. Some Catholic figures talk of confronting a “Eucharist famine”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The document asks the bishops who will attend the gathering, or synod, to discuss making priests of “elders, preferably indigenous, respected and accepted by their community, even if they have a constituted and stable family”. It also moots the idea of women taking part in what it calls “official ministry,” but quite what that could mean is unclear. The bishops would not be able to authorise the change, but they could recommend it to Francis who does have the power to enact it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those versed in the law and lore of Catholicism might be tempted to ask what all the fuss is about. Priestly celibacy is not required by doctrine. It is a tradition, or discipline. There were plenty of married priests in early Christianity. Even today Eastern-rite churches—those in Eastern Europe and the Middle East that have practices similar to those of the Orthodox but regard the pope as their leader—have priests with wives and children. And since 1994, when the Church of England began ordaining women, almost 400 Anglican priests have been accepted into the Catholic church, including many with families. Roughly one in 10 of the Catholic priests in England and Wales was formerly an Anglican.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, what is being proposed now is qualitatively different. The Eastern rite churches are exceptional in many ways and account for less than 2% of the world’s baptised Catholics. The decision by Francis’s predecessor, Pope Benedict, to open the doors to traditionalist Anglican vicars, is in effect a temporary concession. When the last of the Anglican ecclesiastical refugees dies, if no change has been made in the meantime, the Catholic priesthood of the Western or Latin rite will go back to being entirely celibate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In contrast, a decision to ordain married men in the Amazon, however exceptional it might appear, would set a precedent for the entire church. That is in part because the problems of the Amazon reflect a broader challenge that faces the Catholic church in much of the rest of the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In parts of the Amazon basin, the ratio of baptised Catholics to priests exceeds 8,000 to one. But then it is more than 5,000 to one in Africa. Globally, it has risen from about 1,900 to one in 1980 to about 3,100 to one in 2016. Until now, the lowest ratios have been in Europe and North America. But in Europe the average age of priests is high and, as death takes its toll, the figure will rise steeply. In America, the situation is not much better: already, one in five US parishes has no resident priest. The problem facing the Catholic church in the Amazon basin, then, is simply a worldwide problem writ large. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Africa, priestly vocations are rising. In Asia, they are more or less holding steady. But, unless there is a wholly unexpected reversal in the steeply falling trend in other parts of the world, the remedy proposed for the Amazon basin will be just as valid elsewhere. The snappiest phrase from the document is one that refers to facilitating the transition from a “Church that visits” to a “Church that remains”. It is probably not the last time you will hear it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 05:40:18 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump takes aim at Mario Draghi over interest rates]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/18/donald-trump-takes-aim-at-mario-draghi-over-interest-rates]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_fnp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;MARIO DRAGHI was certainly hoping for a reaction when he stood up to speak at the annual conference of the European Central Bank (ECB) in Portugal on June 18th—but perhaps not from the world’s most powerful man. Mr Draghi announced that the ECB stood ready to ease monetary policy if the euro area’s economy did not improve. Hours after he returned to his seat, President Donald Trump denounced him on Twitter for “making it unfairly easier for them to compete against the USA”. The Europeans, he claims “have been getting away with this for years, along with China and others.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The outburst shows again that Mr Trump views interest rates and exchange rates, and not just the trade tariffs he likes to brandish, as weapons of economic warfare.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By declaring that the ECB had “considerable headroom” to ease monetary policy, Mr Draghi was trying to convince sceptical investors that the central bank would be able to boost the euro area’s flagging economy. He seemed to succeed for a while; the euro fell by 0.5% against the dollar on his comments as investors anticipated further stimulus in the coming months. (It made up much of the fall later in the day, though.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market reaction riled Mr Trump: unusually, he singled out “Mario D” for attack. But he has complained about a weak euro before. In July last year he blamed both the EU and China for manipulating their interest rates and exchange rates. Accusations that central banks engage in competitive devaluation are not new, and have even been lobbed at America in the past. When the Fed expanded its quantitative-easing programme in 2010, a number of countries intervened to devalue their currencies, prompting Guido Mantega, then Brazil’s finance minister, to coin the term “currency war”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump&amp;#x27;s criticism of the weak euro—and therefore of the strong dollar—may have been strategically timed. Over the next two days the Federal Reserve meets to discuss monetary policy, and Mr Trump has called frequently for interest rates to be cut. But since the Fed is independent in its rate-setting, he has no direct influence over its decision, let alone the ECB’s. Asked whether he was starting a currency war, Mr Draghi responded that his only objective was to achieve the bank’s inflation target. “We don’t target the exchange rate,” he said. His audience burst into applause.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump can, though, decide to initiate new trade hostilities with Europe. A decision on whether to increase levies on America’s imports of cars is expected by November. If Mr Trump thinks America has been treated unfairly by the ECB, that might make him more disposed to do so. But the ECB’s monetary easing is not a zero-sum game. Although looser policy does work partly through a weaker exchange rate, its effect on boosting the euro area should also create more appetite to buy American motorbikes and bourbon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Mr Trump were to use exchange rates as a reason to whack tariffs on imports from Europe, that could prove self-defeating. The euro zone’s economy would take another knock and Mr Draghi would be forced to inject even more stimulus, pushing the euro down further. Indeed the ECB thinks businesses’ fear of American protectionism, as well as a slow-down in global trade, is already taking a toll on the euro zone. Ironically, Mr Trump might be part of the reason Mr Draghi had to stand up today in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 05:40:17 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Are women less interested in politics than men?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/18/are-women-less-interested-in-politics-than-men]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_woc922.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WESTERN SOCIETY has no shortage of stereotypes about the activities and interests of men and women. Have they shaped how they think about politics? When asked the question “How interested would you say you are in politics?”, the share of men who answer “very” or “fairly” interested is significantly larger than that of women. This phenomenon has been observed across more than a dozen rich countries. It may have harmful consequences. If women are less interested in politics, they may be less likely to take part in it, including voting or running for office. And their views—particularly on social issues like workplace equality, parental leave and child care, which they care about on average more than men do—may not be adequately represented in government.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/abs/10.1111/pops.12600&quot;&gt;new study&lt;/a&gt; by Marta Fraile of Central European University and Irene Sánchez-Vítores of the European University Institute finds that the gap in political interest appears early in life. Using data from the British Household Panel Survey, which polled 10,300 people between 1991 and 2009, the authors find that the gender gap among 15-year-old Britons is already about 20 percentage points. For 25-year-olds, it grows to roughly 30 points. For better-educated people, who tend to be more engaged in politics, the divide is even greater. Among British adults with a university degree, the gender gap in interest in politics is a whopping 37 percentage points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The authors suggest several possible explanations for the gap, ranging from social norms to the under-representation of women in public life. They note one intriguing correlation. In countries with more gender equality—as measured by an index developed by the European Institute for Gender Equality, a think-tank—the gap in interest in politics tends to be smaller. In Portugal, it is about 30 percentage points; but in Denmark and Finland, where women enjoy a comparatively high degree of equality, it is just 10 points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 05:40:16 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The rising cost of education and health care is less troubling than believed]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/18/the-rising-cost-of-education-and-health-care-is-less-troubling-than-believed]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190622_fnd000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMONG THE compensations of ageing is the right to bore youngsters with stories of the prices of yesteryear. Once upon a time a ticket to the cinema cost just five quid, and a hogshead of mead but a farthing. Of course, savvier youths know how to debunk such tales. Adjust for inflation and many things are cheaper than ever. Since 1950 the real cost of new vehicles has fallen by half, that of new clothing by 75% and that of household appliances by 90%, even as quality has improved. Tumbling prices reflect decades of improvements in technology and productivity. But the effect is not economy-wide. Cars are cheaper, but car maintenance is more expensive, and costs in education and health care have risen roughly fivefold since 1950. Though no mystery, this rise is often misunderstood, with serious economic consequences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are as many explanations for the ballooning cost of such services as there are politicians. But as a newly published analysis argues, many common scapegoats simply cannot explain the steady, long-run rise in such prices relative to those elsewhere in the economy. In “Why are the prices so damn high?” Eric Helland of Claremont McKenna College and Alex Tabarrok of George Mason University write that quality has improved far too little to account for it. Administrative bloat is not the answer either. In America the share of all education spending that goes on administration has been roughly steady for decades. Health-care spending has risen faster than GDP in rich countries, despite vast differences in the structure of their health-care systems.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The real culprit, the authors write, is a steady increase in the cost of labour—of teachers and doctors. That in turn reflects the relentless logic of Baumol’s cost disease, named after the late William Baumol, who first described the phenomenon. Productivity grows at different rates in different sectors. It takes far fewer people to make a car than it used to—where thousands of workers once filled plants, highly paid engineers now oversee factories full of robots—but roughly the same number of teachers to instruct a schoolful of children. Economists reckon that workers’ wages should vary with their productivity. But real pay has grown in high- and low-productivity industries alike. That, Baumol pointed out, is because teachers and engineers compete in the same labour market. As salaries for automotive engineers rise, more students study engineering and fewer to become teachers, unless teachers’ pay also goes up. The cost of education has thus risen because of the rising pay needed to fill teaching posts. Other factors matter too, and can explain, for instance, why Americans pay more than Europeans for health care and higher education. But across countries, none is as important as the toll exacted by cost disease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Baumol’s earliest work on the subject, written with William Bowen, was published in 1965. Analyses like that of Messrs Helland and Tabarrok nonetheless feel novel, because the implications of cost disease remain so underappreciated in policy circles. For instance, the steadily rising expense of education and health care is almost universally deplored as an economic scourge, despite being caused by something indubitably good: rapid, if unevenly spread, productivity growth. Higher prices, if driven by cost disease, need not mean reduced affordability, since they reflect greater productive capacity elsewhere in the economy. The authors use an analogy: as a person’s salary increases, the cost of doing things other than work—like gardening, for example—rises, since each hour off the job means more foregone income. But that does not mean that time spent gardening has become less affordable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Neither do high prices necessarily need fixing. Many proposed solutions would be good for growth but would not lessen the disparity in costs between the output of high-productivity sectors and low-productivity ones. Boosting the supply of labour by increasing immigration could depress costs in both, for instance, but the price of a college education in terms of sedans would remain eye-watering. Innovation in stagnant sectors, while welcome, would shift the problem of cost disease elsewhere. A burst of productivity growth in education—because of improved online instruction, say—should contribute to a decline in the price of education per student. But because a given instructor could serve many more students than before, teachers’ potential income would rise, luring some would-be doctors away from the study of medicine and exacerbating the problem of cost disease in health care. A productivity boom in health care might shunt the cost disease to dentistry, or child care, or veterinary medicine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only true solution to cost disease is an economy-wide productivity slowdown—and one may be in the offing. Technological progress pushes employment into the sectors most resistant to productivity growth. Eventually, nearly everyone may have jobs that are valued for their inefficiency: as concert musicians, or artisanal cheesemakers, or members of the household staff of the very rich. If there is no high-productivity sector to lure such workers away, then the problem does not arise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A cure worse than the disease&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;These possibilities reveal the real threat from Baumol’s disease: not that work will flow toward less-productive industries, which is inevitable, but that gains from rising productivity are unevenly shared. When firms in highly productive industries crave highly credentialed workers, it is the pay of similar workers elsewhere in the economy—of doctors, say—that rises in response. That worsens inequality, as low-income workers must still pay higher prices for essential services like health care. Even so, the productivity growth that drives cost disease could make everyone better off. But governments often do too little to tax the winners and compensate the losers. And politicians who do not understand the Baumol effect sometimes cap spending on education and health. Unsurprisingly, since they misunderstand the diagnosis, the treatment they prescribe makes the ailment worse. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 01:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Banking bad—Deutsche’s new division]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/18/banking-bad-deutsches-new-division]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_blm503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T16:32:22Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DEUTSCHE BANK&lt;/strong&gt; plans to create a new division, a “bad bank”, which will hold tens of billions of euros of assets as part of an overhaul of it is operations. Will the remaining firm become profitable enough to satisfy regulators and investors? And, the growing concern in &lt;strong&gt;China&lt;/strong&gt; over balancing the books at a local level. Also, our correspondent takes a trip to &lt;strong&gt;Citeco—France’s museum of economics.&lt;/strong&gt; Patrick Foulis hosts. Runtime: 16 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/f70d13b5-afcd-429e-a072-05b734f2c009&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 00:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why “The Wild Bunch” ranks among the most influential Westerns]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/18/why-the-wild-bunch-ranks-among-the-most-influential-westerns]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190622_BKP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-18T15:14:49Z&quot;&gt;Jun 18th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 1969 three Westerns vied for supremacy. “True Grit”, the first to be released, was a nostalgic throwback. It featured a veteran star of the saddle, John Wayne, as Rooster Cogburn, a one-eyed lawman who comes out of retirement to help a precocious little girl (it won Wayne his only Oscar). “Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid”, which arrived a few months later, had a more modern sensibility. Its pair of outlaws—Paul Newman and Robert Redford, the two most watchable heartthrobs of the era—were transformed into fun-loving folk heroes; it went on to become the highest-grossing film at the American box office that year. But it was “The Wild Bunch”, released 50 years ago on June 18th 1969, which blew fist-sized holes in the genre. It was the least commercially successful film of the lot, but it did the most to change the trajectory of the Western.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the time, cowboys and gunfighters were dominating the small screen on popular shows such as “Gunsmoke”, “Bonanza”, “Rawhide” and “The Westerner” (and providing Clint Eastwood and Steve McQueen with their first glimpse of fame). But on film, the Western had begun its long &lt;em&gt;adios&lt;/em&gt; in the 1950s. “High Noon” (1950), “Shane” (1953) and “The Searchers” (1956) all charted the end of the Wild West, the arrival of civilisation and the hero’s final walk into the sunset. The Spaghetti Western briefly reinvigorated the genre with cheap, nihilistic and stylistically ambitious films, but even Sergio Leone, the maestro of the subgenre, had released the elegiac “Once Upon a Time in the West” in 1968. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ageing outlaws of “The Wild Bunch” are likewise coming to the end of the road. “We’ve got to start thinking beyond our guns,” says Pike Bishop (William Holden), as “those days are closing fast.” Pike leads his gang into one last hold-up, which turns into a massacre when they are ambushed by bounty hunters. The shootout is bloody, bizarre and indiscriminate. Along with the outlaws and lawmen, women, civilians and a tuba player are blown away or trampled by horses. There are no goodies and baddies, just violent, greedy, immoral men and innocents caught in the crossfire. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sam Peckinpah, the director, spoke of violence as “ugly, brutalising and bloody fucking awful”, but he found an aesthetic appeal in it, too. He showed blood spurting from bullet wounds in slow motion. He made use of quick cuts and cacophonous sound design to put the viewer in the middle of the horror and the excitement. The final shootout, between the four remaining members of the Bunch and a Mexican army, surpasses the first in bloody carnage, portraying an ultraviolence unseen in war films—let alone Westerns—at that time. While the movie was being shot in Mexico, Martin Luther King Jr and Bobby Kennedy were assassinated, and riots had broken out from Detroit to New Jersey. The Vietnam war had entered its deadliest period for American troops. The film’s violence reflected that of its time. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Peckinpah’s outlaws are neither countercultural folk heroes like Butch and Sundance nor noble old-timers like Cogburn. Early in the film Pike utters a starkly murderous command: “If they move, kill ‘em!” He pays lip service to the code of the outlaw—“when you side with a man, you stay with him. And if you can’t do that, you’re like some animal, you’re finished”—but he uses one of his group as a decoy to save his own skin, killing another when the man can’t ride a horse. Pike has alienated and betrayed other friends. In other words, he fails even by his own lax standards, let alone the moral sureties that had once underpinned the genre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The three Hollywood Westerns released the following year, in 1970—“A Man Called Horse”, “Little Big Man” and “Soldier Blue”—were similarly brutal, and they also began to unpick the racist myths that underpinned the genre. Peckinpah’s movie had set a new standard for action cinema. Drink and self-destruction would take their own toll on Peckinpah’s talent, but with “The Wild Bunch” he left an indelible bloody thumbprint on the history of cinema.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 23:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>