<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Why Terry McAuliffe is focusing on Virginia]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/06/why-terry-mcauliffe-is-focusing-on-virginia]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_USP512.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-06T18:21:27Z&quot;&gt;May 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ONCE IT became clear that Joe Biden was running for president, the chances that Terry McAuliffe, the former governor of Virginia, would go after the Democratic nomination himself evaporated. Mr Biden, the former vice-president, fills a lane Mr McAuliffe believed could have given him some running room: centre-left in a field of mostly hard-left candidates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now Mr McAuliffe, a long-time ally of the Clintons, has chosen a different path, returning to his former role as a high-decibel, energetic fundraiser and organiser for the Democratic Party. Mr McAuliffe, who was elected governor in 2013, was a front man for Bill and Hillary Clinton in their presidential campaigns. He once called himself a “salesman” and Bill Clinton’s presidency was his “product”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; “I’m staying home to do what I need to do to help Virginians,” he told CNN in late April after announcing he would serve as campaigner in chief for Democrats running for the House and Senate in elections in November.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The elections could scarcely be more important. The anti-Trump tsunami that in 2016 tipped Virginia to Hillary Clinton—it was the only Southern state she carried—hit again in 2017. Ralph Northam was elected governor in a landslide and Democrats nearly took back the House of Delegates, the larger of the two legislative chambers, winning a stunning 15 seats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shift won’t be complete until Democrats again control the legislature. They need two seats each in the House and Virginia Senate to end roughly two decades in the minority and give the party total sway over state government—the governorship, the legislature and the courts—for the first time in nearly 30 years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ahead of big elections, governors tend to provide legislative caucuses and candidates with financial and infrastructural backing. But since admitting in February that he had donned blackface as a student, Mr Northam’s fundraising has atrophied. Despite polls that suggest Virginians want to move on from his embarrassment, the governor is a rare sight on the campaign trail. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Things could improve for Mr Northam. There are signs his fundraising is picking up. He may become more visible on the campaign trail. And recent breakthroughs in policy, from road financing to criminal sentencing, are reminders that Mr Northam remains an effective governor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But with his popularity dented among younger, rigidly liberal voters who constitute a fast-growing slice of the electorate, Democrats are looking to other big names to fill the void. They include the state’s two US senators—Mark Warner and Tim Kaine—and three new members of the House delegation: Abigail Spanberger, Jennifer Wexton and Elaine Luria. All have successfully harnessed the Democratic Party’s largely suburban, increasingly multi-hued base and regularly communicate with it. And lending their names to those of legislative candidates potentially helps when they stand for re-election to Congress.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But as members of Congress, they are subject to federal fundraising rules that limit how much cash they can generate for home-state candidates. Mr McAuliffe has no such encumbrances. In Virginia, there are no limits on fundraising or spending, freeing him to return to what he excelled at as candidate and governor: squeezing big-dollar contributions from business, interest groups and lobbyists. When he ran for governor, Mr McAuliffe raised $38m, nearly twice what his Republican opponent managed and about $4m more than Mr Northam collected for his campaign two years ago.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once in office, Mr McAuliffe set up a political treasury, in part to finance legislative candidates. It collected more than $10m. Thanks largely to gerrymandering, it did not achieve much: Republicans retained control of the General Assembly under his watch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The fund will be available to him now. In campaigning for legislative candidates, Mr McAuliffe will be talking up Mr Northam’s agenda and the promise of more achievements should voters install a Democratic majority. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Mr McAuliffe may also have to answer for his own embarrassments. As governor he was strong on job creation, laying the foundation for a deal, closed by Mr Northam, under which Amazon would locate its East Coast headquarters in Northern Virginia. The online giant vows to bring 25,000 jobs to the Washington, DC suburb over the next decade.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But a much smaller project remains a big headache. Mr McAuliffe committed $1.4m in public funds to a proposed, Chinese-run factory in rural Virginia that would manufacture anti-pollution equipment for motor vehicles. The plant never opened and the company refused to return the money.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, Democrats believe voters have a largely charitable opinion of Mr McAuliffe. His approval rating was just over 50% when he left the governorship—a job he loved and is not ruling out seeking again in 2021. Perhaps 2019 will be his warm-up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:06:37 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[For Western leaders, Ramadan is a time to reassure the world of Islam]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/05/06/for-western-leaders-ramadan-is-a-time-to-reassure-the-world-of-islam]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_blp903.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-06T08:31:21Z&quot;&gt;May 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AT LEAST since 1805, Western heads of government have been making delicate judgments over how exactly to signal their respect for the Muslim fasting month of Ramadan. On December 9th of that year, Thomas Jefferson changed the time of a White House dinner from the usual 3.30 pm to “precisely at sunset”. The shift was made to accommodate the religious obligations of a guest from Tunis who was playing an important role in negotiations to free the young republic from the threat of North African pirates.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In more recent times, leaders of the democratic world have taken the period of daybreak-to-dusk abstinence, the latest enactment of which began at sunset on May 5th, as a cue to salute and reassure Muslims everywhere, in their own countries and around the world. Often they attend or host at least one iftar, the communal meal consumed when darkness falls. Even President Donald Trump and his administration have begun to acknowledge the importance of Ramadan, despite the Islamo-sceptical feelings of many of his supporters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2017, Mr Trump’s first full year in office, both the White House and the State Department broke with the practice of hosting iftar dinners, and a presidential message of greeting contained the acid assertion that the sacred month “strengthens awareness of our shared obligation to reject violence”. But Mr Trump resumed the practice of hosting a White House iftar last year (though he was criticised for inviting mainly foreign diplomats rather than Muslim compatriots). Last year’s communication spoke more positively of the “richness” that Islam brought to America’s “religious tapestry”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This year’s Ramadan salutation was warmer still. In words that might have been taken from a Friday mosque sermon Mr Trump declared: “During Ramadan, Muslims fast from dawn to dusk, recite passages from the Koran, and perform benevolent acts of charity and good will towards others. By doing so, they develop a renewed sense of purpose in their own spiritual journey, deepening their appreciation for God’s grace and mercy.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The American president is not the only Western leader to have used the holy month to counter the impression of being hostile to Islam. In 2015, Canada’s then Conservative prime minister, Stephen Harper, became the first leader of his country to host an iftar: this was despite the widespread perception that his party was playing to anti-Muslim sentiment by, for example, banning face veils during citizenship ceremonies.  His Liberal successor, Justin Trudeau, has been even warmer in his acknowledgement of Ramadan. In one of the first messages issued by a Western leader this year, he said the fast “honours the values at the heart of Islam, like compassion and service to others”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In constitutionally secular France, the head of state could hardly stage anything remotely resembling a religious ritual in his own residence. But President Emmanuel Macron made a pointed gesture in 2017 by attending an iftar laid on by the French Council of the Muslim Faith (CFCM). He said he wanted to thank Muslim leaders for their support in fighting terrorism. But they were disappointed when he failed to repeat the courtesy last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;German politicians, too, know how to practise Ramadan diplomacy. In 2015, Chancellor Angela Merkel made a maiden appearance at the annual iftar hosted in Berlin by her foreign ministry. She wanted to make the point that the Muslim faith has a place in German life, despite statements to the contrary by members of her own coalition and challengers on the far-right. “It is obvious that Islam is a part of Germany,” she said, knowing that the statement was far from self-evident to many of her compatriots. Two years later, Iran’s foreign minister, Mohammad Javad Zarif, was invited to the German foreign ministry’s sundown dinner as part of a delicate rapprochement between Berlin and Tehran.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Britain, where officially organised iftar meals and Ramadan wishes have been standard practice in recent years, the government was a bit slower than usual this year in wishing Muslims well for their month of abstinence. But Theresa May, the prime minister who like Mrs Merkel is a Christian cleric’s daughter, used her Twitter feed to observe that “Ramadan represents the universal values of peace, reflection, devotion and charity”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 22:51:31 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“I’ve trained for this my whole career”—YouTube’s CEO on a mountain of moderating]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/06/ive-trained-for-this-my-whole-career-youtubes-ceo-on-a-mountain-of-moderating]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/youtube.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-06T09:55:10Z&quot;&gt;May 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p dir=&quot;ltr&quot; &gt;&lt;span &gt;&lt;span &gt;SUSAN WOJCICKI, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/briefing/2019/05/04/the-tricky-task-of-policing-youtube&quot;&gt;YouTube&amp;#x27;&lt;/a&gt;s chief executive, tells our correspondent that moderating the streaming giant&amp;#x27;s content is her biggest challenge. No wonder: every minute, 500 hours-worth of it is added. Also, how West African research is being used to address gun violence in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/04/applying-lessons-from-war-torn-africa-to-chicago&quot;&gt;Chicago&lt;/a&gt;. And a look at the declining number of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/international/2019/04/27/how-monarchies-survive-modernity&quot;&gt;royal families&lt;/a&gt;, and why some that have survived will stick around. Runtime: 23 min &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/everythinginmoderation-youtube&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 19:06:27 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Over a third of graduates in Britain are too educated for their jobs]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/06/over-a-third-of-graduates-in-britain-are-too-educated-for-their-jobs]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_wocfne.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-06T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TEENAGERS THINK they know everything (much to their parents’ chagrin). Graduates in Britain actually do know much more than they need to in order to do their jobs, and so earn less than they could.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are the depressing findings of a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.ons.gov.uk/economy/nationalaccounts/uksectoraccounts/compendium/economicreview/april2019/overeducationandhourlywagesintheuklabourmarket2006to2017&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; by the Office for National Statistics, a British government agency. It looked at population surveys from 2006 to 2017 and compared academic attainment of workers against the average educational level for their occupation. It found that 34% of those who graduated after 2007 were overeducated for their jobs, compared with 22% of those who left university before 1992. The most overeducated age cohort is 35- to 49-year-olds, with men and women equally affected. Migrants tend to be the most overeducated, as are people working in London (where most migrants live).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overeducation can happen for different reasons. Graduates may not have enough information about job opportunities to find a job that fits their academic qualifications. Or there may be an oversupply of educated people in the labour market. But the consequences are bad for both employers and employees. Being overeducated for a job means that people do not use the skills they learnt at university, hurting productivity and wages. Overeducated workers earn between 3% and 8% less compared with the wage of a worker with a similar level of education who is matched to the right job.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But all this bad news doesn’t weaken the overall case for staying in education. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://assets.publishing.service.gov.uk/government/uploads/system/uploads/attachment_data/file/797308/GLMS_2018_publication_main_text.pdf&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Data&lt;/a&gt; from the Department of Education released this month show that the median graduate salary in Britain for workers aged 16 to 64 was $13,170 more than that of non-graduates. The disparity was greatest for postgraduates: they take home an additional $7,900 a year. The Institute of Fiscal Studies has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.ifs.org.uk/publications/13731&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;found&lt;/a&gt; that the wage premium is particularly marked for women: holders of degrees earn on average 28% more than those without such qualifications (there is an 8% premium for men). That is probably related to the fact that non-graduate women have children earlier and are more likely to be in part-time work. Overeducation is a problem, then, but it still pays to study.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 19:06:26 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The US-China trade talks are at risk of breakdown]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/06/the-us-china-trade-talks-are-at-risk-of-breakdown]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_blp902.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-06T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUST AS it looked like America and China were close to a deal, President Donald Trump has brought the two countries back to the brink of a full-fledged trade war. In a pair of tweets late on May 5th he threatened to slap 25% tariffs on all Chinese imports, a rate that applies to only a much smaller portion of imports now. “The Trade Deal with China continues, but too slowly, as they attempt to renegotiate. No!” he said. Only a month ago he had trumpeted that an “epic deal” was in the works. The sudden shift in tone rattled investors in Asia, and most of all in China. The CSI 300, an index of major Chinese stocks, fell by nearly 6% on May 6th, its worst day in more than three years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first question is what the fallout will be for trade talks. Intensified meetings in recent weeks had fuelled the impression that an agreement was in the offing. American negotiators, led by Robert Lighthizer, the United States Trade Representative, were in Beijing last week. This week Liu He, a Chinese vice-premier, was due to lead a delegation of dozens of high-level Chinese officials on a trip to Washington for the next round of discussions. Observers had started to scrutinise Mr Trump’s public schedule to find gaps when Xi Jinping, China’s president, might meet with him to sign their pact. June looked like a good option. Few would bet on that today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump might have thought that his threat would ratchet up pressure on China, helping to squeeze out more concessions just before the finishing-line. Instead, there is a real chance that he might provoke a hardening of China’s position. Some even speculated that Mr Liu and his travelling band of officials would pull out of this week’s meetings. “Let Trump raise tariffs. Let’s see when trade talks can resume,” tweeted Hu Xijin, editor of Global Times, a state-owned Chinese tabloid known for its nationalist streak. (Chinese regulators seem content to let Mr Hu use software to evade the Great Firewall and send out such messages on Twitter, which is otherwise blocked in China.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For months the rough outline of a deal has seemed clear. China would pledge to buy more goods from America to narrow its trade surplus, and America would pledge to lower tariffs on Chinese imports so long as China levels the playing-field for foreign companies. But the details were always vexing. How to measure China’s progress in reforming its economy? American officials have grown tired of what they see as China’s foot-dragging in fulfilling its promises. How to enforce the deal? America wanted the right to impose tariffs with no threat of retaliation if China violated the agreement. Chinese advisers said that was a non-starter. Given these difficulties in striking a grand bargain, a woollier set of compromises seemed the more probable outcome. Trade tensions would surely persist, flaring up intermittently in the coming years, but the prospect of tit-for-tat tariffs would diminish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, though, the immediate risk is escalation. Last year America imposed 25% tariffs on $50bn-worth of Chinese imports and 10% on a further $200bn-worth, leaving another $300bn or so untouched. Mr Trump has threatened a two-step increase. First, on Friday, America would ratchet up the 10% tariffs to 25%. Shortly thereafter it would place 25% tariffs on all remaining goods (a public comment period would slow down actual implementation). So far China has been moderate in its retaliation to American tariffs, even lowering duties on car imports from America as talks inched ahead. But if America goes ahead with tariffs across the board, Mr Xi will come under pressure to fight back. Because China imports much less from America than it exports to America, tariffs are only a limited option for it. One scenario is that it could hurt America in other ways—for example, by using state media to turn consumers against companies from Starbucks to Apple, which count on China as a big source of revenue. “The first step in negotiations is to build trust,” says Zhu Ning, an economist at Tsinghua University. “Now it seems that trust is almost gone.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A full-on trade war would, unquestionably, be damaging for both countries. As the bigger exporter, China would probably suffer more. But Mr Trump is fooling himself if he thinks that he can bring China to its knees with tariffs and that America itself will be unscathed. Over the past half-year, China’s government has administered a moderate stimulus that has stabilised growth and fuelled a big rebound in its stockmarket. Even with Monday’s plunge, Chinese stocks are still up by 25% since the start of the year. The government has kept fiscal firepower in reserve, in part because of uncertainty about the trade war. Increasing its stimulus programme would help cushion the blow from higher tariffs. As for America, consumers there have largely been shielded from the impact of tariffs on Chinese imports because they have been focused on industrial inputs. If tariffs were to be applied on all imports, consumers would not be spared: the cost of goods from pillows to smartphones would rise sharply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The risk of mutually assured slowdown has stayed Mr Trump’s hand in the past. It was when the American stockmarket fell sharply in December that momentum toward a trade deal with China began to build. Xu Gao, an economist at Everbright Securities Asset Management, a Chinese firm, remains optimistic that the same logic will prevail. Mr Trump, he reckons, will ultimately back off the tariff threat, for fear of undermining America’s growth. Even with all the bluster, that still seems plausible. But the scope for miscalculation is all too apparent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 18:06:44 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why companies are so bad at hiring]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/05/why-companies-are-so-bad-at-hiring]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_wbp504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-05T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PERHAPS the oldest management cliché is that “people are our most important asset”. If that were true, companies would rigorously assess their own hiring practices, and record, to ensure that they are indeed recruiting the best people. Remarkably, many fail miserably at this task. Only a third of American companies check whether their recruitment process produces good employees. That is one of the striking revelations in a recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://elb.hbr.org/2019/05/recruiting#your-approach-to-hiring-is-all-wrong&quot;&gt;survey&lt;/a&gt; of hiring by Peter Cappelli, professor of management at the Wharton School in Philadelphia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When companies are asked why they do not monitor the effectiveness of hiring, the most common response is that measuring employee performance is too difficult. Given that staff costs are the single biggest expense item at most companies, this is a startling admission. And, as Mr Cappelli points out, there are some simple things employers could do: check how long newly hired workers stay at the company, or ask a supervisor whether they regret the hiring decision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This failure of monitoring is all the odder given the effort that companies expend on recruiting outside their ranks. In the three decades after the second world war, American companies tended to fill around 90% of annual vacancies from within the company. That proportion has since fallen to less than a third. By definition, companies know more about the abilities of their own workers than they do about those of outsiders. But they still opt for the latter, even though research suggests that outside hires take three years longer to perform as well as internal candidates in the same job. They also pay outsiders more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Companies often seem to be channelling Groucho Marx in their approach to applicants: they won’t hire someone who is actively looking for work. Employers seem to operate on the principle that there must be something wrong with someone who is unhappy with their current job. Instead they aim to lure “passive” candidates who have shown no sign of wanting to move. Inevitably, this is time-consuming. It can also come back to bite companies, as rival firms compete to lure away each other’s staff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In turn, the employment merry-go-round leads to an arms race, and thus higher costs. After all, employees happy with their current job are likely to need a greater inducement to move. Mr Cappelli has not discovered any evidence that hiring outsiders is more cost-effective than hiring other workers, or that passive candidates make better employees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Worker-selection techniques are likewise a bit of a mess. Employment agencies offer a battery of tests, checking things like facial expressions and word usage, but it is far from clear how effective these actually are at picking good candidates. Testing the abilities of applicants at the skills required for the job (say, computer programming) is probably the best approach.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alas, even when these tests are conducted, Mr Cappelli has found that managers often ignore the results. Instead companies have doubled the amount of time spent on the interview process since 2009, according to a survey by Glassdoor, a website where employees review companies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best interview strategy is to ask all applicants the same set of predetermined questions. That way answers can be fairly compared. Managers, though, tend to improvise, looking for workers who will be a “cultural fit”, with questions like “what would you do if stranded on a desert island”? Unsurprisingly, this technique is subject to the biases of the interviewers, who then tend to recruit people most like themselves. Automated hiring algorithms reproduce this effect if they are trained on the characteristics of existing employees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So how can companies improve? Mr Cappelli suggests that firms post all job openings internally, check how many positions are filled from within, and make a greater effort to see how outside hires perform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But everyone should worry that companies are less rigorous about evaluating the performance of their staff than about the quality of the raw materials they put in their products. Improving productivity is generally agreed to be the best way to achieve faster economic growth and higher living standards. Recent productivity improvements have been sluggish. Hiring the right people would be an important way to shift the trend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 04:48:07 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How is Brexit affecting FDI into Britain?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/05/how-is-brexit-affecting-fdi-into-britain]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_brp508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-05T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAS THE Brexit vote made Britain less attractive to foreign investors? Remainers point to stories of cancelled plans, from Japanese carmakers building models elsewhere to American banks shifting staff to Frankfurt. But Leavers counter that Britain is more alluring without the dead hand of Brussels. Last month the country topped a ranking by EY, an accountant, of attractiveness for investors. Who is right?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Countries compete hard for foreign direct investment (FDI). When overseas firms enter a domestic market they tend to make it more competitive, which is good for consumers. And when they take over domestic businesses they often boost their productivity. That, in turn, raises wages.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The Leavers’ case appears strong. In 1995-2015 Britain attracted a tenth of global cross-border mergers and acquisitions. Since the referendum of 2016 the proportion has barely budged. Warren Buffett, the world’s most famous capitalist, recently told the Financial Times he was “ready to buy something in the UK tomorrow”. Low corporation tax and a stable legal system continue to draw business to Britain.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;A common counter-argument is that much of the inward FDI since the referendum has been little more than asset-stripping. Foreigners have taken advantage of a weak pound to buy British companies on the cheap and make off with their intellectual property, the argument goes. Yet even FDI in more concrete things, such as offices and research facilities, has risen since 2016.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;So have investors brushed off Brexit? Not quite. Some industries have noticeably cooled on Britain. It was the top destination for cross-border mergers and acquisitions involving American tech firms in 2014-17. But in 2018 it tumbled to eighth place. In October the UK Trade Policy Observatory at Sussex University modelled a counterfactual Britain that had voted Remain, and found that the Leave vote had reduced inward FDI by a fifth.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Brexit affects domestic firms, too. In January Barclays bank received legal approval to move €190bn ($213bn) of assets to Dublin, fearing no-deal. The London School of Economics recently found the Brexit vote had caused a 12% rise in investment by British firms in the rest of the EU. That capital might otherwise have been used at home. FDI remains strong, but it would be stronger minus Brexit. And Britain has not even left yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2019 04:48:06 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[King Vajiralongkorn of Thailand is crowned]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/04/king-vajiralongkorn-of-thailand-is-crowned]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE TENTH MEMBER of the Chakri dynasty, which has ruled Thailand for more than two centuries, appeared initially in a pair of slippers. They matched a white robe, bordered in gold, which he donned for the first ritual of his coronation day on May 4th, initiating three days of celebrations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost exactly 69 years ago King Maha Vajiralongkorn’s more popular father, the late King Bhumibol Adulyadej, appeared similarly garbed for his own sequence of Buddhist and Hindu ceremonies. Then as now, a military regime ran the country. Ahead of a stage-managed election last month, King Vajiralongkorn made plain in public statements his desire for soldiers to continue running affairs. Thailand’s new monarch is a meddler.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So much for the similarities between father and son. In many ways, King Vajiralongkorn is unique. Preferring to live in Germany rather than Thailand, he spends little time in his own country. Scandal dogs him. After a string of abandoned consorts and seven children, news of his fourth marriage broke just days before his coronation. Since his father’s death in 2016 he has also amassed power. Last year it was announced that the assets of a royal investment portfolio—estimated to be worth around $40bn—would be considered his personal property. (He has agreed to pay tax on the haul.) The king has also reshaped the court and the Buddhist priesthood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His coronation day began with a purification ceremony at the royal residence in Bangkok. Holy water was poured over his head and dripped down his back. In preparation the liquid had been collected from 76 provinces, as well as from around Bangkok, in recent weeks. Courtiers and other bigwigs wore spotless white uniforms. They crawled up the steps leading to their seated monarch, bowing repeatedly when they got to the top. The dousing was probably quite pleasant: roasting temperatures would have made the more ornate outfits unbearably hot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After changing into an embroidered golden suit and coat for an anointing ceremony, the king was attended by some of the country’s most powerful figures. Those involved in the anointment rituals included the ancient head of his Privy Council and Prayuth Chan-ocha, the coup-leader who is Thailand’s current prime minister. Thanks to a rigged electoral system, the latter is all but guaranteed to hold onto office after the final results from the recent election are released in full this week—as long as that pleases his majesty, of course.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While awaiting coronation the king received several ornate symbolic objects, including a sceptre, a sword, a fly whisk, a fan, a pair of golden shoes and “the great crown of victory”. Its crust of gold and diamonds brings its weight to more than 7kg, and not even respectful Thai cameramen could hide its awkward teetering. Once crowned, the king uttered his first pronouncement, which echoed that of his father, promising to reign with “righteousness” for the benefit of his people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among the myriad other rites, particular excitement surrounds a grand procession that will take place on May 5th. It will see the king carried in public on his gilded palanquin through the streets of Bangkok. Given the huge crowds who camped for days to witness rituals associated with the cremation of King Bhumibol, the turnout for the procession will be a marker of King Vajiralongkorn’s popularity. Text messages urging Thais to attend have been delivered en masse. Thousands of civil servants and other officials have been bussed in for the long weekend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thais have been encouraged to don yellow, the royal colour, over the coronation period, although a short trip on a local train reveals a lack of broad enthusiasm for this edict. There are some ardent monarchists, however. Standing close to the palace area, yellow-clad Surang Sri-ruang explains that she has travelled from Chiang Mai, a distant northern city, especially for the coronation. Her love of the late king necessitates her love of his son, she says. “It is a once-in-a-lifetime event that I really need to attend to express my loyalty.” Linda Wornkham, a businesswoman from Ayutthaya, an ancient former capital, agrees. “I’m so happy to be here,” she says. The king, for his part, looked stony-faced throughout the proceedings. If precedent is any guide, he will soon be on a flight back to Munich.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 02:08:49 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The case for weighing passengers before flights]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/gulliver/2019/05/03/the-case-for-weighing-passengers-before-flights]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_BLP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-03T20:36:32Z&quot;&gt;May 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;A FAVOURITE PASTIME of air passengers is to moan about all the extra fees that airlines have introduced in recent years. First came charges for stowing baggage in the hold, then more for in-flight food, allocated seating and even for using the overhead lockers. Yet would the idea to charge passengers according to their weight be one extra fee too far?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;This is exactly what could be done with a proposal from Fuel Matrix, a British firm, to weigh passengers before boarding a flight. The company is currently in talks with several airports about “discreet” ways to introduce weighing technology. According to the company’s chief executive, Roy Fuscone, flyers’ weights will be stored in the same secure system as facial-recognition data, another technology some airports are trying out to eliminate the need for paper tickets at boarding gates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Such an approach could easily go down very badly with some flyers. Some would cynically see it as simply a means of charging larger passengers extra. And it would culturally grate in some parts of the world, such as America, where “fat shaming” is socially unacceptable. (For example, when “Thomas the Tank Engine”, a British children’s television programme, was dubbed into American English, the name of an obese character called the “Fat Controller” had to be changed because it was regarded as too rude for American youngsters).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Yet weighing passengers used to be the norm, particularly in the early days of aviation. Before the second world war, most passengers in America and Europe were weighed before take-off and charged more for extra heft (see picture). This was because early planes were smaller and had strict weight limits. For instance, on the inaugural flight of the Boeing 247 airliner in 1933, from San Francisco to New York, the plane could not carry more than 16,805 pounds (7,621kg) including fuel. So the ten passengers with tickets had to get on the scale, as did and their flight attendant, who could not weigh more than 135 pounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;That practice was phased out as airlines began to rely on broad guidelines to estimate how much passengers weighed. But to be on the safe side, that means airlines carry much more fuel than they need to for each passenger. Airline executives reckon that carrying all that extra unnecessary kerosene around itself burns a surprising amount of fuel. That not only pushes the cost of tickets up, but also means that far more emissions are produced than is needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;From there comes the temptation for airlines to start weighing passengers again. In 2013 Samoa Air in the Pacific began to charge passengers according to their weight. In 2015 Uzbekistan Airways started measuring how heavy flyers were for safety reasons. But predictably, the practice has got some airlines a lot of flak from their passengers. In 2016 Hawaiian Airlines announced that it would assign seats on flights to American Samoa based on passengers’ weights, to ensure even distribution. Samoans, who have some of the world’s highest obesity rates, accused the policy of being racially discriminatory against the group. They filed complaints with American regulators, who ultimately sided with the airline. Even so, there may be a reason why Michael O’Leary of Ryanair, Europe’s biggest low-cost carrier and a pioneer of charging passengers extra for anything he could, threatened to charge fat people extra a decade ago—and then never went ahead with his threat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 06:13:52 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The case for weighing passengers before flights]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/gulliver/2019/05/04/the-case-for-weighing-passengers-before-flights]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_BLP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-04T00:36:32Z&quot;&gt;May 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;A FAVOURITE PASTIME of air passengers is to moan about all the extra fees that airlines have introduced in recent years. First came charges for stowing baggage in the hold, then more for in-flight food, allocated seating and even for using the overhead lockers. Yet would the idea to charge passengers according to their weight be one charge too far?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;This is exactly what Fuel Matrix, a British firm, is proposing to do. The company is currently in talks with several airports about “discreet” ways to introduce weighing technology. According to the company’s chief executive, Roy Fuscone, flyers’ weights will be stored in the same secure system as facial-recognition data, another technology some airports are trying out to eliminate the need for paper tickets at boarding gates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Such an approach could easily go down very badly with some flyers. Some would cynically see it as simply a means of charging larger passengers extra. And it would culturally grate in some parts of the world, such as America, where “fat shaming” is socially unacceptable. (For example, when “Thomas the Tank Engine”, a British children’s television programme, was dubbed into American English, the name of an obese character called the “Fat Controller” had to be changed because it was regarded as too rude for American youngsters).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Yet weighing passengers used to be the norm, particularly in the early days of aviation. Before the second world war, most passengers in America and Europe were weighed before take-off and charged more for extra heft (see picture). This was because early planes were smaller and had strict weight limits. For instance, on the inaugural flight of the Boeing 247 airliner in 1933, from San Francisco to New York, the plane could not carry more than 16,805 pounds (7,621kg) including fuel. So the ten passengers with tickets had to get on the scale, as did and their flight attendant, who could not weigh more than 135 pounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;That practice was phased out as airlines began to rely on broad guidelines to estimate how much passengers weighed. But to be on the safe side, that means airlines carry much more fuel than they need to for each passenger. Airline executives reckon that carrying all that extra unnecessary kerosene around itself burns a surprising amount of fuel. That not only pushes the cost of tickets up, but also means that far more emissions are produced than is needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;From there comes the temptation for airlines to start weighing passengers again. In 2013 Samoa Air in the Pacific began to charge passengers according to their weight. In 2015 Uzbekistan Airways started measuring how heavy flyers were for safety reasons. But predictably, the practice has got some airlines a lot of flak from their passengers. In 2016 Hawaiian Airlines announced that it would assign seats on flights to American Samoa based on passengers’ weights, to ensure even distribution. Samoans, who have some of the world’s highest obesity rates, accused the policy of being racially discriminatory against the group. They filed complaints with American regulators, who ultimately sided with the airline. Even so, there may be a reason why Michael O’Leary of Ryanair, Europe’s biggest low-cost carrier and a pioneer of charging passengers extra for anything he could, threatened to charge fat people extra a decade ago—and then never went ahead with his threat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 05:19:15 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>