<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[On Change UK’s inadequacies, political agreements and missing Scots]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/bagehots-notebook/2019/05/20/on-change-uks-inadequacies-political-agreements-and-missing-scots]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_BRP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-20T16:03:00Z&quot;&gt;May 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I WAS much impressed by Heidi Allen’s first speech when she left the Conservative Party to join the Independent Group, now known as the Change UK Party. How could the Conservative high command have ignored such a prodigious talent? But I’m afraid I was very much underwhelmed by her performance at a Beer and Brexit debate on May 14th, organised by King’s College, London. Ms Allen is now the acting leader of Change UK. But even as her job title has grown she seems to have shrunk as a politician. Gently interrogated by Anand Menon, the reigning Brexit guru at King’s, she produced a succession of bland and vague answers that suggested that she’s not capable of either rigorous thought or vigorous organisation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Allen regurgitated a splattering of good-government platitudes about how Britain needs to be much better at harnessing expertise. Politics should be run more like a business. Parties should take an inventory of the skills and talents of each new intake of MPs. Parliament is run like an old-fashioned gentleman’s club, and so on and so forth. There’s some sense in this—particularly about the skills inventory. But isn’t calling for politics to be run more like a business a bit old hat for a party that presents itself as a change-agent? Donald Trump ran on the promise of using his skills as a businessman to shake up Washington, DC in 2016, and Silvio Berlusconi said the same about Rome in the 1990s. And isn’t the boss of Change UK rather badly placed to call for a more business-like approach to politics? The party has lurched from one disaster to another: failing to establish a brand; faffing about over its name; publicly disagreeing over policies; producing ridiculously slip-shod campaign literature; and, in every way conceivable, allowing itself to be out-performed, out-organised, and out-thought by what is supposed to be the party of out-of-touch bigots, Nigel Farage’s Brexit Party. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Change UK looks as if it will get the Palme d’Or for the most risible projects in recent political history. For a moment it looked as if Tom Watson and the Labour Party’s Social Democratic wing might stage a mass walk-out and join the Tiggers (as Change UK members were known when their nascent party was still the Independent Group). But Mr Watson chose to stay and fight and the Tiggers had to rely on the force of their personalities rather than on numbers. The trouble is that this is far from enough: the founders of the Social Democratic Party back in 1983 were big beasts who were capable of making the weather. Change UK is a collection of small beasts who will probably be swept away by the storm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;TO EDINBURGH—that wonderful study in stone as poetry—to debate the future of capitalism with Stewart Wood, a Labour peer, courtesy of Reform Scotland, a think-tank. To be honest we struggled to find big things to disagree about. There is broad agreement across the political spectrum about the toughest problems facing Britain: the over-centralisation of economic and political power in London; the long-tail of low-skilled workers who are trapped in low-paying jobs; the cult of short-termism; financial engineering; the lack of respect for the manufacturing sector. And yet the British political class is instead focusing on policies that are as divisive as possible: on the right, leaving the European Union, and on the left, massive state intervention in the “commanding heights” of the economy such as re-nationalising the utilities and taking 10% of the country’s biggest public companies. While we squabble over what is contentious, we fail to address what we agree about.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;***&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;SCOTLAND AND England are arguably further apart politically than they have been at any time in the history of the Union, and not just because the Scots voted to remain in the EU and the English to leave. The Labour Party once specialised in projecting Scottish politicians to the heights of power in Westminster—Tony Blair, Gordon Brown, John Smith, Ramsay MacDonald, Keir Hardie. The Liberal Party and its various off-shoots had deep roots in Scotland as well as the English provinces (think of Jo Grimond and Charles Kennedy). The aristocratic wing of the Tory Party also boasted deep Scottish connections: Alec Douglas-Home had an estate up there and even David Cameron could boast a Scottish name and Scottish shooting buddies. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;British politics is now as English as it has ever been. The only Scotsman in front line politics is Michael Gove, the adopted son of a Scottish fishmonger, and a man capable of reverting from Oxbridge English to Aberdeen Scottish if need be. The people occupying the great offices of state (the prime minister, the chancellor, the foreign secretary) all seem to be in a competition to see who can be the most southern. The Scottish Labour Party has all but died from complacency and mediocrity and the national party has been captured by a clique of London MPs: Jeremy Corbyn and Emily Thornberry both have seats next door to each other in Islington and Dianne Abbott and John McDonnell both represent London seats. The Scottish Raj that once ruled over its southern neighbour is scattered to the winds: Gordon Brown and Alistair Darling have returned to Scotland and Tony Blair is in a private jet somewhere in the mid-Atlantic. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Political life in Scotland is dominated by a Scottish National Party (SNP) that has no real relevance down south (though it has 35 MPs, and Ian Blackford, their leader, manfully makes the same speech at Prime Minister’s Questions every week about how Britain is taking Scotland out of the EU against its will). The liveliest issue up north at the moment is the upcoming trial of Alex Salmond on charges including sexual assault and attempted rape. (He says he is innocent of any criminality.) This is dividing the SNP—and Scottish politics in general—between admirers of Nicola Sturgeon, who began her political life as Mr Salmond’s protégé but has since turned against him, and Salmond loyalists who think he is being unjustly accused. The squabble could weaken the SNP’s (increasingly death-like) grip on Scottish politics and prepare the way for significant advances for either the Tories or the Labour Party, with profound implications for the next general election down south.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other great issue is Ruth Davidson’s re-emergence on the scene after several months on maternity leave. If things had gone well with Brexit, Ms Davidson would be re-appearing just as the Tory Party was putting Brexit behind it and turning to the question of where Britain needs to go now it is leaving the EU (Ms Davidson is a remainer who has reconciled herself to delivering the will of the people). But the Brexit problem is even more fraught today than it was when she went on leave—and the Tory brand is far more toxic. Ms Davidson resisted enormous pressure from within her party to loosen its connection with the Conservative Party south of the border. With Brexit lurching from disaster to disaster and the Tory Party increasingly associated with the likes of Jacob Rees-Mogg, she may rue her decision.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 04:40:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Does carving up conglomerates create shareholder value?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/20/does-carving-up-conglomerates-create-shareholder-value]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_woc029.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-20T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Corporate fashions come and go, and this season’s is industrial break-ups. In America and Europe, once-sprawling conglomerates are being carved up into focused companies that investors hope will fare better on their own. Those banking on quick returns have mostly been disappointed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conglomerates thrived in the 1970s, and made a comeback after the merger frenzy of the late 1990s. They are beloved of megalomaniac bosses keen to prove they can run empires peddling anything from train carriages to &lt;small&gt;CT&lt;/small&gt; scanners (as Siemens currently does, albeit not, as it announced last week, for much longer). But the argument that diversity lets a firm’s healthy arms prop up temporarily frail ones is, once again, losing ground in the rich world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Private-equity funds have pots of money to buy unwanted divisions. Listing companies—or spinning them off to existing investors—is easier than it once was. Plenty of activist hedge funds are pressing firms to restructure, hoping to cash in when the sum of conglomerates’ parts fetches more than the whole (studies show this can be true in the long run).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gauging the impact of a break-up announcement is hard. Investors price in its likelihood before a company owns up to “exploring strategic options”. Splits often follow bad results that enfeeble the management, which may in turn mean worse news down the line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our chart, which takes the first detailed news reports of a spin-off as its starting-point, shows that of recent break-ups, only Honeywell, which filed listing documents for its car-parts and home-security arms last August, has subsequently outperformed the broader market. United Technologies has kept pace with it. General Electric, Thyssenkrupp, DowDuPont and &lt;small&gt;ABB&lt;/small&gt; have not. If their share prices fall any more, they will be ripe for a takeover.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 04:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Holding out on Huawei]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/20/holding-out-on-huawei]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_wbp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-20T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON MAY 20TH it became clear that some of the world’s most prominent technology companies—Google, Intel and Qualcomm—had stopped selling software, hardware and licences for intellectual property to Huawei, a Chinese manufacturer of phones and networking gear. This followed an announcement by the American government on May 15th that it was banning the export of American technology to Huawei unless companies got a special licence from the Department of Commerce.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Huawei, which sources a sixth of all its components from American companies, appears vulnerable. It has stockpiled enough components to keep its business running for several months. But reconfiguring its supply chain so that it is no longer reliant on American firms, which would be the only way to truly insulate itself from the trade wars, will be hard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google has stopped supplying Huawei with the proprietary components of Android, the search firm’s mobile operating system. That loss will have no effect on Huawei’s biggest market, mainland China, where it only uses the free, open-source components of Android. But outside China, where the firm bundles Google’s own services like Gmail and search with the tens of millions of phones it sells every year, the loss of Google’s software is crippling (and is a boon for Samsung, the South Korean market leader). Huawei is working on its own alternative, codenamed HongMeng OS according to state media, but is unlikely to be able to deploy it without significant disruption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Huawei’s hardware is threatened, too. Intel, Qualcomm and a host of other companies have stopped supplying the parts and designs that Huawei needs to build its phones and network gear. Huawei’s sales grew by 20% in 2018 to $107bn. If the supply tap is not turned back on, 2019 will be rather less rosy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Farther removed from American jurisdiction, Huawei’s Asian suppliers have been more circumspect. TSMC, the Taiwanese company which makes the semiconductors on which Huawei’s entire business (and that of most other technology companies) depends, is still supplying the firm, but says that it is examining its export-control systems to make sure that it is in compliance with American law. Other Taiwanese companies are following its lead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Huawei’s Asian suppliers must obey American law on export control, in theory at least, because it prohibits not just the direct sale of American technology by American firms, but also its transmission through non-American companies like TSMC. In reality, America has few levers to force companies like TSMC to comply with its laws. Losing TSMC as a supplier would be the final blow for Huawei. Currently, that is unlikely, but if conflict escalates TSMC could become the next battleground.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Huawei says it has been preparing for an American assault on its supply chains for years. In April, Peter Zhou, a company executive, suggested that the firm had anticipated the rising tension between China and America and prepared accordingly. The firm says it has been remaking its supply chains and so will not crack under pressure as its domestic competitor, ZTE, did last year when faced with a similar ban (one ultimately lifted by President Donald Trump in response to a personal plea from the Chinese president, Xi Jinping).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the actual state of Huawei’s preparations may be better gauged by comments made by Ren Zhengfei, the boss, on May 18th. He claimed that the company would be “fine” without its American suppliers, yet conceded that he expected revenues to grow 20% more slowly as a result of the ban. If America retains the ban as Huawei’s stockpiles dwindled, the company—and indeed China’s internet ecosystem—would be more seriously damaged. More probably, America will use its ability to withhold components from Huawei as a bargaining chip in a future trade deal with China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Further such action could also harm America and its allies. Beijing would probably retaliate, perhaps disrupting the supply chains of American companies within China. And although American export law is a powerful weapon in this trade war, its impact will diminish with time. Every time America lashes out at a Chinese company it hastens Chinese efforts to find suppliers elsewhere. Huawei’s semiconductor division, HiSilicon, has been designing its own versions of the chips it buys from American companies. The firm’s HongMeng OS is waiting in the wings. Next time America wants to attack the supply chain, it may find that there are fewer convenient targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 04:40:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why some American states are locking up toddlers]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/20/why-some-american-states-are-locking-up-toddlers]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_usp504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-20T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;LIKE MANY people in prison, Ada Lynn listens more than she speaks, spends most of her time with people she knows best, and is deeply wary of strangers: in fact, when she sees one she tends to burst into uncontrollable sobs, because, unlike most people in prison, she is ten months old. Natalie Myers, Ada Lynn’s 23-year-old mother, was pregnant when she was imprisoned for vehicular homicide. Washington is one of just a few states that offer residential nurseries for women who give birth while imprisoned. Ms Myers loves the programme. “This is the best thing that has ever happened to me,” she says. “I always thought I’d never be a functional person because I dug myself into such a hole. But here I’m figuring out who I am with my daughter.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not everyone shares her optimism. Carolyn Sufrin, a professor at Johns Hopkins who researches pregnancy in prisons, says that “as much as [nurseries] decorate the walls with colourful decorations, it’s still prison…What are the unspoken and unmeasurable consequences of that early environment?” Others worry that they are unconstitutional, and would not survive a court challenge brought on behalf of a baby who was imprisoned without due process. Boosters argue that they cut recidivism rates, and are the best of an array of bad options for incarcerated pregnant women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Bureau of Justice statistics, in 2017, 225,000 women were behind bars in America, with 99,000 of them in state prisons (in American parlance, jails house people awaiting trial or serving short sentences; prisons house people convicted of more serious crimes). That is around one-tenth the total number of people incarcerated, but it is nearly ten times as many women as were locked up in 1978—a rate of increase nearly twice as great as took place in the male incarceration population over the same time. And as America’s total prison population has fallen since 2008, in most states the female prison population has either continued to grow or declined more slowly than the male population.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to Dr Sufrin’s study, as of December 2016, 3.8% of newly admitted women prisoners were pregnant. A 1976 Supreme Court ruling found that the Eighth and Fourteenth amendments require states to provide health care to prisoners, but what that means in practice varies wildly, particularly for pregnant women. They are sometimes shackled while giving birth—a practice that often continues, according to Amy Fettig, a lawyer with the American Civil Liberties Union, even after states outlaw it. In most states, babies born to imprisoned mothers end up with relatives or in foster care.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New York opened the first prison nursery in 1901; today 11 states have them. Criteria for eligibility vary, but generally women convicted of child-related or violent crimes are ineligible, as are women with behavioural or mental-health problems, or with a record of disciplinary problems in prison. In Washington, women accepted into the programme must be pregnant at the time of their imprisonment, and have less than 30 months to serve from the time of delivery; mothers and children are released together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Studies have found that prison nurseries are associated with lower recidivism rates, compared with women forced to give up their children, and with fewer behavioural and disciplinary problems than women in the general population. But whether that is because of the programmes themselves, or because non-violent inmates without serious behavioural, disciplinary or mental-health problems able to meet the strictures that prison-nursery programmes impose were headed down the right path anyway is unclear.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conclusions about their effects on children are harder to come by. But, wonders Dr Sufrin, “if women meet these conditions, what are they doing in prison?...I think it’s essential to find ways to maintain family bonds. I just think we need to do it in ways that don’t involve barbed wire.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2019 04:40:11 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Rocketman” is a suitably ostentatious biopic of Elton John]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/20/rocketman-is-a-suitably-ostentatious-biopic-of-elton-john]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_BKP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-20T15:54:23Z&quot;&gt;May 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“BOHEMIAN RHAPSODY”, a biopic of Freddie Mercury and Queen, was almost as big a money-spinner as the band itself. A notoriously troubled production, the film nevertheless went on to gross nearly $700m worldwide, making it the sixth-most-lucrative film of 2018. It was nominated for four Oscars, including Best Picture and Best Actor, an award which was won by its star, Rami Malek. The producers of “Rocketman” will be hoping that this bodes well for their film, another non-fiction drama about a theatrical and hedonistic British pop sensation, this time Elton John. Indeed, after the original director of “Bohemian Rhapsody” left the project, Dexter Fletcher was called in to supervise the last few weeks of shooting—and “Rocketman” is directed by Mr Fletcher, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite all the similarities, though, it would be astonishing if “Rocketman” sold anywhere near as many tickets as “Bohemian Rhapsody” did. That is not to suggest that it is a worse film. On the contrary, the main reason why this buoyant production may underperform is that it is bolder and less conventional, a full-blown musical rather than a biopic with songs. True, it ticks off all the usual scenes in the showbiz rise-and-fall genre—the meetings with key collaborators, the composing and recording of classic singles, triumphal concerts—but it does so with an impressionistic aplomb that “Bohemian Rhapsody” lacked. It discards realism in favour of razzmatazz, and slots in Mr John’s biggest hits as and when they suit the emotional arc of the story, whether the chronology is accurate or not.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Rocketman” makes its intentions clear in its opening moments when the middle-aged Elton (Taron Egerton) struts down a corridor dressed as a bright orange devil, complete with bejewelled horns and feathery wings. He looks both heroic and utterly ridiculous, which is more or less how the film portrays him throughout. He sits down in a group therapy session and lists the many, many substances to which he is addicted. A counsellor asks him about his childhood, and we’re off: with terrific confidence and flair, Mr Fletcher stages a series of fantasy-tinged flashbacks which recount how a dumpy boy from suburban Middlesex named Reginald Dwight reinvented himself as a sequinned extrovert, how he became one of the world’s top-selling musicians, how he feared that being gay would result in a life of loneliness and how he sank into what the tabloids would call a “drugs hell”. (The film’s embrace of sex, drugs and swearing, incidentally, make “Bohemian Rhapsody” seem even more coy than it did already.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Fletcher is the ideal man for the job. As well as helping out on “Bohemian Rhapsody”, he has directed one previous jukebox musical, “Sunshine on Leith”, and one comic biopic starring Mr Egerton, “Eddie The Eagle”. The film’s screenwriter, Lee Hall, is the perfect choice, too: he is best known for his “Billy Elliot” screenplay, about a young ballet dancer from the north of England, and for the subsequent stage musical he co-wrote with Mr John himself. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Their decision to turn Mr John’s life into what is effectively a stage musical is what makes “Rocketman” such ebullient fun, but also what stops it being as moving or as credible as it might have been. Jamie Bell (who starred in “Billy Elliot”) is restrained and soulful as Bernie Taupin, Mr Elton’s long-time lyricist and close friend, but otherwise the film is as bombastic as Mr John’s songs and as garish as his pantomime costumes. Mr Egerton, who sings all the songs himself, brings the requisite gusto, humour and vulnerability, but he isn’t exactly subtle; John Reid (Richard Madden), Mr John’s manager and lover, is evil incarnate; Mr Dwight, his domineering father (Steven Macintosh), is a parody of English reserve. And although Mr John’s bad behaviour is hardly ignored, “Rocketman”, on which the man himself is an executive producer and his husband, David Furnish, is the producer, insists that its insecure hero is more sinned against than sinning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, these objections are probably beside the point. Nobody goes to see a musical about Elton John because they want nuance. They go because they want fireworks, and the film sets off plenty of those. If it had come out two years ago, it is “Rocketman” that would have exploded, and “Bohemian Rhapsody” would have fizzled out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Rocketman” is released in Britain on May 22nd and in America on May 31st&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 23:40:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why are Indians falling out of love with gold?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/05/20/why-are-indians-falling-out-of-love-with-gold]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_BLP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-20T14:08:31Z&quot;&gt;May 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE HINDU festival of Akshaya Tritiya, celebrated on May 7th this year, is considered an auspicious time to buy gold. Queues outside Indian jewellery stores become so long that makeshift tents are set up to accommodate the rush. Cashiers hand-count wads of banknotes in conditions as noisy as those in a busy fast-food restaurant. The salesmen cater to a remarkable level of demand. As a group, Indians buy more gold than anyone apart from the Chinese (who have occupied the top spot since 2014). Indian households are reckoned to have a stockpile of gold worth $800bn. Yet the Indian market is not as healthy as it was. Purchases of the metal have fallen by around a fifth since their peak in 2010. Why is gold losing its sheen?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start with changing tastes and preferences. Around a third of Indians are 18 to 35 years old. They often prefer to spend their money on electronic gadgets, purchased in monthly instalments on zero interest rates, rather than jewellery. In 2017 consumer electronics toppled gold as the second-biggest contributor to India’s national import bill, behind oil. Moreover, the tastes of those who buy gold appear to be changing. Heavy jewellery has given way to lightweight designs, sometimes with lesser caratage. “Gold is no longer a sign of wealth but of fashion,” admits one customer at a jewellery store in Mumbai. As if to confirm this, in February the price of gold rose almost to a five-year high, dampening its allure as a store of value. This discourages those customers who would buy 22-carat bling, the purest gold suitable for jewellery, with a view to melting and reselling it at a later stage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gold is no longer the go-to investment option for those whose money lies outside the formal financial system. In 2014 a state-sponsored programme opened millions of bank accounts. Mutual funds have returned 12.5% annually in the last decade. The Sensex stockmarket index has gained around 60% in the past five years. In that period, the price of gold rose, in rupee terms, by just 7% from a high base, a far cry from the 12 years until 2012 when it rose by over 500%. Its value as a hedge against inflation, at 3%, has diminished too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;India’s government has long tried to wean citizens off gold, almost all of which the country imports. This burns a hole in the current-account deficit, and a depreciating rupee further weakens the balance of payments. Since 2012 officials have raised quotas on gold imports five-fold to 10%, but are wary of increasing the rate higher, lest they push the trade underground. Last year authorities seized 66kg of gold bars, worth $3m, hidden in four cars. Bootleggers will continue to seek creative ways to beat the system. But if consumers are reconsidering their love affair with gold, the government will not try to rekindle the passion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 22:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The management wisdom of Bill Campbell]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/20/the-management-wisdom-of-bill-campbell]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190518_wbp507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-20T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS YOGI BERRA, a legendary Yankees baseball player, coach and master of malapropisms, once said, “Baseball is 90% mental and the other half is physical.” Managers might need a better grasp of maths than Berra. But they require a similar focus on instilling the right mentality, not just in themselves but in their team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That view is held particularly strongly by three Google executives—Eric Schmidt (a former director of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;), Jonathan Rosenberg and Alan Eagle—who have written a book in praise of their mentor, Bill Campbell. His influence on Silicon Valley was so profound that they have called the book “Trillion Dollar Coach”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most outsiders will not have heard of Campbell, who began his career as a college coach of American football. Later, he worked at Apple, heading the marketing campaign for the original Macintosh, and then became chief executive at Intuit, a financial-software company. But his most effective role was in the background, as a board member at Apple (and close friend of Steve Jobs) and as a coach to companies backed by Kleiner Perkins, a venture-capital firm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google was one of Kleiner’s investments and when Mr Schmidt was appointed chief executive of the company in 2001, Kleiner’s John Doerr suggested that he recruit Campbell as his coach. Although Mr Schmidt was initially reluctant to accept the need for coaching, he learned to value Campbell’s advice. In 2004 Campbell helped to persuade the Google boss not to quit when his roles as chairman and chief executive were split.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Campbell acted as an unpaid mentor at Google until his death in 2016. He also coached executives at eBay, Facebook and Twitter, among others. In 2000 he advised the Amazon board not to replace Jeff Bezos as chief executive of the e-commerce company.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a coach, Campbell’s role was not to be in charge of particular projects, or to make strategic decisions, but to make other people work better. Although he advised individuals, his focus was on ensuring that teams were able to co-operate properly. His motto was that “your title makes you a manager, your people make you a leader.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While he was happy to dish out praise in group meetings, and was a generous man in his spare time, he was not a soft touch. He simply believed in giving harsh feedback in private, and was usually adept enough to make the recipient grateful for the telling-off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When he talked to people, he gave them his undivided attention; the discussions were never interrupted and he never checked his smartphone. But coaching had to be a two-way process. Some people were temperamentally incapable of responding properly. To be coachable, Campbell believed, managers need to be honest, humble and willing to learn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A sign of his unique personality is that he has not been replaced since he died. Instead Google is attempting to incorporate his principles into the way the company is run. All managers should, in part, be coaches. The idea seems to be gaining popularity. In their book, “It’s the Manager”, Jim Clifton and Jim Harter of Gallup, a polling organisation, include a whole section called “Boss to Coach”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is linked to the importance of employee engagement. Gallup cites research showing that when managers involve employees in setting their own work goals, the latter are four times more likely to report feeling engaged. Managers are responsible for 70% of the variance in how engaged employees were.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The primary job of any manager is to help people be more effective in their job. One benefit should be that workers will stay with the company; the main reason they change jobs, according to what they tell Gallup, is for “career growth opportunities”. Workers should get regular feedback from their managers—daily if possible, surveys show. An annual performance review is of little use.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But this approach will only work if it comes from the top down. Middle managers tend to emulate their superiors and to respond to incentives; they will coach underlings if this behaviour is reinforced and rewarded.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, even the best coaches and managers have to give their employees scope to find their own way, and make their own mistakes. As Yogi Berra put it, “I’m not going to buy my kids an encyclopedia. Let them walk to school like I did.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 21:40:17 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“They’re more legitimate than the government”—the Taliban in Afghanistan]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/20/theyre-more-legitimate-than-the-government-the-taliban-in-afghanistan]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/afghanistan.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-20T11:30:32Z&quot;&gt;May 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AFGHANISTAN&amp;#x27;S GOVERNMENT still struggles for legitimacy after 18 years and almost a trillion dollars spent fighting the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/18/why-afghanistans-government-is-losing-the-war-with-the-taliban&quot;&gt;Taliban&lt;/a&gt;; we ask why. A list of the world’s ultra-rich reveals a disproportionate number of female self-made &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/18/how-china-forged-self-made-female-billionaires&quot;&gt;billionaires&lt;/a&gt; are from China—but the trend isn’t set to continue. And we examine why presidential &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/04/25/why-presidential-libraries-are-controversial&quot;&gt;libraries&lt;/a&gt; are so controversial, and why Barack Obama’s is no exception. Runtime: 22min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/battleforlegitimacy-afghanistanvthetaliban&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 19:40:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The promise and problems of cities]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/05/20/the-promise-and-problems-of-cities]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_bkp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-20T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 20th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cities: The First 6,000 Years.&lt;/strong&gt; By Monica Smith. &lt;em&gt;Viking; 304 pages; $30. Simon &amp;amp; Schuster; £20&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;MONICA SMITH begins her provocative and engaging tour of 6,000 years of “crowd-based living” with a question: Why cities? The problems that arise from packing too many people into too small a space range from inadequate food supply and housing to unmanageable waste, not to mention disease, crime and the daily indignities of living on top of the neighbours. These difficulties began in ancient Mesopotamia, the Indus river valley, and in the sprawling metropolises of the Mayan and Aztec empires. And yet people continue to flock to urban centres, leaving friends and family behind to risk an uncertain future among strangers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The answer, says Ms Smith, an archaeologist, is that cities are where the species fulfils its destiny. In Mexicali, to take one evocative example, young rural migrants call the move to the city “buscar la vida” (“to seek life”). Cities offer not only increased economic opportunity but also the possibility of reinvention. People who struggled to fit in when they lived in the countryside can often find in a city others who share their values or interests. In a village, “all the ties are strong (in some cases suffocatingly so)”, whereas in cities people “align with their commonalities rather than divide according to their differences”. Living among strangers is not a cause for despair but a chance to throw off the shackles of custom and kinship.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, city life can sometimes be unpleasant. The hustle can foster anxiety. Disease can spread easily in congested neighbourhoods. Newcomers sometimes find themselves no better off than they were in the countryside. All these problems were as familiar in imperial Rome as in Brazil’s favelas today. But Ms Smith is an optimist—perhaps to a fault. Even the worst blights, such as shanty towns and overflowing landfills are, for her, as much cause for celebration as worry. Admitting that much of the urban landscape consists of slums, she insists that “the steady influx of people to these areas of abject poverty demonstrates that even when city life is very unattractive, there’s still plenty that draws people in.” Waste is testament to “the spirit of consumption that has been part and parcel of every urban centre ever known”. Cast-offs are the byproduct of self-expression.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A recurrent theme is the continuity of urban life across both time and space. When the conquistadors encountered the metropolises of the New World, they felt an instant sense of recognition. There were the same broad thoroughfares and marketplaces, grand religious buildings and crowded slums. Ms Smith thinks their “experiences with New World cities like Tenochtitlan and Cuzco provide the nearest thing to a laboratory condition for capturing the universality of the urban form”. Cities, she concludes, are often alike because they are all designed for the same purpose. People like to mingle with other people. Cities let that happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 19:40:55 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cristina Fernández de Kirchner decides she wants to be vice-president, not president]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/05/19/cristina-fernandez-de-kirchner-decides-she-wants-to-be-vice-president-not-president]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_blp906.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-19T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 19th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;DAYS BEFORE she is due to go on trial for corruption, Argentina’s former president, Cristina Fernández de Kirchner, has re-written the script for this year’s election, due in October. On May 18th Ms Fernández announced that she would not be running for president, contrary to what she had signaled only days before. Instead, she said, she was asking her chief adviser Alberto Fernández (no relation) to be the candidate for the top job, and she will be the vice-presidential nominee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Never have we had so many people sleeping on the street, never so many looking for food and work,” Ms Fernández said, attacking the government of the current president, Mauricio Macri. She explained that her new team was designed “not just to win an election, but to govern.” The news astonished some within her own Peronist movement—another former president, Eduardo Duhalde, said he thought it was “a joke” when he first heard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Fernández acknowledged that she had not always agreed with Mr Fernández. He was chief of staff to her late husband Néstor Kirchner during his Presidency from 2003 to 2007, and served her in the same position for a few months after she came to power in late 2007. Mr Fernández is known as a wily, backroom operative, but few have any sense of his own agenda. Speaking to journalists outside his home, he said he was ready to work on solving the “immeasurable crisis” the country faces. He insisted his running mate had been the victim of the “judicial system…..a shameful process, a judicial battering.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even allowing for the unusual way in which the vice-presidential pick chose the presidential nominee, Argentines find the choice of Mr Fernández surprising. He has never run for public office on his own, and his time in elected office is limited to serving in the Buenos Aires city legislature from 2000 to 2003 on a party list. Pollsters say they have never taken soundings on the man’s electability, or name-recognition, or attractiveness to the electorate. “In an election year as unpredictable as this, Alberto is a wild card that only Cristina could come up with,” says one political consultant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Macri, who is facing a tough re-election campaign as recession, 56% inflation and rising unemployment turn voters against him, confined himself to saying that “to return to figures of the past will be self-destruction.” But prominent supporters within his Cambiemos movement were more forthright. Elisa Carrió, once a presidential candidate herself, for her Civic Coalition, tweeted about the new candidate: “They are proposing Jack the Ripper. He guarantees them all impunity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even within the new Fernández-Fernández camp, there are those who acknowledge that the former president had been weighed down by the prospect of her public trial this week. On May 21st she is due to appear with members of her government, some already behind bars, on corruption charges allegedly involving millions of dollars of state funds and unfinished public works in her home state of Santa Cruz.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alfredo Cornejo, the leader of the Radical party, governor of Mendoza and a key figure within Mr Macri’s Cambiemos alliance, suggested that Ms Fernández had chosen someone she can control, and that she plans to run the country from the position of vice-president and protect herself and her family from prosecution. “It’s all about her warding off the trials she faces for the high level of corruption in her government. It’s all about impunity,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Fernández-Fernández ticket will now seek to unify the Peronist movement, and bring in moderates who have been challenging Ms Fernández for the Peronist mantle in August primaries ahead of October’s elections. One well-known Peronist candidate, Sergio Massa, another former chief of staff to Ms Fernández, expressed a willingness to listen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one will be watching more closely than the International Monetary Fund, which agreed to lend Argentina a record $57bn last year. Mr Fernández insisted he had “no fear” of negotiating a way out: “the ideal would be that we find an exit that meets the commitments Argentina has with the world.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;ENDS&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 19 May 2019 22:40:12 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>