<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Patrick Shanahan is likely to be America’s next defence secretary]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/10/patrick-shanahan-is-likely-to-be-americas-next-defence-secretary]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_blp904.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-10T03:48:37Z&quot;&gt;May 10th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PATRICK SHANAHAN has made little on mark on the Pentagon during his two years as deputy defence secretary and then acting secretary following James Mattis’s resignation in December. He has instituted no major reform. He has made no memorable statement on global affairs. People who have worked alongside the former Boeing executive sound ambivalent about him. A newcomer to foreign affairs and security policy, he is not known to have strong views, ideological or otherwise. He is said to be a competent manager, which might be considered a minimal requirement for leading America’s armed forces and the vast Pentagon bureaucracy. On May 9th the White House announced that Donald Trump intended to nominate Mr Shanahan to his job on a permanent basis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This represents a big change in what Mr Trump requires from his defence secretary. He picked Mr Mattis, a highly-respected former marine general, at a time when he was new to foreign affairs, unsure of the demands of the presidency and bedazzled by a man in uniform. He referred approvingly to him by his service nickname, “Mad Dog Mattis,” though the moniker was rarely used and Mr Mattis hated it. Mr Trump’s enthusiasm for Mr Mattis dwindled once it became clear that he was neither the bull-headed killer Mr Trump had taken him for, nor prepared to be the president’s own loyal general.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While on board with some of Mr Trump’s instincts—for example, in his stepped-up bombing campaigns against the Taliban and Islamic State—Mr Mattis quietly repudiated the president’s values. He spent much of his time flying around the world trying to reassure the traditional allies Mr Trump lambasted. He stymied Mr Trump’s efforts to ban transsexuals from the armed forces. He survived in the administration for as long as he did through a combination of discretion, chaos elsewhere in the cabinet, and the defence department’s enormous heft. By replacing Mr Mattis with a much less commanding figure, Mr Trump has signalled his preference for loyalty over stature in the most independent power-base within the government.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shanahan showed his loyalty earlier this year by endorsing Mr Trump’s scheme to siphon billions of dollars from the defence budget to put towards a border-wall. He has also argued for the proposed new Space Force—in effect a sixth service branch—that Mr Trump has demanded. This is said to have won him over to Mr Trump, who had previously resisted pressure to make Mr Shanahan’s acting tenure permanent.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The announcement of Mr Shanahan’s impending nomination follows the conclusion of a month-long Pentagon investigation into whether he improperly promoted Boeing and disparaged its competitors within the department. Though exonerated by the Pentagon’s acting inspector general, Mr Shanahan was described in his report as speaking peculiarly often—in almost every meeting—about his experience overseeing Boeing’s 787 Dreamliner programme. That points, if not to corruption, to his unusual callowness in government, which Republican national-security hawks such as Lindsey Graham are said to be troubled by. It will also make him a target for Democratic senators in his confirmation hearings. An investigation by the New York Times found that the production facility in North Carolina that makes the Dreamliner has been subject to many allegations of poor safety standards, as managers rushed to meet production targets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Assuming Mr Shanahan is confirmed, his low profile and business background could both turn out to be beneficial for the defence department. It is locked in a perpetual struggle with the sorts of glitches, including inefficient basing, overstaffing and costly acquisitions programmes, he prides himself on solving at Boeing. More traditional defence secretaries—including Mr Mattis—routinely vow to get grips with such problems, before getting distracted by global security. That is less likely to happen to Mr Shanahan, who announced when taking over from Mr Mattis that he intended to travel much less than his predecessor had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The flip-side of his leadership would probably be a diminution of the Pentagon’s role in shaping foreign and security policy. This is good news for Mike Pompeo and John Bolton, the belligerent secretary of state and national secretary adviser. They are already profiting from Mr Mattis’s absence. Having the ear of Mr Trump, who likes their style if not necessarily their bellicosity, they have taken the lead on security issues such as Iran—to which Mr Pompeo promised on May 9th a “swift and decisive” US response to any provocation. As well as being far better versed in foreign affairs, both are more adept inter-departmental players than Mr Shanahan, who has the least government experience of almost any defence secretary of recent times. While presiding over by far the biggest government department, he might struggle to check his cabinet colleagues. He will not check Mr Trump.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 13:06:38 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The role of the state in creating economic value]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/05/09/the-role-of-the-state-in-creating-economic-value]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_OPP503_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-09T16:19:50Z&quot;&gt;May 9th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE ECONOMIC reforms of Ronald Reagan in America and Margret Thatcher in Britain in the 1980s unleashed the power of the private sector for economic growth. The deregulation and privatisations that followed not only perked up their own economies, but became a template for reform in many other countries around the world, from Mexico to Russia.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet did the pro-private sector, anti-state ethos go too far? In her book “The Value of Everything: Making and Taking in the Global Economy,” Mariana Mazzucato, an economist at University College London, argues that policymakers and the public have lost sight of government’s ability to create economic value. She believes that our understanding of the origins of value are misguided and that governments should be able to “explore, experiment and take risks” on behalf of the public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That view is not shared by all, since government intervention brings the risk of politicising decisions that are better made by market forces. As part of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s Open Future project, we posed several questions to Ms Mazzucato about her ideas. It is followed by a short excerpt from the book, about how classical economists viewed the role of the state, from Smith to Marx—and what a “humble citizen” today might think.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*       *       *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;An interview with Mariana Mazzucato&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: What constitutes economic value, and what do we know about how and when governments add it?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mariana Mazzucato&lt;/strong&gt;: Value is “co-created” by different actors in the economy when they come together in productive ways to create new types of goods and services—each actor adding time and effort. While this process is well understood in business—that is what they teach in business schools—it is much less understood in the public sector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is because policy is seen at best as fixing market failures, while in reality, policy has been most effective when it has actively co-created and co-shaped markets, not only fixed them: whether this was when the state provided the “investment of first resort” in the IT revolution, or the current role that public investments are playing in the green revolution, such as through the role of organisations like ARPA-E in America, but also of public banks like the KfW in Germany.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In each of these cases, government had to have a vision for the future, and make the necessary investments that later crowded-in more risk-averse private firms. But the key question is “what is being created”? Is it war machines, or tools for an economy that is more sustainable and inclusive? Even fracking initially came from government investments. Once we admit the state can be transformational, the key question is how and what.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp502_0.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: Governments can be too interventionist and make spending decisions that are driven by politics: can that realistically be curtailed?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Mazzucato&lt;/strong&gt;: In order to co-create and co-shape markets the state must have the right organisational structure and capabilities. Yet there is a self-fulfilling prophecy that because there is a narrow framework to understand the role of government, there is also a poor understanding of what capabilities the state requires in order to be effective. This means there is under-investment. Indeed, the irony is that when the state does not understand its role in creating public value through public purpose, then it ends up being ineffective and crowding out, and being more easily captured.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: You have written about sectors that extract value from the economy; rentiers like financial services and parts of big tech. Aren’t governments capable of being just as extractive?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Mazzucato&lt;/strong&gt;: Yes, of course. Both public and private actors can be extractive. The problem is how to transform private and public organisations so that they are more purpose-driven—but also that their interactions are more symbiotic and less parasitic. Adam Smith said that free markets were about making markets free from rent—and that means looking at how to transform both public and private organisations so that they are adding not extracting. It also fundamentally changes how we understand public-private partnerships.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: If society attributes too much value to sectors you regard as unproductive, such as financial services, is that not merely an expression of our collective priorities?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Mazzucato&lt;/strong&gt;: There are strong narratives about value creation that have also enabled more extraction to happen. While there was plenty of value extraction by landlords in the 17th century, they did not pretend to be productive, creative or innovative. They just said: give me your money. Because there is a feedback between how we value things and how things work out in the real economy—what sociologists call “performativity”—we cannot pretend that the status quo is our collective interest. There is a lot of conning going on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I also argue that the mainstream theory of value being taught in economics departments worldwide is too subjective. It’s based on preferences such as “firms maximise profits”, “consumer utility” and “workers choosing between leisure and work”. So it becomes much harder to objectively differentiate profits from rents, which was a key distinction made by the classical economists like Smith, Ricardo and Marx.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist: Around the world, public trust in politicians is dismally low. Would public support give governments a more direct role in economic growth?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Mazzucato&lt;/strong&gt;: The problem is not about giving governments more or less of a role. The problem is what kind of role. There is more corruption and capture when government sees its role as just subsidising, or providing different forms of guarantees and tax cuts—as opposed to investing ambitiously to create new opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have been a strong advocate for a mission-oriented approach to address the key challenges of our time—from climate change to healthy living. But key here is that the missions themselves should be co-created. No so much of a Kennedy-style moon-shot but more of different types of actors defining what a green transition might look like and then government using all it has at its disposal—from procurement to prize schemes—to crowd-in multiple solutions to “get there”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is the lesson from the moon-shot: a clear goal; many different sectors, actors and disciplines coming together to solve the problem; all fuelled by hundreds of projects. Some may fail, so governments need to be willing to explore, experiment and take risks. But risks for the public good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; *       *       *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190511_opp501_0.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Government value in the history of economic thought&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Excerpted from “The Value of Everything: Making and Taking in the Global Economy” by Mariana Mazzucato (Penguin, 2018):&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Economics emerged as a discipline in large part to assert the productive primacy of the private sector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starting with the French physiocrats, economists found that government was required for the orderly functioning of society and thus for setting conditions for the production of value. But in itself, government was not inherently productive; rather, it was a stabilizing background force. The physiocrats pleaded with King Louis XV to &lt;em&gt;laissez-faire&lt;/em&gt;—not to micro-manage the economy by siphoning off as much gold as possible, and thereby upset the intricate mechanism by which value was really created—through productivity of the land, not by accumulating precious metal. According to Quesnay’s &lt;em&gt;Tableau Économique&lt;/em&gt;, value produced in agriculture flowed through the economy. But government was absent, ‘unproductive’. As part of the ruling class, members of the government got a share of the value apportioned simply because they were in power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nevertheless, Quesnay knew, the &lt;em&gt;Tableau&lt;/em&gt; did not work by itself. There was something to be ‘governed’. Quesnay argued that the wealth of the nation could only be upheld through ‘“roper management by the general administration”—what we would call government regulation. He thought that free competition would best benefit the economy—but to achieve this, far from excluding government, he favoured an activist state that would break monopolies and establish the institutional conditions necessary for competition and free trade to flourish and value creation to thrive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adam Smith, meanwhile, devoted the fifth book of his &lt;em&gt;The Wealth of Nations&lt;/em&gt; to the role of government in the economy. His aim was not only to explain the prosperity of the nation, but also “to supply the state or commonwealth with a revenue sufficient for the public services.”. Like Quesnay, Smith believed the state was necessary. Indeed, he was convinced that national wealth could only be increased through division of labour in “a well-governed society”, in which he singled out three crucial functions of government: the military, the judiciary and other public services such as provision of infrastructure. These are public goods—producers cannot exclude anyone from consuming them. For Smith, such public goods had to be paid for by the state; some sort of taxation was therefore necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;David Ricardo was perhaps the most anti-government of the classical economists. Although the title of his &lt;em&gt;The Principles of Political Economy and Taxation&lt;/em&gt; contains a key activity of government (taxation), he never considered how taxation could allow government spending to encourage production and hence value creation. For Ricardo, taxes are the ‘“portion of the produce of land and labour, placed at the disposal of government” to spend on areas such as education. If these expenditures are too high, he writes, the capital of the country is diminished, and “distress and ruin will follow”. Ricardo never asks, as Smith did, whether some taxes are necessary to help capitalists carry out production. He assumes infrastructure—the judiciary and so on—as a given. In effect, Ricardo narrows the production of economic value strictly to the private sphere. Admiring Ricardo’s rigorous analytical arguments, in comparison with Smith’s more fluid and interdisciplinary philosophical and political approach, economists followed him and excluded government from the productive sector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Marx’s view of government, meanwhile, derived from his materialist view of history, whereby the organization of society (including government structures) reflects the economic system (which he called the mode of production) and the underlying social relations: the interaction between classes. So, in his view, under the capitalist mode of production—based on surplus value generated from exploitation of labour—government and law reflected the needs of capitalists. Marx ridiculed some followers of Smith and Ricardo for haranguing state officials as “parasites on the actual producers”, then realizing that they were after all necessary to support the capitalist system. Nevertheless Marx, like Smith before him, while stressing the necessity of some functions of the state, placed state officials in the category of unproductive labourers outside the production boundary. The capitalist class had an interest in maintaining the state in a position strong enough to guarantee the rule of law and advance their class interests—but nothing more than that: “The executive of the modern state is nothing but a committee for managing the common affairs of the whole bourgeoisie.” The question concerning Marx was what constituted the ‘right’ size of government to provide the necessary services without taking away any additional profits.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While the neoclassical economists broke with the labour theory of value, they did not depart from their predecessors’ view that government was necessary but unproductive. Marginal utility, as we have seen, locates value in the price of any transaction that takes place freely in the market. According to this perspective, government produces nothing: it cannot create value. And government’s main source of income is taxes, which are a transfer of existing value created in the private sector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The immensely influential Alfred Marshall was quite nuanced in his discussion of economic life in his Principles, but still recommended that economics should avoid ‘as far as possible’ the discussion of matters associated with government. He believed that government interference in, or regulation of, the market would often happen in response to attempts by vested interests to rig the market in their favour (i.e. government would be ‘captured’ by such interests)—thus only hurting a particular competitor rather than benefiting society as a whole.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To the humble citizen, however, it might not be so obvious that government does not create value. We have already seen three ways in which it does so: bailing out the banks; investing in infrastructure, education and basic science; and funding radical, innovative technologies which are transforming our lives.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The crucial point is that many of these activities involve taking risks and &lt;em&gt;investing&lt;/em&gt;—exactly what austerity doesn’t do—and in so doing they create value. But that value is not easily visible, for the simple reason that much of it goes into the pockets of the private sector.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;_______________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt; Excerpted from “The Value of Everything: Making and Taking in the Global Economy” by Mariana Mazzucato. Published by Penguin. Copyright © 2018 by Mariana Mazzucato. All rights reserved.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 01:06:35 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The ANC is re-elected but without much enthusiasm]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/09/the-anc-is-re-elected-but-without-much-enthusiasm]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_map503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-09T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 9th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I AM WHAT I am today because of the ANC,” says Princess Kgosimang, as she walks the short distance from her house in Soweto to the polling station. The 71-year-old lists the ways her life has improved since the end of apartheid. She has a home of her own, a state pension of 1,700 rand ($118) per month and her grandchildren go to multiracial schools. While she dislikes how corrupt the African National Congress (ANC) became under Jacob Zuma, president from 2009 to 2018, she believes that his successor, Cyril Ramaphosa, can clean house. “I want to give him a chance to make amends,” she says.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On May 8th enough voters like Ms Kgosimang turned out to re-elect the party that has governed South Africa since 1994, when Nelson Mandela was elected as the country’s first black president. At the time of writing the ANC is projected to win 57% of the national vote, according to analysis by Dawie Scholtz, a psephologist. Yet this is not an enthusiastic endorsement. The ANC’s success probably relied on older black voters with memories of the struggle, rather than on younger South Africans who are fed up with corruption, inequality and a lack of jobs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In each of the five previous general elections since the advent of democracy the ANC won more than 60% of the vote. This will be the first time the party’s result fell below that line in a national ballot. Turnout is also down; projections suggest just 65% of the registered electorate voted, compared with 73% in 2014. It is a long way from 1994, when turnout was near universal, with millions of non-white South Africans waking up before dawn to line up for their first opportunity to vote.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Ramaphosa’s supporters will argue that 57% is a decent result. They will point to the 54% of the vote the ANC got in local elections in 2016, arguing that the party’s performance would have been much worse under a different leader. That is most likely true —and their case will be stronger if the ANC can hold on to its majority in Gauteng, the country’s most populous province. (That result was too close to call at the time of writing.) But it is also apparent that the president has not been able to reverse the downward trend in the ANC’s performance at national elections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not that the results were especially encouraging for the two main opposition parties: the Democratic Alliance (DA) and the Economic Freedom Fighters (EFF). Though it will retain majority control of the Western Cape province, which it has governed since 2009, the DA seems to have made little progress nationally since 2014, when it won 22% of the vote. It is projected to win a marginally lower share this time around, according to Mr Scholtz. Another model devised by the Council for Scientific and Industrial Research predicts it will get 24%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Early indications suggest that although the DA increased its share of the black electorate, it lost votes among white Afrikaans-speaking South Africans. These probably went to the Freedom Front Plus party, which may win about 500,000 votes or around 3% of the total. That would represent its best ever showing and a tripling of support since 2014, a reflection of its voters’ concern about policies such as the expropriation of land without compensation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That policy has been championed by the EFF. The populist black-nationalist party is projected to win about 10% of the vote, up from 6% in 2014, and may yet hold the balance of power in Gauteng. Nevertheless its projected tally is a few percentage points below what some polls had suggested—a reflection perhaps of low turnout among young black South Africans, a group that has gravitated towards the EFF.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Though the official final tallies will not be declared until the weekend, attention is already turning to what the results mean for reform under Mr Ramaphosa, whose inauguration is scheduled for May 25th. South Africa is in a perilous state. The official unemployment rate is 27%, debt to GDP has more than doubled over the past decade to 56%, and Eskom, the state-owned utility, struggles to keep the lights on. South Africans are increasingly frustrated that no one has yet been prosecuted for corruption during the era of “state capture” under Mr Zuma, when a corrupt family dictated government policies and the appointment of cabinet ministers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Ramaphosa has slowly begun to repair the country’s institutions. He has said some sensible things about the economy. But he has been constrained by his own party, many of whose members have been “deployed” into state-owned companies or the civil service and fear for their jobs, should the president prove serious about sacking the inept and prosecuting the corrupt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will be a lot of commentary about whether the ANC’s share of the national vote gives Mr Ramaphosa a mandate for reform. More important, though, is whether he is willing to use fully the considerable powers of the South African presidency.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There will be two early clues. The first is the size of his new cabinet. South Africa has more than 30 cabinet ministers, a high number in global terms. A slim-downed executive would be a symbol that the president is less inclined to hand out plum jobs to buy the loyalty of incompetent comrades. The second clue will be who he appoints as ministers. If the last of Mr Zuma’s loyalists, such as Nomvula Mokonyane and Bathabile Dlamini, are removed, while wise hands such as Tito Mboweni and Pravin Gordhan, are retained, then this will be a promising sign.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Twenty-five years after the end of apartheid, the political centre in South Africa has just about held. But the initial results suggest that it is fragile. Parties on the far left and right have picked up voters, while millions more disillusioned South Africans stayed at home. It is Mr Ramaphosa’s task to restore their faith in democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 01:06:34 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The threat of war between America and Iran, the shrinking Mexican-American population and hot French baby names]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/09/the-threat-of-war-between-america-and-iran-the-shrinking-mexican-american-population-and-hot-french-baby-names]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-09T16:30:55Z&quot;&gt;May 9th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THIS WEEK, our cover story reports on the brewing conflict between &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/11/the-brewing-conflict-between-america-and-iran&quot;&gt;America and Iran&lt;/a&gt;. Also, why the Mexican-American population is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/11/the-mexican-american-population-is-shrinking&quot;&gt;shrinking&lt;/a&gt; (10:05). And, what the latest trends in baby names say about how France is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/11/what-french-baby-names-say-about-the-country&quot;&gt;changing&lt;/a&gt; (17:34)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-may9th2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:07:55 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A court says Ohio’s congressional map is unconstitutional]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/09/a-court-says-ohios-congressional-map-is-unconstitutional]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_USP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-09T15:06:12Z&quot;&gt;May 9th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A BOOK-LENGTH &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.brennancenter.org/sites/default/files/legal-work/2019-05-03-262-Opinion%20and%20Order.pdf&quot;&gt;opinion&lt;/a&gt; striking down Ohio’s congressional map by a panel of three federal judges on May 3rd was written with one particular readership in mind—the justices of the Supreme Court. They have the last word on whether the constitution imposes limits on partisan line-drawing. The federal judges, appointees of George W. Bush, Bill Clinton and Barack Obama, explained how Ohio’s map was rigged to ensure that 12 of the state’s 16 seats in the House of Representatives would go to Republicans despite voters’ fairly even red-blue divide. The ruling concludes that “a predominant partisan intent infected the whole map” in violation of the federal constitution, and orders the state to introduce a remedial map by June 14th. (If the deadline passes without an acceptable map, the court will have one drawn up.) But with an appeal on its way to the Supreme Court—and similar cases pending there involving gerrymanders in Maryland and North Carolina—the staying power of the ruling against Ohio’s map is in the hands of the nine justices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 301-page ruling opens with a detailed account of how Ohio’s “remarkably pro-Republican redistricting bill” was crafted and adopted without Democratic input after the 2010 census. Republican legislators gathered in a DoubleTree hotel room stripped of its usual furnishings and, using three computers, ran “Maptitude”, software that allows cartographers to draw lines “down to the census block unit” and see “corresponding demographic and historical election data for the newly drawn districts in real time”. By the time the draughtsmen unveiled the maps to the legislature, the district lines had been tweaked and polished with the help of Republican consultants masterminding similar efforts in other states. Governor John Kasich signed House Bill 369 into law on September 26th 2011. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Relying on testimony from lawmakers, legislative staffers and political scientists, and based on their own examination of the district lines, the judges analysed Ohio’s congressional map by asking three questions. Did Republicans intend to stymie Democrats in the House elections? Did they succeed? And are there reasons other than pursuing a partisan advantage that could explain the contours of the districts? The answers were yes, yes and no. Republicans gerrymandered on purpose, with stunning success, and no evidence suggests the maps served any function other than to guarantee a 3-to-1 advantage for the Republican Party. “[I]nvidious partisan intent”, and nothing else, marked the map-drawing process.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ruling in &lt;em&gt;Ohio A. Philip Randolph Institute v Householder&lt;/em&gt; explains why the plaintiffs have the legal right to sue in court, the issue on which a challenge to a Wisconsin gerrymander &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2018/06/19/the-supreme-court-dodges-big-decisions-on-partisan-redistricting&quot;&gt;foundered&lt;/a&gt; at the Supreme Court last year. It walks through each relevant district, pointing out oddities and laying out how the Democratic plaintiffs were harmed by being “packed” together or by having their influence “cracked” into multiple Republican strongholds. It discusses several metrics political scientists use to measure the extent of cartographical partisanship. And it argues that Ohio’s map dilutes Democrats’ votes in violation of the First and Fourteenth Amendments as well as the Election Clause of Article I. But the heart of the opinion—the passage where the three judges are all but beseeching the nine justices to jump on the anti-gerrymandering bandwagon—is a 10-page section entitled “Pragmatic and Historical Considerations”. Here, the three judges speak clearly and directly to the men and women who will be reviewing their ruling and the companion gerrymandering cases from Maryland and North Carolina.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each of the four points in this section seeks to allay justices’ worries about “justiciability”—the ability of courts to subdue partisan map-makers. First the judges sought to address Chief Justice John Roberts’s concern in the 2017 &lt;em&gt;Gill v Whitford&lt;/em&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/oral_arguments/argument_transcripts/2017/16-1161_bpm1.pdf&quot;&gt;argument&lt;/a&gt; that the court will look like it is siding with one party or another each time it blesses or rejects an electoral map. The impression that the justices are playing favourites will cause, he said, “very serious harm to the status and integrity of the decisions of this court in the eyes of the country”. Not so, the Ohio panel said. Courts are “only fixing &lt;em&gt;the process&lt;/em&gt; by which voters enact political change” when they keep an eye on gerrymandered maps. Scrutinising district lines, Justice Felix Frankfurter wrote in 1946, could be a fraught exercise that brings judges into &amp;quot;the political thicket&amp;quot;; Paul Clement, the lawyer defending the North Carolina gerrymander, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/oral_arguments/argument_transcripts/2018/18-422_5hd5.pdf&quot;&gt;cited that warning&lt;/a&gt; on March 26th. But it is the Supreme Court’s &amp;quot;obligation”, even if &amp;quot;unwelcome&amp;quot;, the Ohio panel wrote, to crack down on politicians seeking to hamstring voters. The justices should not shrink from their duty to “level the playing field” when nefarious actors meddle with the right to vote. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The three-judge panel also refuted Mr Clement’s contention, quoting Justice Sandra Day O’Connor in 1986, that gerrymandering is a “self-limiting enterprise”. That ship has sailed, the court argued. Advances in technology and data-collection (as Justice Elena Kagan wrote last year) “insulat[e] officeholders against all but the most titanic shifts in the political tides”. As for the oft-heard argument that gerrymandering is as old as the republic, the panel noted that the Federalists saw the practice as “a blow at the constitution and a travesty upon the Bill of Rights when it allowed the minority to govern.” That blow is only amplified two centuries later. And the judges threw cold water on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/05/02/are-states-equipped-to-tackle-partisan-gerrymandering-on-their-own&quot;&gt;suggestions&lt;/a&gt; from several justices that gerrymandering can be fixed via state efforts. It would be “absurd”, the judges wrote, to stay out of the thicket and ask plaintiffs to seek redress from “the entity that committed the alleged violation in the first place”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Will the judges who tossed out the Ohio map—together with similar panels striking down gerrymanders in Wisconsin, Maryland, North Carolina and, most recently, Michigan—persuade the Supreme Court to finally take a stand against partisan redistricting? None of the justices seems to enjoy handling a raft of gerrymandering complaints. Justice Breyer lamented in 2016 that racial gerrymandering cases—requiring the justices to wade through “5,000-page records”—just keep coming, year after year. He and other justices are not keen to play map overseer for a new category of skewed-line complaints. But it would seem almost contemptuous for the justices to reject the growing consensus among their lower-court colleagues that gerrymandering claims belong in court and that workable standards exist to adjudicate them. If the Supreme Court gives the green light to contorted line-drawing, attorney Paul Smith said in a 2017 hearing, the coming decade will bring &amp;quot;a festival of gerrymandering the likes of which this country has never seen&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:07:54 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The threat of war between America and Iran, why the Mexican-American population is shrinking and trending French baby names]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/09/the-threat-of-war-between-america-and-iran-why-the-mexican-american-population-is-shrinking-and-trending-french-baby-names]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_4.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-09T16:30:55Z&quot;&gt;May 9th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A selection of three essential articles read aloud from the latest issue of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;. This week, our cover story reports on the brewing conflict between &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/11/the-brewing-conflict-between-america-and-iran&quot;&gt;America and Iran&lt;/a&gt;. Both sides need to step back. Also, why the Mexican-American population is &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/11/the-mexican-american-population-is-shrinking&quot;&gt;shrinking&lt;/a&gt;, despite headlines from the southern border (10:05). And, what the latest trends in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/11/what-french-baby-names-say-about-the-country&quot;&gt;baby names&lt;/a&gt; say about how France is changing (17:34)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-may9th2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2019 00:06:50 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Lyft’s revenues double, losses quintuple—and prospects darken]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/11/lyfts-revenues-double-losses-quintuple-and-prospects-darken]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_wbp501_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-11T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;O&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;N MARCH&lt;/small&gt; 29th Lyft became the first ride-hailing company traded on a stockmarket. The company’s share price jumped by 9% on its debut, valuing it at $22.4bn. By May 7th, the day it reported results for the first quarter as a public company, it was worth $17bn. Some investors thought even that was too generous. Lyft’s share price fell by another 11% the next day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although it posted quarterly revenues of $776m, nearly double the level a year ago, the company also recorded a loss of $1.14bn, more than it lost in all of 2018. Most of that was down to booking stock-based compensation plans for employees, who earned $894m from Lyft’s initial public offering. Lyft’s chief financial officer, Brian Roberts, conceded that 2019 would be its “peak loss year”. It will “move steadily towards profitability” thereafter, he promised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How that might happen is unclear. Lyft is still bleeding cash, even excluding employees’ compensation, as sales and marketing and insurance costs rise. The firm’s adjusted operating loss of $230m showed little improvement on the prior year despite fast top-line growth. And Lyft forecast that sales growth in the second quarter of 2019 would slow down sharply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Everything that is true of Lyft also holds for Uber—only more so. The ride-hailing goliath was due to list its shares on the New York Stock Exchange on May 10th with a market capitalisation several times Lyft’s. Its losses, too, are larger. According to Uber’s own unaudited first-quarter results, it lost another $1bn or so in the first three months of the year. That brings the total since it was founded in 2009 to $9bn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_WBC887.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190511_WBC887.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190511_WBC887.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190511_WBC887.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190511_WBC887.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190511_WBC887.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190511_WBC887.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190511_WBC887.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190511_WBC887.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190511_WBC887.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Both firms have enough cash to continue to burn money for years, but public investors expect a rapid path to profitability. Making it into the black will require either raising prices or reducing the cut of bookings passed on to drivers. The former will be hard; in many markets ride-hailing competes with other cheap modes of transport, such as buses, bicycles and riders’ own cars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latter looks harder still. Drivers on both platforms complain of earnings that barely cover the cost of living. They staged a global strike to coincide with Uber’s &lt;small&gt;IPO&lt;/small&gt;. That is why Lyft and Uber are keen to get rid of drivers altogether. During its earnings call Lyft announced that riders in Phoenix will soon be able to book one of ten robotaxis (all with human safety drivers to begin with). These will be provided by Waymo, the autonomous-car arm of Google’s parent company, Alphabet. In March Uber raised $1bn for its own self-driving venture from investors including Toyota, a Japanese car giant. Both firms’ initiatives have doubtless been designed to signal to Wall Street that there is a way to make red ink turn into gold. Perhaps.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Business&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Public distress&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 21:06:50 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America ratchets up the pressure in its trade war with China]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/09/america-ratchets-up-the-pressure-in-its-trade-war-with-china]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_fnp001_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-09T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 9th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;C&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HINA’S PROPAGANDA&lt;/small&gt; machine grinds slowly. But its output is nothing if not consistent. It took more than 24 hours for state media to report President Donald Trump’s threats, tweeted on May 5th, to ratchet up tariffs on China. By that time Chinese stocks had already plunged, a foretaste of global market ructions. When the response finally came in official editorials, it was a familiar refrain from China’s canon of trade-war statements: “We do not want to fight, but we are not afraid to fight and, given no choice, we will fight.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That sounds bellicose. Yet one lesson from the past year’s dispute with America is that China places more weight on the sentence’s first part, its desire to avoid a full-on fight. At multiple points when the Chinese government could have retaliated against America by targeting its businesses, it has instead tried to win them over.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dodging a fight, though, does not mean giving in. As &lt;em &gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; went to press, officials from both countries were preparing for talks in Washington to see if they could revive a deal which, until Mr Trump’s tweets, had seemed nearly done. The previous evening, America announced its intention to raise tariffs on $200bn of Chinese goods from 10% to 25% from midnight on May 9th. According to Reuters, citing American government sources, China had backtracked on pledges to rewrite laws on everything from competition policy to intellectual property. Chinese advisers counter that it is American negotiators who have become inflexible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This creates two huge uncertainties for the global economy. One dominates discussion. Will there be a deal or will America raise tariffs? The other receives less attention. Is there a point at which China might lash out against America, even at a cost to itself?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is easy to imagine how China could punch back. Given its $380bn trade surplus with America, China is more vulnerable to tariffs. But American businesses, from Apple to General Motors, have big footprints in China. American firms made roughly $200bn more in sales in China in 2015 than Chinese firms did in America, according to Deutsche Bank. The Chinese government could whip up consumer boycotts. It could hold up supplies at customs. It could smother factories with safety inspections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_FNC873.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190511_FNC873.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190511_FNC873.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190511_FNC873.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190511_FNC873.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190511_FNC873.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190511_FNC873.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190511_FNC873.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190511_FNC873.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190511_FNC873.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In its retaliation, China has already used tariffs to hit sensitive targets. It has pushed soyabean farmers in Iowa and Wisconsin, states that will influence whether Mr Trump can win a second term, to the brink of bankruptcy. But it has largely refrained from deploying the dirtier weapons in its arsenal. After briefly delaying American whiskey shipments at the border last year, Jack Daniel’s is flowing again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even more striking are China’s attempts to be emollient. Having long hesitated, it opened the door last year for a range of foreign firms, from carmakers to insurers, to take majority stakes in their Chinese operations. In March it passed a foreign-investment law that, in theory, addresses some big American grievances. It has even undone some tariffs: in December it lifted extra duties that it had imposed on American cars and car parts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China’s decision to opt for a relatively conciliatory strategy can be explained in three ways. Most obvious is its desire to minimise the trade war. If America were to slap 25% tariffs on all imports from China, that could knock two percentage points off Chinese growth over the next 12 months, according to &lt;small&gt;UBS&lt;/small&gt;, a Swiss bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A second factor is China’s play to win back some support in America. Foreign businesses have grown frustrated with China. A more level playing field could change that, especially if China offers evidence of benefits. News on May 8th that JPMorgan Chase, an American bank, might become the first foreign company to own a majority stake in its Chinese mutual-fund business is just the kind of thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The final point is China’s management of domestic opinion. Xi Jinping, the president, is powerful, but he does not want to arm his critics. One government adviser says that left-wing scholars are planning to greet the announcement of any trade deal as a “day of national humiliation”, a reference to the 19th century when foreign powers dominated China. Front-loading reforms offers some insulation: the government can portray the deal as a ratification of what it was already doing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But domestic politicking also sheds light on why the trade talks have hit a rocky patch. China has more incentive to take a harder line at this moment—just when a deal seems to be within reach. Sending Mr Trump into a frenzy on Twitter may worry investors. But to Chinese officials it looks like Mr Xi is driving a tougher bargain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complicating matters, negotiations have been conducted in English, with the draft agreement (reportedly seven chapters and 150 pages) also in English. As it is translated into Chinese and circulated among more officials, changes are inevitable. “You can’t really renege on something that is a non-binding work in progress,” says James Zimmerman, a partner in the Beijing office of Perkins Coie, a law firm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China still wants to avoid a full-fledged trade war. Should America raise tariffs, China’s initial preference will be to continue with limited retaliation, says Wang Yong, director of the Centre for International Political Economy at Peking University. The American economy would, he thinks, suffer enough damage for Mr Trump to change course. If not, China’s fight-back could get much nastier.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Finance and economics&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Speaking softly&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 21:06:49 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thailand’s junta marks the king’s coronation with more election-rigging]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/09/thailands-junta-marks-the-kings-coronation-with-more-election-rigging]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_asp004_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-09T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 9th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HAIS DO NOT&lt;/small&gt; see that much of their king, who spends most of his time in Germany. But for three days starting on May 4th he was on near-constant display for a long and lavish series of ceremonies surrounding his coronation. It all began with a ritual purification at the royal residence in Bangkok. Holy water was poured over the head of Maha Vajiralongkorn, the tenth monarch of the Chakri dynasty. It had been collected from all 76 of the country’s provinces, as well as from around Bangkok. Courtiers and officials wore spotless white uniforms and prostrated themselves before their monarch.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The king changed into an embroidered golden suit for an anointing ceremony. Then he lowered onto his own head a pointed helmet of a crown weighing more than 7kg thanks to its crust of gold and diamonds. A royal procession the next day saw the stony-faced monarch paraded through Bangkok on a gilded palanquin. Accompanying troops roasted in the heat. In a separate procession (pictured), respectful elephants dropped awkwardly to their knees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first substantial moments of the new reign came just days later, when the Election Commission released the final results of an election that took place in March. Palang Pracharat, a party created to support the military junta that came to power in a coup in 2014, battled Pheu Thai, which is loyal to Thaskin Shinawatra, a former prime minister who has feuded with the generals since an earlier coup, in 2006. The junta rigged the system in its favour, banning all political activity until a few months before the election, disbanding a second party linked to Mr Thaksin and awarding itself the power to appoint all 250 members of the upper house. Nonetheless, shortly after the vote, a coalition of seven opposition parties, including Pheu Thai and Future Forward, which is popular with young voters, announced they had won a slim majority in the 500-seat lower house.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is not what the results unveiled this week show. The Election Commission concedes that Pheu Thai won the most seats, 136, followed by Palang Pracharat, with 115, and Future Forward, with 80. It annulled the result in one district won by a Pheu Thai candidate, ordering a fresh election. But the biggest blow to the opposition came in the form of tweaks to the formula whereby the commission allocates the 150 seats awarded on a proportional basis. The result was to reduce the tally of the big parties and hand seats to a plethora of tiny ones. This change appeared to breach the commission’s own rules and the election law, but a court found the new maths constitutionally permissible just hours before the party-list results appeared. Entirely coincidentally, the changes reduced the opposition alliance to a minority of 245 seats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chaos awaits, as 27 different parties now hold seats in the lower house. A weak, pro-military coalition looks the most likely outcome. The junta will soon present a list of senators to the king for approval. The two houses will then vote in a joint sitting to select a prime minister. The incumbent, Prayuth Chan-ocha, who led the coup in 2014, had seemed determined to stay on. Bangkok is rife with rumours, however, that the king might promote the selection of a less divisive figure, perhaps from the Privy Council, which is packed with soldiers and technocrats. Either way, the notion that the government ushered into power by the election will have any democratic legitimacy—always a doubtful proposition—now looks entirely forlorn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As if to underline the point, the authorities have set about persecuting Future Forward and its leader, Thanathorn Juangroongruangkit, with a gusto typically reserved for supporters of Mr Thaksin. The party and its leadership face 16 accusations of wrongdoing. The Election Commission intends to press a charge against Mr Thanathorn for holding shares in a media company, which candidates are not allowed to do. He has also been charged with sedition and computer crimes. He denies all the charges, which could lead to a ban from politics, a prison sentence or the complete dissolution of Future Forward. “I’m prepared. I knew this would happen sooner or later,” he says at his party’s buzzing office in Bangkok. “In order to retain power they are willing to do whatever it takes.” He believes the 16 cases are intended to pressure him to negotiate with the junta’s political allies. At least five of Future Forward’s &lt;small&gt;MP&lt;/small&gt;s have been offered $1m apiece to change party, he claims.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Thanathorn is a threat because he is both popular and unblemished by scandal, two characteristics which neither the king nor the generals (nor Mr Thaksin) enjoy. The king has alienated his subjects not only by his absence, but also by his personal cruelty and insistence on sycophantic protocol. It was not just the elephants and courtiers who were forced to prostrate themselves: days before the coronation the palace released images of the king getting married for the fourth time, in which his new wife, a former stewardess, grovelled before the unsmiling groom. He has disowned children and locked up relatives of one of her predecessors. Only a small share of Thais bothered to wear yellow, the royal colour, as requested during the coronation ceremonies. Thousands of civil servants had to be bussed in to swell the attendant crowds, which were much sparser than at the cremation of his father, who was far more popular.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet King Vajiralongkorn apparently feels secure enough to meddle in political matters. Before the election he intervened, quite hypocritically, to prevent his older sister from getting involved in politics. The courts and the Election Commission followed his instructions slavishly, even though they lacked any clear legal underpinning. Just before polling day he told Thais to vote for “good people”; just after it he stripped Mr Thaksin of several military awards. The risk of royal displeasure seems to have deterred neutral parties from joining the opposition coalition in the lower house. That is no coincidence: a weak coalition would be in no position to stand up to the king. That an election that was supposed to restore Thailand to democracy will instead bolster its preening monarch is a crowning irony.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Asia&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Crown and spectre&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 21:06:47 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Iran’s president does not want to walk away from the nuclear deal]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/11/irans-president-does-not-want-to-walk-away-from-the-nuclear-deal]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_map006.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-11T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;WO YEARS&lt;/small&gt; ago the chairman of Iran’s national airline was eager to travel the world and spend a few billion dollars. In December 2016 Farhad Parvaresh shook hands with a Boeing executive to buy 80 passenger jets. A month later he was in Toulouse, France, to take delivery of a new jet, one of 100 ordered from Airbus. Both contracts were vivid symbols of how the world’s economy was opening up to Iran after the conclusion of a deal in 2015 that eased sanctions in exchange for limits on its nuclear programme.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Times have changed since America’s president, Donald Trump, withdrew from the nuclear agreement a year ago. The reimposition of American sanctions halted both aeroplane contracts and scared away other potential trading partners. The Iranian economy is now isolated. President Hassan Rouhani, in turn, says Iran will stop abiding by parts of the pact.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was not what Mr Rouhani wanted. When America withdrew he said that Iran would still fulfil its commitments under the nuclear deal. The International Atomic Energy Agency confirms that it has. But domestic politics has made his position untenable. As Mr Trump has increased pressure on Iran, he has unwittingly emboldened its hardliners to squeeze Mr Rouhani, one of the architects of the deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Rouhani had hoped that the European Union would blunt the pain of American sanctions by compelling companies and banks to keep doing business with Iran. But European efforts to work around the sanctions and facilitate trade have not been effective. European countries have not taken action against big firms such as Total and Airbus that have backed out of their Iranian contracts. “They don’t want a full-fledged trade war with the &lt;small&gt;US&lt;/small&gt; over Iran because the benefits are too marginal,” says Suzanne Maloney of the Brookings Institution, a think-tank in Washington.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cut off from the global economy, Iran’s economy is plunging. Before Mr Trump was elected one dollar bought 35,000 rial. Today’s black-market rates are upwards of 150,000. Oil sales are hard to track because Iran hides shipments through middlemen and “ghost tankers” with transponders switched off. But analysts think they have fallen to about 1m barrels a day, less than half of their level before sanctions. They will drop more in coming months with the expiry of temporary waivers from sanctions that America granted to the biggest buyers of Iranian oil. New sanctions announced on May 8th target iron, steel, aluminium and copper production, which America says is Iran’s “largest non-petroleum-related source of export revenue”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Suffering Iranians have understandably soured on the nuclear deal and the president who promoted it. A poll in December found that support for the agreement had fallen to 52% from 76% in 2015. Mr Rouhani’s conservative rivals, long suspicious of his attempts to repair relations with America, feel vindicated. Mr Trump’s recent decision to brand the Revolutionary Guard Corps a terrorist organisation gave them another boost; even reformists rallied around them. The ayatollahs who wield power in Tehran have fallen out with those who study in Qom. But Iran is still a clerical regime and the mullahs are in ever-tighter lockstep with the Guards, who also control a big chunk of the economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iran’s parliament has spent months debating legislation meant to remove Iran from a blacklist maintained by the Financial Action Task Force, a global body that sets anti-money-laundering standards. Mr Rouhani risked much political capital to advance these bills, one of which was even opposed by the supreme leader. That effort now looks dead. Hossein Shariatmadari, the curmudgeonly editor of &lt;em &gt;Kayhan&lt;/em&gt;, a state-run daily, calls the bills a sign of “weakness” in the face of American sanctions on the Guards.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Rouhani has tried to buy himself time—and to press Europe into offering economic relief—by setting a deadline of 60 days before breaching the nuclear deal further. Hardliners are praising his “first decisive step”. But his ultimatum does not change the underlying political and economic realities. America wants to batter Iran. Europe cannot stop it. Nor does his move change the calendar: even if a future American president were willing to lift sanctions, Mr Trump still has 20 months left in his first term. That is a long time for a weakened Mr Rouhani to endure. In order to fend off hardline critics he is, by undermining the deal, adopting their policies. Even a tactical win for the president is ultimately a victory for his rivals.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Middle East and Africa&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Rouhani’s remorse&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 20:07:37 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>