<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Cathedrals are neglected in much of Europe]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/04/16/cathedrals-are-neglected-in-much-of-europe]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BLP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-16T14:06:05Z&quot;&gt;Apr 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE CATHEDRAL of Notre Dame in Paris, and the vast outpouring of sorrow over its semi-destruction by fire on April 15th, epitomises the power of great houses of prayer to touch and inspire people. More palpably than any other kind of monument, they connect visitors with another world: one in which the finest composers, singers, sculptors, glass-makers, embroiderers and craft-workers of a given era joyfully mixed their energies in a vast, disinterested enterprise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To some degree, that enterprise continues as long as the building stands. That alone makes great historic churches a source of fascination, even for those with little interest in Christian worship. People want them to be there, even if they don’t wish to share the cost or join the prayers.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In almost every country in Europe, that creates an acute problem. The cost of maintaining the delicate stone fabric of a cathedral seems to rise geometrically, far out-stripping the ability of small congregations to sustain them. Governments and other secular bodies are minded to help but they also feel compelled, in most places, to respect the independence of the buildings’ historic stewards, in other words the churches.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In England, the established church boasts 42 cathedrals (technically defined as the seat of a bishop), of which 39 are listed as historic buildings whose preservation is both mandated by law and entitled to some public help. (About 12,000 of the 16,000 other places of worship controlled by the Church of England are also listed.) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Church of England likes to call the cathedrals one of its “success stories” with rising numbers of worshippers and visitors, and growing revenue. But as a recent report led by a bishop delicately put it, “recent failures of governance and management within a small number of cathedrals have highlighted vulnerabilities across the sector…” In plain language, at least two cathedrals have run into severe financial difficulties, which better stewardship might have avoided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;English cathedrals are relatively independent bodies, run by a cleric known as a dean who relies on a group of advisers known as a chapter. They are free to raise money in many ways, from concerts to exhibitions to simply charging an admission fee, as about a quarter of them do. In recent weeks Derby Cathedral raised eyebrows by hosting films that included graphic sex scenes and depictions of paganism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Churches in Germany have an advantage. The system of religious taxes (under which people of Catholic or Lutheran heritage pay a levy to their respective denominations) has ensured an ample income stream. Germany’s religious masters have done better at hauling in revenue than at retaining worshippers, the figures would suggest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But a massive fund-raising effort, drawing in generous private-sector donors and ordinary well-wishers in Germany and Britain, was needed for one of the biggest church reconstruction projects of modern times: the rebuilding of the Frauenkirche in Dresden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This showpiece of German Baroque was destroyed, along with much of the city, in a British bombing raid in February 1945. The project, completed in 2005, was a complement to the erection in 1962 of a new cathedral in Coventry, replacing the one wrecked by a German air raid on the English Midlands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most European states subsidise their historically dominant Christian denominations, directly or indirectly, while also leaving the sects’ religious masters relatively autonomous. In Italy, despite the notional separation of Catholic church and state, the two are deeply intertwined, through tax breaks and state help for maintaining the artistic heritage which is one of Italy’s greatest tourist draws. Belgium offers generous help to all its main religions, but Catholic cathedrals still charge stiff admission fees as though they were museums.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In church-state relations, France is an outlier. Under the regime of laïcité, or strict secularism, municipalities took over formal responsibility for Catholic churches; clerics and their congregations are merely users. And clerics, in particular, are thin on the ground. In rural France, it is common for a priest to look after 30 old churches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That paucity of active users prompts municipal authorities to assign a low priority to conserving church buildings. In 2013 a huge neo-Gothic church in the northern French town of Abbeville was dramatically demolished by municipal leaders, who said the place was a safety hazard and too expensive to repair. Hundreds of other French churches may soon have a similar fate. Nor have France’s state authorities done very well at protecting houses of prayer from a wave of vandalism, including arson and desecration, that has afflicted them this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, all over western Europe, churches are closing for lack of worshippers. In the Netherlands, a cardinal predicted in 2013 that two-thirds of the Roman Catholic churches in the country would shut by 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But a diametrically opposing trend is at work further east in Europe. Perhaps the most spectacular act of church reconstruction of recent times was the re-erection of Moscow’s Cathedral of Christ the Saviour, which was dynamited by Stalin in 1931 and thrown back up over five years starting in 1995. It was rebuilt in about a tenth of the time needed for the original construction.&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere in Russia, under a crash building programme decreed by the Russian Orthodox church, at least three new churches are said to be opening per day. And in other parts of central and eastern Europe, from Serbia to Georgia, vast new Orthodox churches now adorn capital cities which were already endowed with many places of prayer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, the Russian church building spree extends far beyond the borders of the motherland. Anyone who takes a short walk along the banks of the Seine from the wreckage of Notre Dame will soon see a boldly modernistic structure, topped with onion domes: this “spiritual and cultural” centre, opened in 2016, was a pet project of President Vladimir Putin’s. It competes hard with an older Russian-style cathedral in Paris which the Muscovite authorities, to their frustration, do not control. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the Russian state media were eager to point out, western Europe is gaining some new Christian places of worship even as many others are destroyed, accidentally or otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;See also&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/15/a-terrible-blaze-devastates-notre-dame-cathedral&quot;&gt;A terrible blaze devastates Notre Dame cathedral (April 15th 2019)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:06:53 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tiger Woods made our golf model look silly. Have we learned a lesson?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/04/16/tiger-woods-made-our-golf-model-look-silly-have-we-learned-a-lesson]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BLP501_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-16T13:28:25Z&quot;&gt;Apr 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR EVERY single week between August 2013 and September 2018, betting on Tiger Woods was a losing proposition. Owing to a series of injuries and over-use of pain-killing prescription drugs, golf’s biggest star went five years without winning a single tournament. So in hindsight, it looks like remarkably poor timing that the &lt;i&gt;The Economist&lt;/i&gt; ran an article pouring cold water on Mr Woods’s chances of winning the Masters Tournament in precisely the week that he wound up &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/04/14/tiger-woods-wins-his-fifth-masters-in-a-comeback-for-the-ages&quot;&gt;ending his 11-year-long drought&lt;/a&gt; in major championships. “Our Masters forecast is lukewarm on Tiger Woods”, read the headline on the online version of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/06/our-masters-forecast-is-lukewarm-on-tiger-woods&quot;&gt;story&lt;/a&gt;, which ended by declaring it “more likely than not that he has let loose his last roar”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before the tournament began, betting markets gave Mr Woods a 5% chance to win. That was more than twice the 2.2% estimate produced by EAGLE, our statistical golf prediction model. Did punters know something that the computer did not?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EAGLE may well have under-estimated the probability that the man who once played the game better than anyone else in history would re-capture his mojo. However, close scrutiny of Mr Woods’s showing at the Masters suggests that rather than channelling vintage Tiger, he delivered a merely excellent tournament, not one for the ages. His performance was easily within the capacity of any top-ten golfer, and one that in general is not sufficient to win a major.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, Mr Woods’s four days in Georgia were not even his &lt;i&gt;own&lt;/i&gt; best work at a major since he returned to action. Last year at the PGA Championship, Mr Woods played well enough to win, but was stymied by a competitor who was just a bit better. This time, in contrast, he put in nearly as good an effort, while all of the other contenders in a wide-open field made costly errors at crucial moments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The prodigal son returns&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt; Although EAGLE was far less bullish on Mr Woods than bettors were, the model was actually rather impressed by his comeback. After adjusting for course conditions and difficulty, Mr Woods’s average scores since he returned from injury in December 2017 were the tenth-best in the world during that period. EAGLE ranked him as the ninth-best golfer in this year’s Masters field, with an expected score of 0.36 strokes above par per round under standard conditions for a major tournament.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_WOC555_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190420_WOC555_0.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190420_WOC555_0.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190420_WOC555_0.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190420_WOC555_0.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190420_WOC555_0.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190420_WOC555_0.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190420_WOC555_0.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190420_WOC555_0.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190420_WOC555_0.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is so much round-to-round variability intrinsic to golf that over a mere 72 holes, the best player in the world at the start of a major tournament rarely emerges victorious. EAGLE regarded Dustin Johnson as the leader of the Masters pack by a comfortable margin, but still gave him just an 8% chance to win. (At the tail end of his peak, Mr Woods towered so far above the competition that he reached seemingly unthinkable victory odds around 25%. No one has approached that level since.) Instead, the champion usually emerges from the cluster of players ranked between fifth and 30th—though determining exactly which one of them fortune will smile upon is a fool’s errand. By EAGLE’s estimate, the current version of Mr Woods plays at almost exactly the average skill level of major winners. Then again, so do competitors like Paul Casey and Sergio García, who both wound up buried at the bottom of the Masters leaderboard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rather than unfounded scepticism about Mr Woods’s ability, EAGLE’s estimate of his chances fell short of those of betting markets for two reasons. The first is that in the model’s calculation, punters tend to over-value &lt;i&gt;all&lt;/i&gt; elite or well-known players, while under-estimating those of long-shots. The ranks of major champions include almost all of the greats, but also out-of-nowhere upstarts. In 2009 the unheralded &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Yang_Yong-eun&quot;&gt;Y.E. Yang&lt;/a&gt; rallied from a seven-stroke deficit to beat Mr Woods at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2009_PGA_Championship&quot;&gt;2009 PGA Championship&lt;/a&gt;, which by EAGLE’s estimate was the most improbable major victory of the 21st century. Two years later, Darren Clarke was ranked 111th in the world when he won his first and only major at the Open Championship in England at the age of 42.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Individually, each low-ranked competitor has only a slim chance of victory. Collectively, however, their probability tends to be greater—and thus, the chances of the favourites are lower—than the prices on peer-to-peer betting exchanges suggest. Based on EAGLE’s calculations, the most profitable bet ahead of the Masters was to wager on a stumble by Rory McIlroy, who was heavily favoured in betting markets to win the tournament. Mr McIlroy wound up finishing 21st, offering a healthy pay-out to doubters—including your correspondent—who took odds of 2.5-to-one (a 29% probability) or better that he would fail to make the top 20. EAGLE reckoned his chances of such a disappointing result were just under 50%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The second explanation for EAGLE’s relative pessimism is that unlike bettors, the model treats all players with similar scores over the past few years similarly—regardless of whether or not they happen to be named Tiger Woods. Punters priced Mr Woods as the third or fourth most likely player to win the tournament, a conclusion impossible to justify based solely on his record since 2017. The only way to arrive at such a lofty valuation was to bake in a significant probability that he would recover the form he last displayed nearly a decade ago. As prescient as that looks in hindsight, could it really have been justified in advance?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EAGLE takes a straightforward approach to weighting historical scores: every day, each round result in its database loses about 0.25% of its impact. Scores from a week ago are counted about 98% as much as ones from today; those a month old are worth 93%; those a full year in the past get 41%; and those two years back are assigned 16%. On one hand, this “decay rate”, optimised to produce the most accurate forecasts over the model’s entire dataset of over 1m rounds, looks surprisingly gentle. Few analysts pay attention to scores from even six months ago, not to mention those from two years in the past. But given the length of Mr Woods’s decline phase and absences from the game, the weight EAGLE puts on scores from the last time he won a tournament in 2013 rounds to zero.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For most golfers, ignoring results over six years old would be sensible. But Mr Woods, as always, is a special case. He was ailing during many of the rounds he did play in the intervening years, making those results poor predictors of how he might perform when healthy. Moreover, he might have needed to re-discover his touch during the first months of his comeback. In theory, a well-designed model would need to give him credit for his proven potential, while discounting the importance of scores recorded before he settled into form.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In practice, however, the particulars of Mr Woods’s journey mitigate many of these concerns. Because he barely played in the two years to November 2017, EAGLE’s time-decay function already caused it to disregard the poor scores Mr Woods recorded before his time off. And rather than gaining ground incrementally once he came back en route to his climactic Masters triumph, the rejuvenated star emerged fully formed, like Athena springing from the head of Zeus, from the moment he resumed play. In the first six tournaments he played upon his return, he finished second, fifth, ninth, 12th and 23rd, with only one missed cut—a run that would make a golfer half his age proud. During the following year, he maintained that level of performance—one consistent with a top-ten player, rather than a top-five one—but did not improve upon it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fans of Mr Woods will surely insist that this approach sells their hero short. So as a check on EAGLE’s method, consider a thought experiment. Suppose that back in 2009, when Mr Woods announced he would take a break from golf to repair his broken personal life, that hiatus had lasted for a decade rather than for just a few months. How might we have predicted him to perform in 2019, knowing nothing but how he had played at his peak?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ageing curves are far gentler in golf than in most other sports—no one blinks an eye when a 40-something golfer wins a tournament. But that does not mean that time exacts no toll at all. On the contrary, golfers generally play significantly better in their 30s than in their 40s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since records for the Official World Golf Rankings (OWGR) began in 1986, there have been 16 players other than Mr Woods who were in the top ten just before turning 34—Mr Woods’s age when the scandal broke—and were still active at Mr Woods’s current age of 43 years and three and a half months. Just two of them, Phil Mickelson and Greg Norman, were still in the top ten nine years later, and only three more (Colin Montgomerie, Ernie Els and Jim Furyk) managed to stay in the top 25.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_WOC801.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190420_WOC801.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190420_WOC801.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190420_WOC801.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190420_WOC801.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190420_WOC801.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190420_WOC801.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190420_WOC801.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190420_WOC801.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190420_WOC801.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall, after translating their world rankings into expected scores to par under typical conditions, the average member of this group lost 1.47 strokes per round between the ages of 34 and 43. And just before his infidelity scandal became public, Mr Woods was playing at a level of some 1.19 strokes below par per round. If you add on 1.47 strokes per round for nine years of ageing, you get an estimate of 0.28 strokes above par per 18 holes today—just a hair better than the rate of 0.36 EAGLE derived from Mr Woods’s scoring record during the past 16 months. In other words, Mr Woods’s ability has declined at almost exactly the same rate as that of comparable players from previous eras, albeit from a much higher starting point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Raining on Tiger’s parade&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt; No matter how you slice it, Mr Woods looked like a strong but not top-tier contender when the tournament began. But when the facts change, nimble forecasters change their minds. Now that Mr Woods has donned the Masters victor’s green jacket, surely we can proclaim him “back” and resume debate over how long Jack Nicklaus’s record of 18 major championships is likely to stand—right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not so fast. A useful concept in sports forecasting, devised by Bill James, a baseball statistician, is “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.economist.com/game-theory/2015/04/19/one-swing-is-all-you-need&quot;&gt;signature significance&lt;/a&gt;”—the notion that some achievements are so remarkable that only the elites can accomplish them, even in very small samples of data. A good example in golf would be beating the average score in a major over four rounds by more than 20 strokes. Since 1960, the two best players in history (Mr Woods and Mr Nicklaus) have each done so twice. Mr Woods broke the mark at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2000_U.S._Open_(golf)&quot;&gt;2000 US Open&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1997_Masters_Tournament&quot;&gt;1997 Masters&lt;/a&gt;, while Mr Nicklaus did at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1965_Masters_Tournament&quot;&gt;1965 Masters&lt;/a&gt; and the 1977 Open Championship in Scotland—the notorious “&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/1977_Open_Championship&quot;&gt;Duel in the Sun&lt;/a&gt;” that he somehow managed to lose. The only other golfers to surpass this threshold are the all-time greats Tom Watson (who beat Mr Nicklaus that day), Raymond Floyd, Arnold Palmer and Phil Mickelson—and one merely good player, Henrik Stenson, who had a great tournament when &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.economist.com/game-theory/2016/07/19/phil-mickelson-is-golfs-best-loser-ever&quot;&gt;thwarting Mr Mickelson at the 2016 Open Championship&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_WOC802.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190420_WOC802.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190420_WOC802.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190420_WOC802.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190420_WOC802.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190420_WOC802.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190420_WOC802.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190420_WOC802.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190420_WOC802.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190420_WOC802.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Mr Woods had come anywhere close to exceeding the field average by 20 strokes, EAGLE would have immediately elevated him to the very top tier of its rankings. In fact, his score was quite pedestrian by the standards of major winners. All major victories may count the same, but not all of them are equally impressive. Sometimes, the champion dominates wire to wire, as Mr Woods did at the 2000 US Open, which he won by an astonishing margin of 15 strokes. But, just as often, a golfer sneaks to victory with a solid performance when his closest competitors stumble.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All keen golf fans remember Mr Watson’s run at the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/2009_Open_Championship&quot;&gt;2009 Open Championship&lt;/a&gt;, when, at the age of 59, he led by a stroke with one hole to play, before bogeying and losing in a playoff to Stewart Cink. But the reason why the all-but-geriatric Mr Watson came that close to winning was that no one managed to beat the field average by even eight strokes. In the vast majority of tournaments, Mr Cink’s scorecard would not have come anywhere close to victory. But he had the good fortune to play somewhat better than average over four days when everyone else was off their game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Woods’s recent Masters victory was not quite as underwhelming as Mr Cink’s, but it was not far off. Although his finishing score of 275 looks impressive, the average score among golfers making the cut was a three-under-par 285. Unsurprisingly, there were lots of strong players right on Mr Woods’s heels, all of whom had numerous opportunities to tie with or beat him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It would be hard to argue that Mr Woods’s scorecard at the 2019 Masters was more impressive than Mr Nicklaus’s losing effort at the Duel in the Sun, or Mr Mickelson’s runner-up showing to Mr Stenson in 2016. One way to quantify these differences is to take a player’s score above average, and then adjust it for tournament conditions and rules that cause scores either to spread out widely or to bunch closely together. (In general, the range of scores has grown more compressed over time, with the introduction of cut rules accelerating this trend. And events in which more players make the cut enable more mediocre golfers to post finishing scores, increasing the gap between the victor’s score and the field average.) This modified score above average can then be converted into a probability of winning a tournament. In general, players who beat the field average by 18 adjusted strokes go on to win about 95% of the time, those who exceed it by 13.5 strokes have a 50/50 chance, and ones who only surpass it by nine strokes are just under 5% to win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_WOC803.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190420_WOC803.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190420_WOC803.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190420_WOC803.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190420_WOC803.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190420_WOC803.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190420_WOC803.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190420_WOC803.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190420_WOC803.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190420_WOC803.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;By this measure, Mr Woods’s career tally of major titles has generally hewed fairly closely to the probabilities suggested by his scorecards. He won all eight times his probability was 80% or higher, four of the six times it was between 50% and 80%, and two of the eight times it was between 10% and 50%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His showing at the 2019 Masters, however, is an extreme outlier. In general, players who amass his total of ten adjusted strokes better than the field average go on to win just 8.2% of the time. Mr Woods, of course, had to play well to put himself in contention. But on the final day, he also needed Francesco Molinari to deposit balls in the water on the 12th and 15th holes, Brooks Koepka to send a tee shot into Rae’s Creek on the 12th hole and miss a makeable birdie putt on the 18th, and Mr Johnson to see his furious charge on the back nine fall millimetres short of a final birdie on the 18th. The chances of all those misfortunes coming to pass at once were fairly low. As Mr Woods and Mr Molinari headed to the 12th hole on Sunday, EAGLE gave Mr Woods a 16% chance of emerging with the green jacket.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_WOC804.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190420_WOC804.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190420_WOC804.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190420_WOC804.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190420_WOC804.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190420_WOC804.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190420_WOC804.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190420_WOC804.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190420_WOC804.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190420_WOC804.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;None of this is intended to take away from Mr Woods’s stirring victory—or even to suggest that he has benefited from exceptionally good luck on the whole during his comeback. Before his triumph at Augusta, he had come up just short at the previous two majors: the Open Championship and PGA Championship of 2018. At the former, where he was also paired with Mr Molinari on the final day, Mr Woods briefly secured the lead all to himself before miscues undid him on the back nine—just as they would do to his rivals at this year’s Masters. Mr Molinari emerged as the victor. In the latter tournament, it was Mr Woods who mounted a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.economist.com/game-theory/2018/08/14/despite-woodss-charge-the-pga-was-brooks-koepkas-to-lose&quot;&gt;late push on the last day&lt;/a&gt;, similar to Mr Johnson’s this past weekend. He fell just short, when Mr Koepka proved himself immune to the type of mistakes he would go on to commit eight months later at Augusta. Although Mr Woods ended up as the bridesmaid at the PGA Championship and the bride at the Masters, his scorecard at the earlier tournament actually gave him a slightly better chance to win. His score of 266 was 10.66 adjusted strokes above the field average, and gave him a 12.5% chance of victory.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;The second act goes on&lt;/b&gt;&lt;br/&gt; So where does that leave Mr Woods—and Mr Nicklaus’s record—going forward? If the last three majors are any guide, his most comparable players would be the other two champions in those events, both of whom Mr Woods has been in neck-and-neck races with on the final day: Mr Koepka and Mr Molinari. Mr Koepka has ascended to third in the OWGR, while Mr Molinari is seventh, one spot behind Mr Woods. All of those ranks are roughly consistent with a slight improvement on EAGLE’s take on Mr Woods before the Masters began: a top-ten player, but one below the top tier of Mr Johnson, Mr McIlroy and perhaps Justin Rose. That corresponds to a 2-4% chance of winning any given major, a 9% chance of winning another one this year, and a 50/50 chance of winning at least one more by the end of 2024—before accounting for the performance deterioration and greater risk of injury that ageing will inflict. In other words, Mr Nicklaus should probably rest easy. In all likelihood, Mr Woods was absent or injured for too many prime years to make a run at the all-time record.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may look like consummate stubbornness for us to continue preaching caution on Mr Woods’s future, just two days after he made a mockery of such counsel. But accurate forecasting methods require a sound process and validation over long time periods, not over-reaction to short-run fluctuations. Unsurprisingly, bettors already exuberant about Mr Woods have bid him up further following his Masters victory: he, Mr Johnson and Mr McIlroy are all trading as co-favourites to win the PGA Championship next month. If that continues, we will probably bet against him—and look forward to suffering the financial and reputational consequences when the Greatest Of All Time™ makes EAGLE look silly once again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(此域名已被污染，谢谢大家一直以来的支持)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2019 00:06:52 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cathedrals are neglected in much of Europe]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/04/16/cathedrals-are-at-risk-of-crumbling-in-most-parts-of-europe-but-there-are-exceptions]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BLP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-16T14:06:05Z&quot;&gt;Apr 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE CATHEDRAL of Notre Dame in Paris, and the vast outpouring of sorrow over its semi-destruction by fire on April 15th, epitomises the power of great houses of prayer to touch and inspire people. More palpably than any other kind of monument, they connect visitors with another world: one in which the finest composers, singers, sculptors, glass-makers, embroiderers and craft-workers of a given era joyfully mixed their energies in a vast, disinterested enterprise. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To some degree, that enterprise continues as long as the building stands. That alone makes great historic churches a source of fascination, even for those with little interest in Christian worship. People want them to be there, even if they don’t wish to share the cost or join the prayers.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In almost every country in Europe, that creates an acute problem. The cost of maintaining the delicate stone fabric of a cathedral seems to rise geometrically, far out-stripping the ability of small congregations to sustain them. Governments and other secular bodies are minded to help but they also feel compelled, in most places, to respect the independence of the buildings’ historic stewards, in other words the churches.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In England, the established church boasts 42 cathedrals (technically defined as the seat of a bishop), of which 39 are listed as historic buildings whose preservation is both mandated by law and entitled to some public help. (About 12,000 of the 16,000 other places of worship controlled by the Church of England are also listed.) &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Church of England likes to call the cathedrals one of its “success stories” with rising numbers of worshippers and visitors, and growing revenue. But as a recent report led by a bishop delicately put it, “recent failures of governance and management within a small number of cathedrals have highlighted vulnerabilities across the sector…” In plain language, at least two cathedrals have run into severe financial difficulties, which better stewardship might have avoided.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;English cathedrals are relatively independent bodies, run by a cleric known as a dean who relies on a group of advisers known as a chapter. They are free to raise money in many ways, from concerts to exhibitions to simply charging an admission fee, as about a quarter of them do. In recent weeks Derby Cathedral raised eyebrows by hosting films that included graphic sex scenes and depictions of paganism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Churches in Germany have an advantage. The system of religious taxes (under which people of Catholic or Lutheran heritage pay a levy to their respective denominations) has ensured an ample income stream. Germany’s religious masters have done better at hauling in revenue than at retaining worshippers, the figures would suggest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But a massive fund-raising effort, drawing in generous private-sector donors and ordinary well-wishers in Germany and Britain, was needed for one of the biggest church reconstruction projects of modern times: the rebuilding of the Frauenkirche in Dresden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This showpiece of German Baroque was destroyed, along with much of the city, in a British bombing raid in February 1945. The project, completed in 2005, was a complement to the erection in 1962 of a new cathedral in Coventry, replacing the one wrecked by a German air raid on the English Midlands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most European states subsidise their historically dominant Christian denominations, directly or indirectly, while also leaving the sects’ religious masters relatively autonomous. In Italy, despite the notional separation of Catholic church and state, the two are deeply intertwined, through tax breaks and state help for maintaining the artistic heritage which is one of Italy’s greatest tourist draws. Belgium offers generous help to all its main religions, but Catholic cathedrals still charge stiff admission fees as though they were museums.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In church-state relations, France is an outlier. Under the regime of laïcité, or strict secularism, municipalities took over formal responsibility for Catholic churches; clerics and their congregations are merely users. And clerics, in particular, are thin on the ground. In rural France, it is common for a priest to look after 30 old churches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That paucity of active users prompts municipal authorities to assign a low priority to conserving church buildings. In 2013 a huge neo-Gothic church in the northern French town of Abbeville was dramatically demolished by municipal leaders, who said the place was a safety hazard and too expensive to repair. Hundreds of other French churches may soon have a similar fate. Nor have France’s state authorities done very well at protecting houses of prayer from a wave of vandalism, including arson and desecration, that has afflicted them this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, all over western Europe, churches are closing for lack of worshippers. In the Netherlands, a cardinal predicted in 2013 that two-thirds of the Roman Catholic churches in the country would shut by 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But a diametrically opposing trend is at work further east in Europe. Perhaps the most spectacular act of church reconstruction of recent times was the re-erection of Moscow’s Cathedral of Christ the Saviour, which was dynamited by Stalin in 1931 and thrown back up over five years starting in 1995. It was rebuilt in about a tenth of the time needed for the original construction.&lt;span &gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere in Russia, under a crash building programme decreed by the Russian Orthodox church, at least three new churches are said to be opening per day. And in other parts of central and eastern Europe, from Serbia to Georgia, vast new Orthodox churches now adorn capital cities which were already endowed with many places of prayer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Indeed, the Russian church building spree extends far beyond the borders of the motherland. Anyone who takes a short walk along the banks of the Seine from the wreckage of Notre Dame will soon see a boldly modernistic structure, topped with onion domes: this “spiritual and cultural” centre, opened in 2016, was a pet project of President Vladimir Putin’s. It competes hard with an older Russian-style cathedral in Paris which the Muscovite authorities, to their frustration, do not control. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the Russian state media were eager to point out, western Europe is gaining some new Christian places of worship even as many others are destroyed, accidentally or otherwise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;See also&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/15/a-terrible-blaze-devastates-notre-dame-cathedral&quot;&gt;A terrible blaze devastates Notre Dame cathedral (April 15th 2019)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 23:06:26 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Fosse/Verdon” is a compelling examination of a creative partnership]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/04/16/fosse/verdon-is-a-compelling-examination-of-a-creative-partnership]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BKP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-16T14:51:02Z&quot;&gt;Apr 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“FOSSE/VERDON”, a new mini-series about two Broadway legends, could have been a simple paean to the magic of the stage. Bob Fosse (Sam Rockwell), a director, and his wife Gwen Verdon (Michelle Williams), a dancer, helped to create hits such as “Damn Yankees!”, “Chicago” and “Cabaret&amp;quot;. There is plenty of exquisite choreography, as legs kick in perfect time and dazzling costumes shimmer on twisting bodies, plus a sparkling rendition of “Big Spender”. Elsewhere, in a fantasy scene, Fosse twirls effortlessly down a corridor, surrounded by colourful dancers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the show turns out to be a surprisingly moving examination of the characters of Fosse and Verdon, as well as their extraordinary careers. It opens with the build-up to “Cabaret”, Fosse’s best-known film, which he directed and choreographed in 1971. The viewer is transported from Hollywood to damp, dark Munich, where it was shot, and the pressure is palpable. The film cannot afford to be “another $20m fiasco”, a producer warns, referring to one of Fosse’s previous misses. Fosse, in turn, takes it out on his crew. “I wanna see every muscle, every tendon,” he barks during exhausting rehearsals for “Mein Herr”, one of the nightclub songs. After seeing the first cut, he moans to his assistant that “it’s unwatchable”. On the night of the premiere, he paces in the auditorium rather than watching the film (it was a box-office triumph and would go on to win eight Oscars). His personal torment, and abject terror of failure, is clear. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The programme dances back and forth in time. Title cards, such as “Hollywood: 19 years left” and “Gwen Verdon: 14 years after her last Tony award”, contextualise the scenes, which range across five decades. It allows the viewer to see patterns emerge. A flashback to Fosse’s childhood dance classes, for example—“don’t show me the effort, Bobby, don’t show me the sweat. All they wanna see is that smile”—helps to explain Fosse’s treatment of his own dancers. Depictions of his career highs jar with his descent into depression and alcoholism, as well as scenes of childhood abuse. His wild lifestyle of pills, sex, parties and more pills, is juxtaposed with images of Verdon feeding their daughter dinner and arranging child care. The effect is troubling, and powerful. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Rockwell’s thoughtful and pained performance elicits a surprising amount of sympathy for Fosse, even as he behaves appallingly. One excruciating scene shows a lead dancer refusing his sexual advances; she is subsequently fired. But the decision to give Verdon equal billing in the production was a wise one (the series was originally adapted from “Fosse”, a biography written in 2013, but the producers realised that this would result in a narrow, uneven story). She emerges as a quiet kind of hero, helped by an elegant performance by Ms Williams. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verdon, as well as being Fosse’s long-suffering wife, was his creative collaborator. Her career peaked in the 1950s, when she won a string of Tony awards, but she gradually lost her hold over Hollywood and was eventually eclipsed by her husband. Yet when “Cabaret” hits a crisis—the endless rehearsals are ruining the shooting schedule, and the budget—it is Verdon that Fosse needs, begging her to come and join him in Germany. She sweeps in, taking charge of hair and make-up and fine-tuning the dancing. Where Fosse had used the dancers as moving props, Verdon makes them into fleshed-out characters with backstories. As such, “Fosse/Verdon” reminds viewers that great feats are rarely accomplished alone (a theme that Lin-Manuel Miranda, an executive producer of the series, touched upon in “Hamilton”, his own musical hit). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tributes to Tinseltown and Broadway, such as “La La Land”, often focus on the glamour and romanticism of it all. “Fosse/Verdon” is all the better for lifting the stage curtain to look at the people behind it. The series understands that while show business projects an image of human perfection, its masters are as flawed as they are brilliant.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Fosse/Verdon” is showing on FX in America now. It will be released in Britain on BBC Two later this year&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(此域名已被污染，谢谢大家一直以来的支持)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 22:07:29 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Big carmakers are placing vast bets on battery power]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/04/16/big-carmakers-are-placing-vast-bets-on-battery-power]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_WBP001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-16T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN 1900 ONE in three cars on American roads ran on volts. Then oil began gushing out of Texas. Cheaper than batteries, and easier to top up, petrol fuelled the rise of mass-produced automobiles. Cost and worries about limited range have kept electric vehices (EVs) in a niche ever since. Tesla, which has made battery power sexy again in the past decade, produced just 250,000 units last year, a fraction of what Volkswagen or Toyota churn out each year. For every one of the 2m or so pure EVs and plug-in hybrids, which combine batteries and internal-combustion engines (ICEs), sold in 2018, the world’s carmakers shifted 50 petrol or diesel cars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;EV sales are, however, accelerating as quickly as electric motors. Some industry-watchers reckon that they will account for nearly 15% of the global total by 2025. One in five new cars in China will run on batteries then, according to Bloomberg New Energy Finance, a consultancy. The chief reason such optimistic forecasts no longer look outlandish is the entry into the electric race of the car industry’s juggernauts. A survey by Reuters in January put the industry’s total planned EV-related spending worldwide (including on batteries) at around $300bn over the next five to ten years. From GM and Geely to Mercedes and Nissan, big carmakers all want to turn out millions of such cars—and turn a profit doing so. Their strategies range from cautious to aggressive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;strong&gt;Get our daily newsletter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;p&gt;Upgrade your inbox and get our Daily Dispatch and Editor&amp;#x27;s Picks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;form&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;email&quot; required=&quot;&quot; placeholder=&quot;Email address&quot;  aria-label=&quot;Subscription mail&quot;/&gt;&lt;input type=&quot;submit&quot; value=&quot;Sign up now&quot; /&gt;&lt;/form&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_WBC729.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190420_WBC729.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190420_WBC729.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190420_WBC729.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190420_WBC729.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190420_WBC729.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190420_WBC729.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190420_WBC729.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190420_WBC729.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190420_WBC729.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Making a profitable, mass-produced EV has proved elusive. A battery powertrain can be three times the price of an ICE. But a combination of better technology and greater scale may soon allow EVs to compete on price with petrol vehicles, and enable motorists to drive long distances without the fear of running out of juice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They had better, carmakers are hoping. Worries about climate change and air pollution are prompting authorities around the world to consider phasing out new petrol and diesel engines in the coming decade. In the absence of federal regulations under America’s climate-sceptical president, Donald Trump, some progressive cities and states are tightening local rules. Fiat Chrysler (whose chairman, John Elkann, sits on the board of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s parent company) has just agreed to pay Tesla hundreds of millions of euros to count the Californian marque as part of its fleet, and thus avoid steep fines for exceeding average CO2-emissions standards for carmakers due to come into force in the European Union next year. In China, where half the world’s EVs are already sold, the government sees electrification of transport as a way to combat choking urban smog—and to lap the West technologically.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Western premium brands appear best positioned to take an early lead. While batteries remain pricey, fancy marques can offset the cost with the higher prices that their vehicles command. Jaguar and Audi have already broken Tesla’s monopoly at the lucrative top end of the market. Daimler, which owns Mercedes, has committed €10bn ($11.3bn) to its EQ range and wants 20% of its cars to be fully electric by 2025.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Daimler and BMW, which has been bruised by losses on its poorly selling i3 electric hatchback, are hedging their bets by backing platforms (as the basic architecture of a car is known in the business) that are able to accommodate petrol and diesel engines as well as electric motors. This should help them contain costs, but at the expense of compromises over battery size and layout. Sacrificing range and interior space in this way may dent brands built on luxury and technological prowess, says Patrick Hummel of UBS, a bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many mass-market firms are likewise proceeding cautiously. Their thinner margins leave less room to absorb the cost of batteries. Renault of France and South Korea’s Hyundai are nevertheless toying with the idea of a dedicated electric-only platform. PSA Group has said it plans to electrify more Peugeots, Citroëns and Opels. Fiat Chrysler has made similar noises, though the Tesla tie-up suggests its near-term plans are less ambitious. Toyota’s early bet on hydrogen fuel cells, which lag behind batteries on the road to widespread adoption, had long been a distraction. The Japanese giant has now acknowledged that buyers want battery-power. It is planning ten models by the early 2020s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most daring by a long way is VW. The German group’s heft—it produces 10m cars a year—affords it economies of scale only Toyota could hope to match. The €30bn VW plans to spend on developing EVs over the next five years, plus €50bn to fit them with batteries, leaves all other carmakers in the dust. In March Herbert Diess, its chief executive, promised 70 new electric models by 2028, rather than 50 as previously pledged, and 22m EVS delivered over the next ten years. The company is contemplating a huge investment in a “gigafactory” to supply its own batteries rather than depending on outside suppliers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;VW is already developing a dedicated platform and converting entire factories to EV production. The first, at Zwickau in Germany, will eventually turn out 330,000 cars a year for the VW brand as well as Audi and SEAT. Its medium-sized ID hatchback, to be shipped next year, will cost around €30,000, similar to an equivalent diesel-powered Golf, and travel 400-600km (250-370 miles) on a single charge. On April 14th in Shanghai Mr Diess unveiled a sport-utility vehicle to compete with Tesla’s snazzy Model X in China from 2021. Once the range of EVs reaches full production in 2022, VW believes, such models will start breaking even. By 2025, when it hopes one-quarter of its output will be electric, they should be as profitable as petrol cars.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Mike Manley, boss of Fiat Chrysler, observers, it is no longer a question of whether carmakers can deliver a fleet of EVs but whether people will pay for them. If governments withdraw generous subsidies which EV-owners have enjoyed, charging infrastructure fails to materialise or electric cars’ pitiful resale value does not increase, motorists may be reluctant to abandon their tried and tested petrol wheels. Poor sales, combined with the large upfront investments, would hit carmakers’ margins, which for mass-market brands are already about as exciting as a Soviet-era Trabant in mud brown. The financial consequences could be “ugly”, warns Bernstein, an equity-research firm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Electric field&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;At the same time, the big carmakers can expect more competition from rivals unburdened by complex ICE supply chains and large workforces. VW has 40,000 suppliers worldwide and directly employs 660,000 people. Lower capital intensity, and the relative simplicity of EVs, which use many fewer parts than petrol vehicles and are easier to assemble, is drawing in upstarts. They include Dyson, a British maker of vacuum cleaners, and a raft of Chinese Tesla-wannabes, such as NIO and Byton. Bigger Chinese carmakers, such as Geely and JAC, have also developed expertise in EVs. With domestic sales stalling, they are beginning to eye export markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other technological bumps are meanwhile beginning to test the industry’s chassis. Self-driving cars and ride-sharing are forcing car companies to rethink their established business model. If carmakers miss the electric turn now, they will find it harder to find their way in these futuristic areas. The electric race may prove to be a practice lap for wider disruption.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 21:08:20 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The fire in Notre Dame cathedral, and more from our daily podcast]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/16/the-fire-in-notre-dame-cathedral-and-more-from-our-daily-podcast]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/the_intelligence_54.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-16T11:11:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EMMANUEL MACRON, the president of France, was already dealing with national protests when &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/15/a-terrible-blaze-devastates-notre-dame&quot;&gt;a massive fire broke out at the Notre Dame cathedral&lt;/a&gt;, an 850-year old Parisian landmark. Can the tragedy, and Mr Macron’s leadership, bring the country together? America’s armed forces often don’t know &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/04/04/how-many-civilians-does-america-kill-in-air-strikes&quot;&gt;how many civilians are killed&lt;/a&gt; in its air-strike campaigns—but that’s changing, thanks to pressure from the Pentagon’s loudest critics. And, though the Trump administration has cancelled a deal for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/the-americas/2019/04/13/donald-trump-seeks-to-hurt-cuba-by-shutting-out-its-baseball-players&quot;&gt;Cuban baseball players&lt;/a&gt;, that won’t stop them making their way to the big leagues. Runtime: TK min.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/andthen-silence-aparisiconburns&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 19:06:34 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why British wage growth is picking up at last]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/04/16/why-british-wage-growth-is-picking-up-at-last]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BRP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-16T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 16th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BRC734.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190420_BRC734.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190420_BRC734.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190420_BRC734.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190420_BRC734.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190420_BRC734.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190420_BRC734.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190420_BRC734.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190420_BRC734.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190420_BRC734.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt; PERHAPS NO OTHER factor better explains why so many Britons want radical change, from voting for Brexit to backing Jeremy Corbyn’s far-left Labour Party. Since the financial crisis of 2008-09 Britain’s wage growth has been dreadful. Adjusting for inflation, wages fell from 2007 to 2017, a worse performance than in any other OECD country except Mexico or Greece. At last, however, the tables are turning. Data released on April 16th show that nominal pay is growing at about 3.5% a year (see chart), or 1.5% a year in real terms. Can this growth continue to accelerate?&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The obvious cause of strengthening pay is the tight labour market. When unemployment hit its post-crisis high of 8.5% in 2011, employers knew that they could get away with offering meagre or no pay rises. Workers’ bargaining power has since grown, as joblessness has fallen. Unemployment is just 3.9%, the lowest in four decades. Britain has about three vacancies for each 100 employee jobs, the highest ratio since the data began in 2001, meaning bosses have to try harder to fill posts. Nominal pay in the hospitality sector, which has a particularly high number of job postings, is growing at 5% a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A hot jobs market is not the only cause of rising average pay. Another relates to the mix of jobs in the economy. Following the financial crisis, posts in low-productivity, low-paying sectors such as agriculture proliferated. Having more poorly paid positions dragged down the average. Yet lately Britain has created relatively more high-paying jobs—strawberry-pickers have made way for stock-pickers. In the year to September 2018 the changing composition of the workforce boosted average nominal wage growth by 0.5 percentage points.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stronger pay may also owe something to rising productivity. How much workers produce ultimately determines how much they earn. After stagnating in 2007-14, more recently output per hour has grown by about 1% a year in real terms. Silvana Tenreyro of the Bank of England has floated the idea that some of these gains might not have yet shown up in the statistics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The question is whether wage growth will accelerate further. Workers will hope that it does: at its current rate real pay will not return to its pre-crisis peak until 2022. Yet few economists believe Britain will soon resume the healthy productivity growth of the post-war period, which was consistent with real-terms pay rises of some 3% a year. The IMF expects British productivity growth to be weaker than in any other big, rich country this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Already there are signs that firms are struggling to afford the modest pay settlements that their workers are demanding. The cost of staffing per unit of output, a measure of domestically generated inflation, grew by 1.7% in 2017 but by 2.7% last year. To absorb these extra costs some firms are accepting lower profits. Other firms are passing them on to customers, stoking consumer-price inflation, which hovers around the Bank of England’s 2% target.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now there is little need for the bank to raise interest rates, which would bring down inflation. Uncertainty over Brexit, which is likely to continue until October and perhaps beyond, argues in favour of holding fire. Yet the difficult truth is that Britain’s current rate of wage growth, modest by historical standards, is about as high as it can go without pushing inflation above target. It will be some time before Britons’ pay squeeze is truly over. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 19:06:33 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A terrible blaze devastates Notre Dame cathedral]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/15/a-terrible-blaze-devastates-notre-dame-cathedral]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_blp903.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THEY GATHERED on the bridges over the Seine to watch in disbelief. Some Parisians were in tears; most watched in eerie silence. The devastating fire that broke out in the wood-timbered roof of the gothic cathedral of Notre Dame in the early evening of April 15th rapidly spread before their eyes, consuming the central spire and defeating the efforts of fire-fighters to bring the flames under control. President Emmanuel Macron, spoke for many across France when he tweeted that he was witnessing “part of us burn.”  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By midnight in Paris the worst seemed to be over. The main stone structure appeared to have been saved, and the prompt action of hundreds of fire-fighters had rescued many works of art and relics from the burning building. But as well as the medieval oak-beamed roof and the later-built spire, the damage to the interior has been immense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 850-year-old edifice had survived war, revolution and Nazi occupation, an emblem of resistance in the face of a constantly disrupted history. It was the site of Napoleon’s coronation in 1804 and the inspiration for literary works, most famously Victor Hugo’s “The Hunchback of Notre-Dame”, and one of the city’s most iconic landmarks, visited by 13m tourists each year. Notre Dame was at once a living place of worship for the French Catholic church and the property of the French secular state: a symbol in itself of the country’s history and its present, in all its glorious contradictions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The heartbreak felt by many as they watched nine centuries of history dissolve in flames was profound. Bertrand Delanoë, the former mayor of Paris, called the cathedral a “jewel of the heritage of humanity”. Mr Macron, who had been preparing to give a televised address to the nation at the end of his “great national debate”, cancelled the speech and went straight to the site of the disaster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It will take time and a full investigation before the exact cause of the fire is established. Early reports from the Paris fire service suggested that it was not a work of arson but an accident that broke out in the central roof, where building works were underway to renovate the 19th-century spire. But already questions are being asked about disaster-planning for a monument of this scale and national importance, situated amid narrow streets on an inaccessible island in the centre of the city.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The search for somebody to blame will absorb France for weeks and months to come. The public prosecutor has opened an inquiry. When shock and disbelief turns to anger, many will want to know exactly what precautions were taken by those working on the renovation, and why it was so difficult for fire-fighters to stop the blaze spreading. Five hundred were deployed, but it took them ages to get there. Some will look to Anne Hidalgo, the mayor of Paris, who tweeted that she had “no words for the pain” she felt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Others still will look to Mr Macron. The unpopular president already had his hands full dealing with the gilets jaunes (yellow jackets) protests, which have dragged on since last November. This evening was supposed to mark the moment that he reconnected with the French people, and put his reputation for haughty rule behind him. Now he has a different challenge. Paris, and all of France, is hurting. The tragic devastation of Notre Dame will touch the country for a long time—and put the head of state’s capacity to touch the French with the right words of consolation to a severe test. He made a good start last night, visiting the scene and pledging that &amp;quot;we will rebuild&amp;quot; the cathedral. It is a task that will take many, many years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 19:06:32 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A terrible blaze devastates Notre Dame]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/15/a-terrible-blaze-devastates-notre-dame]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_blp903.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THEY GATHERED on the bridges over the Seine to watch in disbelief. Some Parisians were in tears; most watched in eerie silence. The devastating fire that broke out in the wood-timbered roof of the gothic cathedral of Notre Dame in the early evening of April 15th rapidly spread before their eyes, consuming the central spire and defeating the efforts of fire-fighters to bring the flames under control. President Emmanuel Macron, spoke for many across France when he tweeted that he was witnessing “part of us burn.”  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By midnight in Paris the worst seemed to be over. The main stone struture appeared to have been saved, and the prompt action of hundreds of fire-fighters had rescued many works of art from the burning building. But as well as the mediaeval roof and the later-built spire, the cathedral&amp;#x27;s 13th-century great stained-glass windows are gone, and the damage to the interior will have been immense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 850-year-old edifice had survived war, revolution and Nazi occupation, an emblem of resistance in the face of a constantly disrupted history. It was the site of Napoleon’s coronation in 1804 and the inspiration for literary works, most famously Victor Hugo’s “The Hunchback of Notre Dame”, and one of the city’s most iconic landmarks, visited by 13m tourists each year. Notre Dame was at once a living place of worship for the French Catholic church and the property of the French secular state: a symbol in itself of the country’s history and its present, in all its glorious contradictions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The heartbreak felt by many as they watched nine centuries of history dissolve in flames was profound. Bertrand Delanoë, the former mayor of Paris, called the cathedral a “jewel of the heritage of humanity”. Mr Macron, who had been preparing to give a televised address to the nation at the end of his “great national debate”, cancelled the speech and went straight to the site of the disaster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It will take time and a full investigation before the exact cause of the fire is established. Early reports from the Paris fire service suggested that it was not a work of arson but an accident that broke out in the central roof, where building works were underway to renovate the 19th-century spire. But already questions are being asked about disaster-planning for a monument of this scale and national importance, situated amid narrow streets on an inaccessible island in the centre of the city.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The search for somebody to blame will absorb France for weeks and months to come. The public prosecutor has opened an inquiry. When shock and disbelief turns to anger, many will want to know exactly what precautions were taken by those working on the renovation, and why it was so difficult for fire-fighters to stop the blaze spreading. Five hundred were deployed, but it took them ages to get there. Some will look to Anne Hidalgo, the mayor of Paris, who tweeted that she had “no words for the pain” she felt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Others still will look to Mr Macron, who visited the scene and pledged to rebuild the cathedral. The unpopular president already had his hands full dealing with the gilets jaunes (yellow jackets) protests, which have dragged on since last November. This evening was supposed to mark the moment that he reconnected with the French people, and put his reputation for haughty rule behind him. Now he has a different challenge. Paris, and all of France, is hurting. The tragic devastation of Notre Dame will touch the country for a long time—and put the head of state’s capacity to touch the French with the right words of consolation to a severe test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 07:06:52 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A terrible fire destroys much of the cathedral of Notre Dame]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/15/a-terrible-fire-destroys-much-of-the-cathedral-of-notre-dame]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_blp903.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THEY GATHERED on the bridges over the Seine to watch in disbelief. Some Parisians were in tears; most watched in eerie silence. The devastating fire that broke out in the wood-timbered roof of the gothic cathedral of Notre Dame in the early evening of April 15th rapidly spread before their eyes, consuming the central spire and defeating the efforts of fire-fighters to bring the flames under control. President Emmanuel Macron, spoke for many across France when he tweeted that he was witnessing “part of us burn.”  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By midnight in Paris the worst seemed to be over. The main stone struture appeared to have been saved, and the prompt action of hundreds of fire-fighters had rescued many works of art from the burning building. But as well as the mediaeval roof and the later-built spire, the cathedral&amp;#x27;s 13th-century great stained-glass windows are gone, and the damage to the interior will have been immense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The 850-year-old edifice had survived war, revolution and Nazi occupation, an emblem of resistance in the face of a constantly disrupted history. It was the site of Napoleon’s coronation in 1804 and the inspiration for literary works, most famously Victor Hugo’s “The Hunchback of Notre Dame”, and one of the city’s most iconic landmarks, visited by 13m tourists each year. Notre Dame was at once a living place of worship for the French Catholic church and the property of the French secular state: a symbol in itself of the country’s history and its present, in all its glorious contradictions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The heartbreak felt by many as they watched nine centuries of history dissolve in flames was profound. Bertrand Delanoë, the former mayor of Paris, called the cathedral a “jewel of the heritage of humanity”. Mr Macron, who had been preparing to give a televised address to the nation at the end of his “great national debate”, cancelled the speech and went straight to the site of the disaster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It will take time and a full investigation before the exact cause of the fire is established. Early reports from the Paris fire service suggested that it was not a work of arson but an accident that broke out in the central roof, where building works were underway to renovate the 19th-century spire. But already questions are being asked about disaster-planning for a monument of this scale and national importance, situated amid narrow streets on an inaccessible island in the centre of the city.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The search for somebody to blame will absorb France for weeks and months to come. The public prosecutor has opened an inquiry. When shock and disbelief turns to anger, many will want to know exactly what precautions were taken by those working on the renovation, and why it was so difficult for fire-fighters to stop the blaze spreading. Five hundred were deployed, but it took them ages to get there. Some will look to Anne Hidalgo, the mayor of Paris, who tweeted that she had “no words for the pain” she felt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Others still will look to Mr Macron, who visited the scene and pledged to rebuild the cathedral. The unpopular president already had his hands full dealing with the gilets jaunes (yellow jackets) protests, which have dragged on since last November. This evening was supposed to mark the moment that he reconnected with the French people, and put his reputation for haughty rule behind him. Now he has a different challenge. Paris, and all of France, is hurting. The tragic devastation of Notre Dame will touch the country for a long time—and put the head of state’s capacity to touch the French with the right words of consolation to a severe test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 06:08:29 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>