<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[With “My Songs” Sting underlines the lasting quality of his music]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/04/with-my-songs-sting-underlines-the-lasting-quality-of-his-music]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_BKP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-04T14:02:25Z&quot;&gt;Jun 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERE IS a category of music superstar who, while they once divided opinion, became cherished as they attained veteran status. Encountering somebody with a harsh word for Elton John or Bruce Springsteen is rare enough to be surprising; the same was true before their deaths of David Bowie and Prince. Then there is another category of those who, while popular, still engender antagonism (if sometimes unfairly). Foremost in that rank are two men who rose to fame at the head of rock bands: Bono, the lead singer of U2, and the frontman of the Police, Sting.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even in 1978 Sting was an object of contempt among fans of punk music, who saw him as an interloper, an old-style muso with his roots in jazz, riding punk’s coat-tails into the charts. Perhaps that was true, but it overlooked the fact that Sting was unmistakably a major talent in his own right. He was and has remained an outstanding songwriter. The body of work he has created stands up. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“My Songs”, a new album, is a 15-track overview of Sting’s career, but not a compilation; rather, he has seen fit to re-record a set of his compositions, for the most part so closely to the original versions as to appear redundant. (Artists increasingly revisit their own catalogues in this way, perhaps for licensing and royalty reasons as often as artistic ones.) The few notable differences are puzzling: a funky-house take on “If You Love Somebody Set Them Free”, his first solo single post-Police, feels clunky and outdated; a slightly rockier version of “Demolition Man” sheds no new light on the song.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around half of these tracks were first recorded by the Police, so the title “My Songs” rather makes it sound as if Sting is tetchily wresting them back. Still, why should the man who wrote these songs not take proprietorial pride in them? They are all excellent, and there are plenty more he could have included of the same standard. It is no small thing to have written the exquisite “Fragile”, which has lent itself to a superb, epic reworking by Isaac Hayes; to have created “Walking On The Moon” as a perfect vehicle for the Police’s eerie fusion of reggae and rock; to have fashioned perhaps his most celebrated song, “Every Breath You Take”, which is widely misheard as an account of loving devotion, but which is unsurpassed in pop as an (entirely intentional) account of sinister, obsessive and controlling behaviour. Plenty of renowned artists have accumulated lesser catalogues of music than Sting’s while committing worse sins than being found vaguely irksome by a segment of the public.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is also significant to have forged a solo career that rivals or even eclipses his work as part of a successful group: Sting joins Diana Ross, Paul Simon, Michael Jackson, Phil Collins, George Michael, Robbie Williams, Justin Timberlake and Beyoncé, among a few others, in that select club. His most recent new material, “44/876” (2018) —a collaborative album with Shaggy, a reggae star—has charted around the world, some 33 years since his first solo album, “The Dream of the Blue Turtles”, did the same. Perhaps the moment is approaching when nobody considers it worthwhile to dislike Sting any longer, and the best of his music will speak for itself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 21:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[China erases the Tiananmen story: “It&#x27;s been depressingly effective”]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/04/china-erases-the-tiananmen-story-its-been-depressingly-effective]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_opm502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-04T11:14:43Z&quot;&gt;Jun 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON THE &lt;strong&gt;30th anniversary of the &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/china/2019/05/04/the-communist-party-grapples-with-a-momentous-anniversary&quot;&gt;Tiananmen Square&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; massacre&lt;/strong&gt;, our correspondents recall a dark day and assess &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/china/2019/05/30/many-chinese-know-little-about-the-bloodshed-in-beijing-30-years-ago&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;its legacy&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;—not least the Communist Party&amp;#x27;s effort to suppress the memory of how it crushed China&amp;#x27;s pro-democracy movement. Could such widespread dissent flare up in today’s China? Also, why &lt;strong&gt;laws requiring immigrants to speak host-nations’ languages are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/05/25/the-language-struggles-of-immigrants-to-america&quot;&gt;counter-productive&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. Runtime: 22 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/thirtyyearsofforgetting-tiananmen&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 20:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A revolutionary treatise goes on the block]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/06/04/a-revolutionary-treatise-goes-on-the-block]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_bkp002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;MODERN CAPITALISM began among the European merchant families of the early Renaissance—the Fuggers of Augsburg, Medicis of Florence and, in Venice, one Antonio de Rompiasi, who in 1464 hired a tutor in mathematics for his three sons. Like any sensible teacher, young Luca Pacioli aimed to make his lessons memorable and clear. Good humanist that he was, 30 years later he gathered all the world’s knowledge of the subject into a single massive volume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His “Summa de Arithmetica, Geometria, Proportioni et Proportionalita” was the 615-page work of a mature professor who had spent decades working across northern Italy. The book was revolutionary on more than one count. It integrated computation using Hindu-Arabic numerals with the logic of classic Greek geometry; it was written in the Italian of the marketplace rather than Latin; and it was circulated in large numbers thanks to the new technology of printing. Yet its greatest significance lay in a slim ‘how to’ chapter that described the double-entry accounting system used by Venetian merchants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With examples from dealers in butter to lemons to silk, Pacioli set out the method for tracking income and expenditure and the calculation of net profit or loss, which for the first time allowed an immediate snapshot of a firm’s financial position. This slim section would facilitate the birth of the modern corporation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Without order there is chaos,” Pacioli observed in a breezy style that is still in vogue in business books today. His manual is stuffed with quotes from scripture and Dante and pithy advice such as “Don’t learn from ignoramuses who have more leaves than grapes.” He wrote the accounting chapter to help would-be traders in Venice, then the capital of the financial world, “sleep easily at night”. Without double-entry book-keeping, “their minds would keep them awake with worry”. He could not suspect that what might be called “Book-keeping for Dummies” would become the backbone of business for centuries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like many monumental works of 15th-century printing, Pacioli’s treatise has survived in its original form. Some 120 copies still exist, from an initial run of about 1,000. Now today’s moguls have a chance to own this first folio of finance. Christie’s, the auction house, is offering a first edition in its original vellum binding for sale in New York on June 12th. The starting price is $1m for what it unabashedly calls “the most influential work in the history of capitalism.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pacioli’s later life augments the glamour of the first printed use of ‘plus’ and ‘minus’ signs. Impressed by the book, Leonardo da Vinci convinced his patron Lodovico Sforza to hire Pacioli to teach at the court of Milan. Pacioli and Leonardo collaborated on the treatise “Divina Proportione,” which married maths with art through the study of perspective. Not one, but two Renaissance masters were thus responsible for the exquisite harmony of “The Last Supper”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 20:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“It&#x27;s been depressingly effective”—China erases the Tiananmen story]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/04/its-been-depressingly-effective-china-erases-the-tiananmen-story]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_opm502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-04T11:14:43Z&quot;&gt;Jun 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON THE &lt;strong&gt;30th anniversary of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/china/2019/05/04/the-communist-party-grapples-with-a-momentous-anniversary&quot;&gt;Tiananmen Square&lt;/a&gt; tragedy&lt;/strong&gt;, our correspondents reflect on a dark and confusing day—and the Chinese government’s efforts to suppress the memory of it. Could such widespread dissent flare up in today’s China? Also, &lt;strong&gt;why laws requiring immigrants to speak host-nations’ languages are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/05/25/the-language-struggles-of-immigrants-to-america&quot;&gt;counter-productive&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/strong&gt; Runtime: 22 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/thirtyyearsofforgetting-tiananmen&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 18:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sudan’s generals turn their guns against protesters]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/03/sudans-generals-turn-their-guns-against-protesters]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_map502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-03T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Update, 06.20 BST June 4th 2019:&lt;/strong&gt; The current version of this article cites a higher number of civilians killed, in keeping with more recent reports.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHERE JUST weeks ago the scent of freedom was in the air there is now the smell of smoke and cordite. The sounds of jubilant song have given way to those of automatic gunfire and the screams of the dying. In the early hours of June 3rd Sudan’s armed forces moved against pro-democracy protesters who had been holding a sit-in since April outside the army’s headquarters in Khartoum, the capital of Sudan. They shot and killed at least 35 civilians. All that remains of the carnival of democracy that had sprouted there are burnt tents and rubbish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the worst violence since demonstrations toppled Sudan’s brutal dictator, Omar al-Bashir, in early April. The Sudanese Professionals Association (SPA), which has spearheaded the uprising since it began last December, called it a “bloody massacre” and announced a campaign of “total civil disobedience” to topple the junta that took power in Mr Bashir’s place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trouble had been brewing for some weeks amid a fraught stand-off between protesters and the generals over who would control the country’s transition to democracy. Negotiators for both sides had agreed on some issues, such as the establishment of a civilian-led parliament and cabinet, and a three-year transition before elections. Such was the optimism that on May 15th leaders of the protest movement announced that they would have a deal signed with the generals within 24 hours. But this was premature because they had not reached agreement on the most contentious issue of all: who would be in charge of the sovereign council, the highest decision-making body that would oversee the move towards democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On May 16th, less than 24 hours after the supposed breakthrough, the TMC’s leader, Abdel Fattah al-Burhan, halted the talks and accused the protesters of undermining them by blocking roads in the capital. He claimed “armed infiltrators” had fired on soldiers. The opposition responded on May 28th by declaring a two-day strike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the attack on June 3rd, trust between the two sides has all but evaporated. Protesters say that all the country’s previous transitions were led by the armed forces and that the generals are determined to control this one, too. People in the opposition accuse Muhammad Hamdan Dagalo (who is widely known as Hemedti), the powerful deputy head of the TMC, of foul play. They say that the paramilitary unit he heads, the Rapid Support Forces (RSF), carried out the lethal attack against the sit-in, as well as earlier killings of protesters. Observers, including some foreign diplomats, think that Mr Dagalo wants to become president and that he may undermine any transition that excludes him from power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But he is not the only one with an incentive to act as a spoiler. Mr Bashir kept himself in power for 30 years by playing armed factions against one another and by allowing them to earn illicit incomes. Many in the TMC may lose out if Sudan moves towards democracy and establishes the rule of law. Many of them also fear justice for atrocities committed by government forces and its militias during Sudan’s long civil wars in Darfur and what is now South Sudan. “This is a game with huge stakes,” says Harry Verhoeven, the author of a book on Sudan. “Why would those who have guns give them up voluntarily?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest violence means there is even less hope for compromise. On one side are the generals, who have won the support of powerful autocratic countries in the region including Egypt, Saudi Arabia and the United Arab Emirates. Emboldened, they are no longer bothering to disguise their reluctance to cede power to civilians. “The negotiations were never serious from the beginning,” says Rashid Abdi, an independent expert on Sudan based in Nairobi. “The army was just playing for time.” On the other side are the demonstrators, who are angry at the betrayal of their democratic revolution. “This is not going to stop,” says Reem Abbas, a Sudanese journalist in Khartoum. “The protests are going to continue.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 14:40:11 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How America’s urban-rural divide shapes elections]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/03/how-americas-urban-rural-divide-shapes-elections]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_USP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-03T18:30:03Z&quot;&gt;Jun 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN NINE OF America’s 13 congressional elections between 1994 and 2018, the Republican Party won a greater share of seats than votes. In 2012, Democrats failed to garner a majority of seats while winning a broad popular vote victory. Even in the 2018 mid-terms, which were described as a “wave” election, &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; predicted that the Democrats had to win the popular vote in the House of Representatives by 5-6 percentage points to obtain a bare majority of seats. In the Senate, the situation is worse because of the way states magnify the pro-rural bias of America’s electoral institutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Liberal activists and social scientists alike have blamed the Republican Party’s manipulation of the electoral system for much of this. But Democrats are battling a deeper structural problem than partisan gerrymandering. Jonathan Rodden, a political scientist at Stanford University, has written a book that explores the party’s real challenge: political polarisation has become inextricably linked with economic geography and population density. The electoral system magnifies the voices of the poor, sparsely populated and conservative countryside at the expense of voters in densely populated cities who tend to be richer, racially diverse, and liberal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In “Why Cities Lose: The Deep Roots of the Urban-Rural Political Divide”, Mr Rodden goes back to the 1870s and the origins of the labour movement. The Socialist Party in Reading, Pennsylvania takes on a microcosmic significance: it represented the interests of local manufacturing workers, but failed to win elections that required the input of the rural residents. The socialists were left with no political representation above the city level.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So city-dwelling labourers began to find a home in the Democratic Party, which increasingly took on pro-labour views. Party bosses like Al Smith, the Democrats’ 1928 nominee for president, cut deals with local labour leaders to persuade them to join. While the Democratic Party still garnered a majority of its votes from rural areas in the north, the union between Democrats and urban labourers was born. Mr Rodden writes that in 1916, “a doubling of population density was associated with a 7 percent decrease in Democratic voting. By 1940, a doubling of population density was associated with a 5 percent increase”. The story in the South, where there was little organised labour, was quite different: Democrats’ prospects were kept afloat by predominantly rural segregationists, while business-owning Republican won elections in the cities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When, in the late 20th century, the parties’ realignment became complete, the causes were primarily ideological. Presidential elections in the 1950s had been characterised by the Democrats and Republicans taking opposing views on economic policy but they differed little on social issues. Lyndon Johnson’s signing of the Civil Rights Act of 1964 was a notable moment in this realignment, breaking the Democrats’ hold on the South and catalysing the cultural shifts that produced the modern Republican Party. Through the remainder of the century, the diverse constituencies that made up urban areas—the poor, union members, immigrants and minorities, educated elites and young progressives—gravitated toward the Democrats while Republicans enjoyed increasing vote share among the farmers, the rural poor and ultra-wealthy business owners.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The result of this history was an electoral system that pitted city-dwellers against the exurban and rural population—with the cities losing. This is where Mr Rodden’s talent with statistics is most evident. He recounts that in Pennsylvania in 2012, Democratic candidates for Congress won 51% of the votes state-wide but came away with majorities in only 28% of the districts. This “strikingly counter-majoritarian result” was not just a product of pro-Republican partisan gerrymandering, argues Mr Rodden. After running a computer programme that generates 400 separate, equally populous congressional maps for the state, Mr Rodden finds that even “party-blind” plans disadvantage Democrats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That year was no hiccup. In all but one presidential election since 1952, the mean congressional district in Pennsylvania was much more Democratic than the median one—a testament to Democrats’ inefficient geographic distribution. This was true as recently as 2018—and not just in Pennsylvania, but nationwide. In last year’s mid-term elections, a majority of voters in Michigan, Wisconsin, Pennsylvania and North Carolina all cast ballots for Democratic candidates for state houses, but the party won a minority of seats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Rodden points out that the 2018 elections introduced another issue for the Democrats: whether or not they will move further left. Increasing liberalism within the party threatens the support of key suburban moderates who act as a barrier to further geographical disadvantage. The nomination of a socially moderate candidate for 2020 could help with that. And yet, opposition to President Donald Trump drove up Democratic margins in key suburban swing districts last year. If the president remains unpopular, Mr Rodden suggests, Democrats could win &amp;quot;narrow victories in districts where comfortable Republican victories had been the norm&amp;quot;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Rodden weighs a few longer-term solutions, among them electoral systems used elsewhere in the world. America might, for example, adopt a system of proportional representation. Allocating parties’ legislative seats in proportion to the votes they won would eliminate the geographic disadvantage the Democrats face. But this would require the repeal of a law from 1967, which a Republican-controlled Senate would be almost certain to block.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demographic change is perhaps most likely bring the greatest change in the Democrats’ favour. In the coming years, non-whites and today’s young voters will become increasingly large shares of the electorate. If Democrats run up big margins with these groups, a number of closely-contested states are likely to turn bluer. But winning congressional districts could be hard, and state legislatures harder still, as urban areas with increasing populations would still have to be cracked into several districts to ensure equal populations among them. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the medium-term, Democrats’ best hope of rebalancing the electoral scale lies in converting suburban moderates to their cause and turning out non-voters. Both helped the Democrats overcome a big structural disadvantage in the 2018 mid-terms. But presidential politics are different. And there will still be the small states to magnify the voices of conservative, rural voters, hurting the Democrats’ chances of controlling the Senate. As Mr Rodden writes, &amp;quot;if neither reform nor demographic change is sufficient to diminish urban-rural polarisation, the United States must find ways to function as a divided society.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Why Cities Lose: The Deep Roots of the Urban-Rural Political Divide&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;By Jonathan Rodden. Basic Books; 336 pages; $18.99&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 04:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Sudan’s generals turns their guns against protesters]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/03/sudans-generals-turns-their-guns-against-protesters]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_map502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-03T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;WHERE JUST weeks ago the scent of freedom was in the air there is now the smell of smoke and cordite. The sounds of jubilant song have given way to those of automatic gunfire and the screams of the dying. In the early hours of June 3rd Sudan’s armed forces moved against pro-democracy protesters who had been holding a sit-in since April outside the army’s headquarters in Khartoum, the capital of Sudan. They shot and killed at least 13 civilians (and possibly many more). All that remains of the carnival of democracy that had sprouted there are burnt tents and rubbish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was the worst violence since demonstrations toppled Sudan’s brutal dictator, Omar al-Bashir, in early April. The Sudanese Professionals Association (SPA), which has spearheaded the uprising since it began last December, called it a “bloody massacre” and announced a campaign of “total civil disobedience” to topple the junta that took power in Mr Bashir’s place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trouble had been brewing for some weeks amid a fraught stand-off between protesters and the generals over who would control the country’s transition to democracy. Negotiators for both sides had agreed on some issues, such as the establishment of a civilian-led parliament and cabinet, and a three-year transition before elections. Such was the optimism that on May 15th leaders of the protest movement announced that they would have a deal signed with the generals within 24 hours. But this was premature because they had not reached agreement on the most contentious issue of all: who would be in charge of the sovereign council, the highest decision-making body that would oversee the move towards democracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On May 16th, less than 24 hours after the supposed breakthrough, the TMC’s leader, Abdel Fattah al-Burhan, halted the talks and accused the protesters of undermining them by blocking roads in the capital. He claimed “armed infiltrators” had fired on soldiers. The opposition responded on May 28th by declaring a two-day strike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the attack on June 3rd, trust between the two sides has all but evaporated. Protesters say that all the country’s previous transitions were led by the armed forces and that the generals are determined to control this one, too. People in the opposition accuse Muhammad Hamdan Dagalo (who is widely known as Hemedti), the powerful deputy head of the TMC, of foul play. They say that the paramilitary unit he heads, the Rapid Support Forces (RSF), carried out the lethal attack against the sit-in, as well as earlier killings of protesters. Observers, including some foreign diplomats, think that Mr Dagalo wants to become president and that he may undermine any transition that excludes him from power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But he is not the only one with an incentive to act as a spoiler. Mr Bashir kept himself in power for 30 years by playing armed factions against one another and by allowing them to earn illicit incomes. Many in the TMC may lose out if Sudan moves towards democracy and establishes the rule of law. Many of them also fear justice for atrocities committed by government forces and its militias during Sudan’s long civil wars in Darfur and what is now South Sudan. “This is a game with huge stakes,” says Harry Verhoeven, the author of a book on Sudan. “Why would those who have guns give them up voluntarily?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The latest violence means there is even less hope for compromise. On one side are the generals, who have won the support of powerful autocratic countries in the region including Egypt, Saudi Arabia and the United Arab Emirates. Emboldened, they are no longer bothering to disguise their reluctance to cede power to civilians. “The negotiations were never serious from the beginning,” says Rashid Abdi, an independent expert on Sudan based in Nairobi. “The army was just playing for time.” On the other side are the demonstrators, who are angry at the betrayal of their democratic revolution. “This is not going to stop,” says Reem Abbas, a Sudanese journalist in Khartoum. “The protests are going to continue.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 04:40:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Chernobyl” is on track to become the highest-rated TV series ever]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/03/chernobyl-is-on-track-to-become-the-highest-rated-tv-series-ever]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_woc177.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-03T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AT TWENTY-THREE minutes past one in the morning of April 26th 1986, a safety test at a nuclear reactor in Soviet Ukraine went catastrophically wrong. The resulting steam explosion at the plant near the city of Pripyat, 70 miles north of Kiev, spewed out so much radiation that much of the surrounding area will be uninhabitable for 20,000 years. Harmful isotopes were carried by the winds as far as Ireland within a week. According to some accounts, first responders who were exposed to large doses of radiation suffered agonising deaths. These events, as well as the political intrigue of the Soviet government’s actions, are the subject of HBO’s historical drama series, “Chernobyl”. With one episode to go (the finale will air in America on June 3rd) it is the highest-rated television series of all time, according to crowd-sourced reviews on IMDb, a film and television rating site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reviewers have given the first four episodes of “Chernobyl” stellar ratings. A weighted average calculated by &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; (according to how recently each episode ran and the number of reviews) accords it 9.6 points out of 10. By the same measure, other leading shows—including comparable historical drama series such as “The Crown” and “The People v. O. J. Simpson” (now called “American Crime Story”)—lag behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What is more, each episode of “Chernobyl” has been rated by users at 9.5 or higher, an impressive streak. According to &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s analysis of 517 episodes of popular television dramas, the likelihood that any show would produce four consecutive episodes that each score a 9.5 or above is roughly 0.4%. Apart from “Chernobyl”, only the final four episodes of “Breaking Bad”—previously the highest-rated show—have accomplished this feat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of this is even more impressive given its subject matter. Documentaries typically struggle to gain as much attention as action and fantasy shows such as “Game of Thrones”, and the same is true of historical dramas. Even series about well-known subjects, such as Queen Elizabeth II or the trial of O.J. Simpson, earn user ratings that are typically below those of the most popular shows. In comparison, “Chernobyl” scores better than the greats.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The show has also caused a massive spike in interest about the actual disaster. Web traffic to the entry for the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Chernobyl_disaster&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;Chernobyl nuclear disaster&lt;/a&gt; on Wikipedia, an online encyclopedia, has increased 56-fold since the start of the year. Interest in a comparable nuclear disaster at Japan’s Fukushima Daiichi power plant in 2011 has also increased, though by a more modest 21 times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The final episode of “Chernobyl” already has a preliminary rating of 10 out of 10 among IMDb’s apparently clairvoyant reviewers. Though the episode’s rating might fall below perfect after tonight’s airing, the show looks poised to be not only the most-liked historical drama series of all time, but also, as rated by IMDb reviewers, the best television series in history.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2019 00:41:05 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Liberty, democracy and the art of Martin Puryear]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/03/liberty-democracy-and-the-art-of-martin-puryear]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_BKP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-03T14:13:59Z&quot;&gt;Jun 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AT THE opening of the American pavilion at the Venice Biennale Lewis Eisenberg, America’s ambassador to Italy, stepped up to the microphone. He congratulated Martin Puryear and remarked that the title of his exhibition—“Liberty/ Libertà”— made him think of Ronald Reagan, who had often spoken of freedom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps he had yet to see the exhibition. The American president’s tenure was defined by the cold war and the crumbling of the Soviet Union; Mr Puryear’s focus for five decades has been black Americans’ historic struggle for human and civil rights. When chosen to represent the United States in Venice, he said he would do so “as both an artist and a citizen”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The son of a school teacher and a postal worker, Mr Puryear grew up in Washington, D.C., and his exceptional sculpting skills, most notably with wood, seem to date from his childhood. When he became interested in music, he made a guitar; later, an interest in archery inspired handmade bows and arrows. At university he switched from a degree in biology to one in art, specialising in painting. Later, as a member of the Peace Corp in Sierra Leone, watching African craftsmen at work encouraged him to return to 3D forms. But he studied print-making in Sweden before finally returning home in 1969 to study sculpture at Yale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He won acclaim with his first solo show at the Corcoran Gallery in D.C. in 1977, went on to take the grand prize at the São Paulo Biennial in 1989 and earned the National Medal of the Arts in 2012. In 2007 a retrospective of his work at the Museum of Modern Art in New York travelled to Washington, San Francisco and Fort Worth. But in recent years the 78-year-old African-American artist has probably become best known for “Big Bling”, an ambiguous monumental form topped with a gold-leaf shackle, installed in New York’s Madison Square Park in 2016. Here, as elsewhere, Mr Puryear imbues an abstract form with feeling and figurative references.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Ladder for Booker T. Washington”, made in 1996—a star piece of the touring retrospective and now on show at the Museum of Modern Art in Fort Worth—has a similar effect. An 11-metre ladder made of ash, it snakes tentatively upwards, so narrow at the top that its poles almost touch. The artist had set out to explore scale and perceptions of distance, but once the sculpture was finished it evoked for him “the gradual, often illusory, notion of progress that Washington [a civil-society leader] encouraged blacks to adopt in the 19th century against an overwhelming set of obstacles”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190615_bkp501.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Mr Puryear’s work an everyday object such as a ladder can remind the viewer, unexpectedly, of history. In Venice the neoclassical American pavilion comes with historical baggage of its own: built in 1930, the edifice was inspired by Monticello, the house Thomas Jefferson designed for himself in Virginia. Some artists choose to ignore the architecture, but Mr Puryear engages forcefully with it, creating a work specifically for its central rotunda. A two-metre-high white fluted column, with a shackled stake driven into its top, the piece (pictured above) is a memorial for Sally Hemings, an African-American slave owned by Jefferson. The country’s third president was also the father of her children.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In front of the pavilion Mr Puryear has placed a structure much like a rood screen, with lacy decorations that flow into a black hole at the top. Step around the back and you find that the piece, entitled “Swallowed Sun”, in fact has an ugly black tail. “Is it about the darkness of a solar eclipse—or a blackout when values are in jeopardy?” asked Brooke Kamin Rapaport, the curator of the pavilion, as the artist looked on, saying nothing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Inside the building another commonplace object—headgear—invites the viewer, on the one hand, to celebrate revolutionary struggle, and on the other to contemplate violence. “Big Phrygian”, a smooth red mound of painted cedarwood with a flipped-over peak, evokes the &lt;em&gt;bonnet rouge&lt;/em&gt; worn by revolutionaries in France and later by enslaved blacks in the Caribbean as they rose up against the French (the work might send the viewer trawling Wikipedia to find out more about Trajan’s war against the Dacians, and to grasp how the cap’s symbolism evolved). “Tabernacle” (pictured top), the show’s closer, is shaped like a forage cap worn by both Union and Confederate infantry during the American civil war. The visitor peers in through the hat’s crown to see themselves reflected in a mirrored cannonball nestling in the barrel of a mortar—thus becoming part of the artist’s meditation on gun violence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Puryear has produced one of the most subtle and powerful shows of the Venice Biennale. With eight expertly crafted works he demonstrates both his skill as a sculptor and the originality of his thinking. He once remarked that his work is “more tactile and sensate than strictly cerebral”, but to the onlooker the balance seems fairly even. What impresses is his fusion of the two.       &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The Venice Biennale continues until November 24th&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 21:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“She&#x27;s going to stick to her guns on Huawei. She&#x27;s got nothing to lose”—Theresa May and Donald Trump meet]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/03/shes-going-to-stick-to-her-guns-on-huawei-shes-got-nothing-to-lose-theresa-may-and-donald-trump-meet]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_opm501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-03T11:11:51Z&quot;&gt;Jun 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PRESIDENT DONALD Trump&lt;/strong&gt; kicks off his &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/02/donald-trumps-state-visit-to-britain&quot;&gt;state visit to Britain&lt;/a&gt; with some opening shots at London&amp;#x27;s mayor Sadiq Khan. But larger issues will take centre stage. Amid &lt;strong&gt;Brexit, a leadership contest and simmering security tensions, we discuss the strains on the “special relationship”.&lt;/strong&gt; We consider how regulators and tech giants can tackle the wilds of the internet to &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/25/how-to-make-social-media-safe-for-children&quot;&gt;make browsing safe for children&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. And, &lt;strong&gt;a Ramadan &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/05/30/a-saudi-tv-series-hints-at-the-change-that-is-afoot&quot;&gt;drama in Saudi Arabia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; reveals how the crown prince wants his kingdom to be perceived. Runtime: 22 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/getpompedup-trump-sbritishvisit&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jun 2019 18:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>