<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Steve Bannon’s monastic academy denies monkey business]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/22/steve-bannons-monastic-academy-denies-monkey-business]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_eup003.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-22T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A PLAN BY Steve Bannon, Donald Trump’s former chief strategist, to launch an alt-right academy in an Italian monastery now risks being scotched by the authorities. Evidence has emerged that a key document used to secure tenancy of the property was forged.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Bannon is paying the €100,000-a-year ($111,000) rent on a former Carthusian monastery, the Certosa di Trisulti, in the mountains east of Rome. The property belongs to the state. But in February 2018 Italy’s arts and heritage ministry granted a 19-year lease to a Catholic non-profit organisation then based in Rome, the Dignitatis Humanae Institute (DHI), of which Mr Bannon is a trustee. Two official bodies are investigating the concession: the Attorney General’s department and the regional auditors’ court in Lazio, the region around Rome in which the monastery is situated. An official says the ministry is not ruling out revoking the lease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Bannon has described the Academy for the Judaeo-Christian West that the institute plans to open at its monastery in the autumn as a “gladiator school for cultural warriors”. Benjamin Harnwell, the director of the DHI, says that his institute will offer a master’s course that includes teaching in philosophy, theology, history and economics. Mr Bannon will be personally responsible for additional tuition in the practical aspects of political leadership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The DHI took over the monastery following a competitive tender. Accompanying the institute’s bid was a business plan and a letter endorsing it, apparently provided by the Gibraltar branch of a Danish financial institution, Jyske Bank. But on May 7th &lt;em&gt;La Repubblica&lt;/em&gt;, an Italian daily, reported a statement by Jyske Bank declaring the letter to be fraudulent. The managing director of Jyske Bank in Gibraltar, Lars Jensen, confirms the statement. “It is a fraudulent letter, put together by I don’t know who,” he told &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; this week. The signature purported to be that of “a lady who hasn’t been in the bank for years. Her role was that of an assistant and in that letter she’s a director or something like that. So it is obviously fraudulent,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Harnwell admits that news of the bank’s statement “hit me sideways”. But Mr Bannon told The Economist that “Everything actually is totally legitimate…all of this stuff is just dust being kicked up by the left.” The business plan, however, was crucial to the success of DHI’s bid, which the ministry assessed using a points system. To qualify for the tender, the Institute needed at least 60 points. It secured 72.6. But of those, 17.8 were awarded for its business plan. So if that plan is ruled invalid because the “letter of certification” from its bank is found to have been forged, the authorities could revoke the lease.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The controversy over the DHI’s business plan is only the latest of several blows to the institute in recent months. Since December, the DHI’s chairman, Luca Volontè, a former Christian Democrat politician, has been on trial in Milan, charged with taking a €2.4m bribe from private and public sources in Azerbaijan. Mr Volontè was allegedly paid for helping to block criticism of human-rights abuses in Azerbaijan while a member of the parliamentary assembly of the Council of Europe. Mr Volontè denies any wrongdoing. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Harnwell founded the DHI in 2008 and won support from a variety of prominent Catholics. They included conservatives such as Austin Ruse, president of the Centre for Family and Human Rights in America, and liberals like Lord Alton, a British peer and former Liberal Democrat politician. But Mr Harnwell admits that, as Mr Bannon has taken an increasingly visible role, several of his liberal members and officials, including Lord Alton, have quit. The latest to go was a high-ranking Vatican prelate, Cardinal Peter Turkson.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Mr Harnwell readily agrees, the Institute’s stewardship of the Certosa, or Charterhouse, of Trisulti has brought with it daunting responsibilities. Founded in the early 13th century amid woodlands in a part of Italy renowned for its hermits and mystics, abbeys and convents, the complex covers 86,000 square metres—the size of 12 football pitches. It houses a watermill, a herbal pharmacy, an elaborately frescoed church and a topiary maze.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But many of its roofs are in urgent need of repair, and there is water infiltration in several places. The DHI committed itself in its bid to spend an additional €1.9m on restoration. Mr Bannon says that more than the row over the lease, the bigger concern “is making sure I can pull together all the resources needed to restore the monastery to what it should be”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The local authority has presented a further challenge by demanding €86,000 a year in property tax and for waste collection. Mr Bannon remains unfazed by all this. “I couldn’t be more excited,” he says. More excitement is probably to come.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 05:40:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Data to the rescue: how humanitarian organisations use information]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/22/data-to-the-rescue-how-humanitarian-organisations-use-information]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/aidworkers.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-22T18:50:42Z&quot;&gt;May 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN THIS SPECIAL edition of Babbage, host Kenneth Cukier examines &lt;strong&gt;how humanitarian organisations use data&lt;/strong&gt; and what they can learn from the profit-making tech industry. Access to the right &lt;strong&gt;data can be as valuable in humanitarian crises as water or medical care&lt;/strong&gt;, but it can also be dangerous. Misused or in the wrong hands, the same information can put already vulnerable people at further risk. This episode was recorded live from Wilton Park, in collaboration with the United Nations OCHA Humanitarian Data Centre. Runtime: 24 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistbabbage/babbage-datatotherescue&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 02:40:22 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Who owns the Northwest Passage?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/05/22/who-owns-the-northwest-passage]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_BLP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-22T15:56:08Z&quot;&gt;May 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;MIKE POMPEO, America’s secretary of state, raised Canadian hackles earlier this month when he said during a speech in Finland that Canada’s claim to the Northwest Passage was “illegitimate”. He was there to attend the Arctic Council, a body set up by the eight countries around the Arctic Ocean to resolve differences and disputes relating to the polar region. But if Canada does not own the Northwest Passage (see map), who does?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/economist-explains/20190525_wom998.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/economist-explains/20190525_wom998.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/economist-explains/20190525_wom998.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/economist-explains/20190525_wom998.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/economist-explains/20190525_wom998.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/economist-explains/20190525_wom998.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/economist-explains/20190525_wom998.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/economist-explains/20190525_wom998.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/economist-explains/20190525_wom998.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/economist-explains/20190525_wom998.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For centuries, finding a route between the 36,000 islands that form Canada’s Arctic archipelago was a dream for ambitious adventurers seeking to sail from the Atlantic to the Pacific. Sir John Franklin, a British naval officer, famously perished in 1847 seeking an ice-free passage (an illustration of the scene is pictured above). Roald Amundsen, a Norwegian explorer, completed the first successful crossing of the passage in 1906. Since then, global warming has reduced ice coverage in the late summer and early autumn by more than 30% since 1979, allowing more vessels to operate in the north. Only a few Arctic transits are made each year, mostly on the Russian side of the Arctic Ocean where there is less ice. In the Northwest Passage, 289 transits have taken place since 1906, 32 of them in 2017.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America has long maintained that the Northwest Passage, which has up to seven different routes, is an international strait through which its commercial and military vessels have the right to pass without seeking Canada’s permission. It bases its claim on the case of the Corfu Channel, separating Albania’s coast from the Greek island of Corfu, that was brought before the International Court of Justice in 1947. The court ruled that Albania could not claim the channel as territorial waters because it was an international route for ships between two parts of the high seas over which no country had a claim. Similar disputes exist about the Strait of Hormuz between Iran and Oman; the Bab al-Mandab strait between Yemen and Djibouti; and in parts of the South China Sea. Canada, which officially acquired the archipelago along with Britain’s remaining possessions in North America in 1880, claims sovereignty over the passage because all of its routes run between islands that are Canadian territory. But it has never sought to settle the question in court.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canada and the United States finessed their disagreement in 1988 with a political rather than legal fix, called the Canada-US Arctic Co-operation Agreement. America said it would seek Canada’s consent for any transit, but maintained that this did not mean it agreed with Canada’s position. Mr Pompeo’s recent comment suggests that, with the Arctic opening up to more shipping, America is no longer happy with the deal. Cargo ships can chop days if not weeks off certain journeys by using the Northwest Passage. In 2014 the Nunavik took 26 days to carry nickel from Quebec to China, compared with a previous trip through the Panama Canal lasting 41 days. But the dispute, like Arctic ice, could be transitory. Scientists now speculate that the entire Arctic Ocean will be ice-free in summer in the next few decades. That means ship owners will not have to ask anyone’s permission if they choose a route through the unclaimed high seas at the top of the world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 01:40:11 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bail out British Steel? Why not Jamie Oliver’s restaurants too?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/22/bail-out-british-steel-why-not-jamie-olivers-restaurants-too]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_brp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-22T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BRITAIN’S ONCE-GLEAMING steel industry has grown rusty. In 1970 the country was the world’s fourth-largest producer, behind only America, Japan and West Germany. Since then it has tumbled down the global rankings. Production has fallen by two-thirds. And it is about to get even lower: on May 22nd British Steel, the country’s second-largest producer, collapsed, after rescue talks between the government and the company’s owner broke down. Some 5,000 jobs in Scunthorpe and Teesside are at risk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many thought the government should have done more to save the venerable firm. The Labour Party argued that British Steel should be taken into public ownership. Even the right-wing &lt;em&gt;Daily Mail&lt;/em&gt; appeared sympathetic to the idea of a bail-out. It was odd, then, that there were no calls to save another employer that had gone bust only the day before. The collapse of a chain of 25 mainly Italian restaurants run by Jamie Oliver, a celebrity chef, has imperilled 1,000 jobs around the country. No one has called for the government to step in to save the chain. If helping steelmakers is a good idea, why not restaurateurs too?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The British government used to throw money at big firms whenever they wobbled. In 1971 it nationalised Rolls-Royce, an engine manufacturer. Three years later it bailed out British Leyland, a carmaker. From Margaret Thatcher on, governments took a lighter-touch approach, with the big exception of the crisis of 2008-09, when Gordon Brown spent £140bn ($182bn) bailing out the banks in an attempt to stop the financial system from collapsing. More recently the Tories have shown no mercy to big firms such as SSI, whose Redcar steelworks shut down in 2015, and Carillion, an outsourcer that went under last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;British Steel’s woes have led some to argue that Britain should rediscover interventionism. One argument put forward for a bail-out is that a thriving steel industry is the basis for a healthy manufacturing sector. Yet it is not clear why Britain needs to produce its own steel, since there is a healthy global market in the commodity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another is that the company’s collapse will affect its suppliers and customers, and drive up the welfare bill. IPPR, a think-tank, suggests that in addition to the jobs lost directly, a further 7,000 workers in the supply chain are in jeopardy. Yet it is hard to see why this should not apply to Mr Oliver’s restaurants, too. Laid-off waiters will claim welfare payments. Food suppliers will lose a big client. If these were sensible grounds for a bail-out, any failing company would be entitled to one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There may be no serious case for bailing out British Steel. There is a good case, however, for helping the workers affected by its closure. Mr Oliver’s unfortunate staff will probably find new jobs quickly. The chain’s outlets are mainly in bustling cities with plenty of other opportunities. Across the country, vacancies in hospitality are higher than in any other sector. The prospects for British Steel’s workers look much worse. They are concentrated in a small area (Scunthorpe’s population is around 80,000). The steelworks’ closure will whack the local economy, making it harder still to find new work. After the closure of its own steelworks, Redcar suffered a local depression. Employment slumped, particularly among men. Even today median wages remain lower than in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That calls for the state to supply extra education and training in areas affected by the closure of British Steel. The government’s preferred programme to do this, its “rapid response service”, has a tiny budget. It was deployed in Redcar, to no great effect. Nationalising British Steel is no more sensible an idea than taking over Mr Oliver’s Italian restaurants. But a large portion of help is needed for its workers, &lt;em&gt;subito&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 01:40:10 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Choosing Boris Johnson as prime minister would be a dangerous gamble]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/22/choosing-boris-johnson-as-prime-minister-would-be-a-dangerous-gamble]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_brd000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-22T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE CONSERVATIVE PARTY has a long history of making big bets on mavericks whenever it thinks that its back is against the wall. Before they won the party leadership, three of the greatest Tory prime ministers were cordially loathed by their party. Margaret Thatcher was regarded as a polarising ideologue who lacked the ability to connect with voters or command Parliament. Winston Churchill was a boozy bloviator and serial bungler, launching the Dardanelles campaign and clinging to the gold standard. Benjamin Disraeli was a flashy outsider who had no achievements to his name other than undermining Robert Peel over the Corn Laws. The Tories punted on all three and won big.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It looks as if the party is about to gamble again on Boris Johnson. The former foreign secretary is the overwhelming favourite among party members, who elect the leader. His only obstacle is persuading enough of his fellow Conservative MPs to put him on the shortlist of two. So far they have been sceptical. The charge sheet against Mr Johnson is a long one: a chaotic private life, a habit of bending facts, a lack of focus and discipline and being what Sir Max Hastings, a former editor of the Conservative house journal, the &lt;em&gt;Daily Telegraph&lt;/em&gt;, calls a “gold-plated egomaniac”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the party is in a full-blown panic. It is likely to come a poor fourth in this week’s European election, thanks to the rise of Nigel Farage’s Brexit Party and the implosion of Theresa May’s premiership. If the split on the right continues, it will put Labour’s far-left Jeremy Corbyn in Downing Street. What’s more, for all Mr Johnson’s faults he is a genuine political star, one of a handful of politicians who is known internationally by his first name (if not always for the right reasons). Because of his leading role in Brexit he no longer has the ability to reach out to the cosmopolitan liberals who gave him two terms as mayor of London. But he nevertheless has a rare ability to light up a room. Mrs May was a grand immiserator who made everybody around her feel rotten. Mr Johnson is a booming cheerleader who makes people feel good about themselves. Who better to reclaim wavering Tories from Mr Farage’s Brexit army? And who better to lead the charge against Mr Corbyn’s Leninist-Lennonist troops?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;More thoughtful Conservatives wonder if Mr Johnson might be the ideal vehicle for absorbing and civilising the populist furies that threaten to take the country to a dark place. The Tories have an admirable record of co-opting social movements that destroyed similar parties in other countries, such as the clamour for democracy in the late 19th century and the creation of a welfare state after the second world war. Mr Johnson may represent a chance to do the same with populism. He insists that Brexit is at its heart a liberal rather than a populist project, which will open Britain to the world rather than keeping it imprisoned in fortress Europe. He enthusiastically supports a credo issued by the newly formed One Nation Group of 60 moderate Tory MPs. So it is easy to see why Tories are contemplating taking a punt. Surely a flash of genius is better than mediocrity, even if it is part of a combustible mixture? And surely the fact that three big bets in the past paid off handsomely suggests that it is worth making another one?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The problem with this is that winning streaks eventually fail, and charismatic mavericks can produce disasters as well as triumphs. Before making their bet, Conservatives need to think hard about three big questions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First: can Mr Johnson really negotiate a better deal with the European Union than Mrs May? Mr Johnson blithely argues that the EU, in a sinister alliance with Remainers in the British establishment, has inflated problems such as the Irish border out of all proportion. He suggests that he will be able to renegotiate Britain’s exit deal with a combination of threat (keeping no-deal on the table) and charm. This is unlikely, not just because the EU heartily dislikes a man who made his journalistic career mocking their precious project, but also because it recognises that it can’t concede too much to Britain without threatening the integrity of the union. Making Mr Johnson prime minister significantly increases the chances of a no-deal Brexit that would severely disrupt the economy and alienate voters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second: can Mr Johnson run a government? The Conservatives will be electing not just a party leader but a sitting prime minister. The fate of a country of 66m people, in the middle of one of its most difficult passages since the second world war, will be determined by 124,000 party members. Mr Johnson’s record is not encouraging. He was a reasonably popular mayor but a dreadful foreign secretary. Although he is given to bumbling chaos, he does have a talent for delegation. A new girlfriend has helped to clean up his act: he has cut his hair, lost weight and taken up yoga. But Mr Johnson has never shown any sign that he is capable of dealing with the two things that define modern government: a relentless torrent of work and a demand to make complicated trade-offs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Third: can he hold the United Kingdom together? The link with Scotland is already looser than it has been for decades. There are very few Scots in the upper ranks of Britain’s two main parties. England and Scotland backed opposing sides in the Brexit referendum. A Prime Minister Johnson might snap the link entirely, with his air of Eton-Balliol-&lt;em&gt;Telegraph&lt;/em&gt; entitlement and his Bertie Woosterish mannerisms. Among Scottish voters he is even less popular than the hapless Mrs May.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;A roll of the dice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Perhaps Mr Johnson is exactly the lightning-in-a-bottle that the Conservative Party needs to restore its fortunes as both a campaigning machine and a governing force. But the price of getting things wrong would be extraordinarily steep. A no-deal Brexit, the break-up of the UK, a Marxist in Downing Street—it is a long time indeed since the stakes have been so high and the chances of getting it right so low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 01:40:09 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Republicans are struggling to fix America’s dysfunctional health-care system]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/22/republicans-are-struggling-to-fix-americas-dysfunctional-health-care-system]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_woc111.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-22T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“THE REPUBLICAN PARTY will soon be known as the party of health care—you watch,” President Donald Trump declared in March. “We’re coming up with plans.” Alas, like many of Mr Trump’s claims, this one proved untrue. Days later, following conversations with Mitch McConnell, the Republican Senate majority leader, Mr Trump admitted via tweet that his much-touted health-care proposal would in fact be delayed until at least 2021 after “Republicans hold the Senate &amp;amp; win back the House”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Republican reluctance to embrace health care, despite the president’s best efforts, is understandable. On the one hand, America’s health-care system is woefully dysfunctional: the country spends about twice as much on health care as other rich countries but has the highest infant-mortality rate and the lowest life expectancy (see chart). Some 30m people, including 6m non-citizens, remain uninsured. And yet, though costs remain a major concern—out-of-pocket spending on insurance continues to rise—Americans say they are generally satisfied with their own health care. Eight in ten rate the quality of their care as “good” or “excellent”. Few are in favour of dramatic reform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far the Trump administration has struggled to make headway. Mr Trump tried and ultimately failed to replace Obamacare, his predecessor’s signature health-care law. Since then, he has focused on proposals to rein in the cost of prescription drugs, including tying the prices of some medicines to those in other rich countries and requiring drug companies to disclose their list prices in television advertisements. This month, the president called on Congress to end “surprise” medical bills, the unexpected charges that patients often face after receiving treatment. Such measures, though welcome, are unlikely to make a dent in a system that gobbles up $3.5trn a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today Democrats in Congress will have their say when the House Budget Committee holds a hearing on single-payer health care. Such a system would expand access to medical care and bring down costs by allowing the federal government to negotiate directly with providers. Polls show that Americans like the idea in theory. In practice, however, many are unwilling to accept the necessary trade-offs, including longer waiting times, less access to pricey medical treatments and higher taxes. For proof consider the experiences of Colorado, California and Vermont, left-leaning states that have all tried to implement their own single-payer systems in recent years. All of them have failed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 01:40:08 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Online identification is getting more and more intrusive]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/05/22/online-identification-is-getting-more-and-more-intrusive]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190525_std004.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-22T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;MOST ONLINE fraud involves identity theft, which is why businesses that operate on the web have a keen interest in distinguishing impersonators from genuine customers. Passwords help. But many can be guessed or are jotted down imprudently. Newer phones, tablets, and laptop and desktop computers often have beefed-up security with fingerprint and facial recognition. But these can be spoofed. To overcome these shortcomings the next level of security is likely to identify people using things which are harder to copy, such as the way they walk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many online security services already use a system called device fingerprinting. This employs software to note things like the model type of a gadget employed by a particular user; its hardware configuration; its operating system; the apps which have been downloaded onto it; and other features, including sometimes the Wi-Fi networks it regularly connects through and devices like headsets it plugs into.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The results are sufficient to build a profile of both the device and its user’s habits. If something unusual is then spotted—say, access to a bank account being sought from a phone with a different profile from that which a customer usually uses—appropriate measures can be taken. For example, additional security questions can be posed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;LexisNexis Risk Solutions, an American analytics firm, has catalogued more than 4bn phones, tablets and other computers in this way for banks and other clients. Roughly 7% of them have been used for shenanigans of some sort. But device fingerprinting is becoming less useful. Apple, Google and other makers of equipment and operating systems have been steadily restricting the range of attributes that can be observed remotely. The reason for doing this is to limit the amount of personal information that could fall into unauthorised hands. But such restrictions also make it harder to distinguish illegitimate from legitimate users.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is why a new approach, behavioural biometrics, is gaining ground. It relies on the wealth of measurements made by today’s devices. These include data from accelerometers and gyroscopic sensors, that reveal how people hold their phones when using them, how they carry them and even the way they walk. Touchscreens, keyboards and mice can be monitored to show the distinctive ways in which someone’s fingers and hands move. Sensors can detect whether a phone has been set down on a hard surface such as a table or dropped lightly on a soft one such as a bed. If the hour is appropriate, this action could be used to assume when a user has retired for the night. These traits can then be used to determine whether someone attempting to make a transaction is likely to be the device’s habitual user.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Behavioural biometrics make it possible to identify an individual’s “unique motion fingerprint”, says John Whaley, head of UnifyID, a firm in Silicon Valley that is involved in the field. With the right software, data from a phone’s sensors can reveal details as personal as which part of someone’s foot strikes the pavement first, and how hard; the length of a walker’s stride; the number of strides per minute; and the swing and spring in the walker’s hips and step. It can also work out whether the phone in question is in a handbag, a pocket or held in a hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using these variables UnifyID sorts gaits into about 50,000 distinct types. When coupled with information about a user’s finger pressure and speed on the touchscreen, as well as a device’s regular places of use—as revealed by its GPS unit—that user’s identity can be pretty-well determined, Mr Whaley claims. UnifyID began offering behavioural biometrics to its clients (which include retail banks, online retailers, delivery companies and ride-sharing firms) in 2017. In time, advertisers will pay for the scoop on individuals’ lifestyle-revealing movements, reckons Mr Whaley, though his firm has no plans yet to expand in that direction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The lidless eye&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Behavioural biometrics can, moreover, go beyond verifying a user’s identity. It can also detect circumstances when it is likely that a fraud is being committed. On a device with a keyboard, for instance, a warning sign is when the typing takes on a staccato style, with a longer-than-usual finger “flight time” between keystrokes. This, according to Aleksander Kijek, head of product at Nethone, a firm in Warsaw that works out behavioural biometrics for companies that sell things online, is an indication that the device has been hijacked, and is under the remote control of a computer program rather than a human typist.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On a device with a touchscreen rather than a keyboard, however, the reverse is true. Most people type with their thumbs on touchscreens, so flight times between keystrokes are longer. In this case, therefore, it is short flight times which are a signal of something suspicious going on—for example, that a touchscreen device is actually being operated remotely, using the keyboard of a laptop.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Used wisely, behavioural biometrics could be a boon. As Neil Costigan, the boss of BehavioSec, a behavioural-biometrics firm in San Francisco, observes, the software can toil quietly in the background, continuously authenticating account-holders without badgering them for additional passwords, their mother’s maiden name “and all that nonsense”. UnifyID and an unnamed car company are even developing a system that unlocks the doors of a vehicle once the gait of the driver, as measured by his phone, is recognised.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Used unwisely, however, the system could become yet another electronic spy, permitting complete strangers to monitor your actions, from the moment you reach for your phone in the morning, to when you fling it on the floor at night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 23:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“He really has had his fingers burned”—Austrian scandal and Europe’s fringe parties]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/22/he-really-has-had-his-fingers-burned-austrian-scandal-and-europes-fringe-parties]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/austria.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-22T11:50:03Z&quot;&gt;May 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS A SCANDAL involving &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/18/scandal-fells-the-vice-chancellor-of-austria&quot;&gt;Austria&lt;/a&gt;’s hard-right Freedom party&lt;/strong&gt; causes the government to unravel, we examine the fringe parties of Europe and assess their chances in this week’s &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/briefing/2019/05/18/the-european-parliament-elections-are-responding-to-a-changed-world&quot;&gt;European elections&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. And as tech billionaires continue to indulge their obsessions with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/05/18/jeff-bezoss-ambition-to-colonise-space-is-straight-from-the-1970s&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;space travel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, we look at the sketchy economics of moving off-world. Also, a stark warning for lovers of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/15/americas-avocado-supply-is-set-to-tighten&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;avocados&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: supply concerns make them a volatile brunch choice. Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/ibizaremix-austriaandtheeuropeanfringe&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 20:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“FOOD: Bigger than the Plate” leaves you wanting more]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/22/food-bigger-than-the-plate-leaves-you-wanting-more]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190525_BKP508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-22T12:10:29Z&quot;&gt;May 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOOD IS more than a question of taste. The UN’s Food and Agriculture Organisation &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/briefing/2018/10/13/why-people-in-rich-countries-are-eating-more-vegan-food&quot;&gt;estimates that around 80% of agricultural land is devoted to rearing livestock&lt;/a&gt;, yet it yields only 18% of the world’s calories. Cattle are the fifth-largest producers of methane, a greenhouse gas which affects the climate. Were the world’s eaters to switch to vegetarianism, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2016/04/19/why-eating-more-vegetables-is-good-for-the-environment&quot;&gt;in 2050 agricultural emissions would be 29% lower&lt;/a&gt;—or 70% lower were people to opt for veganism. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new exhibition at the Victoria and Albert Museum (V&amp;amp;A) in London seeks to “pose questions about how the collective choices we make can lead to a more sustainable, just and delicious food future”. Entitled “FOOD: Bigger than the Plate”, it features more than 70 installations by artists, designers, scientists and chefs, divided into four sections: “Compost”, “Farming”, “Trading” and “Eating”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first part, “Compost”, examines how the invention of landfill rubbish-disposal and mains-drainage systems during the Industrial Revolution disrupted the food cycle. Where before people had been aware of the waste they and their food produced, returning its nutrients (and less beneficial byproducts) to the soil, a culture of “flush and forget” permanently changed attitudes towards waste. The projects featured in this section offer ways to restore the cycle—used coffee grounds from the V&amp;amp;A’s café make for nutritious soil beds, which grow mushrooms then used in café meals; an Italian dairy farmer turns the 150,000kg of manure produced every day by his 3,500 cows into a terracotta-like material for bricks, tiles and tableware. Though this is all interesting and innovative, the section rather resembles a sustainable design fair. One problem is being ignored: that of persuading people to consume less in the first place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190525_bkp507.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best parts of the show try to take on these questions of scale. In “Trading”—which focuses on the buying, selling and transporting of food—“Banana Story”, a design project by Johanna Seelemann, points out the vast amounts of international travel hidden in “made in” labels. Her “banana passport” tracks a single banana’s 14-day journey from a tree in Ecuador to a supermarket in Iceland, covering 8,800km and passing through 33 pairs of hands. It succeeds because it attaches bigger questions to a small item: if you had to give that passport a stamp of approval every time you bought a banana in the supermarket, would you still buy it? Would you feel comfortable eating a banana every day once you had seen the energy and human labour required to deliver it to you? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On to “Farming”, and “Our Daily Bread”, a 13-minute film by Nikolaus Geyrhalter and Wolfgang Widerhofer, looks at industrial food production and high-tech farming. Bulls bred to provide sperm for artificial insemination file past the camera, pumped with so much testosterone that their muscles unnaturally bulge like bodybuilders’. In a lettuce field at night, kneeling workers inch forward in silence, following the picking-machine’s basket like dogs behind a bone. The slick processes show how detached and clinical food production has become, which is almost as troubling as scenes of animal slaughter. “Our Daily Bread” is partly screened off—presumably because some viewers or young children might find certain scenes upsetting—but it is one of the few things in the exhibition that fulfils its claim to “question values” or “make us reconsider”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“FOOD: Bigger than the Plate” also features tasty morsels exploring more positive attitudes towards food. In the final section, “Eating”, the visitor is introduced to the Korean idea of &lt;em&gt;son-mat&lt;/em&gt; (literally, “the taste of one’s hands”), an expression which refers to the ineffable brilliance of your grandmother&amp;#x27;s cooking. A table is laid with examples of innovative tableware. There are coloured plates to make eating easier for those with dementia—food is more easily distinguishable on bright blue plates, and the colour apparently stimulates the appetite—and funny-shaped spoons which are said to heighten the sensitivity of the user&amp;#x27;s palate. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite these highlights, the exhibition lacks a clear thesis and invites only superficial engagement. Perhaps the curators are right to avoid an overwhelming sense of doom and gloom, but the show does not prompt the viewer to consider how attitudes towards eating—whether gluttonous and globalised or ascetic and local—affect the environment. The final exhibit is a “food lab”, where staff make a miniature canapé for each visitor based on a quiz about the future of food. Gimmicks such as this are skirting far more interesting questions: a tiny canapé is not going to encourage people to think big, or make big changes. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“FOOD: Bigger than the Plate” continues at the V&amp;amp;A in London until October 20th&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 19:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“He really has had his fingers burned”—Austrian scandal and Europe’s fringe parties]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/22/he-really-has-had-his-fingers-burned-austria-and-europes-fringe-parties]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/austria.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-22T11:50:03Z&quot;&gt;May 22nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AS A SCANDAL involving &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/18/scandal-fells-the-vice-chancellor-of-austria&quot;&gt;Austria&lt;/a&gt;’s hard-right Freedom party&lt;/strong&gt; causes the government to unravel, we examine the fringe parties of Europe and assess their chances in this week’s &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/briefing/2019/05/18/the-european-parliament-elections-are-responding-to-a-changed-world&quot;&gt;European elections&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;. And as tech billionaires continue to indulge their obsessions with &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/05/18/jeff-bezoss-ambition-to-colonise-space-is-straight-from-the-1970s&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;space travel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, we look at the sketchy economics of moving off-world. Also, a stark warning for lovers of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/15/americas-avocado-supply-is-set-to-tighten&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;avocados&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: supply concerns make them a volatile brunch choice. Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/ibizaremix-austriaandtheeuropeanfringe&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2019 19:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>