<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[A warlord’s offensive against Tripoli is flagging]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/07/03/a-warlords-offensive-against-tripoli-is-flagging]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_MAP001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-03T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN TRIPOLI, the capital of Libya, children play on the beach, cafés buzz late into the night and the head of a beauty parlour reports that laser treatments, hair-removals and nose-jobs are on the rise. “War hasn’t put off custom,” says Kherea Dughman. About 15km (9 miles) away a rebel army is fighting to take the capital. But after eight years of civil war, Libyans have become inured to the rumble of artillery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There have been several attempts to stabilise Libya since the overthrow in 2011 of Muammar Qaddafi, its former dictator. In 2016 the UN installed a “government of national accord” (GNA) in Tripoli. But it is beholden to the militias in the west that back it. Khalifa Haftar, the head of the self-styled Libyan National Army (LNA), controls the east and much of the south, including Libya’s largest oilfields.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Talks arranged by the UN to broker a peace between them in April were upended by Mr Haftar, who launched a surprise attack on the capital just after the UN secretary-general had arrived. Mr Haftar has little interest in negotiating a settlement. The 75-year-old former general thinks Libya is not yet ready for democracy and that it needs a strongman—himself. &lt;br/&gt;Mr Haftar returned from exile in America after Qaddafi’s fall and raised a force of perhaps 20,000 fighters. They would, his supporters repeatedly promised, clear the capital of the chaos of “terrorist militia” rule. His sneak-attack was intended to snatch Tripoli swiftly. But three months on Mr Haftar’s forces are being pushed back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Militias that had previously fought each other have rallied against Mr Haftar. On June 26th they captured Gharyan, cutting his supply line to the south (see map). That leaves his troops over 1,000km from their main base at al-Rajmah. Whereas the defenders of Tripoli can go home and shower at the end of a day of fighting, Mr Haftar’s troops are in the desert. The tribes backing him are reluctant to send more men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Haftar, though, has powerful friends. Saudi Arabia, Egypt and the United Arab Emirates (UAE) provide arms, fighter-jets and money to pay recruits. They see Mr Haftar as an ally in their counter-revolution against the popular, and often Islamist, uprisings the Arab spring unleashed in 2011. And they view Libya’s oil, territory and ports as strategic assets that they want to keep out of the hands of their regional foes, Turkey and Qatar. With their support, Mr Haftar hopes to battle on just as he did in Benghazi, Libya’s second city. He took it in 2017 after three years of fighting, but only by destroying and depopulating it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Turkey and Qatar, meanwhile, have sent weapons and armoured trucks to reinforce Tripoli’s defences. Both countries say they are buttressing the forces of democratic and popular change, as well as armed groups who share their Islamist ideology.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Foreign intervention risks turning a civil war into a regional one. In June Mr Haftar’s men threatened to strike all Turkish vessels in Libyan waters. It detained six Turkish sailors and released them only after Turkey threatened military action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The UN Security Council is too divided to restrain the parties. Libya’s former colonial rulers, France and Italy, have backed opposing sides, fuelled by their oil interests. (Total, a French company, has most of its fields in the east; Italy’s oil giant, Eni, is concentrated in the west.) Russia, which favours autocrats across the region, has thrown its support behind Mr Haftar. &lt;br/&gt;America, which could be an umpire, acts like a bystander. Since Barack Obama’s presidency it has opted “to lead from behind”. Donald Trump phoned to congratulate Mr Haftar—a naturalised American citizen—when it seemed his offensive would be successful. America, which had supported calls for a ceasefire in the UN, abruptly threatened to veto them. Since Mr Haftar’s offensive has failed Mr Trump’s interest seems to have waned in another of the Middle East’s “stupid wars”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite the conflict, the dinar has stabilised. Oil production is near its post-2011 peak of 1.1m barrels a day and at current prices could earn Libya $27bn this year. In the current fighting both camps are avoiding anything that might damage the oilfields because revenue from them pays the salaries of armed groups on each side.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Mr Haftar tries to regain the initiative, however, that could change. Although he controls most of the fields, a UN embargo on non-government sales prevents him from boosting his own coffers while shrinking those of the government. Previous efforts to sell oil independently were thwarted by America, but Mr Haftar is thought to be mulling trying again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He may also become more destructive. Since losing Gharyan he has stepped up his bombardment of Tripoli. Fighting has already destroyed the international airport. Now air strikes on Tripoli’s second airport threaten to put that out of use. Power lines and the pipes bringing water from underground reservoirs in the Sahara are also vulnerable to attack. Electricity is down to nine hours a day. Schoolchildren complain it is too hot to prepare for exams. More than 100,000 people have left the capital’s outlying suburbs for the city centre.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Most Tripolitanians want a government able to collect the rubbish and an end to the militias’ extortion, their pilfering of the central bank and turf wars in the capital. (“It’s like taming wildcats in a circus,” is how a government official describes governing Tripoli.) Some may have once welcomed the order that Mr Haftar promised to restore. But his bombardment has punctured such hopes. His flamboyant uniforms, his nepotistic promotion of his sons and backing from the former regime’s henchmen stir fears of a second Qaddafi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile the horror goes on. Field hospitals and ambulances ferrying the wounded have come under attack. A nurse camped in a school with her children after the shelling destroyed her home begs for relief. “Why don’t they both just go away,” she sobs. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 23:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The supernatural appeal of “Stranger Things”]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/07/03/the-supernatural-appeal-of-stranger-things]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BKP506_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-03T14:08:45Z&quot;&gt;Jul 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE RELEASE of the new season of “Stranger Things” gives non-Americans a reason to celebrate July 4th this year. It is probably the most popular show on Netflix—at least according to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.parrotanalytics.com/press/stranger-things-returns-to-top-of-parrot-analytics-digital-originals-chart-pushing-past-black-mirror/&quot;&gt;Parrot Analytics, a television consultancy&lt;/a&gt; (the streaming site itself does not publish viewer numbers). Many fans will devour all eight episodes in one indulgent sitting by the time the weekend comes around. In 2017 Nielsen, a market-research company, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://variety.com/2017/tv/news/stranger-things-season-2-ratings-nielsen-1202605585/&quot;&gt;reported that 361,000 people&lt;/a&gt; watched the entirety of the second season within the first 24 hours of its release. Tickets for a forthcoming immersive “Stranger Things” experience in London, starting at £49 ($60), quickly sold out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What explains the show’s popularity? It is a mash-up of science-fiction, horror, comedy and adventure, set in the 1980s in the fictional town of Hawkins, Indiana. An intrepid band of nerdy kids suddenly find themselves in a real-life version of “Dungeons and Dragons”, a fantasy tabletop role-playing game. They battle monsters from a parallel universe, the “Upside Down”, which was accessed in a shady government facility. Most of the town’s adults are initially oblivious of the danger but the children are aided by Hopper, the kindly local sheriff (David Harbour), and Joyce (Winona Ryder), one of the boys’ mothers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The series draws heavily on the novels of Stephen King (such as “It” and “Firestarter”), the early films of Steven Spielberg (“ET” in particular) as well as cold-war classics such as “Red Dawn”. It is scary, but not too scary—unsuitable for five-year-olds but something most children aged ten or older can cope with. The gore and death is leavened by humour and well-observed family dynamics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2015, when the Duffer brothers began pitching their series, many networks reckoned that a main cast of children would not appeal to a wide audience. In fact, the youngsters are the show’s strength. Carmen Cuba, the casting director, has chosen an exceptional set of child actors, each with their own distinct personality, and they bicker and giggle in a believable manner. The stand out is Mille Bobby Brown, who plays Eleven, a young girl with telekinetic powers. There is also a group of young adults in the form of Nancy (Natalia Dyer), her boyfriend Jonathan (Charlie Heaton) and former beau, Steve (Joe Kerry). &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If those characters draw in the teenage audience, adults are attracted by the air of 1980s nostalgia, helped by the casting of Ms Ryder, Matthew Modine (as the sinister Dr Martin Brenner) and in the coming series, Cary Elwes, star of “The Princess Bride”. Both Ms Ryder and Mr Harbour are given interesting back stories and there is the tantalising will-they-won’t-they possibility of romance between the pair.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, the third season faces a number of challenges. The show has to stay true to the format that made the previous episodes such a success—an episode in season two, where Eleven leaves Hawkins for Chicago, was loathed by fans and critics alike—but avoid feeling tired or repeating itself. The monsters have already been defeated twice, after all. The younger actors are also now 16-17 years old and need storylines to reflect that. But the Duffer Brothers have showed enormous flair so far; Netflix will be confident they can pull off the same trick again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Stranger Things 3” is available on Netflix from July 4th&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 21:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Economic expansions don&#x27;t die of old age”—America’s decade of growth]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/07/03/economic-expansions-dont-die-of-old-age-americas-decade-of-growth]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_blm505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-03T12:13:16Z&quot;&gt;Jul 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 19:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump rebrands Independence Day]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/07/02/donald-trump-rebrands-independence-day]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_blp907.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-02T21:32:43Z&quot;&gt;Jul 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;INDEPENDENCE DAY, which commemorates America serving notice to Britain in 1776, has for decades been scrupulously non-political. Presidents have tended to stay home and host celebrations at the White House or to visit festivities around the country. They have not appeared on the National Mall, the iconic two-mile strip of grass that runs from the Lincoln Memorial to the Capitol, and they have not made prime-time televised speeches. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump is playing it differently this year. In a major break with tradition, he is putting himself at the centre of the action on July 4th, having promised on Twitter, “an address by your favourite President, me!” He will begin with a speech from the steps of the Lincoln Memorial. Before him, a large section of the Mall will have been cordoned off for spectators with tickets, handed out by the White House. Mr Trump’s address will kick off a “Salute to America” event that will be strongly militaristic in tone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The president has promised “planes going overhead, the best fighter jets in the world and other planes too, and we’re going to have some tanks stationed outside.” (He had said there would be “brand new Sherman tanks” but they haven’t been in service since the 1950s.) Mr Trump has reportedly asked that the chiefs of the army, air force and marines stand beside him as aircraft fly overhead. He has also promised the “biggest ever Fireworks!” The 35-minute pyrotechnics will go on twice as long as the usual July 4th display on the Mall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump’s aides say the event is designed to be patriotic rather than political. But for the president to commandeer what has traditionally been a non-partisan event has naturally sparked concerns that he is turning July 4th into a campaign event. He has already broken with presidential norms by using official visits to military bases to lay into the Democrats. Steny Hoyer, the Democratic House Majority leader, accused Mr Trump of turning July 4th into a “political rally”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The plans have also attracted local criticism—perhaps unsurprisingly in a strongly Democratic city. “We have said it before and we’ll say it again”, joked DC’s city council on its official Twitter page. “Tanks, but no tanks”. It appended a snapshot of a memo from the office of the secretary of defence with the words “include wheeled vehicles only, no tanks” highlighted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was a reference to another, related concern, that Mr Trump is turning a celebration that is primarily about democracy, freedom and the citizens who enjoy those things, into a celebration of the military. Tributes to the armed forces and to veterans, especially in smaller military parades, are common on July 4th. But they are not the dominant theme of such festivities. America already celebrates Veterans Day and Armed Forces Day; Mr Trump seems to be suggesting that another such event is necessary and July 4th should be it. “The Pentagon &amp;amp; our great Military Leaders are thrilled to be doing this &amp;amp; showing to the American people, among other things, the strongest and most advanced Military anywhere in the World,” he tweeted on July 2nd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump had originally wanted to hold a bigger military parade, perhaps on Veterans Day, but that was shelved over concerns it would cost too much and that heavy military equipment would damage the capital’s roads. He was inspired by a Bastille Day celebration in Paris that he attended in 2017. &amp;quot;We’re gonna have to try and top it,” he said back then, “but we had a lot of planes going over and a lot of military might, and it was really a beautiful thing to see.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 19:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A new round of violence in Mali]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/07/03/a-new-round-of-violence-in-mali]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BLP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-03T09:41:17Z&quot;&gt;Jul 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SEVEN YEARS ago separatists from the Tuareg ethnic group and jihadists allied to al-Qaeda took over most of the sparsely populated north of Mali. France sent more than 4,000 troops to stop the rebels’ southwards advance on the capital of their former colony, Bamako, and drove them out of the larger cities. The UN has about 15,000 soldiers and police in the country at present, one of its biggest peacekeeping forces in the world. But the jihadist groups, who are sweeping across much of the Sahel, have reformed, rearmed and recruited new fighters. A new cycle of violence has begun. Among the UN alone, 200 personnel have been killed, making it the most deadly such mission since its start in 2013.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government of Mali, a country of about 18m people, has shown little interest in re-establishing control in the north or providing social services there. It tends to focus on the country’s gold-rich south-west. This has allowed drug traffickers, militiamen and jihadists—often the lines between them are blurred—to flourish in the populous central regions. The insecurity has spilled over the country’s long borders and destabilised other weak states including Niger and Burkina Faso, which are now also battling jihadist insurgencies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent violence in Mali has an element of inter-ethnic rivalry that did not previously figure so strongly. The country’s most powerful jihadist group, Jama’at Nasr al-Islam wal Muslimin, has concentrated recruitment efforts on the Fulani ethnic group, many of whom are impoverished, disenfranchised, semi-nomadic herders. Fulani relations with two primarily farming-focused groups in central Mali, the Dogon and the Bambara, are becoming increasingly strained. In the past two years Dogon and Bambara militiamen, claiming to be anti-jihadist, have massacred hundreds of Fulani men, women and children. In response, Fulani groups have armed and now carry out their own killing sprees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The litany of killings is horrendous. In March Dogon militiamen butchered more than 170 people in Ogossagou, a Fulani village in central Mali. The outcry forced the government to resign. In June dozens of gunmen suspected to be from a Fulani “self-defence group” killed 35 people at a Dogon village. (The local mayor claimed the number was almost 100.) And a week later another 41 people were reportedly massacred in two more Dogon villages. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The murders are part of a cycle of tit-for-tat attacks that are also often linked to conflicts about land or theft of cattle. The government has done little to resolve them. Some soldiers have even given Dogon and Bambara militiamen official passes to get through checkpoints, and been on patrols with them. The resulting sense of impunity has had tragic consequences. In seven years more than 1,800 people have died. Mali’s army has proved woefully inadequate for re-establishing governance. Its support for the Dogon and Bambara militias has backfired spectacularly and fuelled the conflict. This year intercommunal violence overtook jihadist violence as the leading cause of violent death in Mali, according to the Armed Conflict Location &amp;amp; Event Data Project, an NGO. To make any sort of progress the new Malian government needs to do more to provide security to all communities, while also encouraging dialogue between militia leaders and helping to settle disputes over land and cattle that fuel some of the violence. Without that, there seems little reason to hope that the bloodshed will end.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 18:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump rebrands Independence Day]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/07/03/donald-trump-rebrands-independence-day]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_blp907.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-03T01:32:43Z&quot;&gt;Jul 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;INDEPENDENCE DAY, which commemorates America serving notice to Britain in 1776, has for decades been scrupulously non-political. Presidents have tended to stay home and host celebrations at the White House or to visit festivities around the country. They have not appeared on the National Mall, the iconic two-mile strip of grass that runs from the Lincoln Memorial to the Capitol, and they have not made prime-time televised speeches. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Donald Trump is playing it differently this year. In a major break with tradition, he is putting himself at the centre of the action on July 4th, having promised on Twitter, “an address by your favourite President, me!” He will begin with a speech from the steps of the Lincoln Memorial. Before him, a large section of the Mall will have been cordoned off for spectators with tickets, handed out by the White House. Mr Trump’s address will kick off a “Salute to America” event that will be strongly militaristic in tone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The president has promised “planes going overhead, the best fighter jets in the world and other planes too, and we’re going to have some tanks stationed outside.” (He had said there would be “brand new Sherman tanks” but they haven’t been in service since the 1950s.) Mr Trump has reportedly asked that the chiefs of the army, air force and marines stand beside him as aircraft fly overhead. He has also promised the “biggest ever Fireworks!” The 35-minute pyrotechnics will go on twice as long as the usual July 4th display on the Mall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump’s aides say the event is designed to be patriotic rather than political. But for the president to commandeer what has traditionally been a non-partisan event has naturally sparked concerns that he is turning July 4th into a campaign event. He has already broken with presidential norms by using official visits to military bases to lay into the Democrats. Steny Hoyer, the Democratic House Majority leader, accused Mr Trump of turning July 4th into a “political rally”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The plans have also attracted local criticism—perhaps unsurprisingly in a strongly Democratic city. “We have said it before and we’ll say it again”, joked DC&amp;#x27;s city council on its official Twitter page. “Tanks, but no tanks”. It appended a snapshot of a memo from the office of the secretary of defence with the words “include wheeled vehicles only, no tanks” highlighted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was a reference to another, related concern, that Mr Trump is turning a celebration that is primarily about democracy, freedom and the citizens who enjoy those things, into a celebration of the military. Tributes to the armed forces and to veterans, especially in smaller military parades, are common on July 4th. But they are not the dominant theme of such festivities. America already celebrates Veterans Day and Armed Forces Day; Mr Trump seems to be suggesting that another such event is necessary and July 4th should be it. “The Pentagon &amp;amp; our great Military Leaders are thrilled to be doing this &amp;amp; showing to the American people, among other things, the strongest and most advanced Military anywhere in the World,” he tweeted on July 2nd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump had originally wanted to hold a bigger military parade, perhaps on Veterans Day, but that was shelved over concerns it would cost too much and that heavy military equipment would damage the capital’s roads. He was inspired by a Bastille Day celebration in Paris that he attended in 2017. &amp;quot;We’re gonna have to try and top it,” he said back then, “but we had a lot of planes going over and a lot of military might, and it was really a beautiful thing to see.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 12:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[EU leaders settle on a new team to run the club]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/charlemagnes-notebook/2019/07/02/eu-leaders-settle-on-a-new-team-to-run-the-club]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BLP510.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-02T21:36:35Z&quot;&gt;Jul 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;URSULA von der Leyen will be the new president of the European Commission and Christine Lagarde will be the new president of the European Central Bank (ECB). That, at least, is the proposal of the EU’s heads of government, who met in Brussels today for an unexpected third day of talks on the allocation of the EU’s top jobs. The European Council, which comprises the heads of government of the 28 member states, initially gathered on Sunday evening. They negotiated through the night and into yesterday morning, at which point Donald Tusk, the council president, extended proceedings to give leaders a chance to sleep and regroup. Today a deal was reached.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Angela Merkel and Emmanuel Macron, Europe’s two most powerful leaders, had initially put forward a package that would have seen Frans Timmermans, a Dutch social democrat, lead the commission. Mr Timmermans was a so-called “Spitzenkandidat” or lead candidate. In other words, his political family had designated him its candidate for the commission job ahead of the European election which took place from May 23rd to May 26th. In some eyes, the Spitzenkandidaten of the various parties had a mandate from the voters (evidence suggest few voters knew who any of them were and even fewer voted to give them a mandate). But Mr Timmermans proved a difficult choice. Leaders of the European People’s Party (EPP), the centre-right group of parties that includes Mrs Merkel’s Christian Democratic Union (CDU) in Germany, objected to the allocation of the powerful commission job to a social democrat. Central Europeans dislike Mr Timmermans for his record of taking on governments like that of Poland for their illiberal excesses.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having failed to agree on a package of appointments with a Timmermans-led commission at its core, today leaders cast their gaze elsewhere. Mr Macron suggested Ms von der Leyen, the German defence minister. A moderate in the CDU, she belongs to the EPP. She is acceptable to the central Europeans, having increased Germany’s military commitment to the defence of NATO’s eastern borders. She was a capable families minister and has pushed to modernise Germany’s armed forces (with patchy results). So she made a broadly acceptable candidate to lead the EU’s executive. With that role settled, the other big jobs fell into place. Mr Macron got a French president of the ECB in Ms Lagarde, who currently leads the IMF. Liberals, who gained seats in the European election and had hoped to clinch the commission, get the presidency of the European Council in the form of Charles Michel, Belgium’s prime minister. Social democrats get Josep Borrell, Spain’s foreign minister, in the role of EU high representative for foreign and security policy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The package is not perfect, but nor is it terrible. Ms von der Leyen, though not dazzlingly charismatic, is a mature and moderate administrator who speaks fluent English. Mr Borrell will be the most heavyweight figure to serve as high representative since the job’s creation in 2009. Mr Michel is a decent deal-broker (you have to be, in Belgium&amp;#x27;s messy politics). And Ms Lagarde is a capable communicator who has said sensible things about the euro-zone, avoiding the ideological hawkishness of her German counterparts. Overall the deal is a win for Mr Macron, who may have killed off the Spitzenkandidat system (which he dislikes) while getting friendly faces into both the commission and the ECB. But all is not yet settled. Ms von der Leyen must be approved by the European Parliament. She will probably clear this hurdle, but European politics is fragmented and unpredictable these days. If she is rejected, the whole package will fall apart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 06:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cori Gauff announces herself at Wimbledon]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/07/02/cori-gauff-announces-herself-at-wimbledon]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_BLP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-02T19:23:11Z&quot;&gt;Jul 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT IS hard to avoid the impression that the tennis world has witnessed a changing of the guard. On July 1st , the opening day of the 2019 Championships at Wimbledon, Cori Gauff, a 15-year-old American prospect, upset the five-times champion Venus Williams in straight sets. Ms Williams, aged 39, was not the highest-ranked player to fall on the first day of the tournament; that honour belonged to the reigning US Open champion, Naomi Osaka, the second seed. But no first-round winner has garnered more attention than Ms Gauff, whose youth causes her to establish new records every time she steps on court. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She is so young that Ms Williams had collected her first two Wimbledon trophies before Ms Gauff was born. The teenager was the youngest ever to gain a place in the draw via qualifying, winning three matches without dropping a set in order to do so. Ranked only 313th among women players (to Ms Williams’ 44th), Ms Gauff is only the 8th woman this century to win a grand-slam match before her 16th birthday, and the youngest since Anna Kournikova carved her way through three rounds at the 1996 US Open. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Kournikova, however, serves as a reminder that not all teenage sensations become superstars. Of the last seven women to win a grand-slam match at 15, none have advanced past the semi-final of a major tournament, or ascended above 7th in the Women’s Tennis Association (WTA) rankings. (Two of them, 20-year-old Catherine Bellis and 17-year-old Marta Kostyuk, may still do so). Thus although Ms Gauff is unquestionably the best 15-year-old tennis player right now, years’ worth of obstacles lie in her path to greatness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So far, she has held her own against much more experienced competition. On court, there is little to distinguish Ms Gauff from her elders. She stands 1.78m tall, and serves as powerfully as Ms Williams—herself one of the most effective servers in the game’s history. Her average first serve on July 1st was clocked at 107 miles per hour (172 km/h), slightly faster than her opponent’s deliveries. Her typical second serve proved more effective than Ms Williams’s comparably cautious offerings. She possesses strong groundstrokes on both the forehand and backside sides, cracking winners with 8% of her shots, in line with the tour average.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although it is tougher to judge a player’s mental assets after a handful of professional matches, early signs suggest that Ms Gauff is unusually mature for her age. Her match against Ms Williams took place on the biggest stage of her career, against a legendary opponent. “I have never played on a court so big, but I had to remind myself that the lines on the court are the same size,” she later declared. Nevertheless, she seemed unperturbed by the sorts of hiccups that often derail young players. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the final set, she had to overcome two particularly severe hiccups. After double-faulting on the fifth and sixth points of her first service game, she immediately bounced back, winning two points with a protracted rally and a strong first serve, to secure the game. In the eighth game of the set, she double-faulted twice more, surrendering a one-break advantage and falling to 4-4 in the second set. But again, she held her nerve and regained the break in the following game.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The immediate challenge facing Ms Gauff is to sustain her level of play. In the second round, she will face Magdalena Rybarikova, an unseeded Slovakian known for her grass-court prowess. If Ms Gauff advances further, her likely third-round opponent will be the 17th seed, Madison Keys, a one-time prodigy who recorded her first US Open win in 2011 as a 16-year-old. The big-hitting Ms Keys will force Ms Gauff to confront an opponent much like herself, only stronger and even more powerful. Ms Williams was one of the most accomplished competitors in the draw, but the unheralded Ms Rybarikova may prove an even stiffer test.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For Ms Gauff, this week’s array of opponents is only the beginning. The tennis season spans ten months of the year and demands stamina on a different scale than is required to win a few matches. Many youngsters with the talent to score upsets are unable to translate early success into a noteworthy career. Ms Gauff won the Roland Garros girls’ singles title in Paris last year, an early indicator of future stardom. Yet of the other 17 women who have won a junior singles title since the 2014 US Open, only one—a 17-year-old American, Amanda Anisimova—has won a tour-level title. Indeed, the balance of power in the modern game has shifted to veterans such as the 31-year-old Wimbledon defending champion, Angelique Kerber, who did not win her first match at the All England Club until she was 22. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is far too early, then, to designate Ms Gauff as the successor to Ms Williams, let alone her even more accomplished sister, Serena. But that does not make the teenager’s exploits any less impressive. It is rare to see a player so dramatically announce her presence on the sport’s biggest stage. If she manages to negotiate the difficult route to the top of the game, fans can look back on July 1st’s upset as a clear starting point from which her ascent began.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 04:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Brexit and the city]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/07/02/brexit-and-the-city]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/moneytalks_brexit_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-02T18:00:56Z&quot;&gt;Jul 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LONDON&lt;/strong&gt; IS home to the world’s biggest international financial centre. But &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/27/can-the-city-survive-brexit&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Brexit threatens to cut the City off from its most important single foreign market.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; Tamzin Booth, The Economist’s Britain business editor, investigates whether the City of London can survive Brexit and how &lt;strong&gt;other cities across Europe, like Frankfurt, are vying to win their rival’s&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/29/londons-reign-as-the-worlds-capital-of-capital-is-at-risk&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;business.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; What is at stake on both sides of the Channel, and are there any winners in this battle? Runtime: 22 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-brexitandthecity&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id420929545?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/2Yvo8QxZf7WlSEsIwKjtX4&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWVjb25vbWlzdG1vbmV5dGFsa3M&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=18377&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/Business--Economics-Podcasts/The-Economist-Money-Talks-p603831/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 04:40:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America’s economic expansion is now the longest on record]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/07/02/americas-economic-expansion-is-now-the-longest-on-record]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190706_WOC339_0.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-07-02T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jul 2nd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I DON’T THINK that expansions just die of old age,” Janet Yellen, a former chairwoman of the Federal Reserve, told economists at a conference in Atlanta on January 4th. That theory may soon be put to the test. As of today, the economic expansion that began in America in June 2009 has continued, uninterrupted, for more than 120 months (3,654 days to be exact), making it the longest in history. The previous record, according to the National Bureau of Economic Research (NBER), America’s official arbiter of recessions, was the ten-year boom that took place between 1991 and 2001.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The business cycle has been getting longer for some time. Between 1945 and 1981, American economic expansions lasted for three years and eight months, on average. Since then they have stretched on for more than eight years. But as they have grown lengthier, they have become weaker, too. During the ten business cycles recorded between 1949 and 2007, the economy grew by an annual rate of 4.7% a year, on average. Since 2009, though, growth has averaged just 2.3%. What is more, GDP per person, a measure of economic growth that strips out the effects of a growing population, has inched up by just 1.5% a year. Across the previous ten cycles, it grew by an average of 3.3% a year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are signs the party may be coming to an end. Investment bears point to an inverted yield curve (when yields on long-term bonds fell below those on short-term ones), historically an accurate harbinger of recessions. Trade wars could also trigger a downturn. Yet professional forecasters surveyed by the Federal Reserve Bank of Philadelphia reckon that there is just a one-in-five chance that a recession will hit next year. They still expect America’s economy to be growing by 1.7% 12 months from now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, recessions are hard to predict; that is what makes them so disruptive. “As Janet says, expansions don’t die of old age,” Ben Bernanke told conference-goers in January, agreeing with his successor at the Fed. “I like to say they get murdered instead.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jul 2019 04:40:11 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>