<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s war on oversight]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/08/donald-trumps-war-on-oversight]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_usp001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-08T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 8th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JAMES WILSON, who signed the Declaration of Independence and assumed one of the Supreme Court’s first six seats, believed that “the house of representatives [shall] form the grand inquest of the state. They shall diligently inquire into grievances”. More than a century later, Woodrow Wilson, then a young scholar of American government, wrote that for a legislature, “vigilant oversight” is “quite as important as legislation.” Multiple Supreme Court decisions have similarly affirmed that Congress enjoys vast investigative and oversight powers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sometimes partisanship influences those powers. A Democrat-dominated Congress investigated Richard Nixon, a Republican. During the Clinton administration, the Republican-led House held hearings on the Clintons’ Christmas-card list, and issued more than 1,000 subpoenas. Presidents may have fought specific requests, but none have done what Donald Trump has: declare “we’re fighting all the subpoenas,” sue to block them and instruct officials to ignore them. He seems to feel that partisanship renders oversight illegitimate. American history, jurisprudence and norms do not share that view. If it prevails, it risks dramatically removing constraints on future presidents’ power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, Congressional oversight power is not limitless. In 1954, the House Un-American Activities Committee convicted John Watkins, a labour-union organiser, of contempt of Congress for refusing to testify about people who had left the Communist Party (he was candid about his own past). The Supreme Court sided with Watkins, holding that Congress cannot “expose the private affairs of individuals without justification,” and that “no inquiry is an end in itself; it must be related to, and in furtherance of, a legitimate task of Congress.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steven Mnuchin, the treasury secretary, hinted at this exception when, on May 6th, he declined to release six years of Mr Trump’s personal tax returns, as well as those from several of his businesses, to Richard Neal, who chairs the House Ways and Means Committee. A law passed in 1924 states that the head of America’s Internal Revenue Service (IRS) “shall furnish…any return or return information” to the House Ways and Means Committee specified by written request.” Mr Neal did just that, but Mr Mnuchin wrote that he “determined that the Committee’s request lacks a legitimate legislative purpose.”&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Mr Neal said that his committee must determine whether the IRS has properly audited Mr Trump. Some may find that justification thin, but the Supreme Court ruled that congressional investigations enjoy a presumption of legitimacy, and courts are reluctant to intervene based on legislative motives. A recent report from the nonpartisan Congressional Research Service noted the privacy concerns inherent to releasing Mr Trump’s tax returns (they will almost certainly leak), but those are counterbalanced by what the Supreme Court has called the “indispensable ‘informing function of Congress’”. A federal court may soon adjudicate this dispute.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They are adjudicating others, too. On April 29th, Mr Trump, along with three of his children and several of his business entities, sued Deutsche Bank and Capital One to stop their compliance with “Congressional subpoenas that have no legitimate or lawful purpose.” That came a week after Mr Trump and several of his businesses sued Elijah Cummings, who chairs the House Oversight Committee, to block Mazars, an accounting firm, from complying with Mr Cummings’s subpoena for records. Mr Trump argues that these subpoenas “have no legitimate or lawful purpose,” and “were issued to harass” him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many presidents feel that way. Partisan and interbranch competition are both inherent to America’s political system. Presidents have the right to keep some things secret, just as Congress has the right to investigate; those rights often conflict. But Mr Trump’s response—a wholesale rejection of Congress’s oversight power—is unprecedented. As Margaret Taylor, a fellow in Governance Studies at the Brookings Institution, notes, “There is a long tradition of back-and-forth between the legislative and executive branches...especially when the parties are different...What’s different here is the full frontal stiff-arm of the House’s oversight efforts.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That makes reaching an accommodation impossible. As one former counsel to a Republican president explained, “It’s not uncommon for a president to say, ‘No way no how am I going to share that information with Congress—they just want to hurt me. Often from that point you can manouevre to a point of agreement. [But] it takes effort and willingness to compromise…[and] the current situation doesn’t seem to have any of the hallmarks of compromise.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nor is this battle only taking place in the courts. On May 7th the White House blocked Don McGahn, a former White House counsel, from surrendering documents subpoenaed by the House Judiciary Committee because of possible executive-privilege concerns. Mr McGahn complied, but as a former rather than current White House official, his compliance was voluntary rather than compulsory. One day later, the White House also claimed executive privilege over the unredacted version of Robert Mueller’s report, and the House Judiciary Committee recommended finding William Barr, the attorney-general, in contempt of Congress for failing to deliver it in response to a subpoena. Also on May 8th, the Republican-led Senate Intelligence Committee subpoenaed Donald Trump junior to answer questions about his prior testimony.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is unclear whether Mr Trump’s executive-privilege claims will survive court challenges. Much of Mr Mueller’s report concerns actions taken before Mr Trump became president, which executive privilege cannot shield. The White House cited no justification for shielding the full Mueller Report other than calling its action “protective,” which implies that the president can withhold any information for any reason. Courts have not endorsed that view. Judges rejected both George W Bush’s claim that executive privilege blocks aides from appearing before Congress (though it may prevent them from answering specific questions) and Barack Obama’s over information that had already been revealed—a ruling that may apply to Mr McGahn, who spoke extensively with Mr Mueller, and to Mr Mueller’s report, most of which has already been released.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Court challenges take time, which works to Mr Trump’s advantage. He can portray them as the actions of spiteful Democrats eager to avenge their 2016 loss, while running out the clock until after the next election, when the subpoenas expire, or at least until public attention moves on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But that is a minor risk compared to the precedent that would be set if Mr Trump faces no consequences for ignoring congressional subpoenas--an action that formed the basis for the third article of impeachment drawn up against Richard Nixon. A private citizen who ignores a subpoena can be jailed; though some Democrats have mooted dusting off Congress’s “inherent contempt” power to detain contemnors, that is unlikely to happen soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since Watergate, presidents have felt obligated to at least appear to comply with Congress’s oversight power, even as they negotiated the most favourable possible terms. Mr Trump feels no such pressure. That risks permanently weakening Congress’s oversight capacity, and rendering presidential power virtually unrestrained. If his party controls Congress, it will line up behind him; if it does not, he can just ignore their toothless demands. Says the former Republican White House counsel, “The next president and the next one after that and so on would have an additional precedent to say, ‘Subpoenas? Contempt? That’s just a vote; that’s just a political act. Nothing for me to worry about.’”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 06:09:20 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Middle America’s brain drain]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/08/middle-americas-brain-drain]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_woc181.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-08T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 8th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN A MORE agricultural era, America’s West and Midwest seemed like the promised land. Starting in the mid-19th century, the federal government distributed free land to settlers who were willing to brave the tribulations of frontier life to forge a new beginning. Today, however, services make up the bulk of the American economy, and rural regions are facing two demographic challenges. First, more people are moving out than are moving in. And to make matters worse, highly educated residents make up a disproportionate share of the leavers. States in the middle of the country contain an outsized share of residents without college degrees, whereas those on the coasts suck up the educated high-fliers, with some exceptions (Texas has been able to buck the trend, largely thanks to a budding tech sector). Economic opportunity has shifted accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Although the depopulation of America’s “heartland” is well-known, the internal redistribution of educated professionals —so-called“brain drain”—poses new economic, social and political difficulties for affected areas. Updated for 2017, new data from Congress’s Joint Economic Committee show that most states in the Rust Belt, Southeast and Plains regions are losing their educated residents to coastal states, as well as to Texas and Illinois. For example, people who move to California are 20 percentage points more likely to be among the most educated third of Americans than people who leave it are. Conversely, people relocating to Pennsylvania were ten percentage points less likely to be in the top third than those moving out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The consequences of a prolonged brain drain could be dire. Because America’s electoral system over-represents small states, the less-educated people living in places with shrinking populations could become more politically influential, even as their numbers decline.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 06:09:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Uber traffic: are ride-hailing apps making congestion worse?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/08/uber-traffic-are-ride-hailing-apps-making-congestion-worse]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/bg_twitter_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-08T19:00:34Z&quot;&gt;May 8th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span &gt;AS UBER prepares for its public listing this week, a new study shows that ride-hailing companies cause major road congestion in San Francisco. Also, how much should smart speakers see as well as hear? And Douglas Rushkoff, an author, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;explains why he thinks the internet and social media are harmful to humans&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span &gt;. Kenneth Cukier hosts. Runtime: 20 min.   &lt;/span&gt; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistbabbage/babbage-ubertraffic&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 03:11:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s trade war hots up]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/08/donald-trumps-trade-war-hots-up]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_fnp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-08T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 8th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;CHINA’S PROPAGANDA machine grinds slowly. But its output is nothing if not consistent. It took more than 24 hours for state media to report President Donald Trump’s threats, tweeted on May 5th, to ratchet up tariffs on China. By that time Chinese stocks had already plunged, a foretaste of global market ructions. When the response finally came in official editorials, it was a familiar refrain from China’s canon of trade-war statements: “We do not want to fight, but we are not afraid to fight and, given no choice, we will fight.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That sounds bellicose. Yet one lesson from the past year’s dispute with American is that China places more weight on the sentence’s first part, its desire to avoid a full-on fight. At multiple points when the Chinese government could have retaliated against America by targeting its businesses, it has instead tried to win them over, giving them better access to its market.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dodging a fight, though, does not mean giving in. As &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; went to press, officials from both countries were meeting in Washington to see whether they could revive a deal which, until Mr Trump’s tweets, had seemed nearly done. According to Reuters, citing American government sources, China had backtracked on pledges to rewrite laws on everything from competition policy to intellectual property. Chinese advisers counter that it is American negotiators who have become inflexible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This creates two huge uncertainties for the global economy. One dominates discussion. Will there be a deal or will America raise tariffs? The other receives less attention. Is there a point at which China might lash out against America, even at a cost to itself?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is easy to imagine how China could punch back. Given its $380bn trade surplus with America, China is more vulnerable to tariffs. But American businesses, from Apple to General Motors, have big footprints in China. American firms made roughly $200bn more in sales in China in 2015 than Chinese firms did in America, according to Deutsche Bank. The Chinese government could whip up consumer boycotts. It could hold up supplies at customs. It could smother factories with safety inspections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In its retaliation, China has already used tariffs to hit sensitive targets. It has pushed soyabean farmers in Iowa and Wisconsin, states that will influence whether Mr Trump can win a second term, to the brink of bankruptcy. But it has largely refrained from deploying the dirtier weapons in its arsenal. After briefly delaying American whiskey shipments at the border last year, Jack Daniel’s is flowing again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even more striking are China’s attempts to be emollient. Having long hesitated, it opened the door last year for a range of foreign firms, from carmakers to insurers, to take majority stakes in their Chinese operations. In March it passed a foreign-investment law that, in theory, addresses some big American grievances. It has even undone some tariffs: in December it lifted extra duties that it had imposed on American cars and car parts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China’s decision to opt for a relatively conciliatory strategy can be explained in three ways. Most obvious is its desire to minimise the trade war. If America were to slap 25% tariffs on all imports from China, that could knock two percentage points off Chinese growth over the next 12 months, according to UBS, a Swiss bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A second factor is China’s play to win back some support in America. Foreign businesses have grown frustrated with China. A more level playing field could change that, especially if China offers evidence of benefits. News on May 8th that JPMorgan Chase, an American bank, might become the first foreign company to own a majority stake in its Chinese mutual-fund business is just the kind of thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The final point is China’s management of domestic opinion. Xi Jinping, the president, is powerful, but he does not want to arm his critics. One government adviser says that left-wing scholars are planning to greet the announcement of any trade deal as a “day of national humiliation”, a reference to the 19th century when foreign powers dominated China. Front-loading reforms offers some insulation: the government can portray the deal as a ratification of what it was already doing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But domestic politicking also sheds light on why the trade talks have hit a rocky patch. China has more incentive to take a harder line at this moment—just when a deal seems to be within reach. Sending Mr Trump into a frenzy on Twitter may worry investors. But to Chinese officials it looks like Mr Xi is driving a tougher bargain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Complicating matters, negotiations have been conducted in English, with the draft agreement (reportedly seven chapters and 150 pages) also in English. As it is translated into Chinese and circulated among more officials, changes are inevitable. “You can’t really renege on something that is a non-binding work in progress,” says James Zimmerman, a partner in the Beijing office of Perkins Coie, a law firm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China still wants to avoid a full-fledged trade war. Should America raise tariffs, China’s initial preference will be to continue with limited retaliation, says Wang Yong, director of the Centre for International Political Economy at Peking University. The American economy would, he thinks, suffer enough damage for Mr Trump to change course. If not, China’s fight-back could get much nastier. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 03:11:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Prince Archie, the first royal Instagram baby]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/08/prince-archie-the-first-royal-instagram-baby]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_brp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-08T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 8th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE PRESS had been camped outside the Lindo Wing of St Mary’s hospital in west London for weeks before the birth of Prince George, son of the Duke and Duchess of Cambridge (better known as William and Kate), in July 2013. The news, when it came, was delivered via a press release sent to the world’s media, before the immaculately turned-out family posed outside the hospital for banks of salivating photographers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Archie Harrison Mountbatten-Windsor made a quieter entrance on May 6th. There were no waiting journalists because his parents, the Duke and Duchess of Sussex (Harry and Meghan), had kept the location of his birth secret. Instead, the first word of his arrival came via &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.instagram.com/sussexroyal/?hl=en&quot;&gt;@sussexroyal&lt;/a&gt;, the couple’s official Instagram account, which scooped the press with a message reading: “It’s a boy!” There followed a video on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.instagram.com/theroyalfamily/?hl=en&quot;&gt;@theroyalfamily&lt;/a&gt;, the monarchy’s account. The next day William and Kate posted a video of themselves telling interviewers that they were “absolutely thrilled”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The relationship between Britain’s royal family and the media has long been strained. But two developments in recent years have made the palace and the press mutually less interested in each other. One is that British newspapers have toned down their royal muckraking. Tighter budgets mean that editors lack the staff to pursue princes and princesses as closely as they used to.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile the Leveson Inquiry, an official probe into the “culture, practices and ethics” of the press in 2011-12, set up a new system of self-regulation and shamed newspaper editors into dropping their most aggressive practices. “When I first started it was like the Wild West,” says Arthur Edwards, who has been the &lt;em&gt;Sun&lt;/em&gt;’s royal photographer since 1977. At work or on holiday, royals were fair game. “But all that’s stopped now. Ever since Leveson.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the same time, the internet has made British papers less important to the monarchy. Readers can get their royal gossip from foreign publications that are not bound by British privacy or libel laws. “You see websites with multiple royal stories a day, often stuff that would never make the cut in a newspaper,” says Victoria Murphy, who writes about the monarchy for international outlets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2012 &lt;em&gt;Closer&lt;/em&gt;, a French magazine, published topless photos of Kate Middleton after British papers turned them down. On that occasion the royal family sued and won. Yet the speed with which information now spreads online makes it impossible to correct. “If they say one story is wrong, do people assume that others are correct?” asks Ms Murphy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is especially true of social media. In 2013, the year Prince George was born, Facebook had 1.2bn users and Instagram just 150m. Those numbers have since risen to 2.4bn and over 1bn. The royal family is upping its social game, hiring a head of digital engagement in 2016. It now has multiple social-media accounts, each with millions of followers, who monitor the royals’ activities alongside those of Beyoncé or Kim Kardashian.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike those superstars, however, the royals benefit from a residual sense of deference on the part of their fans. Candid smartphone pictures of the royals are uncommon online. Mr Edwards says that when Kate takes her children to the park, she asks other mothers to refrain from taking and posting pictures, and they comply. What’s more, when new families come to the park for the first time, it is the other mothers who tell them the rules of engagement. It is not just the British press that self-regulates, but also the public. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 03:11:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Riding alone in a car is an increasingly unaffordable luxury]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/05/08/riding-alone-in-a-car-is-an-increasingly-unaffordable-luxury]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_fnd000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-08T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 8th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;UBER’S INITIAL public offering, due after &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; went to press, will be one of the largest in tech history. The hoopla cannot drown out uncertainty about the firm’s future. Ride-hailing platforms have grown hugely in recent years, changing the face of urban transport. They have also been virtuosic losers of money. Lyft made an operating loss of nearly $1bn in 2018; Uber, about $3bn. The flow of red ink mainly represents subsidies from investors to riders: cash that allows average Joes to feel as though they have a personal car at their beck and call. It will not last. But Uber passengers are not the only road-farers facing straitened circumstances. Car-related subsidies of all sorts are becoming harder to sustain. Their loss could reveal mass travel in single-occupancy cars to be a no-longer-affordable luxury. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;The mania for tech platforms that match cars with riders rests on the idea that they can turn car-hire into critical urban-transport infrastructure. Perhaps ride-hailing could spare millions of people the cost of owning cars that mostly sit idle, and allow vehicles and roads to be used more efficiently. But increased scale has yet to turn losses to profits. To remain viable, Uber and its peers must make more money per trip. They could increase fares. But cheap rides have been crucial to building their user bases. However dominant one or another becomes, competing transport options remain, from personal cars to public transport to travellers’ own two feet. Higher fares will make those alternatives more attractive.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Perhaps instead the firms could cut their per-ride costs. Payments to drivers are the juiciest target, and indeed Uber is keen to develop a fleet of driverless taxis (as are other firms, including Waymo and Tesla). Yet even these may struggle to turn a profit. A recent analysis by Ashley Nunes of the Massachusetts Institute of Technology and Kristen Hernandez, now at Securing America’s Future Energy, an advocacy group, concludes that driving your own vehicle costs about $0.72 per mile (inclusive of ownership costs and expenses such as fuel and parking charges), whereas the lowest break-even fare an operator of driverless taxis could expect to charge is $1.31 per mile. While on duty, taxis rack up costs for items such as petrol, whether or not a fare-paying passenger is in the car. Furthermore, driverless cars would need some minding by human safety monitors, whose salaries must be covered by fares.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Until they turn profits, ride-hailing firms will be vulnerable to a loss of investors’ patience. But drivers of private vehicles also receive plenty of implicit support. Drivers impose environmental hazards on others at no financial cost to themselves, from the health effects of local air pollution to the climate change resulting from carbon emissions. And then there is congestion. The right to use scarce road space is valuable. When it is given away, drivers overuse available roads, and clog them. The waste is colossal. An estimate by INRIX, a consulting firm, suggests that the value of time lost to traffic in 2018 in America alone reached $87bn. &lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Removing the subsidy to drivers means pricing road space by levying tolls that increase with traffic. That would deter driving, and reduce congestion and other social costs of automobile use. Such charges are rarely popular with drivers. But governments’ enthusiasm for new, untolled roads has dimmed. And they do not help much with traffic. Gilles Duranton of the University of Pennsylvania and Matthew Turner of Brown University posit a “fundamental law of road congestion”: unless road space is priced appropriately, new capacity reduces the cost of driving, thereby inducing more of it, leading, eventually, to renewed congestion.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Uber passengers also benefit from subsidies to driving, and contribute to the social costs. According to new research published in the journal Science Advances, from 2010 to 2016 time lost to congestion in San Francisco rose by 62% more than it would have in the absence of ride-hailing vehicles on the city’s streets. Were dirty fuels to face stiffer taxes or road tolls to be increased, those additional costs would probably increase fares. But there is reason to think that eliminating subsidies, while reducing driving, would nonetheless boost the ride-hailing business. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Congestion delays the response to a request for a ride, which inconveniences passengers. And it raises the cost of operating taxis by increasing the time spent between dropping off one rider and picking up the next. The more efficiently firms can serve customers, the better their cost proposition relative to driving alone. So total trips would fall, but a greater share would involve an app-hailed vehicle. Tellingly, both Uber and Lyft spent money advocating for a recent budget measure in New York City that will introduce congestion-charging in parts of Manhattan. Similar efforts in other traffic-choked cities are likely to follow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Just what I needed&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Should congestion pricing spread, ride-hailing firms might gain room to raise fares and survive, even without fresh injections of capital. Urban transport would nonetheless be transformed. Ride-hailing services have gained passengers, in part, by luring them away from public options. Higher fares would induce some to switch back. Ride-hailing firms might retain users by improving their car-pooling options. Congestion pricing would reduce the delay associated with multiple stops. Indeed, in a subsidy-free world car-pooling of all sorts would increase. On a once congestion-clogged highway in Northern Virginia, for example, the number of cars with multiple occupants has risen by 15% since the introduction in 2017 of tolls that vary with the level of congestion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For decades, the striving working class has dreamed of the freedom to commute in the splendid isolation of a private car. “A man who, beyond the age of 26, finds himself on a bus can count himself as a failure,” Margaret Thatcher is supposed to have said. The real failure may be a widespread, persistent reluctance to grapple with the cost of travel in vehicular solitude—whether with or without the aid of an app. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2019 03:11:55 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America and Iran are on a collision course]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/08/america-and-iran-are-on-a-path-to-dangerous-escalation]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_map501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-08T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 8th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“THE UNITED STATES is not seeking war with the Iranian regime,” declared John Bolton, America’s national security adviser, when he announced on May 5th the deployment of an aircraft-carrier strike group from the Mediterranean to waters near Iran. It would be led by the &lt;em&gt;USS Abraham Lincoln&lt;/em&gt;. A separate bomber task-force was also being deployed to the region. The move, Mr Bolton said, was a response to “troubling and escalatory” intelligence warnings about Iran’s behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Few believed Mr Bolton’s peaceable intent. The accusations against Iran—unnamed officials let it be known that it might have been planning to attack America’s forces or its allies—was suspiciously unspecific. Mr Bolton was the man, after all, who in 2015 penned an op-ed article in the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; entitled “To Stop Iran’s Bomb, Bomb Iran”. More worrying, and perhaps of greater consequence, Iran’s president, Hassan Rouhani, appeared to play into Mr Bolton’s hands on May 8th by declaring that Iran would stop complying with some of its commitments under the nuclear deal it signed with America and European powers in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The accord, known as the Joint Comprehensive Plan of Action (JCPOA), placed strict limits on Iran’s nuclear programme, for a decade or more, in exchange for the partial lifting of Western sanctions. Mr Trump ripped up the accord in 2018, calling it “the worst deal in the world”, and reimposed sanctions on Iran. America also threatened harsh penalties against firms that traded with it. American waivers for some countries to continue buying Iranian oil were halted this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until now, Iran has abided by the terms of the JCPOA, in the hope that European states would shield it from the worst of the economic pain. They failed to do that, and it is surely no accident that Mr Rouhani chose the first anniversary of Mr Trump’s withdrawal from the accord to announce a calibrated response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He claimed Iran would be acting within the dispute-resolutions of the JCPOA, without breaching it. “The path we have chosen today is not the path of war, it is the path of diplomacy,” he declared in a televised speech. “But diplomacy with a new language and a new logic.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Rouhani said Iran would begin to build up its stockpiles of low-enriched uranium and of heavy water, which are used in different types of nuclear reactors, thereby threatening to breach limits set by the JCPOA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He told European powers that it would reverse these measures if they found ways to shield Iran’s economy (particularly its oil and banking sectors) within 60 days. If they did not, Iran would also end the limits on the level of uranium enrichment. Under the JCPOA it is producing enriched uranium at a concentration below 4%, used for nuclear reactors, far below the 90% or higher level required for nuclear weapons. Iran also warned that it could rebuild the Arak nuclear reactor, which had been disabled under the JCPOA.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Far from being a new diplomatic concept, this appears to be an old Iranian logic of pushing ahead with its nuclear programme—and so moving closer to the option of building a nuclear bomb—in response to rising pressure from the West. Iran has always claimed to be seeking to develop nuclear technology only for civilian power generation. But much of the same technology can be used to build nuclear bombs. And UN nuclear inspectors had found enough evidence in the past of weapons-related activity to raise serious concerns about Iran’s ultimate goal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Israel had openly considered unilateral military action against Iran, but was dissuaded from it by American pressure. Mr Bolton had been prominent among hawks who believed in using economic pressure to remove the clerical regime, and American (or Israeli) military action to set back the nuclear programme if necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diplomacy with Iran under Barack Obama was intended to break this escalatory cycle leading to the grim choice of an Iranian nuclear bomb or bombing Iran. The JCPOA pushed back Iran’s nuclear programme from being perhaps a few months away from being able to build a bomb to requiring more than a year. But critics said it placed only temporary restraints on Iran, did not restrict missile technology and, by releasing frozen Iranian funds, gave the regime greater means to spread its influence in the Middle East—notably in the wars in Iraq, Syria and Yemen—and fund allied militant groups such as Hizbullah, the Shia militia-cum-party in Lebanon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump’s decision to abandon the JCPOA, despite pressure from European allies and many of his own advisers to reconsider, all but killed the deal. European efforts to keep it on life support are failing; most European firms have chosen to abide by the sanctions despite a European mechanism designed to protect those trading in “humanitarian” supplies with Iran. Now Mr Rouhani may bury the accord altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Iranian president has been under pressure from his own hawks who detested the JCPOA and pressed him to act more forcefully. His announcement is also an attempt to split the Europeans from America. But it is a risky strategy. Breaching the JCPOA and moving towards a nuclear capability would alienate the Europeans, and give America a clear cause to take harsher action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the past, Iran appeared almost to be daring America to take military action, perhaps believing that it would not dare to do so at a time when American troops were deeply entangled in the war in Iraq and vulnerable to retaliatory attacks by Iran’s proxy militias.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That risk has lessened somewhat as the war in Iraq has wound down. And violence by Iran’s proxies may be just the sort of provocation that hawks like Mr Bolton are looking for to justify a military campaign. Mr Trump, a harsh critic of America’s wars in the Middle East, who has wanted to withdraw American forces from the region, probably does not want war. Neither does Mr Rouhani. But hawks on both sides are taking control. Strange as it may seem, next to Mr Bolton it is the president who now seems the cautious grown-up in the White House.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 23:08:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A new exhibition resurrects a forgotten modern master]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/08/a-new-exhibition-resurrects-a-forgotten-modern-master]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_BKP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-08T15:06:51Z&quot;&gt;May 8th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN THE early 20th century Native American art was dominated by the work of the Kiowa Six. The collective drew on Plains hide painting and Ledger art (sketches on paper or cloth), depicting scenes from oral histories to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/01/21/artistic-encounters-with-indigenous-america-is-timely-and-troubling&quot;&gt;evoke a seemingly lost way of life&lt;/a&gt;. Men and women were rendered in an almost cartoonish style, usually hunting, dancing or performing rites; they often wore headdresses or traditional clothing. Karen Kramer, a curator specialising in Native American and Oceanic Art, judges that such iconography persisted for decades because “the art market was hungry for this sentimental imagery of Native life that never seemed to change.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the ’60s, as other ideas about American identity were being questioned, so too did representations of Native Americans evolve. The Institute of American Indian Art in Santa Fe, New Mexico, encouraged its students to depict their heritage using all the tools art and art history provided. As Alfred Young Man, one pupil, explained, they “revelled in the popularity of pop and op [optical] art, and abstract expressionism, and how the French impressionists painted.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;T.C. Cannon, part Kiowa and part Caddo, was also among that group, and a new exhibition at the Museum of the American Indian in New York celebrates his unique visual style and pioneering depictions of Native Americans. Like other artists at the time, he gravitated towards more figurative art after an era defined by abstraction. Cannon was particularly drawn to the Fauvists and their expressive, non-naturalistic, use of colour. He combined styles found in the work of Western painters such as Henri Matisse and Vincent Van Gogh with traditional Native American imagery.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In “Law North of the Rosebud, 1971”, for example, Cannon depicts a tribal policeman against a flat background of red, blue, purple and lime green. A sheriff’s star is pinned to his label and braids spill from a ten-gallon hat, but in his case aviator glasses obscure a more personal identity. He stands with his hand on his hip, slightly slouching, as if tired or unimpressed. The simple modernity of the picture—and its subject’s reluctance to pose—seems like a refusal to bow to what a viewer might want from an “Indian” picture.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190511_bkp505.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elsewhere, Cannon refers to the most recognisable figures in Western art history: the Madonna and the reclining nude. “Cloud Madonna” (1975, pictured top right) uses the intense shade of blue often found in pictures of Mary, but this woman is carrying a gourd, not an infant; she balances a ceramic water jar on her head. The nude in “Collector #3” (1974, pictured above), meanwhile, borrows the pose of Titian’s “Venus of Urbino” but makes the setting wildly colourful, a mishmash of patterns.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cannon enlisted in the US Army in 1966, and a large part of the show is given over to this period. Several posters on display elsewhere in the museum address the apparent paradox of Native American military service, questioning why individuals would serve an army and government that attacked their culture. For many, enlisting was seen as noble, a continuation of the Kiowa warrior tradition, but Cannon returned from his service deeply troubled about his role in the Vietnam war and more cynical about his country. This disillusionment influenced his art. “Two Guns Arakira” (1974-1976, pictured top left), made after his return from the war, seems at first to be another Fauvist delight. The aged warrior, sat in an armchair, has long, violet hair; polka dots form the background. But upon close inspection, it becomes clear that the painting is not playful. The man’s face is grave, peering out of the frame as if expecting someone. He clutches a pistol in each hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“T.C. Cannon: At the Edge of America” is an excellent survey of a dynamic, inventive and wide-ranging artist. As well as the 30 paintings on display, visitors can enjoy his beautiful and sombre poems and listen to his songs (Bob Dylan, one of Cannon’s musical influences, also appears as the subject of a portrait). The exhibition lays bare Cannon’s technical skill, his humour and his ability to distill emotion in both word and colour. Four decades after his death in a car accident, aged just 31, he is finally receiving the recognition he deserves for his outsize influence and talent. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“T.C. Cannon: At the Edge of America” is at the National Museum of the American Indian in New York until September 16th&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 23:07:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America and Iran are on a path to dangerous escalation]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/05/08/america-and-iran-are-on-a-collision-course]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_map005_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-08T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 8th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“THE UNITED STATES is not seeking war with the Iranian regime,” declared John Bolton, America’s national security adviser, when he announced on May 5th the deployment of an aircraft-carrier strike group from the Mediterranean to waters near Iran. It would be led by the &lt;em&gt;USS Abraham Lincoln&lt;/em&gt;. A separate bomber task-force was also being deployed to the region. The move, Mr Bolton said, was a response to “troubling and escalatory” intelligence warnings about Iran’s behaviour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Few believed Mr Bolton’s peaceable intent. The accusations against Iran—unnamed officials let it be known that it might have been planning to attack America’s forces or its allies—was suspiciously unspecific. Mr Bolton was the man, after all, who in 2015 penned an op-ed article in the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; entitled “To Stop Iran’s Bomb, Bomb Iran”. More worrying, and perhaps of greater consequence, Iran’s president, Hassan Rouhani, appeared to play into Mr Bolton’s hands on May 8th by declaring that Iran would stop complying with some of its commitments under the nuclear deal it signed with America and European powers in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The accord, known as the Joint Comprehensive Plan of Action (JCPOA), placed strict limits on Iran’s nuclear programme, for a decade or more, in exchange for the partial lifting of Western sanctions. Mr Trump ripped up the accord in 2018, calling it “the worst deal in the world”, and reimposed sanctions on Iran. America also threatened harsh penalties against firms that traded with it. American waivers for some countries to continue buying Iranian oil were halted this week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Until now, Iran has abided by the terms of the JCPOA, in the hope that European states would shield it from the worst of the economic pain. They failed to do that, and it is surely no accident that Mr Rouhani chose the first anniversary of Mr Trump’s withdrawal from the accord to announce a calibrated response.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He claimed Iran would be acting within the dispute-resolutions of the JCPOA, without breaching it. “The path we have chosen today is not the path of war, it is the path of diplomacy,” he declared in a televised speech. “But diplomacy with a new language and a new logic.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Rouhani said Iran would begin to build up its stockpiles of low-enriched uranium and of heavy water, which are used in different types of nuclear reactors, thereby threatening to breach limits set by the JCPOA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He told European powers that it would reverse these measures if they found ways to shield Iran’s economy (particularly its oil and banking sectors) within 60 days. If they did not, Iran would also end the limits on the level of uranium enrichment. Under the JCPOA it is producing enriched uranium at a concentration below 4%, used for nuclear reactors, far below the 90% or higher level required for nuclear weapons. Iran also warned that it could rebuild the Arak nuclear reactor, which had been disabled under the JCPOA.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;Far from being a new diplomatic concept, this appears to be an old Iranian logic of pushing ahead with its nuclear programme—and so moving closer to the option of building a nuclear bomb—in response to rising pressure from the West. Iran has always claimed to be seeking to develop nuclear technology only for civilian power generation. But much of the same technology can be used to build nuclear bombs. And UN nuclear inspectors had found enough evidence in the past of weapons-related activity to raise serious concerns about Iran’s ultimate goal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Israel had openly considered unilateral military action against Iran, but was dissuaded from it by American pressure. Mr Bolton had been prominent among hawks who believed in using economic pressure to remove the clerical regime, and American (or Israeli) military action to set back the nuclear programme if necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Diplomacy with Iran under Barack Obama was intended to break this escalatory cycle leading to the grim choice of an Iranian nuclear bomb or bombing Iran. The JCPOA pushed back Iran’s nuclear programme from being perhaps a few months away from being able to build a bomb to requiring more than a year. But critics said it placed only temporary restraints on Iran, did not restrict missile technology and, by releasing frozen Iranian funds, gave the regime greater means to spread its influence in the Middle East—notably in the wars in Iraq, Syria and Yemen—and fund allied militant groups such as Hizbullah, the Shia militia-cum-party in Lebanon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump’s decision to abandon the JCPOA, despite pressure from European allies and many of his own advisers to reconsider, all but killed the deal. European efforts to keep it on life support are failing; most European firms have chosen to abide by the sanctions despite a European mechanism designed to protect those trading in “humanitarian” supplies with Iran. Now Mr Rouhani may bury the accord altogether.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Iranian president has been under pressure from his own hawks who detested the JCPOA and pressed him to act more forcefully. His announcement is also an attempt to split the Europeans from America. But it is a risky strategy. Breaching the JCPOA and moving towards a nuclear capability would alienate the Europeans, and give America a clear cause to take harsher action.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the past, Iran appeared almost to be daring America to take military action, perhaps believing that it would not dare to do so at a time when American troops were deeply entangled in the war in Iraq and vulnerable to retaliatory attacks by Iran’s proxy militias.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That risk has lessened somewhat as the war in Iraq has wound down. And violence by Iran’s proxies may be just the sort of provocation that hawks like Mr Bolton are looking for to justify a military campaign. Mr Trump, a harsh critic of America’s wars in the Middle East, who has wanted to withdraw American forces from the region, probably does not want war. Neither does Mr Rouhani. But hawks on both sides are taking control. Strange as it may seem, next to Mr Bolton it is the president who now seems the cautious grown-up in the White House.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 23:06:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“America sees an opportunity to deliver a lethal, decisive blow to Iran”—brinkmanship in the Middle East]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/08/america-sees-an-opportunity-to-deliver-a-lethal-decisive-blow-to-iran-brinkmanship-in-the-middle-east]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190511_blp504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-08T09:27:45Z&quot;&gt;May 8th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A YEAR after President Donald Trump pulled America out of the Iran nuclear deal—and days after America moved warships into the Persian Gulf—Iran has announced that it will break parts of the deal. Is this more than just sabre-rattling? We also examine an impressive new effort to get inside the minds of those unable to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/04/27/how-to-give-voice-to-the-speechless&quot;&gt;speak&lt;/a&gt;. And why does &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/04/how-globalisation-created-british-cuisine&quot;&gt;British food&lt;/a&gt; get such a bad rap? The answer stretches back to the Industrial Revolution. Runtime: 21min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/nucleardiffusion-iran&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 08 May 2019 18:37:11 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>