<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Join us for a day of ideas, debate and inspiration]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/28/join-us-for-a-day-of-ideas-debate-and-inspiration]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_OPP506.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T21:14:10Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Join journalists from &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; for the second annual Open Future Festival on Saturday, October 5th 2019. Held in three cities simultaneously—Hong Kong, Manchester and Chicago—it is a chance for people from across the ideological spectrum to meet and debate vital issues on the future of open societies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hear talks and panels by prominent figures from politics, business, civil society and the arts. The festival themes include free speech and free trade; the environment and inequality; the rise of populism and anxiety over the algorithmic society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Come and share your ideas during a day of exciting discussions, curated content and exhibitions, immersive experiences and the chance to make connections with hundreds of festival attendees. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;More information for the festivals by region:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://events.economist.com/events-conferences/asia/open-future-festival-hong-kong?utm_source=EM8172_Web_OFHUB&amp;amp;RefID=EM8172_Web_OFHUB&quot;&gt;Hong Kong event details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://events.economist.com/events-conferences/emea/open-future-festival-manchester/?utm_source=EM1696_Web_OFHUB&amp;amp;RefID=EM1696_Web_OFHUB&quot;&gt;Manchester event details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://events.economist.com/events-conferences/americas/open-future-festival-chicago/?utm_source=EM2355_Web_OFHUB&amp;amp;RefID=EM2355_Web_OFHUB&quot;&gt;Chicago event details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Learn more about Open Future&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;The Open Future &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/openfuture&quot;&gt;content hub&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Take part in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/26/our-essay-competition-for-young-people&quot;&gt;Open Future essay contest&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Letter from the editor: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2018/04/16/a-letter-to-readers-from-the-editor&quot;&gt;Open Future explained&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Watch &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s editor-in-chief Zanny Minton Beddoes interview &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.youtube.com/watch?v=NAfm5L_DOLM&quot; data-tegid=&quot;ub0s0birid6siht0j726ov5houcptr88&quot;&gt;Steve Bannon&lt;/a&gt; at last year’s festival&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Is capitalism rigged in favour of the elites? &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://debates.economist.com/debate/capitalism&quot;&gt;Read the online debate&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Read &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/01/21/we-need-to-own-our-data-as-a-human-right-and-be-compensated-for-it&quot;&gt;“We need to own our data as a human right—and be compensated for it”&lt;/a&gt;, an Open Future essay by &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://will.i.am/&quot;&gt;will.i.am&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 07:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[In their first primary debate Democrats focused on the issues]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/28/in-their-first-primary-debate-democrats-focused-on-the-issues]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic- data-infographic-js=&quot;/2019/debate-night-interactive/js/bundle.js&quot; data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/debate-night-interactive/css/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/debate-night-interactive/css/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;small&gt;“America does&lt;/small&gt; not want to witness a food fight, they want to know how we’re going to put food on their table.” So said Kamala Harris, the junior senator from California, on the second night of this week’s Democratic primary debate on June 27th. The line, while clearly scripted, provoked raucous applause, suggesting that the assembled audience was more interested in policy disagreements than bickering and personal attacks. That is, for the most part, what the candidates gave them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;According to an analysis of the first Democratic debate by &lt;i&gt;The Economist&lt;/i&gt;, the vast majority of the candidates’ time—more than 70%—was spent discussing specific policies. Elizabeth Warren, a senator from Massachusetts, and Julián Castro, a former housing secretary, impressed with their command of health-care and immigration policy. These issues took up 10% and 9% of the debate, respectively. Bernie Sanders and Pete Buttigieg, meanwhile, spoke at length about economic and foreign policy, which each represented about 10% of debate time. Other topics, such as climate change and gun control, received less attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such issues may be of little concern to primary voters. According to YouGov, a pollster, America’s biggest political divides run along demographic, not policy lines. Nonetheless, this week’s debate may still prove consequential. During Thursday’s tussle, Ms Harris pressed Mr Biden, the front-runner, over his civil rights record, including his opposition to school busing ordered by America’s Department of Education in the 1970s. The exchange may damage his standing among his core supporters. Prior to the debate, punters on PredictIt, a political-betting market, gave Ms Harris a 14% chance of winning the primary in South Carolina, where most Democratic primary voters are black. After her performance on Thursday, her chances jumped to 43%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 03:40:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why did the justices rule that courts cannot curb partisan redistricting?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/28/why-did-the-justices-rule-that-courts-cannot-curb-partisan-redistricting]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_USP505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T11:29:13Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;FOR JOHN LOCKE, the 17th-century political philosopher, anarchy was when a leader “has the liberty to be judge in his own case”. In a properly constituted society, disputes between contending parties are turned over to a third party for adjudication—an independent judge who can apply the law and issue a fair judgement. America’s judiciary generally fills this role. But on June 27th, a bare majority of the Supreme Court declared a crucial issue—partisan gerrymandering—outside its portfolio.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The court told state legislators they are their own bosses when it comes to drawing electoral maps for their legislatures and for Congress. No matter how blatantly or egregiously the lines are skewed, the federal judiciary will remain studiously above the fray. Legislators may choose their voters, rather than the other way around, and nobody will blink. The decision will give a bigger boost to Republicans, because they control more state houses and governor mansions. While it closes the door to claims of political gerrymandering, race-based gerrymandering remains subject to judicial review. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.supremecourt.gov/opinions/18pdf/18-422_9ol1.pdf&quot;&gt;opinions&lt;/a&gt; in &lt;em&gt;Rucho v Common Cause&lt;/em&gt; were penned by the court’s best writers: Chief Justice John Roberts for the five-man conservative majority, Justice Elena Kagan for the four liberal dissenters. But the opinions offer starkly different visions of the courts’ role in preserving democratic norms and institutions. Whereas the chief summoned a raft of arguments to explain why there is simply no manageable way for judges to determine when a gerrymander goes too far, the dissent characterised the ruling as abrogating a “duty to declare the law” on a matter that is fundamental to the very functioning of American elections. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The districting plans at issue here are highly partisan, by any measure”, Chief Justice Roberts began, but the lower courts that struck them down inappropriately “exercised judicial power” by declaring them “unconstitutional as well”. In dutifully laying out the facts of cases from North Carolina and Maryland, the chief expressed no alarm and said little about the bigger picture. He did, however, note some of the most alarming details, including a comment in 2016 from an architect of North Carolina’s congressional map securing a 10-3 Republican advantage in the House of Representatives. The legislator stopped at 10-3—in a state that is fairly evenly split between Republicans and Democrats—because he did “not believe it [would be] possible to draw a map with 11 Republicans and 2 Democrats”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Judges cannot stop stunts like this, even those that may “reasonably seem unjust”, Chief Justice Roberts wrote, because challenges to engineered maps “present political questions beyond the reach of the federal courts”. Objections to partisan gerrymandering are, in technical terms, “non-justiciable”. Federal courts “have no license to reallocate political power between the two major political parties”, the chief justice wrote, because there are “no legal standards to limit and direct their decisions”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In dissent, Justice Kagan replied with a truism: what the court says “can’t be done &lt;em&gt;has&lt;/em&gt; been done”. In recent years, “federal courts across the country...have largely converged on a standard for adjudicating partisan gerrymandering claims” and struck down maps drafted by both parties that are extreme outliers. The same advances in technology that permit modern gerrymanderers to carve precise maps to entrench their power afford challengers a tool to demonstrate just how engineered the lines are. In North Carolina, the Republican Party&amp;#x27;s map was, according to software analysis, “the absolute worst of 3,001 possible maps” for Democrats, the “only one that could produce a 10–3 partisan split even as Republicans got a bare majority of the state-wide vote”. The chief may fret over how much partisanship is too much, and declare that there is nowhere to draw a line, but, the dissent argues, surely the courts could agree that such a map is unfair to voters of the state’s minority party.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a rather feeble attempt to soften the blow of his decision, Chief Justice Roberts wrote that the majority’s “conclusion does not condone excessive partisan gerrymandering” and points to reform measures in Congress and in the states that could ease redistricting concerns. Several states have, indeed, turned line-drawing over to independent commissions in an attempt to push toward fairer maps. But curiously, in 2015, Chief Justice Roberts wrote a strong dissent in a case &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2015/07/02/one-for-the-people&quot;&gt;narrowly upholding&lt;/a&gt; the constitutionality of just such a commission in Arizona. That solution may not survive another challenge in the hands of the Supreme Court’s strengthened conservative majority. And the chief set himself up for ridicule when observing that a redistricting reform bill, first drafted in 2005, “has been reintroduced in every Congress since”. Well, Justice Kagan quipped, it “might be reintroduced until the end of time”. What all the proposals “have in common”, she wrote, “is that they are not laws”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which brings us back to Locke. There is an obvious reason why legislative fixes are not on the horizon. “The politicians who benefit from partisan gerrymandering”, like judges in their own cases, have no incentive to deal fairly with rivals. These legislators “are unlikely to change partisan gerrymandering” and because they “maintain themselves in office through partisan gerrymandering, the chances for legislative reform are slight”. With no one watching over them, and with increasingly sophisticated methods of identifying optimal maps to warp elections, legislators are now empowered to gerrymander at will. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Partisan redistricting has already “debased and dishonoured our democracy”, Justice Kagan wrote, “turning upside-down the core American idea that all governmental power derives from the people”. But with the door now shut on lawsuits and assurances that no one in the federal judiciary will meddle in their plans, gerrymandering legislators have a green light to skew electoral maps exactly as they please—a regime that could “irreparably damage our system of government”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 01:40:28 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Containing Iran, reparations for slavery and Europe’s problem with veggie burgers]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/28/containing-iran-reparations-for-slavery-and-europes-problem-with-veggie-burgers]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_11.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T17:00:34Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A SELECTION of three essential articles read aloud from the latest issue of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;. This week: how t&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/29/as-america-and-iran-inch-closer-to-war-new-talks-are-needed&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;he world should contain &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/29/as-america-and-iran-inch-closer-to-war-new-talks-are-needed&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Iran&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;; the debate around &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/06/29/the-idea-of-reparations-for-slavery-is-morally-appealing-but-flawed&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;reparations for slavery&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (09:08); and Europe heroically defends itself against &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/29/europe-heroically-defends-itself-against-veggie-burgers&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;veggie burgers&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (16:30). Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-june28th2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 00:40:29 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Who are the members of the Conservative Party?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/06/28/who-are-the-members-of-the-conservative-party]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_BLP515.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T14:24:02Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JEREMY HUNT and Boris Johnson are on the hustings, travelling through Britain to seek support for their bids to succeed Theresa May as leader of the Conservative Party, and thus as prime minister. They are not trying to charm millions of voters, just the considerably more exclusive franchise of the Conservative Party’s membership. Whoever polls highest will be declared the winner on July 22nd and move into Downing Street the next day. To some this may seem an eccentric, even undemocratic way to pick the leader of an advanced democracy. But by precedent, the sole criterion to be prime minister is that he or she must command a majority in the House of Commons. So who are the members of the Conservative Party, and whom are they likely to pick?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/economist-explains/20190706_wocc8l.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All Britain’s main political parties have suffered a decline in membership in recent decades, but none more so than the Tories (see chart). In the 1950s they had nearly 3m members. Now they have about 160,000. They are unrepresentative of Britain: according to research from Queen Mary University of London, 86% of Tory members are middle class and 97% are white, whereas only 54% of Britons are middle class and 87% white. Fully 71% of Tory party members are men and 44% are over 65 years old, compared with 18% of the population as a whole. They are disproportionately concentrated in London and the south of England. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These characteristics help to explain the political attitudes of the membership, particularly when it comes to Brexit. About 60% of those over 65 voted to leave the EU in the referendum of 2016, as did about two-thirds of Tory party members. Now, the overwhelming majority of members oppose holding a second referendum. According to a recent YouGov poll, the Tory membership is so dedicated to Brexit that 54% would be willing to destroy the party itself in order to achieve it. Equally, a majority would be happy to break up the United Kingdom to get Brexit—even though the official name of the Tories is the Conservative and Unionist Party. Members are more socially conservative than the average Tory voter and, on the economy, are more likely to be against any government redistribution. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;These are the leanings that Messrs Hunt and Johnson have to take into account. They may choose to tack to the political centre at a general election, but to get into Downing Street in the first place they will have to throw some very red meat to the activists. Thus Mr Johnson’s recent declaration Britain would leave the EU on October 31st, “do or die”, might horrify many voters, but the evidence suggests that it is exactly what party members want to hear. A no-deal Brexit holds no fear for many of them: according to the YouGov survey, 44% believe that such an outcome will win the Tories at least the next election. Little wonder, then, that Mr Johnson, who fronted the Leave campaign in 2016, remains the favourite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 00:40:28 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[For women, running is still an act of defiance]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/news/2019/06/28/for-women-running-is-still-an-act-of-defiance]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190629_efd_001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AT AROUND 5pm on October 28th 2018, the day the clocks went back in Britain, I pulled on my running shoes and left the house. My usual route follows a seven-mile (11km) loop. It starts in the medieval walled city of York, going south on good, firm cycle paths, then on to boggier trails and through a small wood to the nearby village of Bishopthorpe, returning via a few suburban alleys, across a race-course and a paved riverside path. It is flat and untroubled by cars, and I do it once or twice each week, taking one hour and one, two, sometimes even three minutes. As long as it’s not my turn to put my children to bed and I get changed the minute I stop work, I can run and be home before sunset. But on the day the clocks changed, I misjudged things and at 5pm it was already dark. No matter. I shrugged myself into a high-viz vest, donned reflective arm- and ankle-bands, stretched my new head-torch around my forehead, and left the house.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I’ve run for over a decade, since my mid-20s. When I started it brought me little pleasure. I had been running for only a couple of weeks—short bursts, on treadmills—when I decided to jog eight miles along the road from a holiday cottage in the Yorkshire Dales to the nearest town. I wore an ancient pair of Converse and arrived in Pateley Bridge with acute achilles tendonitis.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But I kept running. It fed my tendency to link worth with quantification. I valued things that could be enumerated and their progress measured. I relished the data: the distances, personal bests, calories burnt. But I found running physically unpleasant. My hip and knee would hurt. I would take ever more ibuprofen to get through a half-mara­thon, until I could no longer run through the pain and had to stop. I ran because I felt like I should be a runner. But because it hurt and I was never as fast as I wanted to be, my runs were suffused with a sense of failure.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Only after having children in my mid-30s did running become something else. Unexpectedly, seven months of enforced rest during pregnancy, and physiotherapy for pelvic misalignment and pain, dealt with my niggles. Running again, I felt good as new. I swapped road running for softer paths to protect my pelvis. At first I ran around the muddy perimeter of our local London park, then delved into Epping Forest. When we moved up to York, I discovered the North York Moors and the delights of longer distances across flowering purple heather, through ancient woodlands, and along cliffs cascading down to apricot beaches. And running offered freedom. A day in the hills was rare, precious time in charge of my body and mind, when I could be alone without a child clamouring for sweets or bum-wiping or “Paw Patrol”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I discovered that running up and down hills, vaulting tree roots and crunching along forest paths come with genuine, unquantifiable physical pleasures: clean, sharp air in hard-working lungs. A sudden downpour on parched salty skin. A cold pint in a lakeside pub after a summer run, and a cup of tea and toasted teacake in a village café in winter. The miraculous release from gravity’s pull at the top of a hill, followed by a childlike caper down the other side, with arms outstretched like a plane.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On October 28th the first mile took me along cycle paths, yellow in the glare of street lamps. It was the perfect temperature, just cold enough to slice through the torpor left by a day spent in a centrally heated, fluorescent-lit office. Running brought me back to my body, as if I possessed the liquid soul which the Greek Stoics called pneuma and it was trickling back into me, pushing up against the inside of my skin and inflating me with life. It felt wonderful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After the first mile, my route diverged onto a track that banked onto empty fields below. A small aperture ahead turned silver in the light of my headtorch, but all around was unvariegated charcoal. My stomach lurched and my heart rate increased. I kicked up my heels faster, hurd­ling clods and tussocks to the next stile. “Am I an idiot”, I wondered, “to have come out here, in the dark, alone?”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I run, I tend to meditate on uncomplicated things (paint colours for a room I’m decorating) or I work over mathematical puzzles (the time it will take me to finish an upcoming race, say). Sometimes these transmute into more fearful wonderings, like whether I will get home safely. I know that women are much more vulnerable to assault in their own homes than in dark alleys or parks. I know that by far the majority of rapes, assaults and murders of women are perpetrated by men known to them. I know that not all men are violent, but I also know that in 2017-18 in Britain 93% of those prosecuted for violence against women and girls were men. And I know of women attacked or murdered while running: among them Karina Vetrano, Mollie Tibbetts, Wendy Martinez, all since 2016. Women may be more at risk in the home, but they aren’t necessarily safe outside it, either.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My fear is not all in my head. I have twice been chased by men as I ran. One jogged beside me with a cigarette for nearly a mile, falling away when I sped off. The second was more sinister, and I had to duck into a stranger’s driveway and pretend to knock at the door. I’ve been surrounded by men on mopeds chanting “Cunt! Cunt! Cunt!” I’ve had cigarette smoke deliberately blown into my face, been spat at, tripped up, lunged at, and received heckles, cat-calls and honks: “You look like a paedophile in those leggings!”; “Can’t you run faster than that?”; “Give us a smile, love!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am not alone. “Female runners,” I tweeted not long ago, “would you run alone in the dark?” Stories flooded in: a woman who runs at night only if her neighbours are home to watch for her return. Women who stopped running in the dark after being grabbed or followed or encouraged to get into strangers’ cars, then stopped running alone in the day after facing similar intimidation, and then stopped running altogether. Women who run alone only if accom­panied by a dog or rape alarm or, in America, mace or even a gun carried in a sporty holster under a running skirt. Running’s emotional windfalls couple a sense of profound freedom with moments of euphoric joy. But for me they are always cut through with the fear that as I run alone, a man will abduct, rape, attack or murder me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, as the dark path spilled onto a nearby village’s high street, and propelled me through squares of light from pubs and fish-and-chip shops, I sighed, relieved. But soon I was back in the blackness, running through an alley onto an unlit cycle path bordering deep fields. In the distance, a small bright light swooped closer: a cyclist. “Thank god,” I thought, “a chaperone.” But then I doubled back: “Oh shit, no, maybe he’s a rapist?” Panicky, I tried to rationalise away my fear. From a distance, perhaps I was not distinguishable as a woman? But I’m not tall and the height of my head-torch probably gave me away. Perhaps I could outrun him? But I could not outrun a bike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As we passed one another, I kept my gaze down, reluctant to make eye contact. My fear was disproportionate, but not groundless. How do you calibrate fear to a small but nonetheless existent risk? What is the appropriate level of fear to feel that you probably, but not certainly, won’t be attacked? How do you make yourself less afraid anyway?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The freedom that running promises is complicated for many women. It is often hard-won, limited in scope, perhaps squeezed into brief chinks in a week dominated by the second shift of child care or housework, or tinged with the guilt of temporarily abandoning those duties. The freedom of leaving the house unburdened by anything more than a key in the zip-pocket of your leggings is particularly meaningful for women used to the weight of handbags, buggies, changing bags stuffed with snacks and spare pants. And, as I had found when I was younger, running can be allied to social and psychological forces that inhibit and control us—anorexia, orthorexia, OCD—as much as it has the potential to free us from those forces.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On that particular run, I began to fantasise about a night-time male curfew. Without this fear, what would I do at night? Nothing very dramatic: simply allow my life to unfold into the full 24 hours of day and night. I’d run, anxiety-free, alone in a forest after dark. After a night out, I’d go straight to bed, without waiting up to hear that the female friends I’d been with were home safely. I wouldn’t double- and triple-check the locks on my windows and doors, as I’ve done every evening since I woke one night in my 20s to find an unknown man leaning over my bed, half-suspended through an unlocked window. I wouldn’t endlessly revisit memories of a childhood neighbour—a woman who lived alone—who was raped on the hottest night of the summer by a man who climbed onto her balcony and through her French windows. And I wouldn’t walk home with a makeshift weapon of keys wedged between my fingers, as I’ve done ever since, aged 14, we girls were taken aside at school and solemnly warned of the need to protect ourselves against rape—as if rape were an inevitable natural force, like black ice, and not the result of men’s decisions. (The boys were not subjected to cautionary sessions advising them not to rape women.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_003.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In similar conversations on Twitter recently women have pondered what they would do if men disappeared for 24 hours. Thousands took part. Like me, many fantasised about wearing headphones or heels at night, leaving windows open, travelling home alone from gigs, forgoing bras under their clothes, booking Airbnbs in cheaper, less salu­brious locations. But most often, women’s dreams were variations of being able to “walk alone at night, anywhere I wanted, and not be afraid” or “go for a run really late at night”. Their imaginings are striking in their banality.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After 12 more minutes running, the path I was on joined up with a road and then, home, safe! I stopped my watch: my average pace had been 15 seconds a kilometre faster than usual. I unlocked the front door. My heartbeat slowed and I sank on to the staircase’s bottom step. I thought that I probably wouldn’t run again off-road at night, on my own. Running, or rather not running, had become yet another adjustment that women make all year long in an attempt to avoid becoming victims of assault, adjustments that become more urgent in winter when our lives are constrained by the ever-shortening daylight hours. And look how I’m talking about this, as if what is wrong here is the shifting of the seasons, or the tilt of the Earth’s axis, or the decision in 1916 to move the clocks back in autumn to increase productivity in the morning—anything but the fact that some men deliberately intimidate and assault and kill women, and that one of the more minor but not insignificant outcomes of that fact is that so very many women do not run alone in the dark.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Men have long tried to control women’s running. In the 18th century thousands of spectators gawped at women running in “smock-races” (the prize was often a smock) at village fairs. In the 19th century men bet on female speed-walkers traipsing around tracks in pub gardens. Some running women—such as Greek mythology’s Atalanta, who killed the male suitors she outran—rejected the trappings of femininity. They challenged everything that kept them sexually submissive, physically dependent and domestically servile. No wonder men tried to control and limit them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some men would try to sabotage the female athletes’ feats. At a pub in Bradford in 1864, Emma Sharp, who was attempting to cover 1,000 miles in 1,000 hours, defended herself with pistols against men trying to win their bets by pressing chloroform-soaked cloths into her face. Others fared even worse. In 1874 a Wolverhampton farmer called James Alcock was convicted of assaulting Rebecca Richards, a competitive female runner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Criticism came from other quarters too but the intent was the same: to stop women in their tracks. Journalists derided women’s foot-racing as “unnatural” and “dangerous”. This mirrored the rise of pseudo-scientific medical claims about women’s physiological and psychological frailty. As early as 1827, a medic warned that vigorous “exertion” in post-pubescent women threatened their reproductive health “by wearing out the powers of the body”. In 1928 newspapers reported the apparent collapse of female athletes on the finish line of the 800 metres at the Amsterdam Olympics: one journalist concluded that “women are not built physically to undergo the strain of races. Nature made them to bear children”—as if childbirth were a walk in the park. Women were then banned from Olympic events longer than 100 metres, roughly the length of a football pitch. As late as the 1970s, officials justified this exclusion on the basis that “women are too weak and fragile” and their “reproductive organs would get damaged.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 1967 Kathrine Switzer entered the male-only Boston Marathon under her initials, K.V. Switzer. Once the starting gun had been fired, race official Jock Semple realised that a woman was running and tried to manhandle her off the course, bellowing “Get the hell out of my race,” before Switzer’s male running partner shoved him aside. Switzer completed the run in 4 hours 20 minutes, disproving claims that women were too frail to run long distances. Boston Athletic Association director Will Cloney reacted by threatening “if that girl were my daughter, I would spank her.” But in 1972 the Boston Marathon directors capitulated and formally permitted women to run. Other marathons followed suit but change has been slow. Women’s distance-running events—those longer than 1,500 metres—were not included in the Olympics until 1984.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The history of women’s exclusion still hangs over the running world. Books on running typically feature a silhouette of a single, sleek male physique on the cover. Women are mostly invisible in the stories of bestsellers such as Christopher McDougall’s “Born to Run”, a macho account of ultra-runners in Mexico and America. Those who do appear are scrutinised with the male gaze. In his memoir, “What I Talk About When I Talk About Running”, novelist Haruki Murakami depicts long-distance running as a serious test of mental and physical endurance closely aligned with novel writing. But only the men in his book are up to the task. Its women, with their “blonde hair in a ponytail, and brand-new iPods” are “more mentally cut out for brief runs at high speed.” “Still,” Murakami consoles himself, “it’s pretty wonderful to watch these pretty girls run.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women’s exclusion from running played on my mind in July last year in the Ultimate Trails race, a 55km route around England’s Lake District. Compared with other races in which I’ve participated, the number of women on the start line was unusually high. Female participation in running has steadily risen at all distances and levels since the 1980s. Women’s presence in ultra-distance trail races increased from about 5% of all contestants in the 1990s to around 20-25% today, but it is still well short of parity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cause and consequence of this imbalance is that most races are designed with men in mind. Rules and regulations are often based on the assumption that runners have male bodies. The 106-mile Ultra-Trail du Mont Blanc (UTMB) is one of the most famous and popular trail races in the world. Runners who achieve a rare, hard-won place and then develop an injury can defer to a later year. But female competitors who become pregnant or give birth are not offered a deferral and can obtain a refund only if the race occurs within 15 days of giving birth, after which women are considered to have returned to race form.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A photograph of a runner called Sophie Power at a checkpoint during the 2018 race, breast-feeding her three-month-old son while also expressing milk, went viral as a “powerful and positive” image of a mother’s autonomous identity and strength. Yet it also encapsulated the sexist inconsistency of the UTMB’s deferral policy. Power went to extraordinary lengths to compete: she put aside extra time for expressing; arranged to meet and feed her son during a long, often remote event; and raced that distance in the wake of a lighter training load during pregnancy, the physical exertion of childbirth, and the sleep deprivation that follows.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Long-distance races usually set “cut-offs”, deadlines by which runners must have passed certain points or finished. Cut-offs allow organisers and marshalls to pack up and re-open roads, but they also filter slower runners from the competition. At all levels, from amateur to elite, and at all distances, from 100 metres to 1,000 miles, men’s higher aerobic capacity, lower body fat, greater haemoglobin content and muscle mass, bigger hearts and larger proportion of fast-twitch muscles, make the average male runner around 10% quicker than the average female competitor (although this varies according to distance). So the more stringent the cut-off, the more disproportionately will female competitors be timed out or deterred from entering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This phenomenon is visible in the annual Lakeland Trails marathon around Coniston in the Lake District. There are two versions: both are the same length, but one, the Challenge, has a liberal cut-off of eight hours, and the other, the Race, ends after only six. Female participation in the Challenge is high at around 50%. But it is only 25% in the Race, even though around half of female Challenge finishers typically complete in under six hours anyway. Sports-science studies confirm the obvious implication: men tend to overestimate their speediness but women do the opposite and underestimate their own abilities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When women are included in competitions, it’s often grudging. Women’s races are frequently accorded less time and space than men’s. The English Cross Country Association—the governing body of cross-country running in England—still allows women in the national championships to run only 8km, two-thirds of the length of the men’s race. In the South of England Championships, men run almost twice as far as women. The World Mountain Running Association had the same rules—senior women raced 8km compared with men’s 12km—until January 2017, when they responded positively to a campaign to equalise men’s and women’s distances to 10km each.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preventing women from running as far as men is partly the legacy of Victorian anxiety about women’s lack of endurance, and partly based on “traditionalists’” argument that “women are not as fast” and require a shorter race “so that it takes the same amount of time”. But, as campaigner Maud Hodson points out, women are not a third or half as slow as men, as the cropping of their races might suggest. And, in any case, the South of England Championship doesn’t actually equalise the time spent on the men’s and women’s races. Male runners are granted twice the time women are—90 minutes to women’s 45—which assumes that they are in fact running at the same speed. With double the time and almost double the distance of the women, are men considered “twice as important”?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190629_efd_002.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;This matters. It’s important that women are included in running events, that the specificities of our bodies and lives are considered. The presence of other women in a run can offer a kind of solidarity, a diminished embarrassment derived from shared bodily experience, especially when it comes to the more intimate aspects of ultra-running, such as going to the toilet out in the open. Most importantly, running offers specific joys that are often missing from women’s lives: a focus on strength and health and pleasure rather than thinness and acquiescence. We should not be denied these opportunities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the morning of the Ultimate Trails race, the unusually hot weather forecast led the race directors to revise the mandatory kit list. Warm hats and waterproof trousers were struck off. Instead we were advised to carry two litres of water. I was conscious of the extra weight in my running pack as soon as we left Ambleside. The burning ache in my lower back gradually bore down into my thighs. By the time we reached a short section of road that rises steeply—aptly named “The Struggle”—each lift of a leg was immediately suckered back down again by gravity, and my pack was starting to rub against the edges of my breasts. The bag had been advertised as unisex. In reality it was cut for the planes of a man’s body.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Women’s running kit has been improving steadily since the 1980s. Shoes, for example, are now fitted to women’s physiology. But women still have far less choice than men. The Ultramarathon Running Store currently sells four times as many unisex—that is to say, male—running packs, as those cut for women. I have never found a running cap or pair of gloves tight enough to fit my only-slightly-smaller-than-average female body. At races, the smallest size of finishers’ T-shirt is often still way too big.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lack of specific provision undoubtedly reflects women’s lesser participation in running. But it works both ways. Bras with insufficient support, running packs chafing our breasts, hats and head-torches slipping down over our eyes are all irritants that disfigure our pleasure and discourage women from taking part. This discomfort starts young. Sports clothing advertised for girls is consistently less durable, less waterproof and less accommodating of movement than the equivalent for young boys.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Things are slowly changing. The standard approach to designing women’s garments has been to “shrink and pink” the male version, says Helen Stuart, a designer at Inov-8, which makes running gear. Stuart starts with the women’s design, then adapts it for men. Making products for female bodies is harder so it makes sense to begin with them, she argues. Innovative firms such as EVB Sport are producing active wear specifically to support women’s perineum, pelvic floor and core muscles. But they are still the exception.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the race’s first checkpoint, at the top of Kirkstone Pass, I needed to ease the pain caused by my poorly fitting hydration pack. I decided to reduce its weight, by emptying the reservoir and relying on the water in my flasks. Relieved of a kilo, my feet began to accelerate happily down the path towards Brothers Water, a long downhill trail, peppered with large unstable stones that require nimble legs to sail over without injury. Within a mile, I was not only returned to mental and physical wellbeing, but leapt beyond it to what is often called “runner’s high”: the joy of efficiently working muscles and lungs, oblivion to pain or fatigue and sensory bliss; sun on my face, mountains mirrored in still water, shady paths quenching the skin.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Teetering down a rocky, ankle-imperilling descent into Grasmere, I had to brake suddenly and veer behind a hedge. Since giving birth to twins in 2014, my pelvic floor—the sling of muscles running from the back to the front of the body—has been shot to pieces. I’m one of around 35% of women in Britain who are affected by pelvic-floor disorders (compared with around 4% of men), a propensity that is hugely increased by pregnancy and birth, especially instrumental deliveries, and exacerbated by a lack of post-natal care. In France, pelvic-floor physiotherapy is offered to post-partum women as standard; not so in Britain. Many go back to high-impact sports, such as running, that strain the pelvic floor, without adequate physical checks or advice, resulting in even greater damage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Childbirth has left me with a cystocele and rectocele (when the bladder and rectum respectively collapse into the vaginal wall) and a uterine prolapse (when the uterus drops into the vagina). These affect my running in different ways. The uterine prolapse is painful; an aching sensation, like a ball of descending pressure. But I wear a vaginal pessary, a sturdy silicone ring, slightly smaller than my palm, which sits neatly under my cervix as a crutch for my sagging uterus. Because of the cystocele, I also need to wear incontinence pads when I run. They need changing frequently, and during the Ultimate Trails race, I carried five, which took up more than half of my running pack.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s embarrassing, too. Trail races rarely pass public toilets, and many are unusable anyway. In Britain, since 2010 councils have given up the maintenance of 13% of public facilities, and as many as a third have closed entirely. When I’m out running, I have to duck behind a bush or wall to change my pad every 12km or so. I’m particularly leaky running downhill. If I don’t stop in time, my pad overflows, shadowing my shorts with urine, and it chafes too, rubbing my thighs sore. During my period, the whole procedure becomes even messier and I carry a small pack of wet-wipes to clean my hands of blood. It’s no surprise that a survey of female runners showed that many are deterred from long-distance running by the lack of toilet provision. The paucity of loos on a mountain or moor is unavoidable, and to an extent one becomes inured to pulling down your pants in the countryside. But city races present a much higher level of exposure and embarrassment. There is some hope, though. Louise Greenwood, race director of the Canalathon ultra in Rochdale, has secured permission from pubs en route for competitors to use their toilets. Nevertheless, there’s scope for urban races—where most runners start, and many consequently stop—to make much better provision for women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trail-running is as much about caring for your body as it is about revelling in the scenery. Every runner’s body has a series of eloquent “tells”. I’ve learned that I’m adequately hydrated, salted and fed when my inner voice exclaims with pleasant surprise, “I feel fine. I really do.” Or when I’m able to greet marshalls and other runners with chirpiness. Or when I can sigh happily at the top of a steep ascent, as gravity shifts from encumbrance to emancipation. But I know I’m getting closer to hitting the wall when I panic about mild physical niggles; when I feel bored or obsessed with the finish line; or when I’m grumpy and suffused with nausea. It has taken me years not only to develop this listening habit but to learn to act on it. Women are not supposed to care for our bodies. We’re supposed to beat them into submission instead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As I approached the final two miles of the race, I knew I’d got it right. I had enough energy to speed up, hurtling down the final paved slope, swooping over the footbridge and around the cricket pitch, and over the finish line in 10 hours 12 minutes. The finish-line photograph shows me sweaty, dusty, spots emerging across my face after spending a day doused in salt, hair matted against my head, and utterly triumphant and proud and strong and happy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Rachel Hewittis a lecturer in creative writing at Newcastle University. She is working on a book, “In Her Nature”, about women’s relationships with the natural world&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 29 Jun 2019 00:40:27 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What is a heatwave?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/the-economist-explains/2019/06/28/what-is-a-heatwave]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_BLP514.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T15:03:53Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THIS SUMMER Europe is sweltering in unusual temperatures. Germany, Poland and the Czech Republic have seen record-breaking temperatures for June. France has recorded its highest temperature—45.1C (113.2F)—of all time. Heatwave, scream myriad headlines. But what exactly is it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Martha and the Vandellas had a definition. According to their hit of the same name, released in 1963, a heatwave involved an inability to stop crying, the feeling of being possessed by the devil, high blood pressure, and a “burning in my heart”. Their wording is a model of precision compared with that provided by the World Meteorological Organisation (WMO), the UN agency that calls itself “the authoritative voice on the state and behaviour of the world’s atmosphere”. A heatwave, it says, is a “marked warming of the air, or the invasion of very warm air, over a large area; it usually lasts from a few days to a few weeks”. That sounds downright pleasant to residents of cooler climes and does not capture the lethal menace of the weather phenomenon. Is there not something more precise?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Governments have been late to the game when it comes to establishing exact criteria for heatwaves and public heat-warning systems. They have been more active since 2003, when stories about elderly people in France dying alone while their families were on holiday fed public outrage. And they have also responded to the increased frequency of periods of extreme heat in recent years. Yet a survey by the WMO in 2015 found that around one-third of countries still lacked criteria for defining and reacting to heatwaves. Worryingly there is no commonly accepted definition for the point at which the public should be alerted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some differences are logical because heatwave warnings depend in part on what residents are used to. The temperatures currently keeping Parisians sweating on the Metro would barely warrant a mention in Furnace Creek, California, which has recorded the world’s highest temperature (56.7°C, or 134°F, in 1913). It makes sense to tailor warnings to local conditions. For example, Environment Canada, a government department, warns residents of Prince Edward Island when the temperature will reach 27°C, but sets a threshold of 35°C for the arid interior of south-eastern British Columbia. But maximum temperature is only one of a number of variables that can add up to a killer heatwave. Others include humidity, air pollution, wind conditions, the minimum night-time temperature and how long the hot spell lasts. National definitions vary widely, depending on which of these variables are included, how they are measured, and even on the timing of warnings. An alert in England means the heatwave is expected within three days. In Belgium, it means the hot weather has already arrived.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The WMO is encouraging climate and health scientists to develop a measure that could be used more widely in forecasts and warnings. Many are in development, including a universal thermal climate index, which combines air temperature with measures of its effect on the human body. But for now, the answer to what is a heatwave is that it depends on where you are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 23:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“Yesterday” is more a love letter to the Beatles than a rom-com]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/28/yesterday-is-more-a-love-letter-to-the-beatles-than-a-rom-com]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_BKP511.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T11:20:54Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERE IS a particular genre of comedy in which an unremarkable man suddenly finds himself to be the only person in the world with some miraculous knowledge or power. He might have realised that he is stuck in a time loop (like Bill Murray in “Groundhog Day”), or gained the ability to fast-forward his life (like Adam Sandler in “Click”). Sometimes his gift is godly (such as Jim Carrey’s omnipotence in “Bruce Almighty”), and sometimes sinful (as for Ricky Gervais in “The Invention of Lying”). At first he marvels at his superpower. Then he abuses it. Eventually, he renounces it, having failed to woo a beautiful woman.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To that genre belongs “Yesterday”, a new comedy written by Richard Curtis (of “Notting Hill” fame) and directed by Danny Boyle (an Oscar winner for “Slumdog Millionaire”). This hero’s gift is zany. Jack (Himesh Patel), a shelf-stacker and frustrated busker, wakes up after a traffic accident to find that nobody else has heard of the Beatles. He records every tune that he can remember, winning fans on local radio, then at concerts, and finally with a juicy recording deal in America. Lily James plays Ellie, his old friend and love interest, whom Jack alienates as he becomes (to borrow &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/More_popular_than_Jesus&quot;&gt;John Lennon’s phrase&lt;/a&gt;) more popular than Jesus.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like “Groundhog Day” or “Bruce Almighty”, “Yesterday” gets most of its humour from the supernatural conceit, rather than its characters. The chemistry between ardent Jack and bashful Ellie is enough to keep the plot interesting, as the burgeoning superstar tries to win her over. But it would not carry a film without the Beatles premise. Nor does the patter among Jack’s friends and family produce much hilarity. There are few of the guffaw-inducing &lt;em&gt;faux pas&lt;/em&gt; or witty ripostes that made Mr Curtis’s early work, such as “Blackadder” and “Four Weddings and a Funeral”, so entertaining.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Debra (Kate McKinnon), Jack’s mercenary American manager, yields a few chuckles: she describes Jack’s own, non-Beatles, compositions as “simple but not charming”. Yet her character does little else than tempt Jack with “the poisoned chalice of fame and money”. (“In the name of money, stop!” she yells when he is on the verge of giving it all away.) Ed Sheeran makes a lengthy cameo as an insufferable version of himself, insisting that Jack should call his masterpiece “Hey Dude”, among other unhelpful suggestions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp510.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp510.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp510.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp510.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp510.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp510.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp510.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp510.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp510.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/prospero/20190629_bkp510.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is that sort of riffing on the Fab Four’s work that produces most of the laughs. When Jack first plays “Yesterday” to his friends, one of them remarks that it is hardly as good as Coldplay. His parents refer to his new piano ballad as “Leave It Be”. Jack himself struggles to remember what exactly Eleanor Rigby was doing in the church—a challenge that even Beatles aficionados will find tricky without looking up the lyrics.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The film was made for that sort of fan. Mr Boyle has called it his “love letter to the Beatles and their music”. By coincidence, he and Mr Curtis—who had previously written “The Boat That Rocked”, a film about pirate radio stations in the 1960s—are standing next to each other on &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.telegraph.co.uk/culture/music/music-news/9179906/Sgt-Pepper-revisited-for-2012.html&quot;&gt;a commemorative version of the famous “Sgt. Pepper” album cover&lt;/a&gt;, which Sir Peter Blake, the original artist, redesigned for his 80th birthday in 2012. They have woven countless references to the songs into the script. Jack’s traffic accident occurs to the sound of the crashing piano chords from “A Day in the Life”. While fixing Jack’s teeth, his local dentist explains that he gets by with a little help from his friends. Jack’s first concert as Mr Sheeran’s supporting act is in Russia, and he opens with “Back in the U.S.S.R.”. (Extra keen viewers will even notice mentions of lesser-known tracks, such as “Maxwell’s Silver Hammer” and “Being for the Benefit of Mr Kite”.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like any Beatles composition, there are a couple of profound moments among the fun. The most memorable is an unexpected appearance from a very important figure, who arrives to remind Jack that sometimes love is all you need. That poignant cameo alone is enough to make this essential viewing for any fan of the Fab Four.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other spine-tingling scene comes when a jealous Mr Sheeran challenges Jack, in front of his entourage, to write the best song possible in ten minutes. After the pop star comes up with something vapid about penguins, Jack sits at the piano to play “The Long and Winding Road”. Everyone is spellbound. As Jack points out earlier in the film, when his audience hears one of the songs for the first time, it is “like watching Leonardo da Vinci painting the Mona Lisa right in front of your bloody eyes”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This film is very different to the recent biopics of Freddie Mercury (“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/prospero/2018/10/26/bohemian-rhapsody-is-more-fantasy-than-real-life&quot;&gt;Bohemian Rhapsody&lt;/a&gt;”) and Elton John (“&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/20/rocketman-is-a-suitably-ostentatious-biopic-of-elton-john&quot;&gt;Rocketman&lt;/a&gt;”). But like those dramas, it is a paean to song-writing genius. The disbelief that Jack could compose so many brilliant tunes is a reminder of the improbability that four normal lads from Liverpool actually did produce them. At some point Lennon, Paul McCartney, George Harrison and Ringo Starr were all exasperated nobodies, who gradually astounded the world with their songs. Lucky for the world that they did—and that it will never wake up to find their records have disappeared from the shelf.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Yesterday” is released worldwide on June 28th &lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 20:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Globalisation is dead and we need to invent a new world order]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/28/globalisation-is-dead-and-we-need-to-invent-a-new-world-order]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_OPP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T09:51:59Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAS THE world witnessed “peak democracy”? Is the future one in which open societies with free markets vie for influence in global affairs with authoritarian countries under state capitalism? The very questions evoke a nostalgia for a seemingly simpler past. For Michael O’Sullivan, formerly an investment banker and economist at Princeton University, it is more useful to consider the future. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr O’Sullivan’s book, “The Levelling: What&amp;#x27;s Next After Globalisation” offers a roadmap. He sees a multipolar world forming but international institutions unprepared for this. He voices worries about a world of low growth and high debt—and calls for a “world treaty on risk” so central banks only resort to measures like quantitative easing under agreed conditions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But his most intriguing framing of the issues is his comparison of today’s world and 17th century England’s Putney Debates, when the practicalities of a rights-based democracy were first enunciated by a faction called “ The Levellers” (which inspired the book’s title). The world, he believes, will cleave into “Leveller” countries that hew to rights and freedoms, and “Leviathan” ones that are content with state-managed growth and fewer liberties. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s Open Future initiative, we probed Mr O’Sullivan ideas in a short interview. Below that is an excerpt from his book, on the end of globalisation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* * *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: Describe what comes after globalisation—what does the world you foresee look like?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr O&amp;#x27;Sullivan&lt;/strong&gt;: Globalisation is already behind us. We should say goodbye to it and set our minds on the emerging multipolar world. This will be dominated by at least three large regions: America, the European Union and a China-centric Asia. They will increasingly take very different approaches to economic policy, liberty, warfare, technology and society. Mid-sized countries like Russia, Britain, Australia and Japan will struggle to find their place in the world, while new coalitions will emerge, such as a “Hanseatic League 2.0” of small, advanced states like those of Scandinavia and the Baltics. Institutions of the 20th century—the World Bank, the International Monetary Fund and the World Trade Organisation—will appear increasingly defunct. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: What killed globalisation?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael O&amp;#x27;Sullivan: At least two things have put paid to globalisation. First, global economic growth has slowed, and as a result, the growth has become more “financialised”: debt has increased and there has been more “monetary activism”—that is, central banks pumping money into the economy by buying assets, such as bonds and in some cases even equities—to sustain the international expansion. Second, the side effects, or rather the perceived side-effects, of globalisation are more apparent: wealth inequality, the dominance of multinationals and the dispersion of global supply chains, which have all become hot political issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: Was the death of globalisation inevitable or could (and should) it have been prevented?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr O&amp;#x27;Sullivan&lt;/strong&gt;: One problematic factor here is that there is no central body or authority to shape globalisation, beyond perhaps the World Economic Forum or maybe the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development. In many ways, the end of globalisation is marked by the poor and inconclusive response to the global financial crisis. In general, the response has been to cut the cost of capital and not to tackle the root causes of the crisis. As such, the world economy will limp on, burdened by debt and in hock to easy money from central banks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: The book&amp;#x27;s title comes from the &amp;quot;Levellers&amp;quot; during Britain&amp;#x27;s Putney Debates in the mid 1600s. Who were they and what can their story teach us today? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr O&amp;#x27;Sullivan&lt;/strong&gt;: The Levellers are a hidden gem from British history. They were a mid 17th century group in England, who participated in debates about democracy that took place in a part of London called Putney. Their achievement was crafting “An Agreement of the People,” which were a series of manifestos that marked the first popular conceptions of what a constitutional democracy might look like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Levellers are interesting for two reasons. First, in the context of the time, their approach was constructive and practical. The “Agreement” spells out what people want from those who govern them in a clear and tangible way. For example, they proposed term limits on political office and that laws regarding indebtedness are applied equally to the rich and poor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second, they are interesting for the way the movement was countermanded and then snuffed out by the military leader Oliver Cromwell and the Grandees (the elites of their day). Like so many idealistic political start-ups, the Levellers failed. This should encourage the growing number of new political parties, like Change UK and new candidates to be worldy-wise in how they approach the process of political reform and change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: You foresee new international institutions to replace archaic 20th-century ones that are suited for a different time. How would they work? And can countries with such different values (ie, democratic, market-based &amp;quot;Levellers&amp;quot; and state-managed societies and economies, the &amp;quot;Leviathans&amp;quot;) really cooperate?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr O&amp;#x27;Sullivan&lt;/strong&gt;: A lot is made of the Cold War rivalry between communist Russia and America, and now some want to see a clash of civilizations between America and China. The “Levelling” characterises a future where there are at least two approaches to public life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most distinctive approach to nations doing things in their own way will be for what the Levellers might call the “rights of freeborn men,” or the idea of the open society. The code of the Levellers presents a very clear political formula that Europeans and Americans will recognise for its values, though decreasingly in its practice. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The challenge to this code will come from the rising acceptance of less democratic ways of ordering society, in both developed and developing countries. A related clash will be the desire of a growing proportion of electorates to have a more open society as economies also open up. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the world evolves along the lines of Leveller-type and Leviathan-type societies, it is possible that in some countries, such as Russia, a Leviathan-like approach—that is, order in exchange for reduced democracy and rights—will be the accepted way of life. In other countries, most interestingly China, as its economy loses momentum and evolves, there may be a growing tension between groups holding the Leviathan view (supported inevitably by Grandees) and opposing Leveller-like groups (who favor equality of opportunity and a multiparty system). The role and views of women, especially in China, and of minority groups like the gay community will be pivotal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The emergence of a new world order, based on large regions and coloured by Leveller and Leviathan modes of governance, echoes several periods in history. The challenge in the next few years will be for Leviathan-oriented nations like China to maintain economic stability so that rising unemployment, for instance, does not break the “Leviathan contract”. Equally, the challenge in Leveller countries will be to maintain open, fraternal societies in the face of political and potentially economic volatility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* * *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Good-bye to Globalisation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Excerpted from “The Levelling: What&amp;#x27;s Next After Globalization” by Michael O&amp;#x27;Sullivan (PublicAffairs, 2019).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may well be better that those who have grown fond of globalization get over it, accept its passing, and begin to adjust to a new reality. Many will resist and, like the thirty-five foreign-policy experts who published an advertisement in the New York Times on July 26, 2018, under the banner “Why We Should Preserve International Institutions and Order,” will feel that the existing world order and its institutions should be maintained. I disagree. Globalization, at least in the form that people have come to enjoy it, is defunct. From here, the passage away from globalization can take two new forms. One dangerous scenario is that we witness the outright end of globalization in much the same manner as the first period of globalization collapsed in 1913. This scenario is a favorite of commentators because it allows them to write about bloody end-of-the-world calamities. This is, thankfully, a low-probability outcome, and with apologies to the many armchair admirals in the commentariat who, for instance, talk willfully of a conflict in the South China Sea, I suggest that a full-scale sea battle between China and the United States is unlikely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, the evolution of a new world order—a fully multipolar world composed of three (perhaps four, depending on how India develops) large regions that are distinct in the workings of their economies, laws, cultures, and security networks—is manifestly underway. My sense is that until 2018, multipolarity was a more theoretical concept—more something to write about than to witness. This is changing quickly: trade tensions, advances in technologies (such as quantum computing), and the regulation of technology are just some of the fissures around which the world is splitting into distinct regions. Multipolarity is gaining traction and will have two broad axes. First, the poles in the multipolar world have to be large in terms of economic, financial, and geopolitical power. Second, the essence of multipolarity is not simply that the poles are large and powerful but also that they develop distinct, culturally consistent ways of doing things. Multipolarity, where regions do things distinctly and differently, is also very different from multilateralism, where they do them together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China, in particular, is interesting in the context of the switch from globalization to multipolarity, not least because at the 2017 World Economic Forum the Chinese president claimed the mantle of globalization for China. China benefited greatly from globalization and its accoutrements (e.g., WTO membership), and it played a vital role in the supply-chain dynamic that drove globalization. However, trade flows into China increasingly betray a move away from a globalized world and toward a more regionally focused one. For instance, IMF data show that in 2018, compared with 2011, Cambodia, Vietnam, Laos, and Malaysia traded more with China and relatively less with the United States. These countries, together with Bangladesh and Pakistan, have allowed themselves to be enticed by trade- and investment-based relationships with China and are now in its orbit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, China is itself not globalized: it is increasingly hard for Western companies to do business there on equal terms with Chinese companies, and the flow of both money and ideas—out of and into China, respectively—is heavily curtailed. Flow of people is another indicator. Flows within China are dynamic and are perhaps more managed than before, but flows of foreigners into China are miniscule by comparison to other countries, and China has only recently established an agency (the State Immigration Administration created at the 2018 Party Congress) to cultivate inward flows. So as China has become a major pole, it has become less globalized and arguably is contributing to the trend toward deglobalization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On a broader scale, without picking on individual countries, we can measure the extent to which the world is becoming multipolar by examining aggregate trends in trade, GDP, foreign direct investment, government budget size, and population. All of these are much less concentrated, or more dispersed, than they used to be, and increasingly they are collecting around several poles. For example, in the five years from 2012 to 2017, total foreign direct investment into Australia from China increased at a rate of 21 percent per annum, compared to 6 percent from the United States to Australia, suggesting that Asian investment in Australia is picking up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[…]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if multipolarity is based on the growing dispersion and regionalization of economic power, it is also expressed in other ways, notably military power, political and cyberfreedoms, technological sophistication, financial sector growth, and a greater sense of cultural prerogative and confidence. These are not as easily measured as economic multipolarity, but some clear strands are emerging. To try to synthesize what a pole entails, we can point toward several initial factors: size of a country’s GDP, size of its population, the existence of an imperial legacy, the extent of its regional economic role, its military size and sophistication (e.g., absolute spending, number of fighter jets and ships), its place on the UN Human Development Index relative to its region, and its participation (or not) in a regional grouping (such as NATO or the European Union).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under this schema the European Union, the United States, China, and potentially India are poles, but Japan and Russia would not qualify as distinct poles. Russia, for instance, scores well on certain aspects of multipolarity (e.g., militarily), but in its current state it may never become a true pole in the sense employed here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[…]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The path toward multipolarity will not be smooth. One tension is that since the Industrial Revolution the world has had an anchor point in terms of the locus and spread of globalization (Britain in the nineteenth century and the United States in the twentieth century). The fact that there are now at least three points of reference introduces a new and possibly uncertain dynamic to world affairs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The potential is high for friction, misunderstanding, and conflict among the increasingly different ways of doing things across the major poles. Essentially, multipolarity means that instead of speaking a common language, the major poles speak different policy languages. Trade-based tension is an obvious possibility here. Another form of tension is the crisis of identity created for countries that are not wholly within one of the poles—again, Japan, Australia, and the United Kingdom are the prime examples—and the crisis of ambition for countries, such as Russia, that want to be poles but lack the wherewithal to do so convincingly. At a more grassroots level, the implications of the end of globalization as we know it and the path to multipolarity will become a greater part of the political debate. At the margin, the flow of people, ideas, and capital may be less global and more regional and in time could be reinforced by a growing sense of regionalization across the main poles. In a negative way, a more multipolar world may be the watershed that signals the peak of democracy and potentially the beginning of contests within regions for competing views of democracy, institutional strength, statecraft, and control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;_______________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Excerpted from “The Levelling: What&amp;#x27;s Next After Globalization.” Copyright © 2019 by Michael O&amp;#x27;Sullivan. Used with permission of PublicAffairs (Hachette Book Group). All rights reserved.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 20:40:12 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Globalisation is dead and we need to invent a world order]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/06/28/globalisation-is-dead-and-we-need-to-invent-a-world-order]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190629_OPP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-28T09:51:59Z&quot;&gt;Jun 28th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAS THE world witnessed “peak democracy”? Is the future one in which open societies with free markets vie for influence in global affairs with authoritarian countries under state capitalism? The very questions evoke a nostalgia for a seemingly simpler past. For Michael O’Sullivan, formerly an investment banker and economist at Princeton University, it is more useful to consider the future. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr O’Sullivan’s book, “The Levelling: What&amp;#x27;s Next After Globalisation” offers a roadmap. He sees a multipolar world forming but international institutions unprepared for this. He voices worries about a world of low growth and high debt—and calls for a “world treaty on risk” so central banks only resort to measures like quantitative easing under agreed conditions. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But his most intriguing framing of the issues is his comparison of today’s world and 17th century England’s Putney Debates, when the practicalities of a rights-based democracy were first enunciated by a faction called “ The Levellers” (which inspired the book’s title). The world, he believes, will cleave into “Leveller” countries that hew to rights and freedoms, and “Leviathan” ones that are content with state-managed growth and fewer liberties. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s Open Future initiative, we probed Mr O’Sullivan ideas in a short interview. Below that is an excerpt from his book, on the end of globalisation. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* * *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: Describe what comes after globalisation—what does the world you foresee look like?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp501.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr O&amp;#x27;Sullivan&lt;/strong&gt;: Globalisation is already behind us. We should say goodbye to it and set our minds on the emerging multipolar world. This will be dominated by at least three large regions: America, the European Union and a China-centric Asia. They will increasingly take very different approaches to economic policy, liberty, warfare, technology and society. Mid-sized countries like Russia, Britain, Australia and Japan will struggle to find their place in the world, while new coalitions will emerge, such as a “Hanseatic League 2.0” of small, advanced states like those of Scandinavia and the Baltics. Institutions of the 20th century—the World Bank, the International Monetary Fund and the World Trade Organisation—will appear increasingly defunct. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: What killed globalisation?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Michael O&amp;#x27;Sullivan: At least two things have put paid to globalisation. First, global economic growth has slowed, and as a result, the growth has become more “financialised”: debt has increased and there has been more “monetary activism”—that is, central banks pumping money into the economy by buying assets, such as bonds and in some cases even equities—to sustain the international expansion. Second, the side effects, or rather the perceived side-effects, of globalisation are more apparent: wealth inequality, the dominance of multinationals and the dispersion of global supply chains, which have all become hot political issues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: Was the death of globalisation inevitable or could (and should) it have been prevented?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr O&amp;#x27;Sullivan&lt;/strong&gt;: One problematic factor here is that there is no central body or authority to shape globalisation, beyond perhaps the World Economic Forum or maybe the Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development. In many ways, the end of globalisation is marked by the poor and inconclusive response to the global financial crisis. In general, the response has been to cut the cost of capital and not to tackle the root causes of the crisis. As such, the world economy will limp on, burdened by debt and in hock to easy money from central banks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: The book&amp;#x27;s title comes from the &amp;quot;Levellers&amp;quot; during Britain&amp;#x27;s Putney Debates in the mid 1600s. Who were they and what can their story teach us today? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr O&amp;#x27;Sullivan&lt;/strong&gt;: The Levellers are a hidden gem from British history. They were a mid 17th century group in England, who participated in debates about democracy that took place in a part of London called Putney. Their achievement was crafting “An Agreement of the People,” which were a series of manifestos that marked the first popular conceptions of what a constitutional democracy might look like.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Levellers are interesting for two reasons. First, in the context of the time, their approach was constructive and practical. The “Agreement” spells out what people want from those who govern them in a clear and tangible way. For example, they proposed term limits on political office and that laws regarding indebtedness are applied equally to the rich and poor.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second, they are interesting for the way the movement was countermanded and then snuffed out by the military leader Oliver Cromwell and the Grandees (the elites of their day). Like so many idealistic political start-ups, the Levellers failed. This should encourage the growing number of new political parties, like Change UK and new candidates to be worldy-wise in how they approach the process of political reform and change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist&lt;/strong&gt;: You foresee new international institutions to replace archaic 20th-century ones that are suited for a different time. How would they work? And can countries with such different values (ie, democratic, market-based &amp;quot;Levellers&amp;quot; and state-managed societies and economies, the &amp;quot;Leviathans&amp;quot;) really cooperate?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mr O&amp;#x27;Sullivan&lt;/strong&gt;: A lot is made of the Cold War rivalry between communist Russia and America, and now some want to see a clash of civilizations between America and China. The “Levelling” characterises a future where there are at least two approaches to public life.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The most distinctive approach to nations doing things in their own way will be for what the Levellers might call the “rights of freeborn men,” or the idea of the open society. The code of the Levellers presents a very clear political formula that Europeans and Americans will recognise for its values, though decreasingly in its practice. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The challenge to this code will come from the rising acceptance of less democratic ways of ordering society, in both developed and developing countries. A related clash will be the desire of a growing proportion of electorates to have a more open society as economies also open up. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the world evolves along the lines of Leveller-type and Leviathan-type societies, it is possible that in some countries, such as Russia, a Leviathan-like approach—that is, order in exchange for reduced democracy and rights—will be the accepted way of life. In other countries, most interestingly China, as its economy loses momentum and evolves, there may be a growing tension between groups holding the Leviathan view (supported inevitably by Grandees) and opposing Leveller-like groups (who favor equality of opportunity and a multiparty system). The role and views of women, especially in China, and of minority groups like the gay community will be pivotal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The emergence of a new world order, based on large regions and coloured by Leveller and Leviathan modes of governance, echoes several periods in history. The challenge in the next few years will be for Leviathan-oriented nations like China to maintain economic stability so that rising unemployment, for instance, does not break the “Leviathan contract”. Equally, the challenge in Leveller countries will be to maintain open, fraternal societies in the face of political and potentially economic volatility.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;* * *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Good-bye to Globalisation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Excerpted from “The Levelling: What&amp;#x27;s Next After Globalization” by Michael O&amp;#x27;Sullivan (PublicAffairs, 2019).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/blogs/open-future/20190629_opp502.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may well be better that those who have grown fond of globalization get over it, accept its passing, and begin to adjust to a new reality. Many will resist and, like the thirty-five foreign-policy experts who published an advertisement in the New York Times on July 26, 2018, under the banner “Why We Should Preserve International Institutions and Order,” will feel that the existing world order and its institutions should be maintained. I disagree. Globalization, at least in the form that people have come to enjoy it, is defunct. From here, the passage away from globalization can take two new forms. One dangerous scenario is that we witness the outright end of globalization in much the same manner as the first period of globalization collapsed in 1913. This scenario is a favorite of commentators because it allows them to write about bloody end-of-the-world calamities. This is, thankfully, a low-probability outcome, and with apologies to the many armchair admirals in the commentariat who, for instance, talk willfully of a conflict in the South China Sea, I suggest that a full-scale sea battle between China and the United States is unlikely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Instead, the evolution of a new world order—a fully multipolar world composed of three (perhaps four, depending on how India develops) large regions that are distinct in the workings of their economies, laws, cultures, and security networks—is manifestly underway. My sense is that until 2018, multipolarity was a more theoretical concept—more something to write about than to witness. This is changing quickly: trade tensions, advances in technologies (such as quantum computing), and the regulation of technology are just some of the fissures around which the world is splitting into distinct regions. Multipolarity is gaining traction and will have two broad axes. First, the poles in the multipolar world have to be large in terms of economic, financial, and geopolitical power. Second, the essence of multipolarity is not simply that the poles are large and powerful but also that they develop distinct, culturally consistent ways of doing things. Multipolarity, where regions do things distinctly and differently, is also very different from multilateralism, where they do them together.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China, in particular, is interesting in the context of the switch from globalization to multipolarity, not least because at the 2017 World Economic Forum the Chinese president claimed the mantle of globalization for China. China benefited greatly from globalization and its accoutrements (e.g., WTO membership), and it played a vital role in the supply-chain dynamic that drove globalization. However, trade flows into China increasingly betray a move away from a globalized world and toward a more regionally focused one. For instance, IMF data show that in 2018, compared with 2011, Cambodia, Vietnam, Laos, and Malaysia traded more with China and relatively less with the United States. These countries, together with Bangladesh and Pakistan, have allowed themselves to be enticed by trade- and investment-based relationships with China and are now in its orbit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, China is itself not globalized: it is increasingly hard for Western companies to do business there on equal terms with Chinese companies, and the flow of both money and ideas—out of and into China, respectively—is heavily curtailed. Flow of people is another indicator. Flows within China are dynamic and are perhaps more managed than before, but flows of foreigners into China are miniscule by comparison to other countries, and China has only recently established an agency (the State Immigration Administration created at the 2018 Party Congress) to cultivate inward flows. So as China has become a major pole, it has become less globalized and arguably is contributing to the trend toward deglobalization.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On a broader scale, without picking on individual countries, we can measure the extent to which the world is becoming multipolar by examining aggregate trends in trade, GDP, foreign direct investment, government budget size, and population. All of these are much less concentrated, or more dispersed, than they used to be, and increasingly they are collecting around several poles. For example, in the five years from 2012 to 2017, total foreign direct investment into Australia from China increased at a rate of 21 percent per annum, compared to 6 percent from the United States to Australia, suggesting that Asian investment in Australia is picking up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[…]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even if multipolarity is based on the growing dispersion and regionalization of economic power, it is also expressed in other ways, notably military power, political and cyberfreedoms, technological sophistication, financial sector growth, and a greater sense of cultural prerogative and confidence. These are not as easily measured as economic multipolarity, but some clear strands are emerging. To try to synthesize what a pole entails, we can point toward several initial factors: size of a country’s GDP, size of its population, the existence of an imperial legacy, the extent of its regional economic role, its military size and sophistication (e.g., absolute spending, number of fighter jets and ships), its place on the UN Human Development Index relative to its region, and its participation (or not) in a regional grouping (such as NATO or the European Union).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Under this schema the European Union, the United States, China, and potentially India are poles, but Japan and Russia would not qualify as distinct poles. Russia, for instance, scores well on certain aspects of multipolarity (e.g., militarily), but in its current state it may never become a true pole in the sense employed here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[…]&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The path toward multipolarity will not be smooth. One tension is that since the Industrial Revolution the world has had an anchor point in terms of the locus and spread of globalization (Britain in the nineteenth century and the United States in the twentieth century). The fact that there are now at least three points of reference introduces a new and possibly uncertain dynamic to world affairs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The potential is high for friction, misunderstanding, and conflict among the increasingly different ways of doing things across the major poles. Essentially, multipolarity means that instead of speaking a common language, the major poles speak different policy languages. Trade-based tension is an obvious possibility here. Another form of tension is the crisis of identity created for countries that are not wholly within one of the poles—again, Japan, Australia, and the United Kingdom are the prime examples—and the crisis of ambition for countries, such as Russia, that want to be poles but lack the wherewithal to do so convincingly. At a more grassroots level, the implications of the end of globalization as we know it and the path to multipolarity will become a greater part of the political debate. At the margin, the flow of people, ideas, and capital may be less global and more regional and in time could be reinforced by a growing sense of regionalization across the main poles. In a negative way, a more multipolar world may be the watershed that signals the peak of democracy and potentially the beginning of contests within regions for competing views of democracy, institutional strength, statecraft, and control.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;_______________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Excerpted from “The Levelling: What&amp;#x27;s Next After Globalization.” Copyright © 2019 by Michael O&amp;#x27;Sullivan. Used with permission of PublicAffairs (Hachette Book Group). All rights reserved.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 18:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>