<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[King Vajiralongkorn of Thailand is crowned]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/05/04/king-vajiralongkorn-of-thailand-is-crowned]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190511_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-04T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE TENTH MEMBER of the Chakri dynasty, which has ruled Thailand for more than two centuries, appeared initially in a pair of slippers. They matched a white robe, bordered in gold, which he donned for the first ritual of his coronation day on May 4th, initiating three days of celebrations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Almost exactly 69 years ago King Maha Vajiralongkorn’s more popular father, the late King Bhumibol Adulyadej, appeared similarly garbed for his own sequence of Buddhist and Hindu ceremonies. Then as now, a military regime ran the country. Ahead of a stage-managed election last month, King Vajiralongkorn made plain in public statements his desire for soldiers to continue running affairs. Thailand’s new monarch is a meddler.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So much for the similarities between father and son. In many ways, King Vajiralongkorn is unique. Preferring to live in Germany rather than Thailand, he spends little time in his own country. Scandal dogs him. After a string of abandoned consorts and seven children, news of his fourth marriage broke just days before his coronation. Since his father’s death in 2016 he has also amassed power. Last year it was announced that the assets of a royal investment portfolio—estimated to be worth around $40bn—would be considered his personal property. (He has agreed to pay tax on the haul.) The king has also reshaped the court and the Buddhist priesthood.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His coronation day began with a purification ceremony at the royal residence in Bangkok. Holy water was poured over his head and dripped down his back. In preparation the liquid had been collected from 76 provinces, as well as from around Bangkok, in recent weeks. Courtiers and other bigwigs wore spotless white uniforms. They crawled up the steps leading to their seated monarch, bowing repeatedly when they got to the top. The dousing was probably quite pleasant: roasting temperatures would have made the more ornate outfits unbearably hot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After changing into an embroidered golden suit and coat for an anointing ceremony, the king was attended by some of the country’s most powerful figures. Those involved in the anointment rituals included the ancient head of his Privy Council and Prayuth Chan-ocha, the coup-leader who is Thailand’s current prime minister. Thanks to a rigged electoral system, the latter is all but guaranteed to hold onto office after the final results from the recent election are released in full this week—as long as that pleases his majesty, of course.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While awaiting coronation the king received several ornate symbolic objects, including a sceptre, a sword, a fly whisk, a fan, a pair of golden shoes and “the great crown of victory”. Its crust of gold and diamonds brings its weight to more than 7kg, and not even respectful Thai cameramen could hide its awkward teetering. Once crowned, the king uttered his first pronouncement, which echoed that of his father, promising to reign with “righteousness” for the benefit of his people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Among the myriad other rites, particular excitement surrounds a grand procession that will take place on May 5th. It will see the king carried in public on his gilded palanquin through the streets of Bangkok. Given the huge crowds who camped for days to witness rituals associated with the cremation of King Bhumibol, the turnout for the procession will be a marker of King Vajiralongkorn’s popularity. Text messages urging Thais to attend have been delivered en masse. Thousands of civil servants and other officials have been bussed in for the long weekend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thais have been encouraged to don yellow, the royal colour, over the coronation period, although a short trip on a local train reveals a lack of broad enthusiasm for this edict. There are some ardent monarchists, however. Standing close to the palace area, yellow-clad Surang Sri-ruang explains that she has travelled from Chiang Mai, a distant northern city, especially for the coronation. Her love of the late king necessitates her love of his son, she says. “It is a once-in-a-lifetime event that I really need to attend to express my loyalty.” Linda Wornkham, a businesswoman from Ayutthaya, an ancient former capital, agrees. “I’m so happy to be here,” she says. The king, for his part, looked stony-faced throughout the proceedings. If precedent is any guide, he will soon be on a flight back to Munich.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2019 02:08:49 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The case for weighing passengers before flights]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/gulliver/2019/05/03/the-case-for-weighing-passengers-before-flights]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_BLP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-03T20:36:32Z&quot;&gt;May 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;A FAVOURITE PASTIME of air passengers is to moan about all the extra fees that airlines have introduced in recent years. First came charges for stowing baggage in the hold, then more for in-flight food, allocated seating and even for using the overhead lockers. Yet would the idea to charge passengers according to their weight be one extra fee too far?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;This is exactly what could be done with a proposal from Fuel Matrix, a British firm, to weigh passengers before boarding a flight. The company is currently in talks with several airports about “discreet” ways to introduce weighing technology. According to the company’s chief executive, Roy Fuscone, flyers’ weights will be stored in the same secure system as facial-recognition data, another technology some airports are trying out to eliminate the need for paper tickets at boarding gates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Such an approach could easily go down very badly with some flyers. Some would cynically see it as simply a means of charging larger passengers extra. And it would culturally grate in some parts of the world, such as America, where “fat shaming” is socially unacceptable. (For example, when “Thomas the Tank Engine”, a British children’s television programme, was dubbed into American English, the name of an obese character called the “Fat Controller” had to be changed because it was regarded as too rude for American youngsters).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Yet weighing passengers used to be the norm, particularly in the early days of aviation. Before the second world war, most passengers in America and Europe were weighed before take-off and charged more for extra heft (see picture). This was because early planes were smaller and had strict weight limits. For instance, on the inaugural flight of the Boeing 247 airliner in 1933, from San Francisco to New York, the plane could not carry more than 16,805 pounds (7,621kg) including fuel. So the ten passengers with tickets had to get on the scale, as did and their flight attendant, who could not weigh more than 135 pounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;That practice was phased out as airlines began to rely on broad guidelines to estimate how much passengers weighed. But to be on the safe side, that means airlines carry much more fuel than they need to for each passenger. Airline executives reckon that carrying all that extra unnecessary kerosene around itself burns a surprising amount of fuel. That not only pushes the cost of tickets up, but also means that far more emissions are produced than is needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;From there comes the temptation for airlines to start weighing passengers again. In 2013 Samoa Air in the Pacific began to charge passengers according to their weight. In 2015 Uzbekistan Airways started measuring how heavy flyers were for safety reasons. But predictably, the practice has got some airlines a lot of flak from their passengers. In 2016 Hawaiian Airlines announced that it would assign seats on flights to American Samoa based on passengers’ weights, to ensure even distribution. Samoans, who have some of the world’s highest obesity rates, accused the policy of being racially discriminatory against the group. They filed complaints with American regulators, who ultimately sided with the airline. Even so, there may be a reason why Michael O’Leary of Ryanair, Europe’s biggest low-cost carrier and a pioneer of charging passengers extra for anything he could, threatened to charge fat people extra a decade ago—and then never went ahead with his threat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 06:13:52 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The case for weighing passengers before flights]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/gulliver/2019/05/04/the-case-for-weighing-passengers-before-flights]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_BLP503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-04T00:36:32Z&quot;&gt;May 4th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;A FAVOURITE PASTIME of air passengers is to moan about all the extra fees that airlines have introduced in recent years. First came charges for stowing baggage in the hold, then more for in-flight food, allocated seating and even for using the overhead lockers. Yet would the idea to charge passengers according to their weight be one charge too far?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;This is exactly what Fuel Matrix, a British firm, is proposing to do. The company is currently in talks with several airports about “discreet” ways to introduce weighing technology. According to the company’s chief executive, Roy Fuscone, flyers’ weights will be stored in the same secure system as facial-recognition data, another technology some airports are trying out to eliminate the need for paper tickets at boarding gates.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Such an approach could easily go down very badly with some flyers. Some would cynically see it as simply a means of charging larger passengers extra. And it would culturally grate in some parts of the world, such as America, where “fat shaming” is socially unacceptable. (For example, when “Thomas the Tank Engine”, a British children’s television programme, was dubbed into American English, the name of an obese character called the “Fat Controller” had to be changed because it was regarded as too rude for American youngsters).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;Yet weighing passengers used to be the norm, particularly in the early days of aviation. Before the second world war, most passengers in America and Europe were weighed before take-off and charged more for extra heft (see picture). This was because early planes were smaller and had strict weight limits. For instance, on the inaugural flight of the Boeing 247 airliner in 1933, from San Francisco to New York, the plane could not carry more than 16,805 pounds (7,621kg) including fuel. So the ten passengers with tickets had to get on the scale, as did and their flight attendant, who could not weigh more than 135 pounds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;That practice was phased out as airlines began to rely on broad guidelines to estimate how much passengers weighed. But to be on the safe side, that means airlines carry much more fuel than they need to for each passenger. Airline executives reckon that carrying all that extra unnecessary kerosene around itself burns a surprising amount of fuel. That not only pushes the cost of tickets up, but also means that far more emissions are produced than is needed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;From there comes the temptation for airlines to start weighing passengers again. In 2013 Samoa Air in the Pacific began to charge passengers according to their weight. In 2015 Uzbekistan Airways started measuring how heavy flyers were for safety reasons. But predictably, the practice has got some airlines a lot of flak from their passengers. In 2016 Hawaiian Airlines announced that it would assign seats on flights to American Samoa based on passengers’ weights, to ensure even distribution. Samoans, who have some of the world’s highest obesity rates, accused the policy of being racially discriminatory against the group. They filed complaints with American regulators, who ultimately sided with the airline. Even so, there may be a reason why Michael O’Leary of Ryanair, Europe’s biggest low-cost carrier and a pioneer of charging passengers extra for anything he could, threatened to charge fat people extra a decade ago—and then never went ahead with his threat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 05:19:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Which European country has the most female politicians?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/05/03/which-european-country-has-the-most-female-politicians]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_woc303.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-03T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“WE HAVE set the course towards a fairer Spain,” Pedro Sánchez, the country’s recently re-elected prime minister, told supporters this week. As measured by the representation of women in politics this is certainly true. Spain has become a force for gender parity in politics since Mr Sánchez was first elected prime minister in June 2018. Last year he unveiled the most &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2018/06/08/spain-now-has-the-most-female-cabinet-in-europe&quot;&gt;female-heavy cabinet in Europe&lt;/a&gt;, filling more than half of the top jobs with women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are signs of progress in the Spanish parliament, too. At the general election on April 28th an additional 26 women won seats, taking female representation to 47%, up from 41% in 2018. As a result Spain has overtaken Sweden and Finland to take the crown as the most female parliament in the EU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The EU is a long way from achieving equal gender representation in politics. The average share of women in parliaments is a paltry 32%, albeit an improvement on 24% a decade ago. That may compare favourably with the global average of 24%, but some European countries, particularly in the east, are lagging far behind. In Hungary only 13% of parliamentarians are women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Sánchez can take much credit for accelerating Spain’s feminist development; 52% of the newly elected members of parliament for his Socialist party are women. But the course was set much earlier, by José Luis Rodríguez Zapatero, a previous Socialist prime minister. He introduced gender quotas, requiring women to make up not less than 40% (though not more than 60%) of Socialist party lists in the election of 2008.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 04:26:31 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Do millennials need a wake-up call?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/03/do-millennials-need-a-wake-up-call]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_opp506_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-03T18:30:36Z&quot;&gt;May 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anne McElvoy asks the author and iconoclast Bret Easton Ellis about his decision to take on the social mores of millennials. From the #MeToo movement to anger on social media, he discusses the dangers of a growing generational disconnect—and he apologises for claiming &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/04/30/bret-easton-ellis-is-wrong-about-millennial-reading-habits&quot;&gt;millennials&lt;/a&gt; don’t care about literature.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-breteastonellis&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 03:03:02 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A new adaptation of “Small Island” tells Britons their nation’s story]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/05/03/a-new-adaptation-of-small-island-tells-britons-their-nations-story]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_BKP509.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-03T17:35:27Z&quot;&gt;May 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;LIKE “THE TEMPEST”, “Small Island” starts with a storm. As a tropical hurricane whirls in the opening scenes, the stage of the National Theatre in London is lashed with rain; palm trees bend and sway. Both Shakespeare’s play and “Small Island”—adapted from a novel by Andrea Levy that was published in 2004—unpick the complex, vicious tangle of power relations between coloniser and colonised, insider and outsider. But where the action of Shakespeare’s play takes place on a single small island, Levy’s novel unfolds across two: Jamaica and Britain. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet it is hard to say which island the title refers to. There is a shared history: as Ambalavaner Sivanandan, a novelist, said of colonial migration, “we are here because you were there”. Many of the Caribbean migrants who boarded the HMT Empire Windrush to Britain in 1948 did not see themselves as immigrants at all. They were British citizens, making a homecoming to the “Mother Country”. Many fought Hitler alongside British troops in Commonwealth brigades. But as the protagonists of “Small Island” find out, many British people did not quite see it that way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This epic, compelling production tells Britons the story of their own country, and of themselves. Like the novel, Helen Edmundson’s adaptation jumps between different perspectives and timelines, deftly conjuring the childhoods of two principal guides, Hortense (Leah Harvey) and Queenie (Aisling Loftus). Hortense grows up in a hazy Jamaican idyll of tamarind trees and woodpecker nests, unsettled only by her god-fearing authoritarian foster parents. On the other side of the Atlantic, Queenie, an Englishwoman, hauls guts and fills pies on a wet pig farm in Lincolnshire, before escaping to London. When Hortense and her husband Gilbert (Gershwyn Eustache Jr) follow Hortense’s rakish runaway cousin Michael (CJ Beckford) to Britain, taking up lodgings in Queenie’s house, their lives intersect with all the drama and incidental complexity of a Victorian novel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190504_bkp510.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190504_bkp510.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190504_bkp510.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190504_bkp510.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190504_bkp510.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190504_bkp510.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190504_bkp510.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190504_bkp510.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190504_bkp510.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/prospero/20190504_bkp510.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The play’s extraordinarily wide scope, ranging from Jamaican independence to the Partition of India, reflects the reach of British imperialism. Yet this historical breadth is never at the expense of emotional depth. Ms Harvey enchants with her portrayal of the proud but vulnerable Hortense, her pursed lips occasionally cracked by tears. Mr Eustache is a haplessly likeable Gilbert, and Mr Beckford charming as Michael. No character is redundant; even the non-speaking Arthur (David Fielder) is riveting as Queenie’s shell-shocked father-in-law, the play’s haunting historical conscience. Queenie’s husband Bernard (Andrew Rothney) is, at the beginning, a cliché of English propriety, but he develops into a profoundly complex and flawed character, capable both of deep love and vile racism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bernard is one of many depictions of British prejudice in the play. Gilbert and Michael both joined the RAF and fought in battalions that were—unlike American forces—unsegregated. This only heightens the sense of betrayal, however, when they encounter deep and vicious bigotry on civvy street. The full spectrum of racial hatred is unflinchingly laid out: the sniggering in the street, the faux politeness of landlords as they reject black tenants, all pointing to the real violence that bubbles away beneath the surface, ready to burst forth at the slightest perceived provocation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since the 1940s changes in British law, policy and culture have put paid to many explicit manifestations of racism. Yet prejudice lingers. The word “Windrush”, once a metonym for mythical British tolerance and diversity, is now often suffixed with “scandal” after it emerged last year that elderly immigrants from the Caribbean were being deported as part of the Home Office’s efforts to meet arbitrary net-immigration targets. “Small Island” sharply demonstrates that the scandal was not a one-off aberration: it was just another example of the discrimination that British people from the Caribbean faced from the moment they arrived. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Britain’s understanding of this history of colonialism remains limited. As Gilbert says when a clueless villager asks him if he’s from Africa: “Why don’t they know anything about their own empire?” Seventy years later, the question is still pertinent. “Small Island” goes some way to addressing it, with all the humanity and vividness that this story demands. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;“Small Island” is now playing at the National Theatre in London until August 10th&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 03:03:01 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Silicon Valley: Geography is destiny]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/news/2019/05/03/silicon-valley-geography-is-destiny]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/correspondents_notebook_landscpape.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-03T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT IS A bit like covering the world’s most powerful financial institutions without ever setting foot in New York. For eight years I have written about the technology industry from London—first as an intern at &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;, then as a tech correspondent at Quartz and eventually, in my spare time, as news editor back at &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;. Yet I did so without ever having visited Silicon Valley, the stretch of land between San Francisco and San Jose that forms the spiritual and economic home of all things tech.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In part, this was made possible by the industry’s very nature: distributed, connected and mobile. It is possible to interview Satya Nadella in Paris, pose questions to Eric Schmidt in New Delhi and listen to Mark Zuckerberg in Barcelona. New giants emerge from Beijing, unlikely business models from Mumbai and startups from Nairobi. But Silicon Valley has long been the star around which everything else revolves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet to visit Silicon Valley for the first time is to be disappointed. As Gertrude Stein once said of Oakland, just across the bay from San Francisco, “there is no there there”. There is no big white lettering, as in Hollywood, or sign, as on Wall Street, that you have arrived. First-time visitors sometimes ask where exactly Silicon Valley is, even when they are in it. These observations are not particularly original, but they are crucial to understanding not just Silicon Valley but also the digital world inhabited by most of us, at least outside the firewalled garden of China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unlike the great cities of America—New York, Chicago, even flat, suburban Los Angeles—contemporary San Francisco is defined by its enormous hinterland, known as the Bay Area. In most cities, people live in suburbs and commute in to the centre. Finance is headquartered in the streets of downtown Manhattan; Hollywood studios are still in dense neighbourhoods (at least by American standards).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the Bay Area, though, many young tech workers live in the city and commute out. Every day dozens of plush, Wi-Fi-enabled buses ferry workers out to the Valley. It is 40 miles (or 64km) from downtown San Francisco to Mountain View, where Google is headquartered, roughly the same distance as from central London to Reading, or from midtown Manhattan to Edison, New Jersey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those who cannot bear this commute—generally workers with children—live out in the Valley itself, a bleak, featureless sprawl of American exurbia. It is all office parks, strip malls, single-family homes and highways. Anybody looking for a “there” will be disappointed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After finally seeing the Valley for myself, so many things about the technology it spawns now make sense. For years I wondered why every new product or feature peddled in the annual PR galas put on by Google or Apple involved restaurant recommendations. Coming from India, where a place to eat can be found by sauntering down the road, and having lived for the past decade in Europe, where public transport is efficient and finding nourishment often serendipitous, the American obsession with recommendations, whether for food, shops or services, was baffling. Until, that is, you realise that the people creating these products spend their lives moving around at 60mph in giant tins of fibreglass and plastic. It is not possible to stumble upon a café when you are driving down a six-lane highway. You need to know where you are going to go.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which brings me to driverless cars. The notion of autonomous vehicles navigating the warren of London’s streets elicits only sympathy for those poor, permanently stationary vehicles. But in California, with its runway-like highways, wide lanes and go-kartesque automatic vehicles that practically drive themselves—to say nothing of its lousy to non-existent public transport—it all makes sense. The driverless car is an engineer’s natural reaction to the environment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even the founding mythology of Silicon Valley—the idea that a bunch of guys (always guys) can start tinkering around in a garage and turn that into a world-eating megacorp—is one that makes little sense outside the Bay Area. Most New Yorkers live in apartments the size of a Silicon Valley garage. Most Londoners eschew cars and don’t have garages at all. You could house an extended family of eight Mumbaikars in the footprint of a Ford F-150 pick-up truck. (Though with rocketing property prices in the Valley, new garage-based startups are becoming increasingly rare.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If the geography of the Valley helps to explain the technology it has produced, however, it will matter less to the services it will provide in the future. Google, aware that its growth potential recommending restaurants to residents of Atlanta and Phoenix may have levelled off, has set up a “next billion unit” with the express purpose of figuring out how to make products for people in “Mumbai, not Mountain View”. And Apple, having run out of the world’s limited number of rich people to sell gadgets to, is now trying to fulfil a more universal desire: that for entertainment (in the form of remunerative subscriptions). Unlike running apps or driving directions, movies and music are something consumed by both rich and poor. After all, everybody likes watching stuff on their phones, regardless of whether they live in a four-bed in the East Bay or a 400-square-foot flat in Faridabad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 03:03:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The vile experiences of women in tech]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/open-future/2019/05/03/the-vile-experiences-of-women-in-tech]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190503_OPD001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-03T12:23:07Z&quot;&gt;May 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE TECHNOLOGY industry vaunts itself as a meritocracy. Yet it is roundly criticised for being unwelcoming to women, in ways large and small. In America, women hold just 25% of jobs in computing, and leave the tech and engineering sectors at twice the rate of men. The situation is worse for women of colour: black women hold only 3% of jobs among women in tech, and Latina women just 1% in America. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The gender imbalance is a global problem. In Britain, for example, Europe’s main tech hub, just 15% of people working in science, technology, engineering and mathematics (STEM) fields are women. Only 5% of leadership positions are occupied by women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In “Brotopia: Breaking up the Boys’ Club of Silicon Valley”, Emily Chang, a journalist at Bloomberg, explores the difficulties that women face. Start-up culture is often like a college fraternity house, which makes it hard for women to fit in, especially in senior management. Ms Chang recounts female engineers at Uber describing how they were invited to strip clubs by their male colleagues, for example. Meanwhile, female venture capitalists are scarce.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As part of &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt;’s Open Future initiative, we asked Ms Chang about how the tech industry could be more hospitable to women, how the gender imbalance in venture capital could be redressed and how sexism in tech differs from other industries. Her answers appear after an excerpt from “Brotopia” on the ugly experiences faced by women in gaming.   &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*       *      *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp503.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp503.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp503.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp503.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp503.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp503.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp503.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp503.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp503.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Escape from Trolltopia: Women’s fight to save the internet&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Excerpted from “Brotopia: Breaking Up the Boys’ Club of Silicon Valley” by Emily Chang (Portfolio, 2018)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Brianna Wu has been tormented by online trolls for three years. It started in 2014, when Wu spoke up to defend women in the gaming industry, only to find herself plunged into a roiling controversy called Gamergate that turned her life upside down. The threats of rape and murder hurled at her online became so scary that she and her husband fled their home. To this day, they live in a new location under an alias. But sometimes the trolls still manage to track her down, and online harassment becomes an off-line ambush.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“They found our address and smashed a window of my house. Threw a brick right through it,” Wu told me in April 2017, when I reached her by phone at a number she instructed me never to share. At the time we spoke, the window was still shattered.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The online attacks, like the one perpetrated on Wu, began and gathered force on sites like 4chan, Twitter, and Reddit, the largely unmonitored town halls of the web. All of these sites allow or encourage anonymity and pseudonymity, as well as a laissez-faire approach to free speech, in keeping with the long-standing libertarian ethos of the internet. All of them have tolerated years of online harassment of women.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It should be of little surprise at this point that the sites that harbour the most vicious trolls—4chan, Twitter, and Reddit included—were all started and led by white men, who aren’t usually the targets of the most vicious online harassment. Would these sites be as hostile to women today if they had been built and run by women, or at least included a meaningful number of women leaders early on?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The money in misogyny&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Few places on the internet are more troubled by misogynistic trolling than the world of online gaming. Gaming is a billion-dollar business— much bigger than movies and rivaling TV—including an exploding generation of mobile and social games, classic PC console games, and rising categories like e-sports and virtual reality. Yet the gaming industry is also saddled with a long-standing history of violence toward and degradation of women, allowing gamers to play out dozens of dark fantasies. One of the earliest rape-simulation games, Custer’s Revenge, was released in 1982 by the game maker Mystique. The goal was to rape a Native American woman tied to a cactus, with points awarded for every thrust. More than three decades later, our most popular games feature similar scenes. In Take-Two Interactive’s monster hit Grand Theft Auto (whose fifth iteration is one of the bestselling video games of all time), players can sleep with a prostitute, then murder her. Take-Two’s CEO, Strauss Zelnick, has defended the game, saying, “It is art. And I embrace that art, and it’s beautiful art, but it is gritty.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like the broader tech industry, gaming has systematically excluded women for decades. In 2016, the International Game Developers Association (IGDA) reported that women make up just 22 percent of game developers, with men vastly outnumbering them in management and in powerful technical roles such as programming, software engineering, and technical design. Interestingly, the IGDA also found that men were much less likely than women to believe that diversity in the industry, and in the games it produces, was important. Indeed, women have also been poorly represented in the games themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As the report drily puts it, “Women have long experienced derogatory representations of their gender in videogame content as well as a general invisibility within the wider videogame culture.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It’s not surprising, then, that the most notorious case of online trolling sprang out of the gaming industry and that women were the targets. Gamergate was sparked in 2014 by the peevish post of an unhappy former boyfriend of one of the gaming industry’s few female developers. “This is written almost entirely in shitty metaphors and bitter snark,” wrote Eron Gjoni, an industry coder. “It’s a post about an ex.” Gjoni alleged that his former girlfriend, the game developer Zoe Quinn, had slept with other people in the gaming industry while she and Gjoni were dating.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For reasons that are still somewhat inexplicable, the missive unleashed a volcanic explosion of hate, all of it directed at Quinn, who was a feminist critic of mainstream video games. Though Gjoni never called for any kind of campaign against Quinn, a certain subset of gamers took his nine-thousand-word, she-done-me-wrong post and turned it into a rallying point from which to defend their sacred, mostly male gaming territory. They derided Quinn’s game development as basic, simplistic girl work and claimed she used sexual favors to get good reviews.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Gjoni’s post was put up on 4chan (not by him, he would later attest), an online community founded in 2003 by a then-teenager named Christopher Poole. Today 4chan claims some twenty million monthly visitors, including a large population that seems to delight in wreaking havoc online. They were particularly vicious when attacking Quinn and other women in the gaming industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With 4chan members engaged in the fight, accounts sprang up across Twitter and Reddit to attack Quinn and spread the #Gamergate hashtag. The trolling expanded to target other female game developers on the premise that there was a conspiracy among women trying to ruin the industry by promoting more gender equality in the games themselves and in the studios where the products are produced. The Gamergaters created and shared lists of industry women to target and torment, including Anita Sarkeesian, a media critic who had risen to prominence by calling out sexism in the video game industry. The trolls even created a game called Beat Up Anita Sarkeesian, which enabled users to punch her virtual face. The game’s creators wrote, “There’s been a disgusting large imbalance of women who get beaten up in games. Let’s add a lady . . . She claims to want equality: Well, here it is.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once riled, many internet trolls have no shame. They often compete with each other to see who can be the most cruel. And as Quinn and Sarkeesian found out, they don’t limit their attacks and threats to a single individual. They will threaten family members, including children. They will also instantly direct their bile toward anyone who comes to the target’s defense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is where Brianna Wu enters the story. About two months after Gjoni’s post, Wu, an established game designer, spoke out against the #Gamergate campaign, sarcastically tweeting a meme suggesting that the trolls were saving everyone from an “apocalyptic future” where women might have slightly more influence in the industry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s when all hell broke loose. Shortly after responding to the trolls on Twitter, Wu was inundated with violent, disturbing threats on her life. One series of tweets in particular stands out. “Guess what bitch, I now know where you live;” “Your mutilated corpse will be on the front page of Jezebel tomorrow;” and “If you have any kids, they’re going to die too.” As the threats piled up, Wu and her husband fled their home, crashing on friends’ couches and hiding out in extended- stay hotels. They didn’t have children to worry about, but they did spend an inordinate amount of money boarding their dog while they were on the run. Wu had a choice to make: speak up for what was right or be silenced. She chose to talk back.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“I was angry. I was scared. I was terrified. But within all of that I was trying to reach inside myself and find that bravery to really change the industry for women,” Wu told me. She spent days documenting the dozens of death threats against her so she could provide them to law enforcement officials. At the height of the online vitriol, she hired a full-time staff member to help collect information on her harassers to share with police, but none of that was enough to bring the perpetrators to justice.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wu wasn’t alone. Others who spoke out in support of Quinn or even mildly criticized the trolls or the gaming industry were similarly attacked. Kellee Santiago, a female game developer who went on to work at Google, likened Gamergate to a witch hunt or public stoning, telling me, “It was really shocking to discover that I live in a time and place in which such animosity toward women existed.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Troll army on the march&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wu would later understand that she had been the victim of the trolling playbook, an extremely effective technique used to silence women that anonymous social-media denizens disagree with. &amp;quot;Find the woman and identify something in her past to distort her with,&amp;quot; Wu explains. &amp;quot;If she&amp;#x27;s gay, attack her on that. Larger than size 12? Attack her on that. Transgender? Attack her on that. Find the spot where the woman feels most vulnerable and make her feel unsafe until the cost of speaking out is too great.&amp;quot; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Use of the troll playbook is not limited to the fans or members of the gaming industry. Online harassment is not one of the most disturbing problems plaguing the internet at large.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;______________&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excerpted from “Brotopia: Breaking Up the Boys’ Club of Silicon Valley” by Emily Chang, with permission of Portfolio, an imprint of Penguin Publishing Group, a division of Penguin Random House LLC. Copyright © Emily Chang, 2018.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;*       *      *&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; Is sexism in tech better or worse than in other industries, and does it take on a different form?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Emily Chang:&lt;/strong&gt; “Brotopia” is everywhere, but what makes Silicon Valley’s sexism problem especially troubling is the fact that the tech industry is changing our lives faster than any other industry in the world. Women hold 25% of jobs across the industry, account for 9% of venture capital investors and women-led companies get just 2% of venture capital funding. And yet, Silicon Valley is deciding what we read, how we communicate, what we buy.  It is rapidly reshaping our culture, and yet the vast majority of the decisions made in tech are made by men.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lack of women in Silicon Valley is having an outsized impact on our lives and our children’s lives. Amazon’s facial recognition technology gets white men right almost 100% of the time and darker-skinned women wrong 31% of the time. Imagine being accused of a crime because the tech got it wrong? That kind of bias will enshrine and exacerbate the inequalities that already exist in our society.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For another example, Twitter cofounder Evan Williams told me he thinks if more women had been on the team from the very beginning, perhaps online harassment and trolling wouldn’t be such a problem on the platform. The men who were building the product didn’t think about how it could be weaponised. Imagine if the internet were a friendlier, healthier place, how different might the world be? &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Something else that sets Silicon Valley apart is the entrenched belief among the powerbrokers that they are not only changing the world but changing the world “for the better.” That confidence creates a sense of moral exceptionalism and arrogance that distances Silicon Valley from real-world people and problems. In fact, the tech industry faces many of the same issues that other industries face with sexism, racism and ageism, but is blind to it, which means there is even less of an urgency to change Silicon Valley itself for the better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp502.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp502.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp502.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp502.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp502.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp502.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp502.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp502.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/05/blogs/open-future/20190504_opp502.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; What changes are needed for tech to become a more hospitable environment for women?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Chang:&lt;/strong&gt; If the tech industry can connect the world and build self-driving cars and rockets to Mars, surely industry leaders can hire and promote and fund more women. We are seeing progress at companies where leadership has made this a top priority. The workplace collaboration startup Slack is a good case study. Rather than focusing on unconscious bias training alone, Slack has focused on giving their employees tools to combat their biases—standardising their recruiting, interview and review processes. Rather than complaining about the “pipeline problem,” the real-estate tech company Redfin hired women with non-traditional backgrounds, and recruited women from their marketing team and taught them how to code. It worked! Those women are getting promoted at the same rates as everybody else.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Building a diverse team doesn’t have to take forever and inclusion can start today. All companies need to think harder about how to create cultures where everyone who is at the table also has a voice at the table, and can be the best versions of themselves. We’ve seen a lot of agitation among employees at companies like Google and Amazon for more inclusive workplaces that has made a difference. Employees themselves have a more powerful voice than ever before and should use their voices to make change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; According to a Pew survey in 2018, around half of Americans thought that #MeToo has made it harder for men to know how to interact with women in the workplace. Do you think there is any validity to such concerns?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Chang:&lt;/strong&gt; It’s a good thing that the #MeToo movement has made some people question their behavior. Hopefully this leads to better behavior and better workplace practices. I do believe the folks who think that #MeToo will backfire on women are mistaken. The conversations and policy changes that are happening right now are essential to move workplace culture forward. There might be some additional nerves and uncertainty in the meantime, but it is an important part of a broader shift to ensure that women can reach their full potential in the workforce, which will benefit us all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; The number of women of colour in tech is incredibly disappointing, just 3-4% of Google employees are black. Are a different set of policies necessary to address the plight of “double minorities”?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Chang:&lt;/strong&gt; Companies need to make sure that they are focused on improving all kinds of diversity and improving their cultures to support employees of all different backgrounds. Diversity isn’t just about gender. It’s about race, sexuality, age, socioeconomic background and more. If you are a “double minority” or a “triple minority,” you can double or triple how hard it might be to navigate your own workplace. I do think tech companies should set specific goals around race, in the rank and file, leadership and on the board, given how dismal the numbers are.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Economist:&lt;/strong&gt; Should venture capitalists try to play a role in addressing tech’s gender imbalance, such as signaling to entrepreneurs that they look favourably on startups that have diverse workforces? Or is that idea madness because it interferes with what perhaps should be their sole goal: investing in companies with the best shot at success?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ms Chang:&lt;/strong&gt; Absolutely! Venture capitalists have a huge role to play in making sure they are surfacing and investing in the entrepreneurs and ideas with the most potential. Investors are the “kingmakers” of Silicon Valley but they can and should be “queenmakers” as well. Given that women-led companies only received 2% of venture funding, it is painfully obvious that investors are not surfacing the best ideas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, funding is often doled out based on networks and “warm” introductions and these networks are dominated by men. Many venture firms have zero female partners and some are just hiring their first female partner in decades. In 2018, a group of women investors in Silicon Valley joined together to form a nonprofit called All Raise to increase the number of women investors and the number of women getting funded. They have already raised an incredible amount of awareness around these issues and I’m very hopeful their activism will play an important part of balancing the scale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 23:06:44 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The sitcom that spawned a president]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/news/2019/05/03/the-sitcom-that-spawned-a-president]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190504_efp001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-03T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/articles/20190406_opp602_apple_news.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/articles/20190406_opp602_apple_news.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/articles/20190406_opp602_apple_news.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/articles/20190406_opp602_apple_news.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/articles/20190406_opp602_apple_news.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/articles/20190406_opp602_apple_news.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/articles/20190406_opp602_apple_news.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/articles/20190406_opp602_apple_news.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/articles/20190406_opp602_apple_news.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/articles/20190406_opp602_apple_news.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This piece is from &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.1843magazine.com/&quot;&gt;1843&lt;/a&gt;, our sister magazine of ideas, lifestyle and culture. It was published in the April/May 2019 issue.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The president of Ukraine sits in his office, a glum look on his face. He has just been trounced in the election by a political outsider, and isn’t taking it well. When his successor, Vasyl Holoborodko, tries to move into his office, the outgoing president shoots at him through the door with a shotgun, just missing his target. He’s refusing to leave until his demands are met, says an aide: he wants a litre of vodka, several packs of cigarettes and political asylum in Yugoslavia. “But Yugoslavia doesn’t even exist anymore,” says Holoborodko. “He knows, that’s why he asked for the vodka,” the aide replies.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;br/&gt;The mix of slapstick and satire is typical of “Servant of the People”, a television show that has gripped Ukrainian audiences since 2015. In an astonishing example of life imitating art, Volodymyr Zelensky, the actor and comedian who plays Holoborodko, was elected this month as Ukraine’s president. Despite having no political experience whatsoever, he managed to defeat Petro Poroshenko, the incumbent of five years, with a whopping 73% of the vote. Poroshenko graciously accepted defeat and congratulated Zelensky.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aleksey Kiryushchenko, the actor who plays Zelensky’s on-screen opponent, is also the showrunner of “Servant of the People”, responsible for developing the storyline and producing and directing the show. But now that his star is too busy having meetings with foreign dignitaries and members of parliament, Kiryushchenko is saying goodbye. “We can’t have the show without its hero,” he tells me matter of factly. We are sitting in the canteen of Kvartal 95, Zelensky’s production company, which is housed in a converted Soviet apartment block in Kiev. “There were three seasons, and the fourth is happening now before our eyes,” Kiryushchenko tells me. “It has become reality.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Kiryushchenko was asked to work on “Servant of the People” four years ago, nobody on set seemed to think that the show would be renewed for a second season. Zelensky and his writers knew that the protagonist of their story would be an everyman-turned-politician, but they were struggling to put a fresh spin on a familiar archetype. For inspiration they watched “House of Cards”, “Yes, Minister” and “Boss”, starring Kelsey Grammer. In the end, they decided to set their story firmly in the 21st century: their hero, a Ukrainian schoolteacher, is elected president after his rant against the country’s corrupt establishment goes viral after being secretly filmed and uploaded to YouTube by a student. Zelensky’s character, Vasyl Holoborodko, reluctantly moves into the presidential residence. He resolves to purge Ukraine of corruption but, almost immediately, everyone from his bank clerk to the country’s most powerful oligarchs seek to buy his favour. The question tugging at the minds of viewers is whether Holoborodko will resist the urge to use his office to enrich himself or succumb to it, like so many before him.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“The show is an experiment,” Kiryushchenko says. “We see what happens when you drop an idealistic person into dirty politics, like a clean spoon full of honey into a barrel of tar.” That experiment has been wildly successful. “Servant of the People” was a hit, and is the only Ukrainian programme ever bought by Netflix. Tired of their scandal-ridden politics (Ukraine is the most corrupt country in Europe after Russia according to Transparency International), Ukrainians found in Holoborodko a man who not only entertained them but who also promised to defend their interests against those who would ransack the country. Holoborodko gave his fans hope for a better future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Enter Zelensky. He announced his candidacy on New Year’s Eve last year. Though Kiryushchenko is careful to say that Zelensky didn’t consult him while he was thinking about a run for office, he does recall one conversation they had during that period.“‘You are doing satire,’ I told him. ‘What’s the goal? You want him [Poroshenko] to change? You want him to become better. You criticise him at first gently, then harder and harder, and he doesn’t change. So are you going to do that into old age, barking at his feet like a little dog? Maybe change places and become him yourself.’”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190504_EFP002.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190504_EFP002.jpg 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190504_EFP002.jpg 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190504_EFP002.jpg 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190504_EFP002.jpg 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190504_EFP002.jpg 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190504_EFP002.jpg 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190504_EFP002.jpg 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190504_EFP002.jpg 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190504_EFP002.jpg 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pictured: Kiryushchenko (left) and Zelensky (right) on the set of “Servant of the People”&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That’s when the border between fact and fiction began to blur. The latest season of the show was broadcast during the election campaign. As viewers watched Holoborodko rooting out corruption on screen, they observed his real-life avatar, backed by a political party called “Servant of the People”, criticising Poroshenko and championing ideas first mooted by Holoborodko, such as getting rid of the presidential motorcade which Holoborodko thought frivolous. Zelensky even once addressed his social media audience while he was on set and in costume, and took to the stage on election night as the show’s theme music played on the speakers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Do you think Zelensky would have won if it wasn’t for Holoborodko?” Kiryushchenko asks rhetorically. “People believe in Zelensky’s character on the show and can’t separate them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kiryushchenko claims that he, Zelensky and their team had no idea that their show would prove a highly effective means of mobilising voters. “The show ended up being a new kind of political technology,” he says, using a post-Soviet term for the techniques used to influence voters. “For the world that was a really unexpected political shock. But we didn’t plan that. I would love to say we did, that we have some sort of know-how in political technology. I would have a million offers on my desk from people asking me to do the same thing for them.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part of Zelensky’s appeal is that he is a political outsider, one who isn’t in the pocket of the oligarchs, or so he claims. His opponents disagree. “Servant of the People” is aired on 1+1, a popular TV channel which provided favourable coverage of Zelensky during the campaign. Poroshenko has accused Zelensky of being the puppet of the owner of 1+1, an oligarch called Ihor Kolomoisky. Zelensky denies the claim.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other concerns abound. Many Ukrainians worry about Zelensky’s lack of experience. He may be able to act the part of a president but when the cameras are turned off and the real work begins, what then? He readily admits that his political views aren’t well developed; when a BBC journalist met him in January, the journalist described those views as “still very much a work in progress”. Zelensky has responded to reports that he came across as clueless in briefings with diplomats by promising to surround himself with eggheads. But at a particularly fraught time for the country, which is still at war with Russia, some may reasonably wonder whether Zelensky is fit for office.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever happens with Zelensky’s presidency, “Servant of the People” is on the verge of going global. Even before Zelensky was elected, media companies in over 15 countries, including Fox Studios in America, had bought the rights to remake the series, creating the possibility that copycats will try to launch their own political careers via the characters they play on screen. “I opened Pandora’s box,” admits Kiryushchenko.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;em&gt;Ian Bateson is a journalist based in Ukraine&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 23:06:43 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“This is part of a brewing fight between Donald Trump and Congress”]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/03/this-is-part-of-a-brewing-fight-between-donald-trump-and-congress]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/william_barr.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-03T11:50:07Z&quot;&gt;May 3rd 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE REFUSAL of America’s attorney-general, William Barr, to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/02/donald-trump-is-not-the-first-president-to-fight-subpoenas&quot;&gt;testify&lt;/a&gt; before Congress on Thursday is just the latest example of the White House’s stonewalling policy. We look at the constitutional crisis that may be brewing. Facebook moved yesterday to block certain extremists, but this is just one front on which the social-media behemoth is fighting. Mark Zuckerberg’s bid to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/02/mark-zuckerberg-wants-to-build-wechat-for-the-west&quot;&gt;remake&lt;/a&gt; the platform will probably ape its Chinese rival, WeChat. And in Europe, Vietnamese migrants are &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/04/27/vietnamese-migrants-are-thriving-in-poland-and-the-czech-republic&quot;&gt;thriving&lt;/a&gt; in some notoriously anti-immigration regions. Runtime: 22 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/barr-none-thewhitehouse-sdefiance&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 21:07:15 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>