<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Britons are ever more polarised between no-deal and a second referendum]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/01/britons-are-ever-more-polarised-between-no-deal-and-a-second-referendum]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190601_BRD001_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;E&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;UROPEAN ELECTIONS&lt;/small&gt; are rum affairs, but the latest were stranger than ever. On May 23rd voters went to the polls in elections nobody wanted, as Brexit was meant to happen in March. As expected, Nigel Farage’s new Brexit Party stormed into first place, with 32% of the vote and 29 seats. It was a striking result for a party set up only in February, and was five points better than Mr Farage achieved as leader of the &lt;small&gt;UK&lt;/small&gt; Independence Party in 2014. Adding in the rump &lt;small&gt;UKIP&lt;/small&gt; vote makes the total for parties backing a no-deal Brexit 35%, a big number but less impressive when turnout, though higher than in 2014, was only 37%.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If hard Leavers had a good night, so did hard Remainers. The Liberal Democrats took 20% of the vote and 16 seats, while the Greens got 12% and seven seats. Adding in the new Change &lt;small&gt;UK&lt;/small&gt; party, which had a terrible night and won no seats, and the Scottish and Welsh nationalists takes the combined score of pro-Remain, pro-second-referendum parties to 40%, more than the no-dealers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The big losers were the Tories and Labour. Their combined vote share was just 23%, down from as much as 82% in the 2017 general election and less than half their share in 2014. In effect, the European elections saw the centre squeezed to the advantage of extremes on both sides. On Brexit, the country is more obviously split down the middle than ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For an opposition party, Labour’s performance of coming third with just 14% of the vote and ten seats was abject (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/01/jeremy-corbyn-is-increasingly-isolated-in-his-own-party&quot; target=&quot;_blank&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;). But it is the collapse of the Tories to a mere 9% of the vote and four seats, the party’s worst election result in 185 years, that will have more immediate consequences, because Theresa May, the prime minister, is resigning. A leadership race starts on June 10th. Some 11 &lt;small&gt;MP&lt;/small&gt;s have already put themselves forward. These will be winnowed down by their colleagues to two, who will then be voted on by party members. The hope is that this process finishes by the end of July, with the winner immediately becoming prime minister.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The big question for all candidates is how best to respond to Mr Farage’s success. Many believe that the only way to defeat the Brexit Party now is to back leaving without a deal. Among others, Dominic Raab and Boris Johnson, the front-runner, prefer a deal but want to keep no-deal as an option. Both also insist that Brexit must happen on October 31st, with or without a deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some are more nuanced. Most want to renegotiate Mrs May’s deal, yet are also against no-deal. Michael Gove, the environment secretary, is in this camp. Jeremy Hunt, the foreign secretary, has said no-deal is better than no Brexit. But this week he called no-deal “political suicide”. His argument was that trying to force it through could lead to a general election in which the Tories would be annihilated. Rory Stewart, the international development secretary and another candidate, has said he could not support a Tory prime minister who goes for no-deal.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190601_BRC152.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190601_BRC152.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190601_BRC152.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190601_BRC152.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190601_BRC152.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190601_BRC152.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190601_BRC152.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190601_BRC152.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190601_BRC152.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190601_BRC152.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;A key point is that Parliament has already voted against no-deal. Yet hardliners say that, since leaving without a deal on October 31st is now the legal default, &lt;small&gt;MP&lt;/small&gt;s cannot stop it. The Institute for Government, a think-tank, points out that the routes used before to prevent no-deal are no longer available. But John Bercow, the Commons Speaker, promises that Parliament will not be sidelined. Since he also has no intention of vacating his post as he previously promised, he will surely find a way for &lt;small&gt;MP&lt;/small&gt;s to block a no-deal Brexit if they wish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What of Brussels? &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; leaders were categorical when extending the Brexit deadline that there would be no renegotiation of the withdrawal agreement, which includes the Irish backstop to avert a hard border with Ireland. That rules out a time limit on the backstop, which would negate its purpose. On this, &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; leaders cannot overrule Leo Varadkar, the Irish prime minister. They may be open to another extension, but they will surely reject concessions to a hardliner like Mr Johnson, whom most dislike.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet that could change if a more emollient figure with a clear parliamentary majority emerged. The &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; is happy to revise the political declaration that accompanies the withdrawal agreement. And, as Mujtaba Rahman of the Eurasia Group, a consultancy, notes, one reason that the &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; refused to offer Mrs May even marginal changes to the agreement was that it still doubted she would get it ratified.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In her resignation speech, Mrs May talked of the need for compromise. Many retorted that her own Brexit problems were caused by her very refusal to compromise. The difficulty for her successor is that an increasingly polarised country is more inimical to compromise. That may point to further delays, but it also raises the risk of no-deal. The smart money increasingly backs another referendum as the solution. Whether it would deliver a clear answer is another question.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Britain&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Centre aground&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 17:40:16 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Unable to form a government, Binyamin Netanyahu calls an early election]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/01/unable-to-form-a-government-binyamin-netanyahu-calls-an-early-election]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190601_MAP005_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;T WAS NOT&lt;/small&gt; even two months ago that Binyamin Netanyahu declared “a great victory” after his Likud party took 35 seats in a hard-fought election. The voters seemed to have given the prime minister an unprecedented fifth term; soon he would become Israel’s longest-serving leader. His bloc of nationalist and religious parties held a 65-seat majority in the Knesset (see chart). All that was left was the haggling, over cabinet posts and policies, before Mr Netanyahu announced his new government.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The haggling, though, got the better of him. Bedevilled by the demands of Avigdor Lieberman, a rival on the right, Mr Netanyahu was unable to form a government by the deadline on May 29th. To stop the president from asking the opposition to have a go, he and his right-wing colleagues (along with the Arab parties) finally agreed to dissolve the Knesset and call a new election. Many members had yet to make a speech when they voted to give up their jobs. For Mr Netanyahu it is an unusual failure—one that threatens his political survival.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The situation is unprecedented. Every other election since Israel’s founding in 1948 has resulted in the formation of a government. The finance ministry says there is no money for a new election, which has been scheduled for September. (It will surely find the shekels.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190601_MAC975.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/print-edition/20190601_MAC975.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/print-edition/20190601_MAC975.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/print-edition/20190601_MAC975.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/print-edition/20190601_MAC975.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/print-edition/20190601_MAC975.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/print-edition/20190601_MAC975.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/print-edition/20190601_MAC975.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/print-edition/20190601_MAC975.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/print-edition/20190601_MAC975.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;The ostensible cause of all the chaos is legislation, drafted by the previous government, that would cut into the exemption of religious students from compulsory military service. Under the bill an increasing (though still small) number of such &lt;em &gt;yeshiva&lt;/em&gt; students would be required to serve. Mr Lieberman, who leads Yisrael Beiteinu, a secular nationalist party, insisted that it be passed by the new Knesset without any amendment. But United Torah Judaism (&lt;small&gt;UTJ&lt;/small&gt;) and Shas, ultra-Orthodox parties, oppose the measure. Mr Netanyahu needed the support of all three in order to have a majority. He could not bridge the divide.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The exemption for &lt;em &gt;yeshiva&lt;/em&gt; students has long been a political hot potato. Mr Lieberman insists that for him it was “a matter of principle”. But he is also positioning himself for the day after Mr Netanyahu. The two go back three decades. Mr Lieberman, a former Likudnik, served as his political aide and director-general of the prime minister’s office. He was Mr Netanyahu’s defence minister until last year—when he (unsuccessfully) tried to bring down the government by withdrawing his party from the ruling coalition. He again senses weakness and by choosing an issue popular with secular voters he believes he can increase support for his party in the next election, while hastening his rival’s downfall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Netanyahu normally exudes confidence. But as the deadline to form a government approached, he looked desperate. He tried to tempt Labour to join him by offering it the defence portfolio—even though he has spent years branding the party as weak on security. Perhaps he was just trying to scare Mr Lieberman into a compromise. Perhaps he was scared himself. Mr Netanyahu has been indicted, pending a hearing, in three corruption cases. He was counting on his new coalition to pass laws that would grant him immunity from prosecution and limit the Supreme Court’s power to overturn legislation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Prosecutors accuse Mr Netanyahu of taking gifts from wealthy benefactors in return for favours, and offering help with regulatory matters to publishers in exchange for positive coverage. He denies wrongdoing. The allegations did not seem to hurt him during the last election. But even if he wins the next one, he may not have time (or a majority) to pass his desired laws before pre-trial hearings begin in October. His lawyers have tried to delay the proceedings. They are now ploughing through piles of evidence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Lieberman is the first right-wing politician to rebel against Mr Netanyahu. Will others follow? Within Likud there are grumbles, but only one senior member, Gideon Saar, a former interior and education minister, has criticised the effort to grant the prime minister immunity. The party has never deposed its leader and Mr Netanyahu is still popular with the rank and file. Other potential rivals seem not to share Mr Lieberman’s assessment of the prime minister’s vulnerability. That Mr Netanyahu was able to convince a majority of lawmakers to fire themselves shows the hold he still has over the right wing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is also a testament to the weakness of the opposition. Benny Gantz, the leader of Blue and White, which also won 35 seats in the last election, demanded that he be allowed a shot at forming a government. But he could not muster the votes to block Mr Netanyahu’s move. During the latest election he was unable to cut into the prime minister’s support, instead taking votes from other centre-left parties. Turnout was down. Mr Gantz may have trouble convincing voters to show up in September if he seems likely to lose again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Much can change between now and then. In late June the Trump administration will unveil the economic portion of its plan for peace between Israel and the Palestinians. It had delayed the announcement in order to keep it from becoming an issue in the last election. But the new vote will probably turn into another referendum on Mr Netanyahu, who has four months to convince voters to increase his mandate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Middle East and Africa&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Back to the ballot box&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 17:40:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jeremy Corbyn is increasingly isolated in his own party]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/01/jeremy-corbyn-is-increasingly-isolated-in-his-own-party]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190601_BRD000_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-01T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 1st 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;H&lt;/span&gt;.&lt;small&gt;L. MENCKEN&lt;/small&gt; is said to have defined a politician as “an animal that can sit on the fence and yet keep both ears on the ground”. By that definition Jeremy Corbyn is failing in his vocation. The European elections bulldozed Mr Corbyn’s fence by giving the Labour Party just 14% of the vote in the country as a whole and 9% in its former stronghold of Scotland. They unleashed a furious debate that was ostensibly about the party’s stance on Europe in particular but also about Mr Corbyn’s leadership in general.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senior figures such as Tom Watson, the deputy leader, and Emily Thornberry, the shadow foreign secretary, were quick to blame Labour’s dismal performance on its refusal to offer wholehearted support for holding a second referendum and staying in the European Union. Others, particularly from the party’s working-class wing, were equally quick to push back. Gloria De Piero, &lt;small&gt;MP&lt;/small&gt; for Ashfield, urged her colleagues not to let a single issue—Brexit—“wreck” the party. Len McCluskey, head of the Unite trade union, accused supporters of a second referendum of trying to launch a coup against the leader. Mr Corbyn did his best to rebuild his fence and climb back on it. He promised that “we are ready to support a public vote on any deal”. But he stopped short of offering Remainers what they want: unconditional backing for a second referendum whether or not there is an &lt;small&gt;EU&lt;/small&gt; deal on the table, and a firm commitment to turning Labour into a Remain party.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is actually a good strategic reason for Mr Corbyn’s position on Europe. Labour risks alienating large numbers of voters, particularly in its working-class heartlands, if it turns itself into an overtly Remain party (most of its &lt;small&gt;MP&lt;/small&gt;s sit in constituencies that voted to leave). And fudging may be a much more successful strategy in a general election, which will be fought over lots of issues, than in a European poll. But the party’s Euro-failure is only one of many. Labour has failed to pull ahead of a Conservative government that is doing everything it can to commit suicide. The forthcoming Peterborough by-election may see a Labour seat go to the Brexit Party. Labour is also likely to waste yet another summer in a row over anti-Semitism that can only do it harm. On May 28th the Equality and Human Rights Commission announced that it is launching a formal investigation into whether the party has unlawfully discriminated against, harassed or victimised people because they are Jewish, a measure that it last took against the far-right British National Party. Mr Corbyn is in his weakest position since taking over as his party’s leader in 2015, and his problems are mounting by the day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Senior Labour figures are increasingly willing to criticise his leadership. There is nothing new about Mr Watson’s hostility to Mr Corbyn. But the days when the deputy could be denied a platform at his own party conference are long gone. He has formed a centre-left group of 80 &lt;small&gt;MP&lt;/small&gt;s and 70 peers to argue for more mainstream policies, and played a starring role at the People’s Vote march. Ms Thornberry harbours leadership ambitions of her own. She is also worried about the growing strength of the Liberal Democrats in her Islington South constituency. Sir Keir Starmer, the shadow Brexit secretary, is increasingly a force in his own right rather than just a lawyer for hire. For their different reasons close allies such as John McDonnell, the shadow chancellor, and Diane Abbott, the shadow home secretary, are critical as well. Mr McDonnell is determined to win power at any cost, and Ms Abbott represents a constituency that voted 80% to remain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the same time Mr Corbyn is becoming the prisoner of his closest advisers, who are odd creatures even by the standards of Britain’s increasingly eccentric politics. They are all, in various ways, closely allied to Mr McCluskey, Labour’s most pro-Leave trade-union baron. Two of them, Seamus Milne and Andrew Murray, are privately educated Marxists who have a soft spot for the Soviet Union. Mr Murray was a member of the Communist Party for decades before his recent conversion to democratic socialism. Mr Milne, a ruthless dialectician, exercises a particularly tight hold over Mr Corbyn, a man who managed only two Es at A-level and who, after four years of intense intra-party battles, is beginning to seem worn out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2 &gt;In the bunker&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Corbyn is no stranger to challenges to his leadership: an attempt by &lt;small&gt;MP&lt;/small&gt;s to remove him in 2016 only left him stronger. But the current wave of criticism is unusually damaging for two reasons. The first is that it undermines his claim to be a champion of the people against the elites. Mr Corbyn is in the uncomfortable position of resisting calls for “people power”, in the form of a second referendum, a ballot of all party members or a special conference on the Brexit question, and instead defending a policy of triangulation and prevarication cooked up by a sinister cabal of advisers. The second is that some of the fiercest attacks are coming from normally loyal allies on the left. Paul Mason, a commentator, has raised the possibility of a “Corbynism without Corbyn” and called for “the officials” who masterminded the party’s Euro-elections strategy to be “removed from positions of influence”, perhaps opening the way to Britain’s very own replay of the battle between the Mensheviks and the Bolsheviks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In most ways Mr Corbyn could not be more different from Britain’s departing prime minister, Theresa May. She was the dutiful grammar-school girl who went to Oxford whereas he was the rebellious private-school boy who dropped out and plunged into the Islington of Che Guevara posters and Irish rebel songs. But Brexit makes odd bedfellows, and in strange ways he is beginning to resemble her. Isolated in a bunker of close advisers, criticised by former allies, determined to avoid alienating both Leavers and Remainers, he is beginning to look tired, tainted and out-of-touch. To survive, Mr Corbyn needs to prove that he is both more flexible and more ruthless than his fellow ageing baby-boomer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Britain&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Enemies within&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 17:40:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[New anti-corruption powers aim at foreign buyers of London’s posh homes]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/29/new-anti-corruption-powers-aim-at-foreign-buyers-of-londons-posh-homes]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_brp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUSPECTING THAT a fancy London pad was acquired with stolen money is one thing, proving it another. British crime-busters have long struggled to join the dots to courts’ satisfaction. So last year the country introduced Unexplained Wealth Orders (UWOs), which shift the burden of proof. These can be issued when there is a gap between the value of an asset and the legitimate income of the apparent owner—for instance a foreign official on a modest state salary or one of his relatives. The property can be frozen while police investigate, and seized if suspects subsequently fail to explain the source of their wealth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It emerged this week that three London homes have been frozen by the High Court, in the second use of such orders by the National Crime Agency (NCA). The properties, worth £80m ($101m) when purchased a decade ago, are held by offshore companies. The owner has not been named but is a “politically exposed person”—a politician, state official or someone linked to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first batch of UWOs were aimed at £22m-worth of property, including a house (see photo) in London’s Knightsbridge neighbourhood, belonging to Zamira Hajiyeva, the wife of a jailed Azeri banker. This week details of £16m she spent in the Harrods store over a decade (using 54 credit cards) were laid bare. They included £3.5m on Boucheron jewellery, £160,000 at the perfume counters and £332,000 on Tom Dixon’s furniture and café offerings (mostly the former, presumably). Mrs Hajiyeva denies wrongdoing and is appealing against the possible loss of her homes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government touts UWOs as evidence that it is taking on foreigners who launder ill-gotten gains through property purchases, often hiding behind shell companies. A public register of the owners of offshore firms that hold British property is in the works. (In 2016 Britain became the first G20 country to launch an open register of domestic firms’ owners.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But many more such orders would be needed to reach beyond the tip of the money-laundering iceberg. Transparency International has identified 150 British properties worth £4.4bn bought with iffy wealth, and that is just the “low-hanging fruit”, says the anti-corruption group. The NCA complains of being underfunded, and resources have been diverted from white-collar cases to areas with more visible victims, such as knife crime. Ministers trumpet a new National Economic Crime Centre, attached to the NCA. “Deckchairs rearranged, with little new money,” scoffs a former senior prosecutor. UWOs are a useful tool, but Britain will also need to invest more in investigations if it is serious about driving out corrupt capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 17:40:13 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why European voters are returning to the polls]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/29/why-european-voters-are-returning-to-the-polls]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_eup503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;BALLERINAS PIROUETTED behind a glass wall in a church-turned-dance-studio in Amsterdam. In front of the partition stood Marko, a 26-year-old student, ballot paper in hand. During the elections for the European Parliament, which took place between the 23rd and 26th of May, the studio doubled as a polling station. Marko had not voted in the previous poll in 2014. This time was different. “Right-wing parties are coming up,” he said, ignoring the dancers twirling behind him. “It’s really important to make my voice heard.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was not the only voter feeling more motivated. Around 51% of eligible voters cast their ballots in this year’s European elections, up eight percentage points from five years ago. It was the first time turnout increased since direct elections to the European Parliament were instituted in 1979.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After decades of decline, European voters are returning to the polling booths, for both national and European contests. The trend is uneven. Turnout fell in some countries, such as France and Italy, and flat in others. But it has increased in many states, shooting up by nine points in Spain’s general election last month, to levels not seen in two decades . Sweden’s last year saw the highest turnout since 1986. Voter participation in Dutch and German elections, both in 2017, climbed by seven and five points respectively. What might account for this turnaround?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190601_WOC980.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/20190601_WOC980.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/20190601_WOC980.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/20190601_WOC980.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/20190601_WOC980.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/20190601_WOC980.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/20190601_WOC980.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/20190601_WOC980.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/20190601_WOC980.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/20190601_WOC980.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;One explanation is that more seems to be at stake in recent elections as politics becomes more polarised. Populist parties, which rail against established elites, seem particularly adept at reaching people who do not normally vote. In Germany’s general election in 2017, a study by Infratest Dimap, a German polling agency, suggests that people who previously did not vote were the largest source of new votes for the Alternative for Germany, a Eurosceptic, anti-immigration party. Last weekend, it gained 10 seats in the European Parliament, with turnout across the country up by a quarter from 2014. Spikes in Dutch turnout, such as in the 2002 general election or last month’s provincial elections, have coincided with the formation of new far-right parties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rise of right-wing populism is also boosting turnout among its opponents. Some leftist parties are explicitly using the threat from the far right as a rallying cry. “The boundary between going forward and going backwards...can be just one vote,” Pedro Sánchez, Spain’s Socialist prime minister, told voters before they went to the polls last month. It seems to be working. Like their Eurosceptic counterparts, strongly Europhile parties have gained seats in the European Parliament.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even beyond the far right, smaller parties are growing at the expense of larger established ones, which means voters now have more choices than before. The centre-right Ciudadanos and left-wing Podemos parties in Spain, both of which first gained seats at the national level in 2015, have become mainstays of political life. Eco-friendly Dutch voters can choose between GroenLinks and the more hardline Party for the Animals. Fatima, a teaching assistant at an Islamic school in Amsterdam, says she did not vote until DENK, a party geared towards Dutch Muslims, was founded in 2015.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Growing worries about climate change are probably also driving up political participation, especially among young voters. “I’m here to save the environment,” declares Pierre, a student in the German town of Duisburg, adding that he and many of his friends became politically aware by attending Fridays for Future protests, a series of weekly student strikes that have grown in recent months. Organisers say 320,000 people in Germany participated in them on May 24th. Green parties across Europe won a total of 69 seats last week, up by 19 from 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another factor in increasing turnout is social media. In many countries, Facebook reminds users when elections take place, sometimes offering links to websites that help people find polling stations. “On my way here, I saw a poster telling us to go and vote,” says Pierre. “Social media is like seeing that poster every day.” Even Grindr, a gay dating app, had an advertisement urging users to “vote for your future” in the European elections.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is high voter participation good for democracy? “High turnout is not necessarily evidence of civic health,” argues Peter Kellner, formerly of YouGov, a polling agency. “It can also be a sign of a divided society.” Tom van der Meer of the University of Amsterdam disagrees. Even though rising turnout is associated with greater political polarisation and fragmentation, he says, “democracy is fundamentally about inclusion.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，被墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;新增&lt;a href="https://feedx.net/needhelp" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;“帮你做个RSS”&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 05:40:30 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A new anti-corruption law aims at foreign buyers of London’s posh homes]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/29/a-new-anti-corruption-law-aims-at-foreign-buyers-of-londons-posh-homes]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_brp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUSPECTING THAT a fancy London pad was acquired with stolen money is one thing, proving it another. British crime-busters have long struggled to join the dots to courts’ satisfaction. So last year the country introduced Unexplained Wealth Orders (UWOs), which shift the burden of proof. These can be issued when there is a gap between the value of an asset and the legitimate income of the apparent owner—for instance a foreign official on a modest state salary or one of his relatives. The property can be frozen while police investigate, and seized if suspects subsequently fail to explain the source of their wealth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It emerged this week that three London homes have been frozen by the High Court, in the second use of such orders by the National Crime Agency (NCA). The properties, worth £80m ($101m) when purchased a decade ago, are held by offshore companies. The owner has not been named but is a “politically exposed person”—a politician, state official or someone linked to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first batch of UWOs were aimed at £22m-worth of property, including a house (see photo) in London’s Knightsbridge neighbourhood, belonging to Zamira Hajiyeva, the wife of a jailed Azeri banker. This week details of £16m she spent in the Harrods store over a decade (using 54 credit cards) were laid bare. They included £3.5m on Boucheron jewellery, £160,000 at the perfume counters and £332,000 on Tom Dixon’s furniture and café offerings (mostly the former, presumably). Mrs Hajiyeva denies wrongdoing and is appealing against the possible loss of her homes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government touts UWOs as evidence that it is taking on foreigners who launder ill-gotten gains through property purchases, often hiding behind shell companies. A public register of the owners of offshore firms that hold British property is in the works. (In 2016 Britain became the first G20 country to launch an open register of domestic firms’ owners.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But many more such orders would be needed to reach beyond the tip of the money-laundering iceberg. Transparency International has identified 150 British properties worth £4.4bn bought with iffy wealth, and that is just the “low-hanging fruit”, says the anti-corruption group. The NCA complains of being underfunded, and resources have been diverted from white-collar cases to areas with more visible victims, such as knife crime. Ministers trumpet a new National Economic Crime Centre, attached to the NCA. “Deckchairs rearranged, with little new money,” scoffs a former senior prosecutor. UWOs are a useful tool, but Britain will also need to invest more in investigations if it is serious about driving out corrupt capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 03:41:40 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rash behaviour—behind the resurgence of measles]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/05/29/rash-behaviour-behind-the-resurgence-of-measles]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/babbage_1_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-29T18:15:02Z&quot;&gt;May 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;THE MEASLES &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/05/25/measles-is-often-spread-by-adults&quot;&gt;resurgence&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; around the world has been blamed on parents refusing to vaccinate their children, but &lt;strong&gt;is vaccinating children enough?&lt;/strong&gt; Also, how a new glove for humans is &lt;strong&gt;teaching robots how to feel&lt;/strong&gt;. And Kenneth Cukier asks Carl Benedikt Frey, an economic historian, what can be learnt from &lt;strong&gt;the industrial revolution in today’s world of automation&lt;/strong&gt; and robotics. Runtime: 19 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistbabbage/babbage-rashbehaviour&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 02:41:44 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A new anti-corruption tool targets foreign buyers of London’s luxury homes]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/05/29/a-new-anti-corruption-tool-targets-foreign-buyers-of-londons-luxury-homes]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_brp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SUSPECTING THAT a fancy London pad was acquired with stolen money is one thing, proving it another. British crime-busters have long struggled to join the dots to courts’ satisfaction. So last year the country introduced Unexplained Wealth Orders (UWOs), which shift the burden of proof. These can be issued when there is a gap between the value of an asset and the legitimate income of the apparent owner—for instance a foreign official on a modest state salary or one of his relatives. The property can be frozen while police investigate, and seized if suspects subsequently fail to explain the source of their wealth.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It emerged this week that three London homes have been frozen by the High Court, in the second use of such orders by the National Crime Agency (NCA). The properties, worth £80m ($101m) when purchased a decade ago, are held by offshore companies. The owner has not been named but is a “politically exposed person”—a politician, state official or someone linked to them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first batch of UWOs were aimed at £22m-worth of property, including a house (see photo) in London’s Knightsbridge neighbourhood, belonging to Zamira Hajiyeva, the wife of a jailed Azeri banker. This week details of £16m she spent in the Harrods store over a decade (using 54 credit cards) were laid bare. They included £3.5m on Boucheron jewellery, £160,000 at the perfume counters and £332,000 on Tom Dixon’s furniture and café offerings (mostly the former, presumably). Mrs Hajiyeva denies wrongdoing and is appealing against the possible loss of her homes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The government touts UWOs as evidence that it is taking on foreigners who launder ill-gotten gains through property purchases, often hiding behind shell companies. A public register of the owners of offshore firms that hold British property is in the works. (In 2016 Britain became the first G20 country to launch an open register of domestic firms’ owners.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But many more such orders would be needed to reach beyond the tip of the money-laundering iceberg. Transparency International has identified 150 British properties worth £4.4bn bought with iffy wealth, and that is just the “low-hanging fruit”, says the anti-corruption group. The NCA complains of being underfunded, and resources have been diverted from white-collar cases to areas with more visible victims, such as knife crime. Ministers trumpet a new National Economic Crime Centre, attached to the NCA. “Deckchairs rearranged, with little new money,” scoffs a former senior prosecutor. UWOs are a useful tool, but Britain will also need to invest more in investigations if it is serious about driving out corrupt capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 02:41:43 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The unexpected brightness of new satellites could ruin the night sky]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/science-and-technology/2019/05/29/the-unexpected-brightness-of-new-satellites-could-ruin-the-night-sky]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_stp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IT WAS quite a show: a train of illuminated dots moving across the sky, many of them as bright as Polaris, the north star. These were not new astronomical objects, however. Rather, they were the first tranche of satellites for Starlink, a project intended to provide internet access across the globe, and they were launched into orbit on May 24th by SpaceX, an American rocketry firm.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seeing satellites from the ground with the naked eye is nothing new. But astronomers (professional and amateur) were surprised, and unhappy, at just how many and how bright the Starlink satellites appeared to be. Quite a few of them took to Twitter to raise the alarm and post pictures and videos of the blazing birds. Their worry was that these satellites and their successors could change the night sky for ever. If the initial 60 members of the Starlink network were already causing noticeable light pollution, they reasoned, how bad would it get once the full constellation of 12,000 had been launched?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those who enjoy watching the night sky for pleasure it would surely be sad, for it would more than triple the number of man-made objects in the firmament and thus further degrade the natural beauty of the heavens—a beauty already diminished in many places by light pollution from the ground. For those involved in investigating the universe scientifically, though, it may be more than merely sad. In some cases it could be job-threatening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Preliminary analysis shows, for example, that almost every image from the Large Synoptic Survey Telescope in Chile, currently nearing completion and intended to photograph the entire available sky every few nights when it is operational, could contain a satellite trail. These streaks can be removed, but each correction destroys valuable data. It is possible that some experiments, such as observing at regular intervals the variation in behaviour of astronomical objects, will no longer be feasible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Optical astronomers thus have cause to be nervous about Starlink. For radio astronomers its impact may be even more serious. The satellites’ mode of operation necessarily requires them to send radio signals back to Earth, all of which will be stronger than any signal arriving from deep space. This can be accomodated to a certain extent by knowing which frequencies the satellites are broadcasting on, and adjusting accordingly. But exactly how badly radio observatories are affected will depend on how well the satellites manage to confine their broadcasts within those frequencies, which remains to be seen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Elon Musk, SpaceX’s boss, initially dismissed astronomers’ concerns, tweeting at the weekend that there were “already 4,900 satellites in orbit, which people notice ˜0% of the time. Starlink won’t be seen by anyone unless looking very carefully &amp;amp; will have ˜0% impact on advancements in astronomy.” In later exchanges, though, he struck a more understanding tone. Starlink would avoid the frequencies associated with radio astronomy, he said, and if the satellites’ orientations needed to be tweaked to minimise solar reflection during critical astronomical experiments, that could easily be done. Moreover, as the initial Starlink satellites moved into their operational configuration after the weekend, their brightness dropped—though they still occasionally flared as they crossed the sky, probably because of reflections from their large solar panels.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Musk also seemed, in his tweets, to suggest that the aims of Starlink outweighed the harms. “Potentially helping billions of economically disadvantaged people is the greater good. That said, we’ll make sure Starlink has no material effect on discoveries in astronomy. We care a great deal about science.” His assertion has merit. The problem, as Mark McCaughrean, senior adviser for science and exploration at the European Space Agency, observes, is that there has been little public discussion of the matter. For Dr McCaughrean the night sky is a public commons that risks appropriation in the name of private interest. Whether that serves the greater good should at least be a matter of debate.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For now, astronomers plan to carry out further simulations of the potential impacts of Starlink and other communication-satellite networks planned by companies such as OneWeb. But even when that work is complete, it is unclear what they can actually do to make SpaceX and its competitors listen to their concerns, for there is no legislation which regulates the impact of satellites on the night sky.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;America’s Federal Communications Commission does concern itself with how satellites use the available radio spectrum and with what happens to them after they have done their job. But that is it. With the coming mega-constellations of communications satellites, it is surely time for this to change, and for governments (not only America’s) to involve themselves more deeply in the uses of heaven.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 01:40:31 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How the trade war between China and America is changing global business]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/05/29/how-the-trade-war-between-china-and-america-is-changing-global-business]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/05/articles/main/20190601_ldp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-05-29T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;May 29th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IF YOU WANT to understand how cooling relations between America and China are changing global business, a good place to look is Alibaba, an internet giant. It is China’s most admired and valuable firm, worth a cool $400bn. For the past five years it has also been a hybrid that straddles the superpowers, because its shares are listed only in America. Now it is considering a $20bn flotation in Hong Kong, according to Bloomberg. The backdrop is a rising risk of American retaliation against Chinese interests and the growing clout of Hong Kong’s capital markets. A listing there would be a sign that Chinese firms are taking out insurance to lower their dependence on Western finance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The world looked very different back in 2014, when Alibaba first went public. Although based in Hangzhou and with 91% of its sales from mainland China, it chose to list its shares in New York, home to the world’s deepest capital markets, which also permitted its complex voting structure. Wall Street banks underwrote the offering. Alibaba’s boss, Jack Ma, already a rock-star in China, was toasted in Manhattan high society as the kind of freewheeling capitalist Americans could do business with. He was not alone: 174 other Chinese firms have their main listing in America today, with a total market value of $394bn, including the tech stars Baidu and JD.com. A recent notable arrival is Luckin Coffee, a Starbucks wannabe, which floated for $4bn in May.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Alibaba has found, however, America has become less hospitable. The firm’s profits have soared and investors have made hay. But in January 2018 Ant Financial, its payments affiliate, was blocked from acquiring MoneyGram, an American rival, on national-security grounds. In November Mr Ma’s American halo slipped when it was revealed he was a Communist Party member, like many Chinese tycoons (he is due to retire this year). Silicon Valley’s chiefs whisper that Alibaba’s global cloud business is a threat to American interests. If Alibaba invests in startups it could fall foul of a new law, known as FIRRMA, that requires foreign purchases of “critical technology” to be vetted. The firm is not yet under attack, unlike its compatriot Huawei, but the mood is tense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trade war between America and China has already spread from tariffs to a wide terrain encompassing legal extradition, venture capital and the global dollar-payments system. It is easy to see how an American listing could become a vulnerability. If, for example, China were to boycott Apple or Boeing, America could respond by suspending the trading of Chinese firms’ shares and stopping them from raising capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mainland China’s vast but immature capital markets are not a substitute for Wall Street. Hong Kong, China’s offshore hub, is far from perfect, not least because China appears intent on gradually undermining the rule of law there. Still, it has become a plausible alternative venue for China’s global companies. It now welcomes firms with dual-share classes after a rule change in 2018. It has expanded its role as a conduit through which mainland investors can buy shares and global investors get access to China. Last year more money was raised in listings in Hong Kong ($37bn) than on Nasdaq or the New York Stock Exchange.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hong Kong’s rise has been accompanied by an erosion of Western hegemony in Asian high-finance. A decade ago Chinese banks were peripheral. Now Wall Street firms are not as essential as they used to be. Last year seven of the top 20 equity underwriters in Asia were Chinese firms. Chinese banks are among the largest cross-border lenders in Asia. America still controls the dollar-payments system, but in time that could change, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With a Hong Kong listing, Alibaba would have an alternative place to raise capital. It is still expanding fast—sales grew by 51% last year. New York will continue to thrive as a financial centre, even if Chinese firms start to shy away. But the bigger message is that, as the trade war rumbles on, the immensely complex global network of financial and commercial ties is adjusting. Big hardware firms are tweaking their supply chains. Retailers are shifting their sourcing so that goods sold in America are not made in China. Banks are cutting their exposure to counterparties that could face American sanctions. And even the world’s most successful firms, such as Alibaba, feel they need a backup plan. It is a very different vision from the one Mr Ma held out when he rang a ceremonial bell at the New York Stock Exchange back in 2014.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 01:40:30 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>