<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Google rewards reputable reporting more than left-wing politics]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/08/google-rewards-reputable-reporting-more-than-left-wing-politics]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-08T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 8th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;“G&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;OOGLE &amp;amp; OTHERS&lt;/small&gt; are suppressing voices of Conservatives”, tweeted Donald Trump in 2018. “They are controlling what we can &amp;amp; cannot see.” The president’s charges of bias are often dubious. But many people worry about algorithms absorbing human prejudices. Robert Epstein, an academic, has compiled data that show Google suggesting more positive terms when users type “Hillary Clinton” than when they look up Mr Trump. &lt;small&gt;PJ&lt;/small&gt; Media, a conservative blog, claims that liberal sites get 96% of results for “Trump” on Google’s news page, a compilation of links to recent articles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Google says that the 10,000 human evaluators who rate sources for its search engine assess “expertise” and “trustworthiness” but not ideology. Web-traffic figures support this defence. Sites with high scores from fact-checking groups, whose judgments probably resemble Google’s, draw larger shares of their visitors from search engines than sites with low scores do. Factually inaccurate sources also tend to have strong left- or right-wing slants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nonetheless, a subtle bias might not show up in such broad statistics. To test for favouritism, &lt;em&gt;The Economist&lt;/em&gt; ran an experiment, comparing a news site’s share of search results with a statistical prediction based on its output, reach and accuracy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We first wrote a program to obtain Google results for any keyword. Using a browser with no history, in a politically centrist part of Kansas, we searched for 31 terms for each day in 2018, yielding 175,000 links.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next, we built a model to predict each site’s share of the links Google produces for each keyword, based on the premise that search results should reflect accuracy and audience size, as Google claims. We started with each outlet’s popularity on social media and, using data from Meltwater, a media-tracking firm, how often they covered each topic. We also used accuracy ratings from fact-checking websites, tallies of Pulitzer prizes and results from a poll by YouGov about Americans’ trust in 37 sources.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190608_GDC141_newsbias/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;If Google favoured liberals, left-wing sites would appear more often than our model predicted, and right-wing ones less. We saw no such trend. Overall, centre-left sites like the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; got the most links—but only about as many as our model suggested. Fox News beat its modest expectations. Because most far-right outlets had bad trust scores, they got few search results. But so did Daily Kos, a far-left site.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our study does not prove Google is impartial. In theory, Google could serve un-biased links only to users without a browsing history. If fact-checkers and Pulitzer voters are partisan, our model will be too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Moreover, some keywords did suggest bias—in both directions. Just as &lt;small&gt;PJ&lt;/small&gt; Media charged, the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt; was over-represented on searches for “Trump”. However, searches for “crime” leaned right: Fox News got far more links than expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This implies that Google’s main form of favouritism is to boost viral articles. The most incendiary stories about Mr Trump come from leftist sources. Gory crime coverage is more prevalent on right-leaning sites. Readers will keep clicking on both. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Sources: Google; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.adfontesmedia.com/&quot;&gt;Adfontesmedia.com&lt;/a&gt;; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://mediabiasfactcheck.com/&quot;&gt;Mediabiasfactcheck.com&lt;/a&gt;; YouGov; Meltwater; SimilarWeb; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.pulitzer.org/&quot;&gt;Pulitzer.org&lt;/a&gt;; Facebook&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-js=&quot;/2019/gd-google-news-bias/js/bundle.js&quot; data-infographic-css=&quot;/2019/gd-google-news-bias/css/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2019/gd-google-news-bias/css/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Graphic detail&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Seek and you shall find&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 22:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s visit to Britain goes well—at least for him]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/06/donald-trumps-visit-to-britain-goes-well-at-least-for-him]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_brp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-06T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;D&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;ONALD TRUMP&lt;/small&gt; saw only people cheering, not protests, reports of which the president branded “fake news”. They did not seem so fake on Whitehall. Placards said “Dump Trump”, “Trump: Climate Disaster” and “Keep Trump away from our &lt;small&gt;NHS&lt;/small&gt;”. One optimistic poster proposed “Stop Brexit, stop Trump”. Most bizarre was a banner saying “Man Utd fans against apartheid”. The mood was cheerful, even carnival-like—at least until it rained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As ever, Labour’s Jeremy Corbyn came out to back the protests. But his disdain was diluted after Mr Trump revealed that he had rejected a meeting request from Mr Corbyn, whom he dubbed a “negative force”. He said the same of Sadiq Khan, London’s mayor, calling him a “stone-cold loser”. This contrasted with his enthusiasm for Brexiteers, singling out Boris Johnson as a great potential successor to Theresa May as prime minister. He also met Nigel Farage, whose new Brexit Party is eating into Tory support, and suggested that he should be one of the Brexit negotiators.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The president clearly valued hobnobbing with royalty and feasting in Buckingham Palace with the queen (whom he called a “fantastic woman”) more than bilateral discussions with Mrs May. But although he said he would have negotiated Brexit differently, by suing the European Union, he also praised Mrs May’s deal. And he glossed over differences on Huawei, a Chinese telecoms giant mistrusted by America but cautiously accepted in Britain, by saying that the two countries would soon reach an agreement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trade was trickier. Mr Trump promised a “phenomenal” post-Brexit deal that would double or even triple bilateral trade. But he also echoed his ambassador by saying that everything should be on the table. That includes not just farm products but access to the &lt;small&gt;NHS&lt;/small&gt;. When most Tory leadership candidates instantly said the health service was not for sale, Mr Trump backtracked. But his own trade negotiating documents make clear that America will look for more &lt;small&gt;NHS&lt;/small&gt; contracts and higher drug prices. What’s more, Congress has said it will not ratify any trade deal if Brexit is seen to threaten peace in Northern Ireland. A bilateral deal looks both hard and far off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The British managed to get in a few subtle digs of their own, with the queen and Mrs May going out of their way to praise the role of international institutions, which Mr Trump has criticised or in some cases abandoned. The prime minister openly admitted to differences on climate change and Iran, and she used this week’s &lt;small&gt;D&lt;/small&gt;-Day commemoration to remind the president of the value of &lt;small&gt;NATO&lt;/small&gt; in upholding the global order. Mr Trump’s response was to repeat his demand that &lt;small&gt;NATO&lt;/small&gt; allies spend more on defence.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Besides praising Mr Johnson, with whom he spoke by phone, Mr Trump sought meetings with Jeremy Hunt, the foreign secretary, who he said would make a good prime minister, and with Michael Gove, the environment secretary, whom he claimed not to know. The White House has clearly decided these are the three strongest candidates to succeed Mrs May. It is not obvious that Mr Trump’s support will prove helpful, any more than did Barack Obama’s backing for the Remain campaign in 2016. Yet it could weigh with some Tory party members. Certainly Mr Hunt and Mr Gove seemed pleased. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Britain&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;When the Donald calls&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 22:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Advertising may make people miserable, but it still has its uses]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/06/advertising-may-make-people-miserable-but-it-still-has-its-uses]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_fnd000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-06T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;E&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;VERY YEAR&lt;/small&gt;, as Americans polish off their Thanksgiving feasts, a particular genre of advertisement begins to air. The details vary, but the plot does not: one family member surprises another with the Christmas gift of a luxury car, often adorned with a cartoonishly large bow. The recipient never betrays a hint of the dismay one might expect of someone whose partner has spent tens of thousands of dollars without consultation. Such a car can easily cost more than the median annual income of an American household, and most people who see these ads will not be able to afford one. But the envy such spots induce serves an economic purpose, even as it leaves the majority feeling worse about themselves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ads and other forms of marketing ostensibly serve a straightforward economic role. Firms selling goods and services need to tell consumers about the availability and desirability of their wares, and spend on advertising to do so. By informing consumers about the relative merits of various products, ads improve the quality of purchasing decisions and, conceivably, leave both firms and shoppers better off than they would be in an ad-free world.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet advertising might fall short of this ideal in many ways. It need not be honest or representative of the full range of available products, for example. Some firms target impressionable children, in ways which could contribute to long-run health risks. London has recently banned junk-food advertising on its transport network, a prohibition campaigners want to extend. And honest or not, successful ads induce a desire to spend, perhaps on things the audience does not need or cannot afford. The information content of ads for fancy vacations, bespoke cars or diamond-studded watches does not much matter for people whose budgets cannot accommodate them. Their main takeaway is that others get to enjoy things that they themselves cannot afford. If the effect of advertising is mostly to encourage people to want things that they cannot have, rather than to direct them towards items that are a good match for their needs and tastes, then it is possible that spending on advertising leaves society worse off overall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some recent research suggests this might indeed be the case. A forthcoming paper by Chloé Michel, now at Swiss Re, Michelle Sovinsky of Mannheim University, Eugenio Proto of Bristol University and Andrew Oswald of Warwick University attempts to unpick the effect of advertising on welfare. The researchers used three decades’ worth of survey results from a sample of nearly 1m Europeans, spread across 27 countries, to compare information on self-reported life satisfaction with variation in total advertising spending as a share of &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt;. After taking account of other macroeconomic variables such as unemployment, and individuals’ socioeconomic characteristics, they find a significant and inverse relationship between spending on advertisements and national welfare. They estimate that a doubling of ad spending is associated with a subsequent drop in reported satisfaction of 3%—an effect about a quarter as strong as a spell of unemployment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is possible that this result reflects the effect of some other factor which influences both advertising and well-being. And the authors are careful to note that they cannot be certain about the causal mechanism at work. But their findings may illustrate an aspect of the economy that has puzzled some economists for more than a century. In “The Theory of the Leisure Class”, published in 1899, Thorstein Veblen, a Norwegian-American economist, explored the nature of what he termed “conspicuous consumption”. Veblen argued that consumption is not merely about satisfying needs, but is also used to signal status and prestige.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The priciest cars may offer more nifty features and a smoother ride than a cheaper marque, but the vast difference in price is not primarily down to such advantages. Rather, the buyer is paying for such cars’ value as a status symbol, which derives from the fact that very few people can afford one. (Following his insight, economists use the name “Veblen good” for items for which demand rises with price, though it is not the high price itself that generates the increased demand but rather the exclusivity that the high price confers.) These luxury items defy normal economic logic. In the mass market, productivity-boosting innovations that allow firms to sell better products at lower prices are a route to success. For producers of conspicuous-consumption items, such cost-cutting does not conquer the market but destroys it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;Less good than a feast&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The notion that people might buy high-cost items in preference to serviceable alternatives simply to set themselves apart from the less well-off would seem absurd, were the economy not chock-a-block with examples, from designer handbags to silver cutlery to oxygenated energy drinks. Advertising enables the process. For goods to grant high status, there must be consumers who want but cannot have them. Ad campaigns featuring sleek cars bedecked with oversized bows add to the value of luxury brands by informing the masses of how desirable they are—and how inaccessible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Veblen, though, saw the rich as a largely unproductive class of capital-owning moochers, who profited off the useful labour of working people (hence the “leisure class”). In recent decades, however, the share of Americans working long hours has grown, and has risen fastest among those earning the highest wages—an odd exception to the global norm that working time declines with income. The status envy induced by conspicuous consumption may play a role. In rich countries, most people’s basic needs have long since been met. To keep workers striving—those on higher incomes especially—there must always be more desirable consumer goods and services just out of reach. Perpetual dissatisfaction may well boost economic growth by keeping highly productive workers who might otherwise enjoy more time with their families chained to their desks. But it is a funny sort of prosperity that depends on people never being satisfied with their lot. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Finance and economics&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Enough is never enough&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 20:40:48 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Asian countries fear China, but many won’t side with America]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/06/americas-vision-for-the-indo-pacific-gets-a-lukewarm-reception]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_asp503.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-05T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 5th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;W&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HAT DO YOU&lt;/small&gt; buy the Asian defence minister who has everything? How about a “beautiful” photo-book of North Korean ships illegally transferring oil at sea? Patrick Shanahan, America’s acting defence secretary, presented the collection of grainy aerial shots to his Chinese counterpart, General Wei Fenghe, at the Shangri-La Dialogue, an annual gathering of military bigwigs in Singapore from May 31st to June 2nd.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was an emollient gesture in fractious times. When Banyan asked Mr Shanahan what he planned to say to General Wei in private, the answer was not a tirade about Huawei or the South China Sea. Instead Mr Shanahan said he was “excited” to explore areas of cooperation. North Korean sanctions-busting—which often occurs in Chinese waters—was top of the list. Such collaboration would show that America and China could “compete in a constructive way”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On June 1st the Pentagon published its plans for that competition in an Indo-Pacific strategy. At its heart was the idea of a “free and open Indo-Pacific” (&lt;small&gt;FOIP&lt;/small&gt;), a nebulous concept conceived by Japan and enthusiastically taken up by the Trump administration. In essence, &lt;small&gt;FOIP&lt;/small&gt; is a rules-based rejoinder to China’s vision of spheres of influence, gunboat diplomacy and murky loans. “No one nation can or should dominate the Indo-Pacific,” said the Pentagon in its report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shanahan’s notion of responsible competition—in contrast to the no-holds-barred clash of civilisations favoured by some of his head-banging colleagues—is laudable. It is also savvy. Asian states are likelier to sign up to &lt;small&gt;FOIP&lt;/small&gt; if they are persuaded that America is not spoiling for a fight. But on both counts—stabilising the relationship with China, while rallying partners to push back against it—America has an uphill task.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start with the olive branches. General Wei did not so much ignore them as snap them into pieces. “Arise, all those who do not want be enslaved,” he thundered in his speech on June 2nd, quoting China’s national anthem. “Let us build the new Great Wall with our flesh and blood.” He warned that China’s army was “not afraid of sacrifice” and that “we make no promise to renounce the use of force” against Taiwan.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One might think that such bluster would send Asians rushing to sign up to &lt;small&gt;FOIP&lt;/small&gt; and into America’s arms. In some cases, it has. Narendra Modi will deepen defence ties with America in his second term. Japan is beefing up its armed forces and sending its navy into the South China Sea. Officials from America, Australia, India and Japan—the “Quad”—now confer routinely, most recently on May 31st.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All pay lip service to the idea that the Association of South-East Asian Nations (&lt;small&gt;ASEAN&lt;/small&gt;), a club of ten mostly smaller powers, should be at the core of &lt;small&gt;FOIP&lt;/small&gt;. The problem is that not all in &lt;small&gt;ASEAN&lt;/small&gt; are sold on the idea. For one thing, many are unconvinced that America will truly stick around, as the costs of any war with China grow over time. So why risk China’s ire? “The Chinese coast guard is bigger than Malaysia’s warships,” lamented Malaysia’s defence minister.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Shanahan did his best to assuage these concerns. He pointed out that the Indo-Pacific was America’s “priority theatre”, with four times as many American forces as any other American military command. America’s freedom of navigation operations in the South China Sea were also growing more routine: unusually, there were two in May alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But muscle is only half of it. The larger issue is that Donald Trump’s unpredictably incendiary foreign policy sits uneasily with the principles of &lt;small&gt;FOIP&lt;/small&gt;. Tensions with Iran are pulling America’s attention back to the Middle East. The compulsive resort to tariffs undercuts a rules-based trading order. Mr Trump’s lack of interest in human rights hardly furthers freedom. And to many in Asia, America’s war on Huawei or its sanctions against buyers of Russian arms or Iranian oil look an awful lot like China’s “toolkit of coercion”, as Mr Shanahan put it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is unfair. An Asian order sculpted by China would be more capricious and suffocating than anything Mr Trump could devise. General Wei’s defence of the crushing of the Tiananmen Square protests—he called it a “correct policy” that gave China the stability to grow richer—was a reminder of the ideological stakes. Australia, India and Japan are on board. Singapore and Vietnam’s sympathies are clear. But most &lt;small&gt;ASEAN&lt;/small&gt; countries hate the idea of taking sides, despite widespread misgivings about China’s intentions. Mr Shanahan reckons they will eventually come round: “I think they’re building up their confidence.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 20:40:47 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The long-term decline in bond yields enters a new phase]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/06/the-long-term-decline-in-bond-yields-enters-a-new-phase]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_wbd003.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-06T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;A&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;T THE END&lt;/small&gt; of 1989, an American in London received a call from a friend back home. The caller had watched the fall of the Berlin Wall and the toppling of Nicolae Ceausescu in Romania with growing dismay. He was at the end of a four-year course in Russian Studies at an elite university with hefty tuition fees. He had learned all the Kremlinology a would-be cold warrior could need—but not that the cold war might suddenly end. “I just took a $60,000 bath,” he said.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This story comes to mind not so much because of fears of a new cold war, this time with China, but because of the bond market’s recent response to such fears. Long-term interest rates have tumbled almost as swiftly as communism fell in Europe. The yield on a ten-year Treasury bond has plunged from 2.5% to 2.1% in the past month. Ten-year Bund yields have turned negative again and have reached a new all-time low.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What happens to long-term interest rates in large part reflects what is expected to happen to short-term rates. The bond market’s Kremlinologists expect the Federal Reserve to cut them soon. Other central banks will seek to keep money easy. One consequence is that the secular decline in real interest rates is unlikely to reverse soon (see chart). The implications are far-reaching: the whole edifice of asset prices is founded on a low-rate regime. But what if that regime were to come to an abrupt eventual end?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/ImageObject&quot;  &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_fnc198.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_fnc198.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_fnc198.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_fnc198.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_fnc198.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_fnc198.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_fnc198.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_fnc198.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_fnc198.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/images/2019/06/articles/body/20190608_fnc198.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is hard to be truly confident about the future path of real interest rates. The reasons for their decades-long decline are not well understood or agreed upon. One school stresses an increased desire for saving. Demographic change is part of this story. As a large chunk of the rich world’s population approaches the end of their working lives, they seek to set aside more of their income for retirement. The integration of high-saving China into the world economy is another factor. In this view, long-term interest rates had to fall simply to clear the saturated global market for savings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another school says that low bond yields are a distortion caused by the policies pursued by central banks in the rich world. They have kept short-term interest rates close to (or in some cases below) zero for much of the past decade. They have also spent trillions of dollars buying government bonds with the explicit goal of driving down long-term interest rates. In their defence, central bankers say they set interest rates to keep the economy purring. If they had pressed down too hard on the monetary pedal, the result ought to be a burst of rising prices.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the absence of rising inflation it seems reasonable to expect that the era of low interest rates will last. If yields on the safest government bonds remain low, the expected returns on other assets—the earnings yield on equities, say, or the rental yield on property—should stay in line. The result would be that all assets will continue to look expensive relative to their long-run averages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As logical as this seems, it is nevertheless disquieting. At some stage the influences that have pushed down yields will attenuate, even if this is not soon. Long-term interest rates will surely rise again. It is reasonable to believe that this will not be sudden. Demographic change happens slowly. So perhaps asset prices will adjust slowly to the new reality, whenever it dawns. But it is quite hard to imagine a world in which real interest rates grind upwards and asset-holders avoid taking a capital loss, says Shamik Dhar of &lt;small&gt;BNY &lt;/small&gt;Mellon, a fund-management group. The uncertainty about the timing of even a gradual adjustment creates headaches, for instance for someone hoping to own a home. Buy at the wrong time, and you end up with a house that slowly loses value.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And what if real interest rates rise a lot more quickly than they fell? Well, they might. China is already a spent force in the global savings glut: its current-account surplus has dwindled to next to nothing. Baby-boomers moving into retirement might step up their spending. If rich countries turn once again to fiscal policy as a tool for ginning up their economies, there are plenty of asset-heavy projects (airports, roads, fibre-optic networks) to soak up savings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kremlinologists look for signs of shifting authority, for who’s up and who’s down. But when everyone is focused on who will be the next boss, they may all miss signs that the regime itself is cracking. For now, financial-market Kremlinologists are preoccupied with which assets to hold and which to avoid. But at some point capital will become scarcer. Somebody may find that they have taken an expensive bath.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Finance and economics&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Bath time for bonds&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 20:40:46 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Charity begins at work]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/06/charity-begins-at-work]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_wbd001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-06T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HE REPORT&lt;/small&gt; was devastating. The working environment at the organisation was described as “toxic”. There was widespread bullying of staff and a bunker mentality among senior management; 39% of employees developed mental or physical health issues as a result of their work. An investment bank or a technology firm in Silicon Valley? No. This was Amnesty International, a human-rights charity. Five managers have just left the organisation following the report’s findings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Workplaces create their own hierarchies, regardless of whether the aim of the operation is to help people or make money. Two female partners at &lt;small&gt;KPMG&lt;/small&gt;, an accountancy group, recently left out of concern at the behaviour of a male colleague. Coming from a family of teachers, Bartleby can attest that school staff rooms are beset by bitter rivalries. Universities are famous for their internecine disputes, as captured in the adage that “academic politics are so vicious precisely because the stakes are so small.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Amnesty, the problem was not with staff motivation. The report, by the KonTerra group, a consultancy, makes clear that many employees regarded their job as a “vocation or life cause” that provided them with “a compelling sense of purpose and meaning”. But that commitment proved to be a double-edged sword.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, in the eyes of workers, managers believed the importance of the &lt;small&gt;NGO&lt;/small&gt;’s work was so great that they did not need to listen to staff concerns. Employees, the higher-ups seemed to conclude, “should be grateful for being able to work at Amnesty”. Second, workers found it difficult to set healthy boundaries on their hours (or on their tolerance of a toxic climate) owing to a deeply held belief in their mission.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One cause of stress was a process called the Global Transition Programme, which moved Amnesty’s staff away from headquarters and closer to the abuses they covered. Workers felt that their views about these transfers were not seriously considered and that the implementation of the programme was rushed. As a result, employees found their work patterns disrupted, even as some moved to high-risk locations. Concerns came to a head when Gaëtan Mootoo, a long-time employee, committed suicide, leaving a note blaming work pressures. Another staff member committed suicide shortly afterwards, although inquiries found no evidence that the death was work-related. These tragic incidents led to the commissioning of the report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So what went wrong? On the surface, Amnesty seemed to offer services to help employees cope with stress. Staff were eligible for five counselling sessions, and an external reporting service for whistle-blowing had been created. Programmes were developed to train leaders and to help staff support their colleagues. But these efforts were described as “ad hoc, reactive and inconsistent”. In a survey 85% of employees said they had not been given enough guidance to support the well-being of their colleagues.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The problem clearly came from the top. If senior management is not committed to a caring atmosphere, no amount of discussion groups or special programmes will make things better.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A certain amount of stress at work is inevitable. Most organisations are hierarchical. Deadlines are a part of life, as is uncertainty over whether individual projects are going to succeed. But workers who are stressed and fearful are unlikely to stay in their jobs or be productive in the long run.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many managers derive a lot of their status from their oversight role. That is, in part, why organisations create such roles: they can reward high-achieving employees with a title as well as with extra money. But power is seductive. Peter Cappelli, a scholar of human resources at the Wharton School in Philadelphia, says that toxicity arises when “the boss acts like a dictator and actively punishes people who articulate different views or express disagreement”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Amy Edmondson of Harvard Business School explains in her book, “The Fearless Organisation”, the ideal is to create an atmosphere of “psychological safety” where workers can speak their minds. Managers need to learn the art of “respectful inquiry”, where they ask employees questions and listen intently to the answers. The bosses at Amnesty may have listened to the political dissidents whose causes they were championing. But they clearly weren’t listening to their staff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 20:40:45 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[A revolutionary treatise goes on the block]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/books-and-arts/2019/06/06/a-revolutionary-treatise-goes-on-the-block]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_bkp999.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-06T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;M&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;ODERN CAPITALISM&lt;/small&gt; began among the European merchant families of the early Renaissance—the Fuggers of Augsburg, Medicis of Florence and, in Venice, one Antonio de Rompiasi, who in 1464 hired a tutor in mathematics for his three sons. Like any sensible teacher, young Luca Pacioli aimed to make his lessons memorable and clear. Good humanist that he was, 30 years later he gathered all the world’s knowledge of the subject into a single massive volume.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His “Summa de Arithmetica, Geometria, Proportioni et Proportionalita” was the 615-page work of a mature professor who had spent decades working across northern Italy. The book was revolutionary on more than one count. It integrated computation using Hindu-Arabic numerals with the logic of classic Greek geometry; it was written in the vernacular of the marketplace rather than Latin (see Johnson); it circulated in large numbers thanks to the new technology of printing. Yet its greatest significance lay in a slim “how to” chapter that described the double-entry accounting system used by Venetian merchants.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With examples from dealers in butter to lemons to silk, Pacioli set out the method for tracking income and expenditure and the calculation of net profit or loss, which for the first time allowed an immediate snapshot of a firm’s financial position. This brief section would facilitate the birth of the modern corporation.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Without order there is chaos,” Pacioli observed in a breezy style that is still in vogue in business books today. His manual is stuffed with quotes from scripture and Dante and pithy advice such as “Don’t learn from ignoramuses who have more leaves than grapes.” He wrote the accounting chapter to help would-be traders in Venice, then the capital of the financial world, “sleep easily at night”. Without double-entry book-keeping, “their minds would keep them awake with worry”. He could not suspect that what might be called “Book-keeping for Dummies” would become the backbone of business for centuries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Like many monumental works of 15th-century printing, Pacioli’s treatise has survived in its original form. Some 120 copies still exist, from an initial run of about 1,000. Now today’s moguls have a chance to own this first folio of finance. Christie’s, the auction house, is offering a first edition in the original vellum binding for sale in New York on June 12th. The starting price is $1m for what it unabashedly calls “the most influential work in the history of capitalism”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pacioli’s later life augments the glamour of the first printed use of “plus” and “minus” signs. Impressed by the book, Leonardo da Vinci convinced his patron Lodovico Sforza to hire Pacioli to teach at the court of Milan. Pacioli and Leonardo collaborated on the treatise “Divina Proportione”, which married maths with art through the study of perspective. Not one, but two Renaissance masters were thus responsible for the exquisite harmony of “The Last Supper”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Books and arts&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;The first folio of finance&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 20:40:44 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What it’s like to spend half a life in solitary confinement]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/06/06/what-its-like-to-spend-half-a-life-in-solitary-confinement]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190608_usp004.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-06T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;ONY MEDINA&lt;/small&gt; is a polite, burly man with heavily tattooed arms. Like all those confined at the Allan B. Polunsky Unit, he is dressed in white. The prison’s squat grey buildings hold 214 death-row convicts. Locked into a tiny booth in a visiting room, handcuffs off, he compares being “out here” to a vacation. It is quiet, save clangs of metal doors. The room is also cooled and, a rarity, he can see through Plexiglas to the face of another human.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was convicted in 1996, aged 21, for a drive-by shooting that killed two children at a new-year party. Since then, for 23 years, he has been awaiting execution. In Texas the death penalty is applied to those found guilty of a heinous crime who are also judged to be a threat to others. Mr Medina’s legal appeals are continuing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A deafening wall of noise was “my clearest first memory of death row”, he says. “It’s gates slamming, the steel on steel, prisons are all concrete and steel, so it echoes, echoes, echoes. It never stops.” On his first night he was placed in a darkened wing full of shouting inmates, a dumbfounding experience, “like ThunderDome-type noise, yelling and screaming and banging and everything multiplied”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://w.soundcloud.com/player/?url=https%3A//api.soundcloud.com/tracks/632130738%3Fsecret_token%3Ds-VmRq8&amp;amp;color=%23ff5500&amp;amp;auto_play=false&amp;amp;hide_related=false&amp;amp;show_comments=true&amp;amp;show_user=true&amp;amp;show_reposts=false&amp;amp;show_teaser=true&amp;amp;visual=true&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At first he shared a cell. Then, after other prisoners tried an escape in 1998, all death-row inmates were shifted to solitary. He complains that this is agony. “I wasn’t sentenced to solitary confinement. I was sentenced to death.” Every day since, for 19 years, he has been alone for 23 hours inside a concrete box measuring 7 feet by 11 feet. Guards pass trays of food through a slat in a door. Standing on his bed he can peer from a vent-window, a few inches high, near the ceiling. “Some guys spend all day long” doing so, he says. He never does, shunning “what is out there that I can’t touch”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He gets an hour in an enclosed yard, most days, for recreation. Again he is alone. In his cell he reads (at the moment a series about survivalists), writes or sometimes paints. Relations and volunteers, mostly European women, visit and send messages. Inmates shout to each other, cell-to-cell. But Texas, unlike some states, denies solitary prisoners any physical contact, other than frequent body inspections by guards. He says he last touched a relative, hugging his mother, on August 1st 1996.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other states with the death penalty, and federal prisons, have less strict conditions. In many, young inmates and those with mental-health problems are no longer isolated for long. Even Texas, with more prisoners in solitary than any other state—about 4,000 as of 2017—is reducing its numbers. A report in 2018 by the Liman Centre at Yale estimated that 61,000 inmates were kept isolated in America, including 1,950 who had endured six months or more. That tally is probably lower today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Medina believes Texas goes on isolating its death-row prisoners out of vindictiveness, not because of security. He calls the practice outright “torture”, “cruel and inhumane”, a means of “intimidation to break a person mentally” before his execution. (On average a death-row prisoner in Texas waits nearly 11 years before being put to death; the longest wait was 31 years.) It is hard to dispute his claims.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dennis Longmire, of Sam Houston State University in nearby Huntsville, says prolonged use of solitary cells is costly and needless. The &lt;small&gt;UN&lt;/small&gt; and advocacy groups routinely condemn the practice. He has testified at 40 trials that older inmates are not especially violent to others. He recalls that his own visits to death row were deafening and unpleasant. Unsurprisingly, many guards demand to work elsewhere.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many inmates suffer mental deterioration, and some turn to suicide, says Mr Medina, whose once “solid” immediate neighbour broke after 15 years. Prisoners grow anxious from isolation and sensory deprivation and obsessed by what they see as official petty malevolence. Inmates in Polunsky were refused permission to buy nail-clippers for 17 years. Nor are they supposed to decorate their cell walls.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some crack while waiting for execution. When close friends are taken away—sometimes noisily resisting—for lethal injections, there is added turmoil. He counts 437 executions in Texas since he arrived on death row, including “guys that I’ve considered brothers”. It is especially distressing, he says, hearing guards chat and joke as condemned men are removed for execution. Many inmates arrive with mental difficulties. One death-row inmate in Polunsky, Andre Thomas, gouged out his own eyes and ate one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In conversation Mr Medina is articulate and measured, but he says isolated confinement takes a toll. He experiences intense rage, which he calls beneficial, towards “the system—the way I hold onto my sanity is by reminding myself to be angry at the people that put me here.” The anger helped him “build a lot of walls very high…in my mind”, but “it’s not very healthy” for it “can eat at you”. He has heard of inmates in Texas, released from solitary, unable to cope among other people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His response echoes the words of Albert Woodfox, a prisoner kept in solitary confinement in Louisiana for 40 years before being released in 2016, aged 69. Mr Woodfox recently published a book, “Solitary”, in which he writes that “the fight for sanity never goes away” and says he “shut my emotional system down” to cope with being locked away alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At issue is not whether to punish the guilty—though Mr Woodfox did eventually prove he was wrongfully convicted. It is whether America should treat even its worst offenders like this. “I feel like we’re seen in the same light as places like China, Saudi Arabia and Iran. That’s the company we keep,” says Mr Medina. “Human beings are not meant to be isolated in this way.” &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;United States&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Two decades in a concrete box&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 20:40:43 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“The crisis isn&#x27;t around the corner, yet”—the EU challenges Italy’s finances]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/06/the-crisis-isnt-around-the-corner-yet-the-eu-challenges-italys-finances]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190608_blm507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-06T11:30:07Z&quot;&gt;Jun 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;EUROPEAN OFFICIALS have threatened a substantial &lt;strong&gt;fine if &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/11/italy-is-out-of-recession-but-for-how-long&quot;&gt;Italy doesn’t shrink its debt&lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/05/11/italy-is-out-of-recession-but-for-how-long&quot;&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; and budget deficit. Whether or not it follows through, markets are already punishing the country. Tens of thousands of &lt;strong&gt;refugees have crossed the border into Canada from America&lt;/strong&gt;, but as an election looms, the government is rethinking its openness. And, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/05/16/the-joy-of-absence&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;the plague of “presenteeism”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;: when your work is done, just go home. Runtime: 20 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/basta-theeuchallengesitaly-sfinances&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 19:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[America is aggressively deploying a new economic arsenal to assert its power]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/06/america-is-aggressively-deploying-a-new-economic-arsenal-to-assert-its-power]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/print-edition/20190608_LDD001_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-06T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 6th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;W&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HEN DONALD TRUMP&lt;/small&gt; arrived in the Oval Office he promised to restore America’s might. His method has turned out to be a wholesale weaponisation of economic tools. The world can now see the awesome force that a superpower can project when it is unconstrained by rules or allies. On May 30th the president threatened crippling tariffs on Mexico after a row over migration. Markets reeled, and a Mexican delegation rushed to Washington to sue for peace. A day later preferential trading rules for India were cancelled. Its usually macho government did not put up a fight and promised to preserve “strong ties”. China faces a ratcheting up of tariffs soon, and its tech giant, Huawei, has been severed from its American suppliers. The country’s autocratic leaders are enraged, but on June 2nd they insisted they still seek “dialogue and consultation”. A tighter embargo on Iran, imposed over European objections, is strangling its economy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Trump must view this scene with satisfaction. Nobody takes America for granted any more. Enemies and friends know that it is prepared to unleash an economic arsenal to protect its national interest. America is deploying new tactics—poker-style brinkmanship—and new weapons that exploit its role as the nerve centre of the global economy to block the free flow of goods, data, ideas and money across borders. This pumped-up vision of a 21st-century superpower may be seductive for some. But it could spark a crisis, and it is eroding America’s most valuable asset—its legitimacy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You might think that America’s clout comes from its 11 aircraft-carriers, 6,500 nuclear warheads or its anchor role in the &lt;small&gt;IMF&lt;/small&gt;. But it is also the central node in the network that underpins globalisation. This mesh of firms, ideas and standards reflects and magnifies American prowess. Though it includes goods traded through supply chains, it is mainly intangible. America controls or hosts over 50% of the world’s cross-border bandwidth, venture capital, phone-operating systems, top universities and fund-management assets. Some 88% of currency trades use greenbacks. Across the planet it is normal to use a Visa card, invoice exports in dollars, sleep beside a device with a Qualcomm chip, watch Netflix and work for a firm that BlackRock invests in.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Foreigners accept all this because, on balance, it makes them better off. They may not set the rules of the game, but they get access to American markets and fair treatment alongside American firms. Globalisation and technology have made the network more powerful although America’s share of world &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt; has fallen, from 38% in 1969 to 24% now. China cannot yet compete, even though its economy is approaching America’s in size.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite this, Mr Trump and his advisers are convinced that the world order is rigged against America, pointing to its rust-belt and its trade deficit. And rather than mimic the relatively restrained tactics of the last trade conflict, with Japan in the 1980s, they have redefined how economic nationalism works.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First, instead of using tariffs as a tool to extract specific economic concessions, they are being continuously deployed to create a climate of instability with America’s trading partners. The objective of the new Mexican tariffs—fewer migrants crossing the Rio Grande—has nothing to do with trade. And they breach the spirit of &lt;small&gt;USMCA&lt;/small&gt;, a free-trade deal signed by the White House only six months ago, which will replace &lt;small&gt;NAFTA&lt;/small&gt; (Congress has yet to ratify it). Alongside these big fights is a constant barrage of petty activity. Officials have skirmished over foreign washing machines and Canadian softwood lumber imports.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second, the scope of activity has been extended beyond physical goods by weaponising America’s network. Outright enemies such as Iran and Venezuela face tighter sanctions—last year 1,500 people, firms and vessels were added to the list, a record figure. The rest of the world faces a new regime for tech and finance. An executive order prohibits transactions in semiconductors and software made by foreign adversaries, and a law passed last year known as &lt;small&gt;FIRRMA&lt;/small&gt; polices foreign investment into Silicon Valley. If a firm is blacklisted, banks usually refuse to deal with it, cutting it off from the dollar payments system. That is crippling—as two firms, &lt;small&gt;ZTE&lt;/small&gt; and Rusal, discovered, briefly, last year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Such tools used to be reserved for times of war: the legal techniques used for surveillance of the payments system were developed to hunt al-Qaeda. Now a “national emergency” has been declared in tech. Officials have discretion to define what is a threat. Though they often clobber specific firms, such as Huawei, others are running scared (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/06/american-trustbusters-are-rattling-google-amazon-facebook-and-apple&quot; data-tegid=&quot;sutbeg5m9euojh52aesftem8h2sk5kpf&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;). If you run a global company, are you sure your Chinese clients are not about to be blacklisted?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The damage to America’s economy so far has been deceptively small. Tariffs cause agony in export hubs such as northern Mexico, but even if Mr Trump imposes all his threatened tariffs, the tax on imports would be worth only about 1% of America’s &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt;. His poll ratings at home have held up, even as they have slumped abroad. His officials believe the experiment in weaponising America’s economic network has only just begun.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, the bill is mounting. America could have built a global coalition to press China to reform its economy, but it has now squandered precious goodwill. Allies looking for new trade deals with America, including post-Brexit Britain, will worry that a presidential tweet could scupper it after it has been signed. Retaliation in kind has begun. China has begun its own blacklist of foreign firms. And the risk of a clumsy mistake that triggers a financial panic is high. Imagine if America banned the $1trn of Chinese shares trading in New York, or cut off foreign banks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the long run the American-led network is under threat. There are hints of mutiny—of America’s 35 European and Asian military allies, only three have so far agreed to ban Huawei. Efforts to build a rival global infrastructure will accelerate. China is creating its own courts to adjudicate commercial disputes with foreigners (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/china/2019/06/06/a-belt-and-road-court-dreams-of-rivalling-the-wests-tribunals&quot; data-tegid=&quot;ml6l113d3ne0sbg20poev9hdeacp5mtp&quot;&gt;Chaguan&lt;/a&gt;). Europe is experimenting with building a new payments system to get round the Iran sanctions, which could in time be used elsewhere. China, and eventually India, will be keen to end their dependence on semiconductors from Silicon Valley. Mr Trump is right that America’s network gives it vast power. It will take decades, and cost a fortune, to replace it. But if you abuse it, ultimately you will lose it.&lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Leaders&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Weapons of mass disruption&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2019 19:39:55 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>