<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Have Arthur Miller’s plays lost their edge?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/04/15/have-arthur-millers-plays-lost-their-edge]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BKP502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-15T16:20:27Z&quot;&gt;Apr 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ARTHUR MILLER did not aim to please his audiences. He reckoned that new ideas were a “humiliation” and an “affront” not only to people’s sensibilities but to their convictions, too. Like the ancient Greeks, Miller thought of drama as a “civic art”, a discipline that could contribute towards a state’s social and political progress. Unlike his contemporaries, he was not commercially minded. He said what no one else had the courage to, and his audiences would weep, or sit with their heads bowed. Irate patriots picketed theatres, and producers shied away from his work. Actors who appeared in his plays were shunned by their friends. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miller’s observations hold true in the 21st century, particularly about the fallacy of the American Dream. Many still think of material wealth and status as essential to happiness, as Willy Loman does in “Death of a Salesman”. “The American Clock”, which reflects on the Wall Street Crash and the Great Depression, is a reminder of the perils of short-termism. “The Price”, set 30 years later, focuses on the longer-term repercussions. In “All My Sons” Miller questions individualist thinking. “The Crucible” examines the destructive allure of ideologies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those insights, far from alienating today’s audiences, are now Miller’s selling points. Productions of his work have increased since his death in 2005, according to Susan Abbotson, the president of the Arthur Miller Society. He has been among the ten most-performed playwrights in American theatres for the past four years. Six productions of his work are currently being staged in London, an unusually high number for any playwright other than William Shakespeare. Tickets in the West End sell for as much as £142 ($186), a sum Miller would no doubt have been uncomfortable with given his belief that theatre should be affordable. Does this popularity suggest that his plays have lost their subversive edge?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps—time can dull even radical ideas. It is no longer shocking to hear that humans are doomed to repeat their mistakes. But Miller’s fashionableness also suggests that directors have stopped confronting their audiences, and have started pandering to them. A recent production at the Union Theatre of “An Enemy of the People”, Miller’s adaptation of Henrik Ibsen’s play, had an image of President Donald Trump on its poster. The action was set in a contemporary “small-town Republican” community. Mayor Stockmann, a manipulative politician, dresses in a red suit, grinning and waving to chants of “USA! USA!” Miller never assigned a political persuasion to the play’s characters—he saw himself as a mediator, showing disparate groups what they have in common—but the suggestion here was that only Republicans can succumb to populist rhetoric and misinformation. This version of “An Enemy of the People” reinforced divisions, and allowed its audience to leave feeling smug.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Productions can also be too reverent of the source material. “The Price” (at Wyndham’s Theatre) strives for a historically accurate depiction of New York in the 1960s. The audience sees Gregory Solomon, a Russian-Jewish émigré, blessing his meagre lunch—a hard-boiled egg—in Hebrew. When the play was first performed in 1968, such details invited audiences to reflect on their city’s recent past, particularly the emotional fall-out from the boom and busts of the ‘20s and ‘30s. Now heightened for comic effect, they seem alien and strange. Miller wanted his plays to be relatable, not preserved in aspic—“there are museums for such activities,” he said—and so the setting must be familiar. In 2012 a production in Mumbai turned Solomon into a Muslim nonagenarian to great effect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Miller’s plays provoked because they were about the audience as much as for them. “The Crucible” (pictured, at the Yard Theatre) opens with the townspeople of Salem dressed in the same style of clothing—beanie hats, baggy t-shirts, cargo trousers—as the audience of this edgy North London theatre. They are invited to confront an uncomfortable truth: any society, no matter how educated or tolerant it believes itself to be, can submit to hysteria. Reactions ranged from brow-furrowed confusion to wide-eyed fascination.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is difficult for Miller’s plays to have the same effect today as when their themes were still unfamiliar, even taboo. Perhaps contemporary playwrights are better placed to touch modern nerves. But thoughtful stagings can continue to make audiences reflect on their own prejudices and shortcomings.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2019 00:08:43 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[India’s enormous election, and more from our daily podcast]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/15/indias-enormous-election-and-more-from-our-daily-podcast]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/the_intelligence_53.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-15T11:09:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE WORLD’S largest democratic exercise is under way in India. The prime minister, Narendra Modi, looks likely to win on a divisive platform of Hindu nationalism and aggression towards Pakistan, even if those are not voters’ biggest concerns. Social-media companies are increasingly under the microscope of regulators; we take a look at the seemingly intractable problem of policing online content. And pole-dancing is trying to shed its seedy image. But can it develop into a global sport? Runtime: 21 min. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/modi-soperandi-india-senormouselection&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/ &quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 19:06:29 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tiger Woods wins his fifth Masters in a comeback for the ages]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/04/15/tiger-woods-wins-his-fifth-masters-in-a-comeback-for-the-ages]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BLP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-15T03:02:53Z&quot;&gt;Apr 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUST A YEAR and a half ago, the most common question about Tiger Woods’s future was not whether he would win another major tournament, but whether he would ever play competitively again. After an unprecedented run of glory in which he won 14 majors in just over 12 years, Mr Woods saw his career derailed by an infidelity scandal, injuries and over-use of prescription drugs. Already on the wrong side of 40 years old, Mr Woods’s legacy appeared to be fixed: a star that burned brighter than any other but was extinguished far too soon, a victim of the hubris caused by too much success at too young an age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was then. On April 14th Tiger unleashed his roar once again—literally. After winning the Masters Tournament for the fifth time and a major championship for the 15th, he screamed at the top of his lungs while lofting his arms and putter high into the air, before embracing his caddy, family members and vanquished rivals as he seemed to fight back tears of joy. Much like the broader narrative of his career, it was also the first time he had come from behind to secure a major: in all of his previous victories, he had led at the start of the final round. Mr Woods’s title is not only a personal triumph, but also a welcome boon to golf as a game. Only the presence of its biggest star atop the leaderboards enables it to compete with the most popular team sports for viewership and cultural relevance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one would confuse the play of the grizzled, 43-year old Mr Woods with that of the 21-year-old phenom who won the Masters by a record 12 strokes in 1997. Whereas the young Mr Woods was so dominant that he barely seemed to be playing the same sport as his competitors were, this version seemed all too human. He frequently sprayed drives into the trees and misfired on straightforward putts, turning birdies into pars and pars into bogeys. He trailed by four strokes after the first round, by one at the cut and by two on Sunday morning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But just as Mr Woods has learned how to deal with adversity in his personal life, so too has he mastered how to limit the cost of mistakes on the golf course. Time and again, Mr Woods found a window through trees or a path around hazards, recovering from an errant tee shot with a pinpoint approach. (His driving accuracy of 62.5% was among the worst in the tournament, while his 81% rate of reaching greens in regulation was the best.) On the par-four ninth hole on the final day, his second shot landed at the far end of a long, downward-sloping green—a predicament in which the younger Mr Woods rarely found himself, where escaping with a par would feel like an eagle. Now a wily veteran, Mr Woods uncorked a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.golf.com/news/2019/04/14/masters-2019-tiger-woods-lag-putt&quot;&gt;lag putt for the ages&lt;/a&gt;. He aimed the ball on a line far above the straight path to the hole, and barely tapped it despite the vast distance. It almost stopped short as it approached the ridge—and then veered hard towards the hole, gaining speed as it plunged downhill, before coming to rest just inches from its target. The stroke he saved after tapping in for par wound up constituting his entire margin of victory, encapsulating the story of the tournament: unlike his rivals, Mr Woods refused to beat himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/tiger_winprob.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/tiger_winprob.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/tiger_winprob.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/tiger_winprob.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/tiger_winprob.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/tiger_winprob.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/tiger_winprob.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/tiger_winprob.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/tiger_winprob.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/tiger_winprob.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even after that par save, Mr Woods trailed Francesco Molinari by a stroke—a deficit that doubled after he bogeyed the tenth hole. EAGLE, &lt;i&gt;The Economist&lt;/i&gt;’s statistical win-probability model for golf tournaments, gave Mr Molinari a 65% chance of victory heading into the 12th hole, while Mr Woods languished at 16% (see chart). Just last July, Mr Molinari got the better of Mr Woods, when they were in the same playing group on the final day of the Open Championship in Scotland and Mr Molinari went on to win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This time, however, Mr Molinari succumbed to the demons that have undone so many a contender on the back nine on Sunday at Augusta National Golf Club. He left his tee shot short on the par-three 12th, seeing it disappear into the waters of Rae’s Creek, and then failed to make his putt for bogey. Mr Woods, in contrast, played it safe and made par. Three holes later, Mr Molinari saw his hopes of trying on his first Masters victor’s green jacket dashed for good. A poor drive on the par-five 15th forced Mr Molinari into an awkward approach shot, which bounced off a tree and wound up in the water as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Woods, meanwhile, displayed the steely resolve that made him an icon a decade ago. On the same hole that finished Mr Molinari, Mr Woods secured a birdie with a dead-centre drive, a meticulous approach to the green, and a clean two-putt. And on the next hole, the par-three 16th, he delighted the fans with a taste of his magic of yesteryear. His high-arcing tee shot first hit the green beyond one-putt range. But it then rolled sideways towards the hole like a heat-seeking missile, until he was assured of a tap-in birdie and a two-stroke lead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even then, Mr Woods wound up needing stumbles from his rivals to compensate for his own. Both Dustin Johnson, who by most statistical measures is currently the best player in the world, and Brooks Koepka, who had won three of the past six majors he had entered, reached the 18th green at 12 under par with achievable, if challenging, birdie putts. Both missed—barely, in Mr Johnson’s case. That wound up making the difference in the tournament, as Mr Woods muffed both his approach shot on the 18th and his putt for par. No one dreams about winning the Masters with a bogey, but it was a fitting end to a gritty triumph.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Must it be St Nicklaus?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Woods’s victory gives him a long-overdue 15th major title, leaving him three behind Jack Nicklaus’s all-time record of 18. Mr Nicklaus won his last at the age of 46, suggesting that Mr Woods has at least three more years to bridge the gap. Now that Mr Woods has rediscovered his form, might golf’s most treasured record now be within reach?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The afterglow of Mr Woods’s win is probably not the best time to preach faith in statistical golf models. EAGLE gave him just a 2.2% chance of winning the Masters, less than half the probability implied by pricing in betting markets. Although such odds might appear uncommonly long, they were no knock on Mr Woods’s game: most major victors start the tournament with less than a one-in-20 chance. In EAGLE’s estimation, Mr Woods was playing sufficiently well before the Masters began that he was already one of the top ten players in the world. Instead, the daunting odds were merely a reflection of how much good fortune is required, in addition to elite skill, to beat a field containing all of the world’s best players over just 72 holes. Even Mr Johnson, whom the model anointed as the favourite and finished tied for second, had less than a 10% shot to win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brutal arithmetic of large golf tournaments suggests that if Mr Woods is now a top-five player, he would be expected to win another major roughly once every 3.5 years. As a “mere” top-ten competitor, that frequency would fall to around one every six years. From this perspective, Mr Nicklaus should only feel threatened if Mr Woods manages to regain his former status as the unquestioned world number one despite his advanced age. That would mean following up this Masters victory with a steady drumbeat of scores in the 60s and finishes in the top 5 and 10 of PGA Tour events. (Mr Woods’s Masters performance alone has improved EAGLE’s estimate of his expected score on a typical course by over a tenth of a stroke per round).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Otherwise, the smart money will probably remain on Mr Woods’s major-championship tally remaining at 15. However, statistical models rely on extrapolating historical patterns into the future. And since no one has ever played golf as well as Mr Woods did at his best, there is no precedent on which to train a model for the second act of such a career. As the crowds roared following his every birdie and his rivals’ every misstep, distracting players two or three holes away, a victory that was still statistically improbable already felt inevitable in the heart of every fan who had seen Mr Woods in his heyday. Much to the delight of the lords of golf, even the most casual of observers will make sure to tune in the next time Mr Woods strides to the tee box with a major on the line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 16:07:41 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Tiger Woods wins his fifth Masters in a comeback for the ages]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/04/14/tiger-woods-wins-his-fifth-masters-in-a-comeback-for-the-ages]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_BLP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-14T23:02:53Z&quot;&gt;Apr 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JUST A YEAR and a half ago, the most common question about Tiger Woods’s future was not whether he would win another major tournament, but whether he would ever play competitively again. After an unprecedented run of glory in which he won 14 majors in just over 12 years, Mr Woods saw his career derailed by an infidelity scandal, injuries and over-use of prescription drugs. Already on the wrong side of 40 years old, Mr Woods’s legacy appeared to be fixed: a star that burned brighter than any other but was extinguished far too soon, a victim of the hubris caused by too much success at too young an age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That was then. On April 14th Tiger unleashed his roar once again—literally. After winning the Masters Tournament for the fifth time and a major championship for the 15th, he screamed at the top of his lungs while lofting his arms and putter high into the air, before embracing his caddy, family members and vanquished rivals as he seemed to fight back tears of joy. Much like the broader narrative of his career, it was also the first time he had come from behind to secure a major: in all of his previous victories, he had led at the start of the final round. Mr Woods’s title is not only a personal triumph, but also a welcome boon to golf as a game. Only the presence of its biggest star atop the leaderboards enables it to compete with the most popular team sports for viewership and cultural relevance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No one would confuse the play of the grizzled, 43-year old Mr Woods with that of the 21-year-old phenom who won the Masters by a record 12 strokes in 1997. Whereas the young Mr Woods was so dominant that he barely seemed to be playing the same sport as his competitors were, this version seemed all too human. He frequently sprayed drives into the trees and misfired on straightforward putts, turning birdies into pars and pars into bogeys. He trailed by four strokes after the first round, by one at the cut and by two on Sunday morning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But just as Mr Woods has learned how to deal with adversity in his personal life, so too has he mastered how to limit the cost of mistakes on the golf course. Time and again, Mr Woods found a window through trees or a path around hazards, recovering from an errant tee shot with a pinpoint approach. (His driving accuracy of 62.5% was among the worst in the tournament, while his 81% rate of reaching greens in regulation was the best.) On the par-four ninth hole on the final day, his second shot landed at the far end of a long, downward-sloping green—a predicament in which the younger Mr Woods rarely found himself, where escaping with a par would feel like an eagle. Now a wily veteran, Mr Woods uncorked a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.golf.com/news/2019/04/14/masters-2019-tiger-woods-lag-putt&quot;&gt;lag putt for the ages&lt;/a&gt;. He aimed the ball on a line far above the straight path to the hole, and barely tapped it despite the vast distance. It almost stopped short as it approached the ridge—and then veered hard towards the hole, gaining speed as it plunged downhill, before coming to rest just inches from its target. The stroke he saved after tapping in for par wound up constituting his entire margin of victory, encapsulating the story of the tournament: unlike his rivals, Mr Woods refused to beat himself.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure &gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/tiger_winprob.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;  srcSet=&quot;/sites/default/files/imagecache/200-width/tiger_winprob.png 200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/300-width/tiger_winprob.png 300w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/400-width/tiger_winprob.png 400w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/640-width/tiger_winprob.png 640w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/800-width/tiger_winprob.png 800w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1000-width/tiger_winprob.png 1000w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1200-width/tiger_winprob.png 1200w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1280-width/tiger_winprob.png 1280w,
/sites/default/files/imagecache/1600-width/tiger_winprob.png 1600w&quot; sizes=&quot;(min-width: 600px) 640px, calc(100vw - 20px)&quot;/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even after that par save, Mr Woods trailed Francesco Molinari by a stroke—a deficit that doubled after he bogeyed the tenth hole. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://eagle.economist.com&quot;&gt;EAGLE&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;i&gt;The Economist&lt;/i&gt;’s statistical win-probability model for golf tournaments, gave Mr Molinari a 65% chance of victory heading into the 12th hole, while Mr Woods languished at 16% (see chart). Just last July, Mr Molinari got the better of Mr Woods, when they were in the same playing group on the final day of the Open Championship in Scotland and Mr Molinari went on to win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This time, however, Mr Molinari succumbed to the demons that have undone so many a contender on the back nine on Sunday at Augusta National Golf Club. He left his tee shot short on the par-three 12th, seeing it disappear into the waters of Rae’s Creek, and then failed to make his putt for bogey. Mr Woods, in contrast, played it safe and made par. Three holes later, Mr Molinari saw his hopes of trying on his first Masters victor’s green jacket dashed for good. A poor drive on the par-five 15th forced Mr Molinari into an awkward approach shot, which bounced off a tree and wound up in the water as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Woods, meanwhile, displayed the steely resolve that made him an icon a decade ago. On the same hole that finished Mr Molinari, Mr Woods secured a birdie with a dead-centre drive, a meticulous approach to the green, and a clean two-putt. And on the next hole, the par-three 16th, he delighted the fans with a taste of his magic of yesteryear. His high-arcing tee shot first hit the green beyond one-putt range. But it then rolled sideways towards the hole like a heat-seeking missile, until he was assured of a tap-in birdie and a two-stroke lead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even then, Mr Woods wound up needing stumbles from his rivals to compensate for his own. Both Dustin Johnson, who by most statistical measures is currently the best player in the world, and Brooks Koepka, who had won three of the past six majors he had entered, reached the 18th green at 12 under par with achievable, if challenging, birdie putts. Both missed—barely, in Mr Johnson’s case. That wound up making the difference in the tournament, as Mr Woods muffed both his approach shot on the 18th and his putt for par. No one dreams about winning the Masters with a bogey, but it was a fitting end to a gritty triumph.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Must it be St Nicklaus?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Woods’s victory gives him a long-overdue 15th major title, leaving him three behind Jack Nicklaus’s all-time record of 18. Mr Nicklaus won his last at the age of 46, suggesting that Mr Woods has at least three more years to bridge the gap. Now that Mr Woods has rediscovered his form, might golf’s most treasured record now be within reach?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The afterglow of Mr Woods’s win is probably not the best time to preach faith in statistical golf models. EAGLE gave him &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/06/our-masters-forecast-is-lukewarm-on-tiger-woods&quot;&gt;just a 2.2% chance&lt;/a&gt; of winning the Masters, less than half the probability implied by pricing in betting markets. Although such odds might appear uncommonly long, they were no knock on Mr Woods’s game: most major victors start the tournament with less than a one-in-20 chance. In EAGLE’s estimation, Mr Woods was playing sufficiently well before the Masters began that he was already one of the top ten players in the world. Instead, the daunting odds were merely a reflection of how much good fortune is required, in addition to elite skill, to beat a field containing all of the world’s best players over just 72 holes. Even Mr Johnson, whom the model anointed as the favourite and finished tied for second, had less than a 10% shot to win.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The brutal arithmetic of large golf tournaments suggests that if Mr Woods is now a top-five player, he would be expected to win another major roughly once every 3.5 years. As a “mere” top-ten competitor, that frequency would fall to around one every six years. From this perspective, Mr Nicklaus should only feel threatened if Mr Woods manages to regain his former status as the unquestioned world number one despite his advanced age. That would mean following up this Masters victory with a steady drumbeat of scores in the 60s and finishes in the top 5 and 10 of PGA Tour events. (Mr Woods’s Masters performance alone has improved EAGLE’s estimate of his expected score on a typical course by over a tenth of a stroke per round).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Otherwise, the smart money will probably remain on Mr Woods’s major-championship tally remaining at 15. However, statistical models rely on extrapolating historical patterns into the future. And since no one has ever played golf as well as Mr Woods did at his best, there is no precedent on which to train a model for the second act of such a career. As the crowds roared following his every birdie and his rivals’ every misstep, distracting players two or three holes away, a victory that was still statistically improbable already felt inevitable in the heart of every fan who had seen Mr Woods in his heyday. Much to the delight of the lords of golf, even the most casual of observers will make sure to tune in the next time Mr Woods strides to the tee box with a major on the line.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 09:05:46 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Chevron is buying Anadarko for $33bn]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/business/2019/04/13/chevron-is-buying-anadarko-for-33bn]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190420_blp901.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-13T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;IN RECENT MONTHS a question has been hanging over the plains of Texas: what would be the next big shale deal? The logic for consolidation seemed clear. Texas’s Permian basin is America’s most productive oilfield, despite a patchwork of plots with hundreds of owners. Shale companies looked cheap, with investors sceptical about firms’ ability to produce both oil and profits. On April 12th the curious got their answer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Chevron, a giant oil company, will pay $33bn in cash and shares to buy Anadarko, an independent producer with rich holdings in the Permian. It will also assume Anadarko’s $16bn debt. The deal transforms Chevron into the world’s second-biggest publicly traded oil-producer, behind only ExxonMobil. It is the latest sign of shale’s growing importance to the world’s biggest energy firms.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oil majors have arrived relatively late to fracking. Small, independent companies were first to set about coaxing oil from shale. They developed ways to drill not just down but horizontally, then assault shale with water and sand until the rock gave up its hydrocarbon riches. But the industry titans have warmed to the idea. Unlike, say, a complex deepwater project in a distant jurisdiction, shale offers quick drilling times, predictable cashflow and favourable American regulation. Smaller companies have often fracked frenetically, eager to reinvest proceeds and chase growth. Too frenetically at times; some took on more debt than they could handle. Giant companies have less experience with the technique. But their diversified revenue and larger balance-sheets allow them to accumulate acreage even as they drill at a more measured pace. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last year &lt;span&gt;BP&lt;/span&gt;, a British firm, paid $10.5bn to acquire the shale assets of BHP, a giant miner. ExxonMobil and Chevron have placed the biggest bets. Chevron’s shale holdings were vast even before the Anadarko deal. The company controlled 1.7m acres (690,000 hectares) in two of the Permian’s most productive regions. In March ExxonMobil said it expects production in the Permian to exceed 1m barrels a day within five years. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With Anadarko, Chevron’s Permian production may be 60% higher than ExxonMobil’s, according to Rystad Energy, a research firm. Anadarko gives Chevron more than just shale. Its assets include a liquefied-natural-gas project in Mozambique and holdings in the Gulf of Mexico. Still, Anadarko’s Permian plots would have been the main lure. With them, Chevron can drill more wells, more efficiently. Adjacent plots will let the company move farther sideways through the rock and simplify the transport of equipment and other inputs, such as the millions of gallons of water required to wrest oil from each well. Chevron reckons that the deal will bring $2bn in savings, all told. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some investors hope that, as shale companies consolidate, they will mature and their performance will improve. Independent producers may now bulk up, following the lead of Concho Resources. Last year it bought RSP&lt;span&gt; &lt;/span&gt;Permian, a rival, for $9.5bn. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Meanwhile, the supermajors’ holdings look poised to expand. ExxonMobil has said it would consider additional shale acquisitions. Royal Dutch Shell is rumoured to be weighing the purchase of Endeavor Energy, whose headquarters sit in the heart of the Permian. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not all investors are sold on the attractions of shale. Follow This, a group of them concerned about climate change, expressed disappointment that Chevron would spend $33bn on Anadarko, rather than on renewable energy. At its annual meeting next month, Chevron’s shareholders will vote on a resolution that would compel the company to disclose how it can reduce its carbon footprint in line with the Paris climate agreement. Chevron insists that it is “positioned to win in any environment”. An environmentally friendlier one may be an exception. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(此域名已被污染，谢谢大家一直以来的支持)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 23:42:17 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pete Buttigieg is emerging as a serious contender for the Democratic nomination]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/04/12/pete-buttigieg-is-emerging-as-a-serious-contender-for-the-democratic-nomination]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190413_USP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-12T17:11:47Z&quot;&gt;Apr 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;PETE BUTTIGIEG does a good line in self-deprecation. He knows that many voters do not know who he is. On the stump he describes how a woman at an airport asked if he was a reporter covering a political campaign. He jokes about his lack of physical height. He speaks of the “audacity of someone like me”, meaning a 37-year-old mayor of a smallish city joining the 2020 race for the presidency. He also tells crowds he is not a “prototypical candidate”, saying his youth is a virtue that makes him focus on long-term concerns, like climate change.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For a man with a hard-to-pronounce Maltese name and little experience of national politics, Mr Buttigieg is enjoying an extraordinarily good start to his campaign. His political memoir is selling fast. Television news shows and other media are following him closely. That interest is driven in part by the novelty of his having a husband, Chasten. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Buttigieg has been on the road and fundraising for weeks but will formally launch his campaign on April 14th in South Bend, the city in Indiana where has been mayor since 2012. On April 11th he received his first serious endorsement, from Steve Grossman, a former chairman of the national Democratic Party and a well-known political figure in Massachusetts. Mr Grossman will no doubt encourage more donors to give to the campaign. Mr Buttigieg has already raised a decent $7m, a figure that includes many small donations, a hallmark of a serious candidate. He mentions, over a beer in a New Hampshire brewery, that he now has the means to expand his campaign team across several states, and notes that everything is moving faster than he had expected a few weeks ago. He says he is braced for a “marathon, not a sprint”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Polls show voters warming to him. Bernie Sanders and Joe Biden (who has not yet declared) are consistently ranked in the lead in the Democratic race, but Mr Buttigieg seems to be jostling for the third spot in a crowded field. A poll in Iowa, published on April 11th, gave him 9% overall support. That rises to 12% among voters who are under 50 and 12% among respondents with a college degree. That is a big shift: three months ago Mr Buttigieg did not register among pollsters at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The veteran, who served in Afghanistan, is proving to be a capable campaigner and a strong orator. With his measured speaking style he can sound a bit like Barack Obama (who, he sometimes reminds his audiences, described him once as a future prospect for the party). As a participant in televised debates between Democratic candidates later this year he is likely to perform well. Much of the recent interest in him was sparked when he spoke eloquently at a town-hall meeting broadcast by CNN in early March. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At recent events in New Hampshire the crowds were large. When an art gallery in Manchester overfilled with 300 guests, he addressed the roughly equal number that had gathered outside. Standing on a bench he spoke about freedom, security and democracy. He also touched some emotional notes, mentioning his father’s recent death and the loving support of his husband. He repeated the performance inside.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rise of long-shot candidates from outside Washington has a long tradition. Bill Clinton’s jump from governor of Arkansas to Democratic nominee in 1992 surprised many. Jimmy Carter, who had been governor of Georgia, was little known before his successful run in 1976.  His clean-cut, God-fearing, small-town, virtuous persona appealed to many after the Nixon presidency.  Mr Buttigieg also emphasises his Christian faith and small-town virtues, playing up his distance from Washington. He talks, earnestly, of a public yearning for moral national leadership, saying “people are ready for something different” and it is time for “decency, honesty”. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How far can this carry him? The fact that Mr Buttigieg is openly gay is, on balance, an asset—progressive Democrats can less easily shun him as a white man who studied at Harvard and Oxford before working as a consultant for McKinsey. At the same time, his identity as a Christian, married, with business and military experience, all suggest he could be popular among more centrist Democrats. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He has weaknesses. Just over a quarter of South Bend’s population is African-American, but he has so far said little about their needs as unusually poor community. In his memoir he describes a battle to rename one avenue after Martin Luther King Junior, but mentions little else about African-Americans there. He has tried reaching out to black voters, for example by saying he would support the study of reparations for descendants of slaves. But it is unlikely African-Americans would see him as their most powerful champion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He has also been a bit shy about which policies he would make his own. He suggests there is little variation between Democrats on policy, saying it matters more to talk of values and aspirations rather than offer up a “14-point plan” for every policy area. He mentions issues—such as cyber security and climate change—that matter to him. But he is not ready to spell out in detail how he would address them. Before long he will have to do so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 02:06:21 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Do people become happier after 40?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/04/12/do-people-become-happier-after-40]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190413_WOC710.png&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;“LIFE BEGINS at forty”, according to an old saying popularised by a self-help book from the 1930s. The theory goes that years of hard work are rewarded with less stress and better pay; children begin to fly the nest; and with luck, a decent period of good health remains. A quick glance at self-reported happiness across the world appears to corroborate this view.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People in their teens and early 20s start out reasonably cheerful. Gallup, a pollster, asked a representative sample of people in 158 countries to rate their life satisfaction on a scale from zero to ten. The data reported by the authors of the World Happiness Report, an academic study backed by the UN, show that happiness among people across the world aged 15-19 was 5.35 on average in 2016-18. A slow depression then appears to set in. By the age of 35-39 average self-reported happiness falls to 5.09 points. Once people hit 40 their depression gradually lifts. At the age of 70 an individual’s self-reported happiness rises to 5.58 points, on average. On this basis happiness during a person’s lifetime follows a gentle U-shape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Life satisfaction does not follow this pattern in all countries. Self-reported happiness in former Soviet states declines markedly with a respondent’s age. Among males in India it is an inverted U: happiness rises to middle-age before declining into old age. Generally, Indians are among the gloomiest in the world, their average life satisfaction has &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/03/21/economic-growth-does-not-guarantee-rising-happiness&quot;&gt;fallen by 1.2 points&lt;/a&gt; over the past decade. When Indian men reach their 70s they are among the least happy in the world, reporting average life satisfaction of just 3.6 points. In contrast women aged 70 and over in America appear to be the world’s happiest group of people, with life satisfaction of some 7.5 points. The reasons for these differences are not well understood, but the idea of a U shape has been discussed by sociologists for decades.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One difficulty is that the data provide just a snapshot, so may simply be measuring cohorts of people rather than changes in individuals’ happiness as they age. By using longitudinal data, which tracks the same people over a long period of time, several studies have tried to find out whether happiness really is U-shaped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.sciencedirect.com/science/article/pii/S0167268112000601&quot;&gt;2012 study&lt;/a&gt; of happiness among Australians, Britons and Germans between 1980 and 2010 found that after controlling for income, relationships, health and the fact that longitudinal panels may be biased, self-reported happiness was flat between the ages of 20 and 55. It then rose through to the age of 75 as people enjoyed a stress-free life before declining sharply as their health deteriorated. Another &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://onlinelibrary.wiley.com/doi/full/10.1111/ecoj.12256&quot;&gt;study&lt;/a&gt; published in 2015 used the same data but employed a different methodology and found evidence for a U-bend in life. It posits that happiness is a simple function of vitality and emotional maturity: the latter rises with age, while vitality deteriorates with age, but in concert they combine to minimise happiness at around middle age.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Children play a part, too. A recent &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.nber.org/papers/w25597&quot;&gt;working paper&lt;/a&gt; published by NBER finds that children increase the happiness of European parents, especially for the first ten years. Parents become less happy, however, if having children causes them to encounter financial difficulties. It follows, then, that happiness bounces back for financially-stretched parents once those children become financially independent, but decreases for those parents that enjoyed their children in financial comfort. Evidence for the U-bend of life might be mixed but if life does begin at 40 then it might be down to the matter of money and kids.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(此域名已被污染，谢谢大家一直以来的支持)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 02:06:20 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Julian Assange: journalistic hero or enemy agent?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/04/12/julian-assange-journalistic-hero-or-enemy-agent]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190413_BLP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;JULIAN ASSANGE, hauled out of the Ecuadorian embassy in London on April 11th after nearly seven years of self-imposed confinement, pale and hirsute, was not a pleasant house-guest. He is alleged to have smeared faeces on the wall of the embassy and neglected his cat, among other uncouth behaviour, according to Ecuador’s exasperated foreign minister. Even so, claim his supporters, his expulsion and arrest was a grave assault on press freedom. Others think it a long-overdue reckoning with justice for a man who had unleashed information anarchy upon the West, culminating in the destabilisation of American democracy. Is Mr Assange a heroic journalist, reckless activist or even an enemy agent?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is no doubt that Mr Assange and his organisation, WikiLeaks, have published some of the most dramatic leaks of the past decade. These include documents exposing American wrong-doing in Iraq and Afghanistan (including larger estimates of civilian casualties in Afghanistan than previously reported, and video footage of an indiscriminate attack by an American helicopter in Iraq) in 2010. The same year it released a trove of over 250,000 juicy American diplomatic cables, stolen with the help of Chelsea Manning, then a junior soldier. Perhaps most seriously, in 2016 WikiLeaks was the conduit for Russian-hacked emails from the Democratic Party that may have swayed the course of America’s presidential election.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Assange’s admirers ask: what distinguishes him from the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt;, which published the leaked Pentagon Papers in 1971, exposing damning details of the Vietnam war? In some ways, Mr Assange was doing no more than following in the footsteps of such illustrious news organisations, which had long given a platform to anti-government leakers–and enjoyed First Amendment protections while doing so.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet there are several reasons why Mr Assange’s conduct puts him in a different category. The American charges against him point to one notable difference. They accuse Mr Assange not only of publishing leaked information—that is something that journalists do all the time–but also of helping Ms Manning to crack the password to a secret Pentagon network, making him a “co-conspirator” in illegal hacking. Many journalists egg on their sources to provide more information, as Mr Assange is alleged to have done; most do not help their sources pick physical or digital locks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;President Barack Obama’s justice department acknowledged that it could not prosecute Mr Assange’s leaking without criminalising the quotidian work of the media. But it warned, reasonably, that journalists did not have carte blanche: if they were believed to be agents of a foreign power, or conspiring in crimes with one, they could be legitimately booked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of WikiLeaks’ behaviour may have come close to crossing this line (though the extent of Mr Assange’s personal role in its activity is unknown). According to an indictment published by the special counsel, Robert Mueller, in 2016 WikiLeaks urged Russian spies—operating under a flimsy pseudonym—to send it emails relating to the then Democratic candidate, Hillary Clinton. Its aim was to sway the election in favour of her Democratic rival, Bernie Sanders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Donald Trump was the real beneficiary. “Boy, I love reading WikiLeaks,” he declared in 2016 (now, as president, he says WikiLeaks is “not my thing”). Mike Pompeo, then a Republican congressman, gleefully tweeted about WikiLeaks during the campaign. But in April 2017, having become director of the CIA, he called WikiLeaks “a non-state hostile intelligence service often abetted by state actors like Russia”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This points to a second difference between Mr Assange and ordinary reporters. Most responsible journalists would not implore an authoritarian country’s spies to send them secrets for the purpose of disrupting a democratic election; nor would they fail to inform readers about the dubious provenance of the information.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;WikiLeaks’ willingness to serve as an uncritical and enthusiastic laundromat for Russian intelligence reflects the group’s longer history of publishing material with little or no newsworthiness, but calculated to undermine American interests. A cache of CIA hacking tools published in 2017 was one example. In contrast, WikiLeaks almost never publishes leaks that might undermine America’s autocratic rivals. Mr Assange may not be an enemy agent, but he has at least been a useful idiot.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Assange’s commitment to dumping information, rather than reporting it, has put him directly at odds with real journalists. In 2011 he published the unredacted version of the American diplomatic cables, having disagreed with the decision of several newspapers to publish only redacted ones the previous year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His five partners—the &lt;em&gt;Guardian&lt;/em&gt;, the &lt;em&gt;New York Times&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;El País&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Der Spiegel&lt;/em&gt; and &lt;em&gt;Le Monde&lt;/em&gt;—condemned the move, pointing out that Mr Assange had revealed sensitive personal information and national-security details with little news value. Some named sources, such as an Ethiopian journalist, were forced to flee their countries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is right to be sceptical of the motives of Donald Trump’s administration. Britain should be wary of extraditing a high-profile suspect to a country whose justice department is in a state of political flux, and where details of the central offence of hacking are still sketchy—not least whether it was successful and what information, if anything, was stolen. But that does not mean the freedom of the press rests on the fate of Mr Assange. If Mr Assange deems himself to be a journalist, he is in desperate need of a remedial course on the basic ethics of the profession. Whether in Britain or America, he is likely to have plenty of time for that in the months ahead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 02:06:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Michael Nesmith’s back catalogue is a long-hidden treasure trove]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/04/12/michael-nesmiths-back-catalogue-is-a-long-hidden-treasure-trove]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190413_BKP507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-12T16:10:19Z&quot;&gt;Apr 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE COUNTERCULTURE of the 1960s produced a number of musicians who were simultaneously nourished by its spirit of change yet deeply rooted in, and fascinated by, America’s past. It would be mistaken to call this a movement; it was more an attitude. Its standard-bearers were The Band, whose mix of ramshackle rock’n’roll and old-timey aesthetics would form the basis of the Americana genre. Folk and country music were its principal sources, but such diverse figures as Van Dyke Parks, Harry Nilsson and Randy Newman would draw on more metropolitan sounds, including ragtime, vaudeville, musicals and American classical, as well as those of the American Gulf coast and the Caribbean.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A key figure is often left out of this story. The omission might seem odd, given that he was a member of one of the decade’s most successful bands: the Monkees, assembled by television producers for the comedy show of the same name. It made no odds that Michael Nesmith, like fellow Monkee Peter Tork (who died in February), was a product of the folk-music scene. His five-year tenure as a teen idol in a “manufactured” pop group (a dismissive phrase which overlooks how all groups are manufactured in one way or another, as well as Mr Nesmith’s revolt against that interference) would define him in the mind of the public, while his subsequent recording career would go overlooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A new box set, “Songs”, contains the first 11 of Mr Nesmith’s 14 (thus far) solo albums, along with a compilation from 1989. It offers an opportunity to reassess his body of work, and discover why he is so influential among musicians—acts as varied as the Breeders, the Jayhawks, Susanna Hoffs and Run-DMC have covered his songs—and cherished by a small but ardent following which at last has easy access to the bulk of his catalogue.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The set divides neatly into two parts. The first six discs cover a creative flurry between 1970, when Mr Nesmith took a hefty financial hit to be released from his Monkees contract, and 1973. These are the country-rock albums he recorded with his short-lived backing group, the First National Band, its successor of even briefer tenure, the Second National Band, and finally as the sole credited artist (now going by Michael, to distinguish him from the woolly-hatted television character “Mike”). The first of these albums, “Magnetic South”, would yield the only top-40 single of his solo career, “Joanne”—a reversal of fortune for the former member of an act which had scored five top-three singles and four number-one albums in a two-year period. Mr Nesmith’s fifth solo LP, in 1972, would bear the sardonic title “The Hits Just Keep On Coming”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was not that Mr Nesmith wished to be obscure or uncommercial, and there was nothing about his solo material that determined it should be. His composition “Different Drum” had five years before been a substantial hit for Linda Ronstadt’s group, the Stone Poneys, whose version stands as a minor classic. It is Mr Nesmith’s most celebrated song, and it says a great deal that many who enjoy it will have no idea he wrote it. His own, folksy take—strikingly different from the chiming, driving Stone Poneys number—underlines his distinctive qualities as a writer and performer: his way with a melody, his phrasing of concise narrative detail and his capacity to be at once wry and rueful.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Timing and circumstance condemned those first six records to obscurity. Mr Nesmith signed to Nashville’s leading label, RCA, but the burgeoning hip country-rock scene—for which his music would have been a natural fit—was suspicious at best of the ex-bubblegum pop star. Monkees fans, meanwhile, had already abandoned that group as it strove for artistic independence; they would have been bewildered by what they heard, if they heard it at all. Today, those albums make up a treasure trove, liable to delight the first-time listener.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Nesmith became notably less prolific as other interests intervened: it took him two decades to issue as much music as he did in those first three years. The video clip he made for “Rio”, one of his better-known songs, led him to devise a show called “PopClips” for Nickelodeon, a children’s cable channel. Acquired by TimeWarner, “PopClips” became the basis for MTV, the standalone channel that transformed music, and the music business, in the 1980s.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Rio”, with its Latin lilt, demonstrated how Mr Nesmith’s palette expanded from the mid-1970s onwards, as he released music on his own Pacific Arts label. The second half of “Songs” shows him becoming ever more experimental, with such pieces as the soundtrack to a book (“The Prison”, 1975) and its chiefly instrumental companion album, “The Garden” (1994). His more overtly pop albums utilise the sounds of the Americas in a way that prefigures the work of David Byrne. Never compromising, never anything other than amiably inventive, never sounding—no matter what form he works in—like anyone other than himself, Mr Nesmith has lived up to the pseudonym he once used in the 1960s: Michael Blessing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(此域名已被污染，谢谢大家一直以来的支持)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 00:06:15 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Can the law still do justice in America?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/04/12/can-the-law-still-do-justice-in-america]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://cdn.static-economist.com/sites/default/files/20190413_blp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-04-12T16:08:00Z&quot;&gt;Apr 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ANNE MCELVOY talks to Preet Bharara, a former federal attorney in New York, who successfully took on some of the biggest crimes in America involving corruption, organised crime and terrorism. He explains why Wall Street executives were not prosecuted for the financial crisis. He also expresses his concern about how politicised the Mueller report has become. And, Mr Bharara reveals what crime he would be tempted to commit and why he loves mafia movies.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-preetbharara&quot; width=&quot;500&amp;amp;quot;&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com&amp;amp;gt;Apple Podcasts | &amp;amp;lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.com https:=&quot;&quot; spotify=&quot;&quot; com=&quot;&quot; show=&quot;&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWVjb25vbWlzdGFza3M&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=142125&amp;amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/Business--Economics-Podcasts/The-Economist-Asks-p999213/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2019 00:06:14 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>