<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Who is blowing up ships in the Gulf?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/13/who-is-blowing-up-ships-in-the-gulf]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_blp504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-13T04:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SHINZO ABE hoped this was a moment for diplomacy. His visit to Tehran this week, the first by a Japanese prime minister since the Islamic revolution in 1979, was meant to reduce tensions between America and Iran. After a meeting with Iran’s president, Hassan Rouhani, Mr Abe warned that the region could “accidentally” slip into conflict. And then, a few miles off Iran’s southern coast, came an illustration of how that might happen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On June 13th two tankers in the Gulf of Oman sent distress calls after they had been damaged by large explosions. The Front Altair, flagged in the Marshall Islands and owned by Frontline, a Norwegian shipping company, was hauling a cargo of naphtha, an oil derivative, from Abu Dhabi; the Kokuka Courageous, registered in Panama and operated by the Japanese company Kokuka Sangyo, was laden with methanol. Both were bound for Asian ports. Photos from Iranian news agencies showed a fire burning on the starboard side of the Front Altair. The plume of black smoke overhead was thick enough to appear in satellite images. One-fifth of the world’s supply travels through the Strait of Hormuz, an important chokepoint for international shipping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the second time in just over a month that tankers have been damaged in the Gulf. On May 12th four ships anchored off Fujairah, a port in the United Arab Emirates (UAE), had holes blown in their hulls. A preliminary investigation suggests that they were damaged by limpet mines. The latest explosions caused far more damage, forcing crews to evacuate both ships as they were underway. It will take weeks to probe what happened, amid reports of torpedoes being used. But the explosions do not seem accidental. The president of Kokuka Sangyo said the Kokuka Courageous vessel was “attacked” twice in a three-hour period.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nor is it likely that two sets of explosions, weeks apart and in the same area, were mere coincidence. Though a UAE-led investigative team did not assign blame for last month’s sabotage, it said an unnamed “state actor” carried it out. America has blamed Iran for both sets of attacks. Iran, which is a regional rival of the UAE and Saudi Arabia, both American allies, has denied responsibility and hints that the latest explosions were orchestrated by its rivals. “Suspicious doesn’t begin to describe what likely transpired,” tweeted Iran’s foreign minister, Muhammad Javad Zarif, on June 13th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Iran has in the past threatened to close the Strait of Hormuz if it were ever attacked. Some will see the strikes against ships in the area as a veiled warning of its readiness to make good on its threat. Messrs Zarif and Rouhani probably understand that attacking regional shipping would be to play with fire. But they do not call all of the shots in Iran. They are stuck in an internal battle with Iran’s ruling mullahs, who are more distrustful of the West, and their Revolutionary Guards, who back local forces in Syria and Yemen that have fought against Emirati- and Saudi-backed forces. Iran has a history of irregular warfare that allows it to maintain a measure of plausible deniability. In the 1980s it fought the so-called tanker war with Iraq. The conflict ravaged international shipping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tensions in the region have been rising since last spring, when Donald Trump withdrew from the deal, signed in 2015, that loosened sanctions on Iran in exchange for limits on its nuclear programme. Mr Trump reimposed sanctions and added new ones, in effect cutting Iran off from the global economy. After a year of abiding by the agreement, a bid to win European sympathy, Iran last month said it would begin enriching uranium in excess of the prescribed limits. Mr Rouhani warned that he would abrogate other provisions unless other signatories—Britain, France, Germany, Russia, China and the European Union—helped his country bypass American sanctions, which is unlikely to happen. Critics of Mr Trump’s approach have long warned that economic distress would lead Iran to lash out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the Arab states across the Gulf, these latest explosions fit into a troubling pattern. In May, two days after the Fujairah incident, two blasts in the centre of Saudi Arabia, 700km north of the Yemeni border, damaged an oil pipeline that carries crude across the kingdom. On June 12th a rocket hit the international airport in Abha, a Saudi city 200km from the Yemeni border, injuring 26 people. Both attacks were carried out by the Houthis, a Shia militia that controls large parts of Yemen and is fighting a Saudi-led coalition there. A United Nations panel of experts has said that Iran supplied weapons to the Houthis, including drones and missiles, though the group does not always act at Iran&amp;#x27;s behest.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But Saudi Arabia and its allies have tried not to escalate directly a conflict that would wreak havoc on their oil exports, and thus their economies. The UAE has been particularly circumspect in its public statements about last month’s sabotage (though in private officials evince little doubt about Iran’s involvement). If there is to be a response, they would like it to come from America. Mr Trump’s hawkish national security adviser, John Bolton, has long supported regime change in Iran, and even military action against it. But the president, as ever, is erratic, toggling between fiery threats and offers of dialogue. He is reported to have given Mr Abe a message to pass to Iran’s supreme leader, Ali Khamenei (who declined to reply). “We do not believe at all that the US is seeking genuine negotiations with Iran; because genuine negotiations would never come from a person like Trump,” said Ayatollah Khamenei.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump has already bolstered America’s military presence in the region. Last month he rushed an aircraft-carrier strike group to the region. Those vessels have not transited the Strait of Hormuz, an effort to avoid further tension. They will probably step up their patrols; an American destroyer picked up some sailors from the stricken tankers (Iran says it rescued some too). The Pentagon is deploying an extra 1,500 troops to bases in Qatar, Bahrain and Iraq, and Mr Trump is invoking emergency powers to override congressional objections and sell weapons to Saudi Arabia and the UAE.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All sides insist they do not want war. But even if they are sincere, good intentions go only so far. The Gulf states (and their American protector) cannot tolerate threats to shipping. Mr Abe was right to push for diplomacy between America and Iran. But his visit, and the events that overshadowed it, underscore how difficult that will be.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 03:40:00 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why are the Chicago White Sox commemorating Disco Demolition Night?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/13/why-are-the-chicago-white-sox-commemorating-disco-demolition-night]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_BKP508.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-13T16:26:02Z&quot;&gt;Jun 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ON THURSDAY nights the Chicago White Sox give something back to baseball fans, usually T-shirts for the first 10,000 people through the gates of Guaranteed Rate Field. On July 4th the garment is a handsome navy-blue number to mark Independence Day; on July 25th they remember the legendary Sox team of 1983 with a “Miracle on 35th Street” tee. And today, June 13th, when they play the New York Yankees, they are planning to commemorate one of the strangest—and, for many people, most disgraceful—episodes in their history with a T-shirt bearing the legend: “Disco Demolition – the night records were broken.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disco Demolition Night took place on July 12th 1979 at the Sox’s old stadium, Comiskey Park. Trying to boost attendance in a season of poor crowds, the Sox invited a local DJ named Steve Dahl to provide some entertainment between the first and second games of a double-header against the Detroit Tigers. Mr Dahl, a rock DJ, had lost his slot at a radio station when it switched formats to disco, and when he got a new job he made much of his unequivocal hatred of the music. This hatred was to be the entertainment for fans. Mr Dahl invited his listeners to bring disco records to the ballpark where he would blow them up, to “end disco once and for all”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Sox had hoped for a crowd of 20,000; they got 50,000, with a further 20,000 locked out. During the first game, vinyl records began showering down on the outfield from the seats. The explosion during the break prompted a pitch invasion of several thousand people. Writing in 2014 Mr Dahl recalled it as “a joyous heat- and beer-infused celebration”, though footage shows fans tearing down the bullpen, building bonfires in the outfield and burning banners in the stands. It was described as “a riot” on local news, and it took mounted police in riot gear to clear the field. The second game was abandoned.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What made Disco Demolition Night infamous was that it seemed to symbolise the rage of white, male heterosexuality against black, Latino and gay culture. Comiskey Park was situated in the white working-class neighbourhood of Bridgeport, and there had been a history of racist incidents in the area. One African-American member of the stadium staff said that fans didn’t just bring disco records, they brought records by any black artist that came to hand. In &lt;em&gt;Rolling Stone&lt;/em&gt; Dave Marsh described it as “your most paranoid fantasy about where the ethnic cleansing of the rock radio could ultimately lead”, while Nile Rodgers of Chic, a disco and funk band, compared it to Nazi book-burning. Mr Dahl continues to insist that it was just a bit of fun—simply “one of the greatest radio promotions in history”, plus an expression of rebellion against a “trendy social elite”, a choice of words that echoes today. He has maintained that he has never been remotely racist or homophobic (he did not respond to a request for comment for this article). Yet the event has come to be seen as an appalling outbreak of prejudice. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So there has been a furious reaction to the Sox’s decision to mark the event, with Mr Dahl throwing the opening pitch. “I almost couldn’t believe it, I thought it was a joke,” Marea Stamper, an activist and American DJ who works under the moniker of The Black Madonna, says. She has no truck with Mr Dahl’s defence that he was simply aggrieved about losing his job to DJs playing disco, nor that it was a celebration. “I come from the South, and this was like people burning ‘race’ records—that was white families burning the black music their kids were listening to, and a way of enforcing racial borders and social barriers, with records as an effigy.” &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For all the decades of writing about Disco Demolition Night, and the analyses of it as a mass act of bigotry, the Sox seemed to have been caught by surprise by the furious reaction to their plans. In response to a request for comment they sent this statement: “This year’s Disco Demolition T-Shirt giveaway was intended to recognise the anniversary of a historic off-the-field moment...We have been communicating with our community partners who have raised concerns to make it clear that the intent of this giveaway was only meant to mark the historical nature of the night 40 years later. We have reinforced that the White Sox organisation is dedicated to advocating for a safe, welcoming ballpark experience for all people and communities...We remain proud of our franchise’s longstanding record on advocating for inclusion and diversity.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms Stamper laughs in contempt at that. “It’s not as if they were offering context—it’s not as if there’s a display at the ballpark saying what this riot was about, or even what some people say it was about. If it’s historical, where’s the history?” She thinks it is an ill-thought-out promotional event. “Take any other book burning or destruction of art, and imagine slapping a picture of it on a shirt and giving it away!”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 01:40:25 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hong Kong rattled by protests, the changing nature of war, and Australia’s nanny state]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/13/hong-kong-rattled-by-protests-the-changing-nature-of-war-and-australias-nanny-state]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/editors_picks_9.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-13T16:00:14Z&quot;&gt;Jun 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A SELECTION of three essential articles read aloud from the latest issue of The Economist. This week, huge demonstrations in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/13/the-rule-of-law-in-hong-kong&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Hong Kong&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; have rattled the territory’s government (08:50). America’s biggest defence merger highlights the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/15/the-utc-raytheon-deal-highlights-the-changing-nature-of-war&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;changing nature of war&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; (17:11). And, why Australia’s pioneering image cloaks a &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/asia/2019/06/15/australias-surprising-disregard-for-free-speech&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;nanny state&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;. Runtime: 23 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomisteditorspicks/editor-spicks-june13th2019&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 00:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The race to become Britain’s next PM]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/13/the-race-to-become-britains-next-pm]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-13T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HERESA MAY&lt;/small&gt; stepped down as leader of the Conservative Party on June 7th. She will remain as prime minister until her successor is chosen. Nominations for the Tory leadership closed on June 10th, to be followed by several rounds of voting among MPs to whittle down the ten candidates, a process that will take a week or two. The MPs will then send two names to party members who will make the final choice. The result of their vote will be announced before Parliament rises for summer. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;Betfair Exchange, a gambling website, has been tracking punters’ predictions on the next Tory leader. According to the wisdom of the betting crowd, a handful of candidates stand out. But there is only one clear frontrunner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Friday&amp;#x27;s edition of &lt;i&gt;The Economist asks&lt;/i&gt;, Anne McElvoy spoke to Jeremy Hunt and Rory Stewart about their leadership plans: &lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistasks/theeconomistasks-whocanleadbritainthroughbrexit-&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Adrian Wooldridge, our political editor, assesses the chances of some of the leading Conservative politicians hoping to take the top job in this short film: &lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://www.youtube.com/embed/ychDrZ2QzlE&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;315&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p data-interactive-&gt;Source: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.betfair.com/exchange/plus/politics&quot;&gt;Betfair Exchange&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 21:40:31 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Cricket’s increasing sizzle owes much to India]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/graphic-detail/2019/06/15/crickets-increasing-sizzle-owes-much-to-india]]></link><description>&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-15T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 15th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190615_GDC500cricket1/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;C&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;RICKET MATCHES&lt;/small&gt; between India and Pakistan are always heated. Their World Cup fixture on June 16th will be particularly fierce: in February an attack by militants on Indian police in Kashmir led to tit-for-tat airstrikes. Even neutral spectators, however, eagerly await pyrotechnics on the pitch. Scoring rates in cricket have been rising for decades, but in recent years they have exploded in the sport’s newer, shorter formats. The game’s evolution into a faster-paced, more exciting spectacle has been most notable in India. The Indian Premier League (&lt;small&gt;IPL&lt;/small&gt;), founded in 2008, has become cricket’s most lucrative product by copying the franchise system of American sports and importing star foreign players in a huge country with growing &lt;small&gt;TV&lt;/small&gt; viewership.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;small&gt;IPL&lt;/small&gt;’s other innovation was to adopt the T20 format, devised in England in 2003. Unlike Test matches—in which each team bats for two innings, taking up to five days—T20 gives each side one innings of 120 balls, limiting games to four hours. The rules are the same. Batsmen score as many runs as possible during an innings. Whacking the ball over the boundary rope yields four runs if it bounces on the field, and six if it does not. The fielders try to get the batsmen out by hitting the wooden wicket or catching an errant shot (among other methods of dismissal). Each side bats until either ten players are out or the fixed number of balls, or days, is used up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;In Test cricket batsmen often block the ball defensively, to preserve their wickets. But because it is rare for ten men to get out in just 120 balls, players in T20 try riskier shots in pursuit of faster rewards. The result makes baseball look sedate. Whereas an average night at Yankee Stadium produces two home runs, an average T20 match features 39 boundary shots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;These aggressive tactics have also been adopted in one-day internationals (&lt;small&gt;ODI&lt;/small&gt;s), the format used in the World Cup, which gives each side one innings of 300 balls. Boundary rates in &lt;small&gt;ODI&lt;/small&gt;s have soared since 2003. In contrast, the long increase of run-scoring in Tests stopped just when T20 was invented. It may not be possible to hit much more than 6.4% of balls to the boundary, as batting teams did in 2000-03, while occupying the crease for five days.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;https://infographics.economist.com/2019/20190615_GDC600cricket2/index.html&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Purists insist that slow-building Tests are more gripping than a flurry of sixes. But a survey of fans in 2018 found that only 69% are interested in Tests, rising to 92% for T20. Media Partners Asia, a consultancy, expects broadcasters to pay $1.4bn a year for T20 over the next four years, compared with $190m for Tests. England and Australia hope to emulate the &lt;small&gt;IPL&lt;/small&gt;’s success, using a similar template. Once a sporting imitator, India is now setting the trend. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure data-infographic-css=&quot;/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot;&gt;&lt;link href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://infographics.economist.com/2018/site-fixes/style.css&quot; rel=&quot;stylesheet&quot;/&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Graphic detail&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Beyond a boundary&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 20:40:22 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pebble Beach should give shorter hitters a chance at the U.S. Open]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/06/13/pebble-beach-should-give-shorter-hitters-a-chance-at-the-us-open]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_BLP502_facebook.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-13T11:47:36Z&quot;&gt;Jun 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NOWHERE BEATS Augusta National for tradition, but by common consent America’s most beautiful golf course is Pebble Beach Golf Links. Hugging the Pacific Ocean cliffs just south of Monterey, California, the stunning property is regularly voted country’s best public course. It has also been the site of many of the sport’s most memorable moments, including Tom Watson’s famous &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DO6qIg7aInw&quot;&gt;chip from thick rough&lt;/a&gt; to beat Jack Nicklaus in the 1982 U.S. Open.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nine years after the U.S. Open was last held at Pebble, the tournament returns to its most picturesque venue on June 13th. Two players in particular will be chasing history. After &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/04/14/tiger-woods-wins-his-fifth-masters-in-a-comeback-for-the-ages&quot; data-tegid=&quot;eu045r07t49jb6jg1o3h9jr7ocrbkk3l&quot;&gt;winning the Masters&lt;/a&gt; at Augusta in April, the 43-year-old Tiger Woods is on the hunt for a 16th major trophy, which would leave him just two behind Mr Nicklaus for the all-time record. And Brooks Koepka, fresh off a victory at the PGA Championship last month, is campaigning to become the first player to win the same major in three consecutive years since &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Peter_Thomson_(golfer)&quot;&gt;Peter Thomson&lt;/a&gt; managed the feat in 1954-56.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The swirling ocean winds at Pebble Beach can be nearly as frustrating for statistical modellers as they are for players. By the standards of modern major tournaments, it is a relatively short course, at just 7,075 yards for a par-71. (In contrast, last year’s U.S. Open, at Shinnecock Hills on Long Island, measured 7,445 yards and was only a par 70.) In theory, such accessible distances should yield a flock of birdies and perhaps even an &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.dictionary.com/browse/aerie&quot;&gt;aerie&lt;/a&gt; of eagles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But what Pebble lacks in length, it makes up for with nature and design. The omnipresent water hazard crashing alongside most of the course not only swallows up double and triple bogeys, but also forces cautious players into taking indirect lines and awkward lies. And the course’s sharp doglegs, towering trees and narrow fairways limit the use of drivers to a handful of holes. With a humped green that can send even well-placed approach shots scurrying away from the flag, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://www.sfgate.com/sports/kroichick/article/Pebble-Beach-s-14th-hole-is-pure-evil-3184718.php&quot;&gt;Pebble’s 14th &lt;/a&gt; is the hardest hole, relative to a typical hole of its distance and par value, measured at any major this millennium. According to EAGLE, &lt;i&gt;The Economist&lt;/i&gt;’s statistical golf-forecasting system, par-fives around 580 yards long typically took around 4.82 strokes to complete in majors in 2010, the last time the U.S. Open was held there. The unfortunate souls who had to navigate Pebble Beach’s 580-yard par-five that year averaged 5.44. (You can follow EAGLE’s predictions for the U.S. Open as they update in real time at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttp://eagle.economist.com&quot;&gt;eagle.economist.com&lt;/a&gt;.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because course organisers frequently modify holes from year to year—and adjust green conditions and hole locations once tournaments are underway—EAGLE places little weight on course-wide scoring data from the distant past. (In contrast, the relative difficulty of each hole to the course average tends to be stable over time.) As a result, the model currently expects scoring at Pebble to roughly match the level of a typical course of its length, after accounting for unusually tough holes like the 14th. That would come to an average of 72.35, 1.35 strokes above par, during the first two rounds. The best players, such as Dustin Johnson and Mr Koepka, should fare about three strokes better than that. However, the last time the U.S. Open was held at Pebble Beach, &lt;i&gt;nobody&lt;/i&gt; finished below par: Graeme McDowell lifted the trophy at one-over. Should similar carnage be expected on the course this time around?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is good reason to believe this year’s Open field may get the best of Pebble. Overall, by EAGLE’s reckoning, the average golfer in a major today is about a full stroke per round better than they were a decade ago. Since the configuration of Pebble Beach has barely changed since the 2010 Open, that suggests finishing scores for players making the cut should wind up about four strokes lower. Further evidence that Pebble can be beaten can be found in the scores from the AT&amp;amp;T Pebble Beach Pro-Am tournament, held at the course this February. Based on the skill of the players who participated in that event and the course layout—about 200 yards shorter than the U.S. Open design—EAGLE would have expected the average round score in the Pro-Am to be 72.41. The actual average was 71.57, suggesting that the course played slightly &lt;i&gt;easier&lt;/i&gt; than expected. Nonetheless, EAGLE is designed to adjust its forecasts rapidly when new data contradict its expectations. If bogeys abound and the birdies are in hiding on Thursday morning, the model’s predictions for all players’ scores will turn bearish in a hurry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pebble’s modest yardages should also open the field to a wider range of plausible contenders than longer courses do. Whereas the leaderboards on 7,500-yard courses often resemble lists of the biggest drivers, Pebble Beach rewards judgment and precision. That might enable a shorter hitter like Matt Kuchar to end his long-running major curse, or Henrik Stenson, Webb Simpson or Jim Furyk to double their hauls of major trophies. At the other extreme, players whose games depend on power, such as Bubba Watson, Gary Woodland or Tony Finau, could prove ill-suited to Pebble’s demands.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nonetheless, EAGLE’s favourites for the U.S. Open are mostly familiar faces, many of whom wield potent drivers. In the model’s estimation Mr Johnson remains the world’s best player, as he has been for nearly two years, and is the front-runner, with an 8% chance of victory. Thanks to a new adjustment that &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/05/20/brooks-koepka-saves-his-best-work-for-a-major-yet-again&quot; data-tegid=&quot;5t5k43g2oj11kgul4npe1lguuc8rd4eh&quot;&gt;grants credit to players who have performed better in majors than in other tournaments&lt;/a&gt;, Mr Koepka—or #MajorKoepka, as we have dubbed him on Twitter—now ranks second, at just under 7%. Fresh off a victory at the RBC Canadian Open, Rory McIlroy is the third-most-likely champion, with a 5-6% chance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just two months ago, we were &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/game-theory/2019/04/09/why-dustin-johnson-is-our-favourite-to-win-the-masters&quot; data-tegid=&quot;oqou31kstlhicqufhhnpongak12it4gr&quot;&gt;touting&lt;/a&gt; Patrick Cantlay, whom betting markets priced as a 100-to-one longshot to win the Masters, as a promising “sleeper pick”. But after finishing ninth at Augusta, third in his next two tournaments (including the PGA Championship), and winning the Memorial Tournament two weeks ago, the public has caught on to Mr Cantlay. He is EAGLE’s fifth-most-likely player to win, with a 4% shot—but now ranks even higher in betting markets, which put him fourth at a 5% probability.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In what is likely to be a recurring pattern, the player EAGLE is most bullish on relative to punters is Jason Day. Starting with this year’s U.S. Open, we have modified EAGLE to consider not just players’ final scores on each hole, but also more granular measures of their skill. Although Mr Day is currently ranked just 16th in the world, and has not won a tournament in over a year, his underlying performance measures are outstanding. Among the 156 players who will tee off at Pebble, he ranks second in putting, 11th in driving distance and 17th in scrambling by EAGLE’s reckoning. The only other players in the top 20 in three categories are Mr Johnson, Mr Cantlay and Mr Kuchar. It was just 26 months ago that Mr Day, still just 31 years old, was ranked first in the world. And he has proven he can put it all together on the biggest of stages: in 2015 he shot 20 under par to win the PGA Championship, one of the best marks in modern memory. The only real weaknesses in Mr Day’s game are occasionally spotty iron play and a propensity for errant tee shots. As long as he can find himself on or around the green in regulation, this year’s Open could well prove his—ahem—Day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 20:40:21 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“It was a very Russian nightmare”—the Ivan Golunov case]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/13/it-was-a-very-russian-nightmare-the-ivan-golunov-case]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_eum507.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-13T09:58:59Z&quot;&gt;Jun 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AN INVESTIGATIVE journalist’s release may look like a press-freedom win in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/europe/2019/06/12/what-ivan-golunovs-ordeal-reveals-about-russia&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Russia&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;—but it represents much more than that. Democratic presidential hopefuls in America have no shortage of transformative ideas, yet &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/06/08/democratic-presidential-candidates-are-making-promises-they-cannot-deliver&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Senate arithmetic&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; ensures there’s little hope of realising them. And, we visit a place where &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/middle-east-and-africa/2019/06/08/eastern-congo-has-the-worlds-largest-quinine-plantations&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;malaria&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt; rages while a cure literally grows on trees. Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/vladtheun-jailer-theivangolunovcase&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 20:40:20 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The rule of law in Hong Kong]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/13/the-rule-of-law-in-hong-kong]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_LDD001.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-13T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;T&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;HREE THINGS&lt;/small&gt; stand out about the protesters who rocked Hong Kong this week. There were a great many of them. Hundreds of thousands took to the streets in what may have been the biggest demonstration since Hong Kong was handed back to China in 1997. Most of them were young—too young to be nostalgic about British rule. Their unhappiness at Beijing’s heavy hand was entirely their own. And they showed remarkable courage. Since the “Umbrella Movement” of 2014, the Communist Party has been making clear that it will tolerate no more insubordination—and yet three days later demonstrators braved rubber bullets, tear gas and legal retribution to make their point. All these things are evidence that, as many Hong Kongers see it, nothing less than the future of their city is at stake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the face of it, the protests were about something narrow and technical (see &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/briefing/2019/06/13/a-proposed-extradition-law-triggers-unrest-in-hong-kong&quot; data-tegid=&quot;f8hp3rjl4rujga3d3h2iktr6h1rpb2j2&quot;&gt;article&lt;/a&gt;). Under the law, a Hong Kong resident who allegedly murdered his girlfriend in Taiwan last year cannot be sent back there for trial. Hong Kong’s government has therefore proposed to allow the extradition of suspects to Taiwan—and to any country with which there is no extradition agreement, including the Chinese mainland.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the implications could not be more profound. The colonial-era drafters of Hong Kong’s current law excluded the mainland from extradition because its courts could not be trusted to deliver impartial justice. With the threat of extradition, anyone in Hong Kong becomes subject to the vagaries of the Chinese legal system, in which the rule of law ranks below the rule of the party. Dissidents taking on Beijing may be sent to face harsh treatment in the Chinese courts. Businesspeople risk a well-connected Chinese competitor finding a way to drag them into an easily manipulated jurisdiction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That could be disastrous for Hong Kong, a fragile bridge between a one-party state and the freedoms of global commerce. Many firms choose Hong Kong because it is well-connected with China’s huge market, but also upholds the same transparent rules that govern economies in the West. Thanks to mainland China, Hong Kong is the world’s eighth-largest exporter of goods and home to the world’s fourth-largest stockmarket. Yet its huge banking system is seamlessly connected to the West and its currency is pegged to the dollar. For many global firms, Hong Kong is both a gateway to the Chinese market and central to the Asian continent—more than 1,300 of them have their regional headquarters there. If Hong Kong came to be seen as just another Chinese city, Hong Kongers would not be the only ones to suffer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The threat is real. Since he took over as China’s leader in 2012, Xi Jinping has been making it clearer than ever that the legal system should be under the party’s thumb. China must “absolutely not follow the Western road of ‘judicial independence’,” he said in a speech published in February. In 2015 Mr Xi launched a campaign to silence independent lawyers and civil-rights activists. Hundreds of them have been harassed or detained by the police. The authorities on the mainland have even sent thugs to other jurisdictions to abduct people, including a publisher of gossipy books about the party, snatched from a car park in Hong Kong and a tycoon taken from the Four Seasons hotel in 2017. The message is plain. Mr Xi not only cares little for the rule of law on the Chinese mainland. He scorns it elsewhere, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Hong Kong government says the new law has safeguards. But the protesters are right to dismiss them. In theory extradition should not apply in political cases, and cover only crimes that would incur heavy sentences. But the party has a long record of punishing its critics by charging them with offences that do not appear political. Hong Kong’s government says it has reduced the number of white-collar offences that will be covered. But blackmail and fraud still count. It has said that only extradition requests made by China’s highest judicial officials will be considered. But the decision will fall to Hong Kong’s chief executive. That person, currently Carrie Lam, is chosen by party loyalists in Hong Kong and answers to the party in Beijing. Local courts will have little room to object. The bill could throttle Hong Kong’s freedoms by raising the possibility that the party’s critics could be bundled over the border.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a perilous moment. The protests have turned violent—possibly more violent than any since the anti-colonial demonstrations in 1967. Officials in Beijing have condemned them as a foreign plot. Ms Lam has been digging in her heels. But it is not too late for her to think again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In its narrowest sense, the new law will not accomplish what she wants. Taiwan has said that it will not accept the suspect’s extradition under the new law. Less explosive solutions have been suggested, including letting Hong Kong’s courts try cases involving murder committed elsewhere. Anti-subversion legislation was left to languish after protests in 2003. There is talk that the government may see this as the moment to push through that long-shelved law. Instead Ms Lam should take it as a precedent for her extradition reform.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rest of the world can encourage her. Britain, which signed a treaty guaranteeing that Hong Kong’s way of life will remain unchanged until at least 2047, has a particular duty. Its government has expressed concern about the “potential effects” of the new law, but it should say loud and clear that it is wrong. With America, caught up in a trade war with China, there is a risk that Hong Kong becomes the focus of a great-power clash. Some American politicians have warned that the law could jeopardise the special status the United States affords the territory. They should be prudent. Cutting off Hong Kong would not only harm American interests in the territory but also wreck the prospects of Hong Kongers—an odd way to reward its would-be democrats. Better to press the central government, or threaten case-by-case scrutiny of American extraditions to Hong Kong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But would this have any effect? That is a hard question, because it depends on Mr Xi. China has paid dearly for its attempts to squeeze Hong Kong. Each time the world sees how its intransigence and thuggishness is at odds with the image of harmony it wants to project. When Hong Kong passed into Chinese rule 22 years ago, the idea was that the two systems would grow together. As the protesters have made clear, that is not going to plan. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Leaders&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Hong Kong&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 20:40:19 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[SOAS, one of Britain’s most unusual universities, is in trouble]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/britain/2019/06/13/soas-one-of-britains-most-unusual-universities-is-in-trouble]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_brp501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-13T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;F&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;OR YOUNG&lt;/small&gt; folk in search of a grounding in Austronesian languages, say, or perhaps Sinhalese or Tibetan, London’s School of Oriental and African Studies (&lt;small&gt;SOAS&lt;/small&gt;) has long been the place to go. Founded in 1916 to train colonial administrators, military officers and the odd spy, the university came to be home to scholars with knowledge of the most obscure corners of the globe, as well as experts on rising countries like China and India. Its academics have composed the Swazi national anthem and written sweeping histories of the Meiji restoration; they have also been killed by the Khmers Rouges. In the words of a former director, “They must have formed the single biggest bunch of eccentrics in Europe.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today 4,345 students from more than 130 countries study courses ranging from global pop music to accounting and finance. Since the 1960s the erstwhile colonial training centre has been a hub of radical politics (a recent campaign by students sought to “decolonise our minds” by changing the curriculum). It also represents a type of university—small, specialist and focused on languages—that has struggled in recent years. Since 2016 &lt;small&gt;SOAS’&lt;/small&gt;s undergraduate admissions have fallen by 37%. In a warning seen by &lt;em&gt;Times Higher Education&lt;/em&gt;, the school’s director wrote at the end of last year that without action &lt;small&gt;SOAS&lt;/small&gt; would “exhaust [its] cash reserves” in another two years.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is not that the university is frozen in time. There has been growth over the past two decades in the number of students taking degrees in social sciences and law, which have the advantage of being cheap to teach, and can thus subsidise niche language courses. Nevertheless, while uptake of languages such as Japanese, Chinese and Arabic has risen, some less popular ones have fallen by the wayside. As Ian Brown, a &lt;small&gt;SOAS&lt;/small&gt; expert on South-East Asia, notes in a history of the university, there are no longer teaching posts in Bengali, Punjabi or Tamil, and social scientists do not need to master a non-Western language, as was once expected.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main problem is that &lt;small&gt;SOAS&lt;/small&gt; has struggled in a more competitive environment. The old system of state grants helped support universities that did a lot of language teaching. Nowadays in England most of their funding comes from tuition fees, and since 2015 universities have been free to recruit as many students as they want. In the words of an internal &lt;small&gt;SOAS&lt;/small&gt; memo, rival institutions “went growth-mad”, with King’s College and Queen Mary University London hoovering up students. &lt;small&gt;SOAS&lt;/small&gt; initially responded by lowering its admission standards to attract more applicants. It has since changed tack, raising the bar in order to maintain its position in league tables. Insiders say the school has been slow to tap donors to make up the shortfall. “It’s not a terribly capitalist institution,” is the verdict of one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The university promises measures to turn things round, including investments in the estate, better teaching and more overseas education. It says that applications for next year are looking perkier. Yet after last year’s disastrous admissions cycle, an extra £2.6m ($3.3m) had to be cut from academic staffing costs by 2021-22, on top of planned cuts of £3.4m since 2017-18.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If things don’t improve, &lt;small&gt;SOAS&lt;/small&gt; may have to lay on fewer courses, or perhaps even be absorbed by another institution. “There’s no way of teaching languages like Burmese or Zulu profitably,” accepts Justin Watkins, a linguistics professor at the university. But if the school ends up going under, “something will have been lost that will be very hard to reacquire.” &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Britain&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;SOS for SOAS&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 20:40:18 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How to stop governments borrowing behind their people’s backs]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/13/how-to-stop-governments-borrowing-behind-their-peoples-backs]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_fnp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-13T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 13th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span data-caps=&quot;initial&quot;&gt;I&lt;/span&gt;&lt;small&gt;N 2016 THE&lt;/small&gt; government of Mozambique confessed to secret debts of $1.4bn, or 11% of &lt;small&gt;GDP&lt;/small&gt;, mostly as loan guarantees for state-backed companies. Growth faltered, the currency slumped and foreign donors pulled back. The results have been “devastating”, says Denise Namburete, a civil-society activist, describing health centres that have gone two years without medicines. American prosecutors are pursuing eight people involved in the scandal, including three foreign bankers and a former finance minister, on charges of money-laundering and fraud.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Mozambique case may be unusual—or not. Even the &lt;small&gt;IMF&lt;/small&gt; is scratching its head about how much governments truly owe. In some places the mystery is loans from China and other emerging lenders. In others it is advance payments from oil traders, liabilities from public-private partnerships or hidden loans from commercial banks. The Institute of International Finance (&lt;small&gt;IIF&lt;/small&gt;), a group of banks and financial institutions, has responded to mounting concern by drafting principles on debt transparency. Finance ministers of &lt;small&gt;G20&lt;/small&gt; countries endorsed them at a summit in Fukuoka, in Japan, on June 8th-9th.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;small&gt;IIF&lt;/small&gt; principles are voluntary and would apply only to lending from the private sector, not from states. Lenders would disclose any loans they make to low-income governments or state firms within 60-120 days of funds being released. Details would include the loan’s purpose and structure, and a range within which the interest rate falls. The data would be held by an international institution, perhaps the &lt;small&gt;IMF&lt;/small&gt; or World Bank.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The &lt;small&gt;G20&lt;/small&gt; countries could use their voting power at the &lt;small&gt;IMF&lt;/small&gt; to insist it stores the data. Their endorsement will have weight with the private sector, says Sonja Gibbs of the &lt;small&gt;IIF&lt;/small&gt;. Although lenders benefit from knowing more about government debts, some are reluctant to share information they consider commercially sensitive. They will need to be pressed to take part. “It will be a name and shame game,” says Mark Plant of the Centre for Global Development, a think-tank. “That sometimes works, it sometimes doesn’t.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;How to give the scheme bite? One proposal is that sovereign-loan contracts that are not publicly disclosed within 30 days of signature should be unenforceable in court. Most international loans are made under New York or English law—as Mozambique’s dodgy deals were—so tweaking the rules in those two jurisdictions would be a good start. Case law and legal institutions are so well established that business would be unlikely to move elsewhere, argues Tim Jones of Jubilee Debt Campaign, the British charity behind the idea. Some 51 &lt;small&gt;MP&lt;/small&gt;s have written to the British chancellor to support Jubilee’s proposal, among them former Labour and Conservative secretaries of state for international development. On June 5th the Labour Party said it would implement the idea if it wins power.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Legal changes are not yet on the &lt;small&gt;G20&lt;/small&gt;’s agenda. But rising debts are fuelling a sense of urgency. The &lt;small&gt;IMF&lt;/small&gt; reckons that 44% of low-income countries are in debt distress or at high risk of it—even without more nasty surprises. The average developing country’s external-debt payments have risen from 6.6% of government revenue in 2010 to 12.2% in 2018, calculates Jubilee. Clandestine debts could mean the actual picture is even worse. &lt;span data-ornament=&quot;ufinish&quot;&gt;◼&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;footer itemProp=&quot;publication&quot; &gt;This article appeared in the&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span itemProp=&quot;articleSection&quot;&gt;Finance and economics&lt;/span&gt; &lt;!-- --&gt;section of the print edition under the headline&lt;!-- --&gt; &lt;span&gt;&amp;quot;Open book&amp;quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/footer&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jun 2019 20:40:17 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>