<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>The Economist</title><description>The Economist全文RSS。获取更多全文RSS：https://feedx.net</description><link>https://www.economist.com</link><item><title><![CDATA[Girish Karnad was one of India’s foremost storytellers]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/06/12/girish-karnad-was-one-of-indias-foremost-storytellers]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_BKP504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-12T14:57:53Z&quot;&gt;Jun 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;SIRSI, A sleepy town in the southern Indian state of Karnataka, was infamous for its power cuts. With little else to do, a favourite pastime of its denizens was to share stories. At home, grandparents would spin yarns; at school, if a teacher failed to turn up, students were instructed to regale each other with tales. As a child Girish Karnad partook of this tradition, and would accompany his father, a physician, on free trips to performances at the local theatre, too. (The area was affected by malaria and actors could need treatment at short notice.) “I saw play after play after play,” he said, “and theatre got into my blood without my realising it.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a teenager, Mr Karnad dreamt of being a poet—though he knew his verse was clunky and awkward—and fantasised about winning the Nobel prize. He would spend hours drawing sketches of famous writers such as Agatha Christie and T.S. Eliot, sending these portraits with pleas to sign and return them to him. One of his idols, Sean O’Casey, a great Irish dramatist, advised him to stop wasting his time with autographs and write something of his own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was sage advice. Mr Karnad’s first play, “Yayati”, was published in 1961 when he was 23 years old. It drew on a story in the “Bhagavata Purana”, a Hindu text, about a lustful king cursed with premature old age who orders his son to sacrifice his youth for him. With no formal training in script-writing, and working in Kannada, his native tongue, the play “just poured out,” Mr Karnad recalled. “I was like a steno-typist writing down whatever [the characters] were saying. It was an ecstatic process.” It was a hit, and was translated into several Indian languages. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The work popularised the idea of the “Yayati complex” or “reverse Oedipal complex”, where children forsake their freedom to submit to their parents’ demands. It was hardly a coincidence that Mr Karnad had written the play just weeks before taking up a Rhodes Scholarship to study philosophy, politics and economics at Oxford, against his parents’ wishes—they wanted him to be a bureaucrat in the Indian Administrative Service. (They also worried that he would marry a white woman without seeking their blessing.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His writing often combined contemporary concerns with history and mythology. “Tughlaq”, a play which had its premiere in 1964, retold the story of Muhammad bin Tughlaq, a 13th-century Mughal king who banned public prayers and introduced madcap economic schemes. It was an instant success at a time when India was growing impatient with its own leader, Jawaharlal Nehru, and his ideals. “Taledanda” or “Death by Beheading”, first staged in 1990, charted the rise of radical protest and reform movements in 12th-century Karnataka. Mr Karnad probed ancient, but persistent, problems in the caste structure and tensions between the Hindu and Muslim communities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet for all his accomplishments as a playwright, Mr Karnad was best known as an actor. “I got into Hindi films to make money and pursued money quite single-mindedly,” he said. In more than 100 movies, he played corrupt cricket officials, dance teachers, professors, lawyers and ministers. He was brilliant on the small screen, too. In “Malgudi Days”, a cult television series broadcast in the 1980s, he played a strict father: the actor who played his child often said that a cold stare from Mr Karnad was enough to put him in a catatonic state. He directed many award-winning movies in Hindi and Kannada, and his contribution to the arts earned him India’s third- and fourth-highest civilian awards, the Padma Bhushan and Padma Shri, as well as the Jnanpith award, the country’s highest literary honour.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Off-screen, Mr Karnad was a scathing critic of political leaders who stoked communal tensions. “I really feel that secularism is the great legacy that we have and we need to fight for it. There are forces that have eaten away at it and made the country a dangerous place,” he once declared on national television. During the recent elections he was among 200 writers who appealed to Indians not to fall prey to the sectarian campaign run by the ruling Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP), and urged people to vote for a “diverse and equal India”. The BJP, led by Narendra Modi, won with a thumping majority. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking his mind had consequences. His home in Bangalore was frequently pelted with stones. Sometimes the threats warranted police protection. A special investigation found that Mr Karnad was a target of a far-right militant group that in 2017 had shot dead Gauri Lankesh, a journalist. At a memorial of Lankesh’s death last September, he declared that he was “proud to be part of the hit list”.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He derived his life force from storytelling and speaking out, even in ill health. In his penultimate film, “Tiger Zinda Hain” (“Tiger is Alive”, 2017), he acted with a tube in his nose, tethered to an oxygen cylinder. He played his part, of a suave secret service officer, with a flourish.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 22:39:57 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Why Hong Kong’s protesters are braving tear gas and rubber bullets]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/china/2019/06/12/why-hong-kongs-protesters-are-braving-tear-gas-and-rubber-bullets]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_cnp502.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;A POWERFUL INSIGHT of modern psychology is that humans are hard-wired to fear loss, and will take greater risks to avoid it than to realise a gain. Such insights help to explain protests that have paralysed central Hong Kong in recent days. On June 9th hundreds of thousands of people—over a million, organisers say—peacefully marched in opposition to a government bill that would allow extraditions from Hong Kong to mainland China. Things turned nastier on June 12th, when protesters surrounded the Legislative Council building and forced a delay in the debate on the bill, scoring a temporary victory. As protesters blocked streets with metal barriers and hurled water bottles, police fired tear gas and rubber bullets, and threatened to use more force to disperse the crowds.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;figure role=&quot;presentation&quot; itemType=&quot;https://schema.org/WPAdBlock&quot;&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hong Kong’s chief executive, Carrie Lam, appointed by a panel of local loyalists of the Communist Party in Beijing, talks of “plugging a loophole” with the bill. She says opponents will leave the territory a refuge for fugitives. That is to suggest that previous leaders somehow forgot to draft rules for sending criminal suspects to China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, there was no omission, says Margaret Ng, a barrister who represented the legal profession in Hong Kong’s legislature from 1995 to 2012, under first British then Chinese rule. When drafting an extradition law before the handover in 1997 officials took a deliberate decision to maintain a firewall between Hong Kong’s justice system and that of the mainland, “to protect the rule of law in Hong Kong and confidence in Hong Kong as an international hub free from China’s much mistrusted system.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;China’s law courts explicitly serve as instruments of party control, rather than as any check on state power. Hong Kong authorities note that the extradition bill excludes those accused of political crimes. That offers no reassurance, retort opponents: Chinese dissidents routinely face trumped-up charges like bribery or blackmail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The prospect of losing the legal firewall between Hong Kong and China, in a bill that is being rushed with minimal debate, is what brought out vast crowds, many dressed in white, the colour of mourning. Several confided that this was their first time at a political demonstration. Such scenes are a surprise. By now, 22 years after the British colony became a Special Administrative Region of China, its people were supposed to have accepted the fate envisioned for them by rulers in Beijing: a life of well-fed but politically neutered domestication, like so many golden-egg laying geese. Rewards are on offer for those who comply.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Communist leaders pledged that Hong Kong’s capitalist system, independent courts and Western-style freedoms of speech and assembly would be preserved for 50 years, under the slogan “one country, two systems”. There were ambiguous promises that Hong Kong might move towards democratic elections for its legislature and for the post of chief executive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Increasingly, though, that emphasis on autonomy has been being replaced by proposals that would leave Hong Kong merely the wealthiest and most international city in China. Hong Kong remains valuable as a global financial centre. But Communist bosses increasingly expect Hong Kong to know its place. The territory represented over 18% of China’s GDP when British rule ended in 1997, but less than 3% in 2018. Ms Lam has promoted integration with the “Greater Bay Area”, a region spanning Hong Kong, Macau and the mainland province of Guangdong.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The costs of defiance, meanwhile, have risen. In 2003 authorities shelved an anti-sedition law that Beijing wanted to impose on Hong Kong, after large street marches. Since then the central government has grown less patient, notably after Xi Jinping became party leader in 2012. In April this year several leaders of Occupy Central (also known as the Umbrella Movement), a pro-democracy campaign of civil disobedience that blocked streets for weeks in 2014, were jailed for up to 16 months for causing “excessive inconvenience” during those protests, in the words of a Hong Kong judge. Politicians have been barred from running for office unless they pledge loyalty to China.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When Chaguan last year met Benny Tai, a rumpled law professor from Hong Kong University and an Occupy Central leader, he sadly wondered when his city might witness large demonstrations again. “People are concerned that it is not safe to protest, especially in the business sector,” he sighed. He talked of “holding the line” while waiting for democracy in mainland China. It would be interesting to hear Mr Tai’s views now, but he is currently in prison.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;An American newspaper this week asked if China had created a million new dissidents in Hong Kong. That is to mistake the mood. The protesters are not marching to gain new freedoms, but to avoid losing those that they still have. Anson Chan, who served as chief secretary of the Hong Kong government under the British and for the first four years of Chinese rule, spent four and half hours among the marchers on Sunday. Many probably “held out very slim hope that the government will change these proposals”, she says. “But they wanted to stand up and be counted.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fighting without hope of winning&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;In commentaries intended for overseas consumption, Chinese state media accuse “foreign forces” of trying to create “havoc” in Hong Kong. Actually, though the British and American governments have expressed concern about the extradition bill, and Congress could revoke trade and visa privileges granted to Hong Kong, this movement’s backers include prominent, local lawyers, priests and entrepreneurs. Politicians and scholars have drafted moderate compromise proposals, including a one-off arrangement to send to Taiwan a murder suspect whose case is the ostensible pretext for amending extradition laws.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is a clarifying rebuke for China’s rulers. Exposure to their version of the rule of law feels like an unbearable loss to many in Hong Kong, outweighing the rewards of integration with a faster-growing China. Assuming that the extradition law is rammed through anyway, it will be a win for fear and resignation, not love. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 20:39:59 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The EU must keep its promise to North Macedonia]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/12/the-eu-must-keep-its-promise-to-north-macedonia]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_eup504_0.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-12T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;ENLARGING the European Union long ago fell out of fashion. No country has joined since Croatia, in 2013. As Hungary and Poland attack their judiciaries and clamp down on media it seems quaint to argue, as many once did, that negotiating membership could instil democratic habits in countries with memories of dictatorship. How much harder to make the case in the Balkans, the EU’s inner courtyard of unfinished business. Kosovo and Serbia are permanently at daggers drawn. Bosnia is an ungovernable mess.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But these problems should not distract from the extraordinary progress in the country known, since February, as North Macedonia. After years of authoritarian misrule the new government, led by Zoran Zaev, has started tackling corruption and reforming the judiciary. In a region riven by ethnic strife, the country’s Slavic majority and Albanian minority enjoy good relations. Most of all, last year Mr Zaev’s government signed the Prespa agreement with Greece, ending an absurd but destabilising dispute over the country’s name by adding a geographical signifier to it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is why the European Commission wants the EU’s governments to open membership talks with North Macedonia, along with Albania. It was the promise of accession to the EU (and NATO, which is forthcoming) that gave Mr Zaev space to push through Prespa at home. Yet in June 2018 his bid to start talks was kicked down the road for a year. Now further delay is likely. Such treatment is not only shabby, it is dangerous.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To start membership talks with a candidate country, every EU government must agree. Until now France and the Netherlands were the stumbling blocks. Emmanuel Macron’s argument that Europe must deepen before broadening concealed his fear that encouraging enlargement would help Marine Le Pen, his nationalist opponent. Now, just as Mr Macron is softening, a fresh obstacle has emerged in Germany. Angela Merkel’s government needs backing from the Bundestag to approve EU bids, and MPs from her Christian Democratic Union are resisting. They claim they need more time for debate. But that is a fig-leaf for opponents of enlargement. Some distrust Albania’s judicial system, but the two countries’ bids can be decoupled. Others simply want to give Mrs Merkel a black eye. And the chancellor’s authority is dwindling as the sun sets on her political career.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The original plan was to greenlight the two candidates’ EU bids at a meeting on June 18th. That now looks impossible. A special summit of leaders could be convened in July were North Macedonia’s bid sure to pass. But the Bundestag will soon begin its summer break. Another opportunity will not arise until October, and by then the habit of delay may have become ingrained.&lt;br/&gt;Every day lost is perilous for Mr Zaev’s government. Having already suffered one delay, voters are sceptical. The opposition, still smarting at its ejection from office, will pounce at the first sign of failure. Moreover, by autumn Greece is likely to have a new centre-right government that will face pressure from anti-Prespa voters to veto the talks. More broadly, for the EU so brazenly to break its promise to one Balkan state will boost leaders in others who say the Europeans cannot be trusted. Other powers sniffing around, from Russia to China to Turkey, will nod sagely.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Conversely, opening talks with North Macedonia will strengthen the hand of pro-European reformers throughout the Balkans. (A delay for Albania, which remains politically unstable, is on balance justified.) Starting talks is no guarantee of successfully concluding them, as Turkey—which began negotiating in 2005 and is going backwards—demonstrates so depressingly. Croatia’s accession lasted eight years. The EU should not lose confidence in its most potent foreign-policy weapon. To reject North Macedonia would be cruel, self-defeating and wrong. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 20:39:58 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[“A profound improvement in humanity’s aggregate happiness”—the internet’s second half]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/12/a-profound-improvement-in-humanitys-aggregate-happiness-the-internets-second-half]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_blm505.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-12T11:20:32Z&quot;&gt;Jun 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;HALF OF humanity is now &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/leaders/2019/06/08/the-second-half-of-humanity-is-joining-the-internet&quot;&gt;online.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; What will the second half do when it logs on? The same as the first: friendly chat, personal expression and a lot of &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/briefing/2019/06/08/how-the-pursuit-of-leisure-drives-internet-use&quot;&gt;cat videos&lt;/a&gt;. Despite appearances, &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/united-states/2019/05/09/race-plays-an-ever-more-important-role-in-voting&quot;&gt;racism&lt;/a&gt; in America&lt;/strong&gt; is actually going down; the problem is that America’s politics is increasingly fractured along racial lines. And, why is it that &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/prospero/2019/04/25/a-brief-cultural-history-of-the-scream&quot;&gt;screams&lt;/a&gt; are so prevalent in popular culture?&lt;/strong&gt; Runtime: 21 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theintelligencepodcast/oncemore-withfelines-halftheworldgetsonline&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 19:23:37 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Joe Biden and Donald Trump trade insults in Iowa]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/11/joe-biden-and-donald-trump-trade-insults-in-iowa]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_blp904.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-11T22:46:06Z&quot;&gt;Jun 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEARLY 17 MONTHS before voting day, it is beginning to feel as if the first days of two-person campaigning for the 2020 presidential election have already begun. Both President Donald Trump and Joe Biden, the front-runner in a crowded field of candidates for the Democratic nomination, were on the stump in Iowa on June 11th. Mr Biden focused on the eastern portion of the state, including flood-hit Davenport on the Mississippi. Mr Trump toured an ethanol plant in the far west followed by a political fundraising dinner in Des Moines, the state capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each man has good reason to show his face in Iowa. Mr Biden was making some diplomatic amends. He had seemed to snub Iowa’s Democrats on June 8th and 9th, by failing to join 19 (out of 23) candidates running for the Democratic nomination at an event in Cedar Rapids. (He claimed a prior commitment, at his granddaughter’s school graduation in Washington.) Given his strong lead in the polls Mr Biden can probably afford to stand apart from the fray. Nonetheless he must avoid any suggestion that, at the age of 76, he lacks the energy for a scrap or that he is aloof from ordinary voters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump, meanwhile, is wary of losing support from rural Midwesterners who backed him heartily in 2016. The president attended a rally in northern Wisconsin in late April. He knows rural folk in the region have suffered in the past couple of years. That has happened in part due to his chaotic approach to international trade. Confrontations with China have led to a dramatic fall in demand for soy-bean exports, while higher prices for imported steel have pushed up equipment costs. Economic uncertainty and terrible spring flooding have hit rural areas. Federal financial relief has flowed but farmers take that grudgingly, reluctant to be seen as ever more reliant on subsidies and other government hand-outs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Appearing in Iowa simultaneously probably suits both men for another reason. It is a chance for each to test how they might spar close-up. Mr Biden is not guaranteed to win the Democratic nomination, but Mr Trump evidently judges that he is likely to. And the president’s frequent attacks almost certainly bolster Mr Biden among Democratic primary voters. The president called Mr Biden “a loser”, “weak mentally” and lacking in energy, on June 11th. Such comments suck attention away from other Democratic candidates and may suggest, at least to Democrats, that the president is rattled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent opinion polls, reportedly including a private Republican one, suggest that Mr Biden is more popular than the president in many battleground states. Mr Biden may calculate that the more he gets under Mr Trump’s skin, the further ahead he can pull from the rest of the primary field. And because most Democrat voters seem to care more about ejecting the incumbent from the White House than any particular ideology, they are likely to back a nominee who is best placed for the confrontation. That is likely to mean coalescing around a front-runner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Biden’s comments on June 11th, in Davenport, seemed designed to provoke the president. He called Mr Trump an “existential threat” to America and its values, then jeered that Mr Trump knew nothing about trade and economics. According to excerpts of that speech, released early in the morning and leapt upon by the media, it also contained the observation that supermarket cashiers grasped better than the president that American consumers—not foreign producers—pay the price for his imposing tariffs on imports. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why then is Mr Trump focusing on Mr Biden if doing so helps an already popular opponent become the Democratic nominee? It may be that Mr Trump is too undisciplined to behave differently. Or he might simply believe Mr Biden is destined to be his opponent. If so, he will want as much time as possible to develop lines of attack, hoping to characterise Mr Biden as weak, unenergetic, or an establishment insider, well before Election Day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump sees an advantage in dwelling on Mr Biden’s age and biography. “He’s a different guy,” the president said as he left the White House for Iowa. “He looks different than he used to. He acts different than he used to. He’s even slower than he used to be.” The president is hardly youthful: he turns 73 this week. But he can try to pitch himself not only as younger than the Democrat, but as a relative outsider. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Biden as vice-president, spent eight years in the White House, and has already struggled a little in defending a political record that spans several decades. Last week he changed his position on whether there should be federal funding for abortions (he used to be against, but is now in favour). Mr Trump, after four years in office, may have the gall to claim that he is an insurgent. After all, that worked among many voters in the Midwest last time around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 19:23:36 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Joe Biden and Donald Trump trade insults in Iowa]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/12/joe-biden-and-donald-trump-trade-insults-in-iowa]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_blp904.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-12T02:46:06Z&quot;&gt;Jun 12th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;NEARLY 17 MONTHS before voting day, it is beginning to feel as if the first days of two-person campaigning for the 2020 presidential election have already begun. Both President Donald Trump and Joe Biden, the front-runner in a crowded field of candidates for the Democratic nomination, were on the stump in Iowa on June 11th. Mr Biden focused on the eastern portion of the state, including flood-hit Davenport on the Mississippi. Mr Trump toured an ethanol plant in the far west followed by a political fundraising dinner in Des Moines, the state capital.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Each man has good reason to show his face in Iowa. Mr Biden was making some diplomatic amends. He had seemed to snub Iowa’s Democrats on June 8th and 9th, by failing to join 19 (out of 23) candidates running for the Democratic nomination at an event in Cedar Rapids. (He claimed a prior commitment, at his granddaughter’s school graduation in Washington). Given his strong lead in the polls Mr Biden can probably afford to stand apart from the fray. Nonetheless he must avoid any suggestion that, at the age of 76, he lacks the energy for a scrap or that he is aloof from ordinary voters.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump, meanwhile, is wary of losing support from rural Midwesterners who backed him heartily in 2016. The president attended a rally in northern Wisconsin in late April. He knows rural folk in the region have suffered in the past couple of years. That has happened in part due to his chaotic approach to international trade. Confrontations with China have led to a dramatic fall in demand for soy-bean exports, while higher prices for imported steel have pushed up equipment costs. Economic uncertainty and terrible spring flooding have hit rural areas. Federal financial relief has flowed but farmers take that grudgingly, reluctant to be seen as ever more reliant on subsidies and other government hand-outs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Appearing in Iowa simultaneously probably suits both men for another reason. It is a chance for each to test how they might spar close-up. Mr Biden is not guaranteed to win the Democratic nomination, but Mr Trump evidently judges that is likely to. And the president’s frequent attacks almost certainly bolster Mr Biden among Democratic primary voters. The president called Mr Biden “a loser”, “weak mentally” and lacking in energy, on June 11th. Such comments suck attention away from other Democratic candidates and may suggest, at least to Democrats, that the president is rattled.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Recent opinion polls, reportedly including a private Republican one, suggest that Mr Biden is more popular than the president in many battleground states. Mr Biden may calculate that the more he gets under Mr Trump’s skin, the further ahead he can pull from the rest of the primary field. And because most Democrat voters seem to care more about ejecting the incumbent from the White House than any particular ideology, they are likely to back a nominee who is best placed for the confrontation. That is likely to mean coalescing around a front-runner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Biden’s comments on June 11th, in Davenport, seemed designed to provoke the president. He called Mr Trump an “existential threat” to America and its values, then jeered that Mr Trump knew nothing about trade and economics. According to excerpts of that speech, released early in the morning and leapt upon by the media, it also contained the observation that supermarket cashiers grasped better than the president that American consumers—not foreign producers—pay the price for his imposing tariffs on imports. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Why then is Mr Trump focusing on Mr Biden if doing so helps an already popular opponent become the Democratic nominee? It may be that Mr Trump is too undisciplined to behave differently. Or he might simply believe Mr Biden is destined to be his opponent. If so, he will want as much time as possible to develop lines of attack, hoping to characterise Mr Biden as weak, unenergetic, or an establishment insider, well before Election Day.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Trump sees an advantage in dwelling on Mr Biden’s age and biography. “He’s a different guy,” the president said as he left the White House for Iowa. “He looks different than he used to. He acts different than he used to. He’s even slower than he used to be.” The president is hardly youthful: he turns 73 this week. But he can try to pitch himself not only as younger than the Democrat, but as a relative outsider. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Biden as vice-president, spent eight years in the White House, and has already struggled a little in defending a political record that spans several decades. Last week he changed his position on whether there should be federal funding for abortions (he used to be against, but is now in favour). Mr Trump, after four years in office, may have the gall to claim that he is an insurgent. After all, that worked among many voters in the Midwest last time around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 11:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[The benefits of pre-schooling may extend for generations]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/democracy-in-america/2019/06/11/the-benefits-of-pre-schooling-may-extend-for-generations]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_USP502_1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-11T18:29:16Z&quot;&gt;Jun 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AMERICA HAS fewer of its three- and four-year-old children in pre-school than other rich nations. But it is beginning to catch up. Between 2002 and 2017, the proportion of four-year-olds enrolled in state pre-kindergarten programmes rose from 14% to 33%. And a big, bipartisan push is underway to get more children into education before they start school. Three Republican-leaning states—Georgia, Florida and Oklahoma—have introduced universal pre-kindergarten. Several contenders for the Democratic presidential nomination, including Joe Biden, Bernie Sanders and Elizabeth Warren, boast universal pre-school policies in their campaigns. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Analyses of large-scale pre-school programmes in the last few years have often been disappointing. But the potential value of pre-school has become clear as participants in long-run studies have grown older. Two new papers look at the long-term effects of perhaps the best known of these, a 1960s-era pilot programme, on both the former pre-schoolers and their children. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Between 1962 and 1965, 128 African-American children from the Perry Elementary School district in Ypsilanti, Michigan were enrolled in an experiment. After being sorted into two groups with similar IQs, gender balance, and socio-economic backgrounds, a coin toss selected one of the groups to receive two-and-a-half hours of pre-school education each weekday for the two years before they entered primary school. They also received an hour-and-a-half of home visits a week from Perry Elementary teachers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since then, the participants have been repeatedly surveyed; most recently, most of them were interviewed at the age of 55. James Heckman and Ganesh Karapakula, economists, have examined the long-gathered results in two new papers, using techniques designed to factor in the experiment’s small size, flaws in the randomisation process and missing survey responses. The researchers found that the pre-schooled kids—and in particular the boys—have had considerably different lives as a result. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The pre-schooled group, they found, had about half the average number of violent felony convictions as the control group. Males in that group spent an average of 27 days in jail between the ages of 20 and 50 compared to 136 days for boys in the control group. They also had more success in employment, increased earnings in mid-adulthood and better health. Perry Pre-school Project boys are significantly more likely to have been in stable marital relationships. And the effects appear to persist across generations: the children of beneficiaries have fewer school suspensions, higher levels of education and employment and lower levels of criminal activity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Another pre-school experiment that has been followed up over years, the Abecedarian Project in North Carolina, which divided 111 children into a test and control group, suggests similar results. Both programmes were expensive, small and run by committed teams, involving a greater level of intervention than the large-scale pre-kindergarten programs being rolled out today. The home visits may have made a particular difference. The researchers report suggestive evidence that the Perry project had some of its biggest effects outside school. Male participants interviewed in their 50s were far less likely to report having been verbally abused by an adult when they were children, having felt neglected, or having been abducted by one parent to hide from another.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Large-scale pre-school progammes do not compare well to these small experiments. While there is widespread research evidence suggesting that pre-schooling yields immediate learning gains, these fade over time. Researchers studying children randomly assigned to the Tennessee Voluntary Pre-kindergarten Programme, for example, found that while participants performed better on a battery of achievement tests at the end, the achievement gap subsequently reversed. And analysis of the rollout of universal pre-Kindergarten in Georgia suggests that there were no significant changes in test scores at fourth grade (around the age of 9-10) among those exposed to the programme compared to similar students from other states where it was was not rolled out. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some studies do suggest more positive results for disadvantaged subgroups.Results from a pre-school programme in Texas found improvements for low-income students and those who were not proficient in English. The first national randomised evaluation of the Head Start programme, which gives matching grants to states providing early education, health care and nutrition services to children as well as training in parenting, found it made a great difference to cognitive achievement during pre-school. That benefit faded, but it persisted up until first grade for a subsample of Spanish speakers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All of this suggests pre-school programmes are difficult to deliver effectively to thousands rather than tens of children. The design of such programmes is also important. Elizabeth Cascio, an economist from Dartmouth College, used the nationally representative Early Childhood Longitudinal Study of children born in 2001 to study the impact of different pre-school programmess across America. She found that universal programmes can improve the reading ability of four-year-olds from low-income families, while means-tested programmes have no impact. This, she suggests, may be because universal programmes are higher-quality and more rigorous academically.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The big and sustained effects of the Perry programme suggest that intergenerational inequality can be permanently reduced by early childhood interventions. The priority for policy makers is to figure out how that can be achieved—at scale.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 05:40:14 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[All the presidents men—who will lead the ECB?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/podcasts/2019/06/11/all-the-presidents-men-who-will-lead-the-ecb]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_blm504.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-11T16:00:05Z&quot;&gt;Jun 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;THERE ARE no women in the running to take over as the &lt;strong&gt;next President of the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/04/13/mario-draghis-successor-at-the-ecb-has-plenty-to-do&quot;&gt;European Central Bank&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;later this year. We take a look at the most hotly tipped candidates. Also, the problems at &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.economist.com/business/2019/06/06/troubles-at-the-woodford-investment-group-point-to-a-wider-trend&quot;&gt;Woodford&lt;/a&gt; investment management group &lt;/strong&gt;show that&lt;strong&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;even star fund managers can struggle to outperform the market. And why do &lt;strong&gt;German billionaires&lt;/strong&gt; avoid the limelight? Simon Long hosts. Runtime: 19 min&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;div &gt;&lt;iframe src=&quot;//embed.acast.com/theeconomistmoneytalks/moneytalks-allthepresidentsmen&quot; width=&quot;560&quot; height=&quot;215&quot;  frameBorder=&quot;0&quot; scrolling=&quot;auto&quot;&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Listen on: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/id1449631195?mt=2&amp;amp;ls=1&quot;&gt;Apple Podcasts&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://open.spotify.com/show/12zKAMNyS2GNentUzxq9QN&quot;&gt;Spotify&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.google.com/podcasts?feed=aHR0cHM6Ly9yc3MuYWNhc3QuY29tL3RoZWludGVsbGlnZW5jZXBvZGNhc3Q&quot;&gt;Google&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://www.stitcher.com/s?fid=357733&amp;amp;refid=stpr&quot;&gt;Stitcher&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.economist.comhttps://tunein.com/podcasts/News--Politics-Podcasts/The-Intelligence-p1186979/&quot;&gt;TuneIn&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 03:39:56 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Europe’s secularists worry about the rise of Christian-nativist populism]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/erasmus/2019/06/11/europes-secularists-worry-about-the-rise-of-christian-nativist-populism]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/20190615_BLP501.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-11T15:36:15Z&quot;&gt;Jun 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;AROUND 15 years ago, when the machinery of the European Union was being refashioned into its present form, one of the hottest debates concerned what role, if any, would be set aside for God. The Vatican and some mainly Catholic states, like Poland, wanted theistic language in the EU’s constitutional treaty; a secular camp led by France was opposed. In the end, the nearest thing to a spiritual reference was a statement in the treaty’s preamble that signatories were “drawing inspiration from the cultural, religious and humanist inheritance of Europe…”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In another clunky compromise, Article 17 of the subsequent Treaty on the Functioning of the European Union obliges the EU’s institutions to conduct an “open, transparent and regular” dialogue with churches and other religious groups, and also with philosophical and non-confessional organisations. On the secular side, the European Humanist Federation, grouping about 60 smaller bodies in more than 20 countries, is the EU’s main interlocutor. It counterbalances the advisory role of outfits like the Conference of European Churches, which is mainly Protestant and Orthodox, and COMECE, the Catholic bishops’ group. Both those bodies maintain active lobbying operations around the EU’s institutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The religious types and the secularists are still squabbling about how much access they should enjoy to the upper echelons of the Euro-bureaucracy. In recent weeks a tempest erupted in the teacups of Strasbourg when it emerged that Mairead McGuinness, an Irish politician who is one of the European Parliament’s vice-presidents, had mooted the idea of intensifying the legislature’s exchanges with Article 17 partners. Instead of merely attending three seminars a year, they might be invited to meet officials involved in the planning of parliamentary business, enabling them to flag up matters of concern. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ms McGuiness adamantly insisted that these proposals, leaked by an investigative reporter, Sian Norris, were merely being floated, and that any enhanced access would be granted in equal measure to religious and secular groups. But Virginie Rozière, a French MEP and staunch advocate of secularism, said it was “completely crazy” to contemplate any change that boosted the churches’ role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite this sparring, the pompous expression “cultural, religious and humanist inheritance” does actually correspond to something real. Whether they are on the Christian Democratic centre-right or the generally more secularist centre-left, most European politicians, and ultimately their voters, have in recent years shared many common ideals: a belief in a universal franchise, freedom of speech, the rule of law and due process, and antipathy to racism. In their understanding of Europe’s past, some would emphasise the Judaeo-Christian inheritance, while others would stress the struggle against clerical authority proclaimed by the Enlightenment. But none would aspire to re-impose Christianity by top-down methods. After all, the advent of Christian Democracy after 1945 marked a final break with Christian authoritarianism.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Despite all that, the delegates who met in Iceland recently for the annual gathering of the European Humanist Federation saw troubling portents on the horizon. A whole range of threats to the enlightened order were cited by Giulio Ercolessi, an Italian liberal who is the federation’s president. As he put it:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;Human Rights, individual liberties, the rule of law, the secular character of our institutions and the very idea of constitutional democracy are under attack, in the world and also in our continent…Scientific achievements that have made our lives healthier and easier in the last decades are called into question…Religious fundamentalism conspires [to use] religious traditions as weapons to be brandished against newcomers, in the hands of fear-mongers of the worst sort…&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of the developments that troubles Mr Ercolessi and his fellow humanists is the rise across Europe of the populist, xenophobic right, which often dresses itself in religious or Christian-nativist clothing, even though its leaders are not usually very devout. Parties of roughly that stripe have already taken centre-stage in Hungary, Italy and Austria. In last month’s European elections the nationalist right made substantial gains in Britain and France. Such parties are not, in general, openly opposed to liberal democracy or the rule of law; but some of their supporters are less than respectful of those values.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It may be a sign of the times that Europe’s most important Christian Democrat, Germany’s Chancellor, Angela Merkel, felt obliged to say, in an interview with CNN after the European ballot: “We have to face up to the spectres of the past...we have to tell our young people what history has brought us... why we are for democracy, why we stand up against intolerance [and] why we show no tolerance of violations of human rights.”&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mr Ercolessi was also preoccupied with a less obvious consequence of the current wave of migration into Europe. Given that many of the new arrivals are from countries dominated by Islam or other conservative religious beliefs, he detected a widespread concern even on the European centre-left that waves of migration might increase the number of ultra-conservative immigrant micro-communities, portending a “new obscurantism” on the continent. Such fears were palpable across the political spectrum in France and the Netherlands, said Mr Ercolessi. As a result, anti-immigrant sentiments could be heard even from progressive politicians.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The best way to counter all this, in Mr Ercolessi’s view, is to showcase an important but neglected fact: many of the new arrivals in Europe are not bringing ultra-conservative religion with them, but fleeing from it. These include at least some people from the Middle East who face persecution because they are LGBT or atheist or members of a religious minority.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short, the influx of newcomers from poor and often brutal places, and the complex political consequences of that influx, are a challenge to Europe’s “cultural, religious and humanist inheritance” as the treaty-writers, with a mixture of political expediency and inspiration, described it. People of many different metaphysical beliefs will be needed to defend that inheritance.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 03:39:55 +0800</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[How compatible are democracy and capitalism?]]></title><link><![CDATA[https://www.economist.com/finance-and-economics/2019/06/11/how-compatible-are-democracy-and-capitalism]]></link><description>&lt;img src=&quot;https://www.economist.com/sites/default/files/images/2019/06/articles/main/20190615_fnd000.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot;&gt;&lt;div&gt;&lt;time  itemProp=&quot;dateCreated&quot; dateTime=&quot;2019-06-11T00:00:00Z&quot;&gt;Jun 11th 2019&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div  itemProp=&quot;description&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;OF LATE THE world’s older democracies have begun to look more vulnerable than venerable. America seems destined for a constitutional showdown between the executive and the legislature. Brexit has mired Britain in a constitutional morass of its own. Such troubles could be mistaken for a comeuppance. In recent years political economists have argued that rising inequality in the Anglo-American world must eventually threaten the foundations of democracy; a book on the theme by Thomas Piketty, a French economist, has sold well over a million copies. That argument channels a time-worn view, held by thinkers from Karl Marx to Friedrich Hayek, that democracy and capitalism may prove incompatible.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As powerfully as such arguments are made, the past century or so tells a different story. The club of rich democracies is not easy to join, but those who get in tend to stay there. Since the dawn of industrialisation, no advanced capitalist democracy has fallen out of the ranks of high-income countries or regressed permanently into authoritarianism. This is not a coincidence, say Torben Iversen of Harvard University and David Soskice of the London School of Economics, in their recent book, “Democracy and Prosperity”. Rather, they write, in advanced economies democracy and capitalism tend to reinforce each other. It is a reassuring message, but one that will face severe tests in years to come.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p &gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Economists and political theorists have imagined all sorts of ways capitalist democracies might fail. The oldest is the worry that grasping masses will vote to expropriate the wealth (hard-earned or not) of entrepreneurs and landowners—and without secure property rights there can be no capitalism. Hayek thought that the governments of the early 20th century, in responding to the concerns of the masses, had over-centralised economic decision-making, a road that led eventually to totalitarianism. Other thinkers followed Marx in reckoning that it was the greed of the capitalists that would do the greatest harm. Joseph Schumpeter feared that as firms grew more powerful, they might push a country towards corporatism and clientelism, winning monopoly rights that would generate profits they could share with politicians. Mr Piketty and others say that inequality naturally rises in capitalist countries, and that political power becomes concentrated alongside economic power in an unstable way. Other economists, like Dani Rodrik, have argued that full participation in the global economy forces a country to give up a degree of either national sovereignty or democracy. Lowering barriers to trade means harmonising trade and regulatory policies with other countries, for instance, which reduces each government’s ability to accommodate domestic preferences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But if capitalism and democracy are such uneasy bedfellows, what explains their long co-existence in the rich world? Mr Iversen and Mr Soskice see capitalism and democracy as potentially mutually supporting, with three stabilising pillars. One is a strong government, which constrains the power of large firms and labour unions, and ensures competitive markets. Weaker countries find it harder to resist the short-term expediency of securing power by protecting monopolies. The second is a sizeable middle class, forming a political bloc that shares in the prosperity created by a capitalist economy. A bargain is struck in which the state provides mass higher education on generous terms, while encouraging the development of frontier industries that demand skilled workers. Middle-class households thus reckon that economic growth is likely to benefit them and their children. (Rising inequality is not a threat to capitalist democracies, the authors reckon, because middle-class voters care little about the poor and do not support broader redistribution that could raise their tax bills.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Providing the education, infrastructure and social safety net that support a prosperous middle class requires substantial tax revenue. For the system to hold a third pillar is needed: large firms that are not very mobile. Before recent rapid globalisation that was no problem. Yet even now firms are more rooted than commonly thought. Though multinationals are adept at shifting production and profits around the world, in a knowledge economy leading firms cannot break their connections to networks of skilled individuals like those in London, New York or Silicon Valley. Their complex business plans and frontier technologies require the know-how developed and dispersed through these local networks. That increases the power of the state relative to firms, and allows it to tax and spend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Middlemarch&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt;Quibble with the details, but the overarching story—immobile companies giving governments a degree of sovereignty, which they self-interestedly use to boost the middle classes—seems a plausible account of the stability of advanced capitalist democracies. It leaves plenty to be concerned about, however. It hinges on the middle classes feeling confident about the economy. A sharp slowdown in growth in real median incomes, as in America and Britain in recent years, might not send voters rushing to the barricades, but could strengthen the appeal of movements that threaten to disturb the status quo. Governments, too, are becoming less responsive to middle-class priorities. America’s is too dysfunctional, and Britain’s too distracted by Brexit, to focus on improving education, infrastructure and the competitiveness of markets.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Demographic change might also take a toll: older and whiter generations may not much care whether a would-be middle class that does not look like them has opportunities to advance or not. Then, too, the authors may have underestimated the corrosive effect of inequality. Threatening to leave is not the only way the rich can wield power. They control mass media, fund think-thanks and spend on or become political candidates. Proud democracies may well survive this period of turmoil. But it would be a mistake to assume survival is foreordained.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;hr&gt;&lt;div&gt;获取更多RSS：&lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.net" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.net(永久域名，墙)&lt;/a&gt; &lt;br&gt;&lt;a href="https://feedx.co" style="color:orange" target="_blank"&gt;https://feedx.co(临时域名)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;</description><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 03:39:54 +0800</pubDate></item></channel></rss>